big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
well 2013 is already getting a little long in the tooth here it is the second
day of January 2012 and we are live ladies and gentlemen on this Wednesday
edition and we will have open phones yet again today here in the new year after I
cover the news obviously you do know the news don't you
$1 in government cuts for every $41 in taxes increased we're gonna explain why
that is see once they get you in debt you pay almost all your taxes to foreign
banks on interest and then the whole infrastructure implodes and that's by
design and then after the infrastructure implodes they come in and buy everything
up with your money for pennies on the dollar and people are too ignorant and
too dumb running around drinking fluoride water and talking about Obama
phones to be able to even able to understand exactly what's happening to
them so $1 in cuts for every 41 in taxes deal means higher taxes on 77% of
households in the country I thought it was on the evil greedy 2% the 2% that
means the 2% that are making a couple hundred thousand a year not the
billionaires that control trillions offshore they're the ones that wrote all
this they're the ones that took the country over but the Obama phone lady
she had never gonna figure that out that's why she's poor that's why she's
you know down and out because she believes in the system congressional
budget office adds 3.9 trillion more to deficit and Paul Ryan votes yes
Cantor no is Boehner finishes speaker of the GOP torn in half
you know that's why the collectivists are so happy they go the GOP is over
it'll implode where if you know some western and southern states will be
conservative like Arizona and Texas and but the rest of its ours we've got
people dependent they actually brag about it you see them in the news and
yeah because the globalist have bought off the Republican leadership
they've totally absolutely bought them off and that's why you're going to see
the Congress pass total open borders totally legal alien legalization free
health care form everything else citizens won't get it it's already that
way that's why you're gonna see the gun ban physically and make you turn them in
and they want to have a war with you they've gone to Congress and said we're
dropping the hammer you lined up you like your insider trading money you like
your hookers good we got photos with you with all of them we're bringing America
down you don't do what you're told you're dead
this is a foreign banking takeover our military is now under their control
we're now under NATO UN Bilderberg control now it's so outrageous that if
we speak out against it at the grassroots they won't get away with it
but they're committed they're imploding things now so they've got to totally
take over and pose as saviors as we kind of bounce down the cliff into oblivion
and the foreign banks of course the control the fraudulent stock market with
all their high-frequency trading and all their put options and scams and plunge
protection team they boosted the stock market hundreds of points the Dow Jones
Industrial so everyone goes oh good increasing taxes is good for an economy
it's like going into somebody who's dying of cancer or something and
they've got family flying into town to see him before they die and the person's
having trouble breathing and they'll ask them they say you know you'll be dead in
about an hour we don't give you a bunch of adrenaline and drugs you want these
drugs actually been there when this was happening to somebody they were at an
organ failure and the family's like yeah shoot him up and they just kept pumping
pumping adrenaline and drugs into him and the guy's dad got there got to see
him and then they got passed out and died they said he'll be dead in a few
minutes is his veins of all clothes we can't even inject him anymore so the
bankers will do that up stay with us we'll be right back
we have witnessed two terrible storms in the east but we are still in the eye of
the perfect storm the most devastating economic conditions since the Great
Depression America's worst drought in agricultural history and now the
economic results of the presidential election this perfect storm is a huge
threat to everyone's food supply I just doubled down and got even more supplies
from eat foods direct and I recommend you do the same it's time to get your
own supply for me foods direct I know I won't be standing in a bread line
trading my freedom for food I'm taking control of my future and you're nuts if
you don't do the same go to eat foods direct calm forward slash Alex to find
the specials and you can start with a holiday gift pack that's normally $80
now under 50 bucks remember I can warn you but I can't feed you
call eight hundred four oh nine five six three three or eat foods direct calm
forward slash Alex would you rather prepare six months too early or one day
too late or oh nine five six three three or eat foods direct calm forward slash
Alex Alex Jones here with a very important announcement for truth
seekers we've carried a lot of amazing films and books over the years on the
online video bookstore at info Wars calm and out of all the titles we've carried
one stands out because it is just so chillingly convincing and that's dreams
from my real father by Joel Gilbert available at info wars calm this film
exposes the fraud that Obama is like nothing I've seen if you want to know
who Obama's real daddy is this is the film for you don't forget your purchase
supports our broadcast and our growing media network you'll also find it info
war shop calm none dare call a conspiracy by Gary Allen the book that
woke me up we're also carrying behind the green mask you in agenda 21 by Rosa
Corey this book is coffin nails to the globalist takeover the greater good the
most professional and up-to-date film I've ever seen exposing the scourge that
is vaccines these titles and a lot more are all available at info war shop calm
sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and
laughing as you get sick and die start purifying your water with pro pure my
friends I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar
none is pro pure and it's available discounted at info wars calm its
filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth there's no
priming required it's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce
fluoride up to 95% easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity purify
water from lakes streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial
minerals which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that
leaches from the plastic probe here is the best gravity-fed filter out there
it's what my family uses info wars calm already has the lowest price on probe
here but if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10%
off and info wars calm you can also call to order 888-25-3-1
3-9 will you fight against that no we will run and we will live I fight and
you may die run and you'll love at least a while and dying in your beds many
years from now would you be willing to trade all the
days from this day to that for one chance just one chance to come back here
and tell our enemies that they may take our lives but they'll never take our freedom
rallying patriots worldwide in defense of human liberty it's Alex Jones
it is the second day of January 2013 I am Alex Jones your host we are going to
be here live for the next three hours former congressional fraud investigator
Bob Fletcher who was a Iran contra whistleblower and more will be joining
us to talk about the mafia nature and the complete criminal takeover of our
government in the third hour we will have open phones in the first and second
hour and third hour today you know I hate to say see I told you so but we
talked about this months ago Ron Paul has talked about it here on the
broadcast a month ago or so by the way it's time to get Ron Paul back onto the
crew he said he wanted to come back on in the new year we've all been on record
because they even in Brazil and in other countries in Japan in Europe three or
four times the last few years depending on the country with the EU over them
they have said fiscal cliff we're going to collapse if we don't increase taxes
this is how they got the taxes up to 80% on average in France and then 75% on top
of the money you keep if you're the quote top 2% so the top 2% would be
paying over 90% in taxes
okay they had a bunch of actors and people who are really the nouveau riche
the new rich who were leaving so now France is backing off and saying okay
it'll only be a 50% tax on everybody who makes more than a million euros a year
so you pay all these taxes and then if you keep a million over that
you make ten million dollars you keep two million you make ten million euros
you keep two million and they go well that's over a million we're gonna get
75% of that so you'd have to make ten million dollars to make half a million I
mean does that really quote sound fair to all of you that love big government
and do you know that people that make that type of money are the folks that
actually buy services and are the heart of the economy but see if you're a
Rothschild or a Rockefeller or a Queen of England they're all in giant tax-free
foundations grandfather that nobody else is allowed to set up you can't set up a
family partnership like Rockefeller Brothers Foundation and pay zero tax
they are allowed to and Bill Gates was allowed to and Warren Buffett was
allowed to they've been doing this since 1906 with the Sherman Antitrust Act with
Teddy Roosevelt that they sold as a way to soak the robber barons who were a
bunch of exempt from the law private armies of Pinkerton out murdering people
in mass I mean they wanted your property from the 1850s on they just had you know
a trainload of armed troops show up private troops they come kill you that's
on record so people started getting together and
the the Rockefellers on record had a bunch of their people wiped out
repeatedly when towns would get together when Pinkerton and others would go
slaughter people the towns would get together with their guns and go after
them so then in some cases they call the army in to back up the Rockefellers I
mean our country has been through this over and over again the globalist the
multinational corporations in Latin America and in Africa and in Burma in
places you can go look up 4,000 killed in British takeover of Burma but back in
like 98 I mean there's all these examples where they set up a UN
biodiversity zone and just went in and killed the natives earlier this year the
New York Times even reported but back of the paper that the UN in Central Africa
and in South America in different countries would go in and they're like
is it right the UN soldiers went in to the ancestral lands and burned down the
villages and shot people they're like well it is for the earth of all places
it's in Uganda where they say we need to invade because of a guy who hadn't been
seen in six years that's just the cover oh we're there because the Kony and
meanwhile the UN is lining them up and killing them in fact we guys type in UN
killing people in Uganda for UN killing villagers in Uganda as part of
environmental zones I mean what's frustrating is I know the UN is a murder
crew the most murderous we've ever seen after Mao Zedong I know the globalist
literally line up villages and just mow the people down and it's even in the
news and then I got to watch Obama up there crying over Sandy Hook with no
tears completely fake
I mean I know what the globalists stand for I know who they are I know what
their fruits are and I told everybody I said they're gonna massively increase
taxes across the board scores of new taxes are going in right now scores on
everybody they are going to continue to get us in debt yeah there it is armed
troops burned down homes kill children to evict Ugandans in name of global
warming neo-colonial land grabs carried out on behalf of World Bank based
British company UN troops pull up block the roads the mercenaries go in and do
the actual killing just like in the case of Uganda that you heard the UN dropped
the ball of the million dead they didn't drop the ball they took out the ruling
class Christians killed almost some estimates are over a million but the
official has been under a million eight hundred thousand plus Christians who
were the 10% minority who own most of the country they just came in with the
UN and foreign mercs and the majority animist that's rock worshipping animal
worshipping group and just slaughtered everyone I mean there's video and photos
online of the UN troops chopping children up and burning them over fires
just any and I and when I see Miss America or Miss USA because they're told
do this to win this is what the judges want to hear they go I just want to
thank the UN I just want to serve the UN the UN is just so great Oh Angelina Jolie
and then you're getting your hair cut my son was getting his hair cut and I'm
listening to this woman talking and she's going I just can't wait you know I
want to go to college and be a UN you know delegate and I want to be an
ambassador someday and I want to save people through the UN and she's got
stars in her eyes and I'm like you know the UN runs giant mass murder operations
and she just looks at me like I'm a terrorist and she's not a bad person
it's just they believe a fantasy like a two-year-old that believes a fat guy in
red pajamas is really coming down the chimney and it's not true so I knew
100% what was gonna happen with the fiscal cliff I said the Republicans will
sell out because they were already sold out it's like saying Beelzebub is gonna
shell out to the devil Beelzebub is the devil
it's like saying you know a grizzly bear is gonna sell out to the Bears he is a
bear it's like saying a prostitute is gonna become a hooker it's like saying
water is gonna become wet or fish are going to start swimming in the sea or
sheep are going to start braying and buying a bad man and the problem is most
people that know about this get cynical and go well the world's run by evil the
public's too dumb to help I'll just join the evil when you do that everything
collapses okay and you will be destroyed as well and and and and the world is
giving into evil right now before I get into the fiscal cliff numbers you know
Mexico roughly has three times and it's only about half the geographic area
Mexico has three times the natural resources that the United States has and
Mexico most cities outside tourist areas have sewage running down the street with
children walking around with their ribs sticking out and it looks like the
souls been sucked out of the people because they've been under tyranny so
long that their very essence has been pulled out of them
that's what corruption does and we're going under that where the elites live
in their walled armored cities and they're not safe either and we're all
out here in squalor and and and the establishment says they're doing this
consciously by design that's what agenda 21 is is turning civilization on its
head and building civilization around the destruction of civilization or a
boot stomping on the human face forever a society that becomes more ugly more
trampled trampled and being trampled upon aka 1984 so I've watched this done
in the third world over and over again there's an IMF World Bank manual the
112 points that's public since 2002 when it got leaked when stickles left how
they engineer it how they collapse societies it's all a blueprint so I'm
going okay and then you know it's like when you're reading Bambi to your kid
okay honey I was reading my four-year-old I go this is a sad part where
the mommy deer gets shot turn the page mommy gets shot on the next page I read
Bambi probably 20 times I mean I know I probably had it read to me 20 or 30
times and then I've read it 20 or 30 times I know how Bambi goes see and see
I know how this goes it's not my opinion
they're going to bankrupt us and the equation is about 90 percent of all the
taxes will go to offshore banks who will then use it to come in and develop but
only develop to drive down wages and turn green fields around their bases
into squalid people living in cardboard boxes with one-third of the children
born in Mexico City with a disorder where they have no upper brain they can
breathe but there's no brain and the parents love them and take care of them
but that's how toxic the waste is you never hear environmentalists talk about
that because that's their program in fact Henry Kissinger documents came out
where they said ship the toxic waste the third world well forget that there was
one with summers Larry Summers put out a memo I think ten years ago or longer he
was under Clinton saying let's ship the toxic waste down there to get rid of
Brazilians I mean these people just sit around publicly writing let's send stuff
to Brazil you know that'll get I'm gonna check the quote I'm 90% sure it was
summers we'll be right back we have witnessed two terrible storms in the
East but we are still in the eye of the perfect storm the most devastating
economic condition since the Great Depression America's worst drought in
agricultural history and now the economic results of the presidential
election this perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply I just
doubled down and got even more supplies from eat foods direct and I recommend
you do the same it's time to get your own supply for me foods direct I know I
won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food I'm taking
control of my future and you're nuts if you don't do the same go to eat foods
direct calm forward slash Alex to find the specials and you can start with a
holiday gift pack that's normally $80 now under 50 bucks remember I can warn
you but I can't feed you call 800 409 5633 or eat foods direct calm forward
slash Alex would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late or
oh nine five six three three or eat foods direct calm forward slash Alex
would it save you time to get the best quality water filters and the best
quality storable foods from one company you bet it would and now you can add Big
Berkey water filters calm Big Berkey water filter products and great tasting
long-lasting storable wise foods are both now available on one website Big
Berkey water filters calm wise foods ready to eat meals are packed in airtight
nitrogen pouches and come with a 25 year shelf life Big Berkey water filters are
powerful enough to purify treated untreated or even stagnant pond water
combine Berkey water filters with wise foods for an unbeatable preparedness
combination get free shipping on every order over $50 and GCN listeners receive
5% off all ceramic filter systems visit big br ke y water filters calm or call
eight seven seven ninety nine Berkey that's eight seven seven ninety nine
br ke y or go to Big Berkey water filters calm hempusa.org has a newly
designed website and a new and improved detoxification product order our new
micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins minerals iodine and probiotics
and we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder absolutely free micro plant
powder only at hempusa.org call nine oh eight six nine one two six zero eight
that's nine oh eight six nine one two six zero eight and see what our powder
seeds and oil can do for you only at hempusa.org only this offer ends
January 31st hi this is Ted Anderson have you ever wondered why banks stock
workers investment advisors won't talk about gold IRAs they've been available
since 1986 yet the financial industry won't recognize the value of gold for
your retirement gold is outperform paper investments yet no word about IRAs if
you would like to have gold for your retirement call 800 686 2 2 3 7 don't
get left behind by rising inflation and low returns call 800 686 2 2 3 7 secure
your future and call 1-800 686 2 2 3 7 you land in Buenos Aires then a shuttle
to Santa Rosa where a nicely furnished cabin with all amenities Wi-Fi executive
food and wine and laundry service awaits after a good night's sleep your
adventure begins you're on a golden stag safari for big game but it's not Africa
it's Argentina one-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo
sugar bighorn Rams wild boar and the biggest stag deer in South America all
gold medal quality all the action you can handle land rovers top rental guns
with scopes all food beverages hunting guides ground transportation included
and more all more affordable than you can imagine the adventure of a lifetime
starts at golden stag safaris dot-com the big game hunting ranch golden stag
safaris dot-com
ladies and gentlemen we have a maximum red alert maximum red alert we knew
this was coming they are moving on every front we're gonna get to that maximum
red alert a moment again when I say something I always double-check it yeah
Larry Summers in 1991 and Wikipedia has a link to the official memo that he put
out we'll put that on screen go ahead and scroll down it's also in
mainstream news where he said let's ship our toxic waste to Brazil that'll help
get their population down as well
and he goes over the reasons well you need to you need to be gotten rid of so
again this is their attitude about you and they're gonna raise taxes where
you're not gonna be able to live in the countryside they're going to live in the
countryside you'll need to have tens of millions even live in the countryside
soon if they have their way they're they're tearing up roads all over the
country while building napta superhighways that are UN zones you've
got to pay taxes on oh and by the way Perry just reauthorized that even the
legislature voted it down what twice but separately on national news they'd say
there's no napta superhighway even though it's all Department of
Transportation official North American Union agreements I've got clips of CNN
going Ron Paul is literally insane he is imagining something called a napta
superhighway when we had billboards up all over Texas announcing it and they're
building it and taking over our existing roads to pay for the building of it
putting toll roads on I mean it's like hey we should arm our teachers like
Israel Israel doesn't arm teachers that's a lie well no it's admitted
here's Israeli news no no no such thing as Israeli news hey here's the memo
where they say ship toxic waste to Latin America to kill their people but they
want to open the borders to let them come in to drop down wages here it's not
because they care about the Latin Americans it's because they want to
destroy all our countries shut up racist but no they say they want to ship the
toxic waste down there so one-third of their kids are born with this one
disorder where they have literally no upper brain and have have no brain waves
all they have is a brain stem be quiet racist oh what next you're gonna say the
brain exists I mean this is just how the system responds and there ladies and
gentlemen I was looking at the new issue of the magazine that about a week and a
half ago we finished writing my letter editor's letter to the public when
Feinstein did not put her bill out yet where I say they will physically come
for the guns because I knew about their statements and what they'd said
previously and how handgun control Inc and others had said look we're gonna
physically get them in his next reelection they don't just brag to each
other this is a this is a militarized mercenary globalist group these aren't
liberals that's their cover and when they say something folks they're gonna
try to do it when they're talking to each other well I mean when you get
these mob Don's talking to each other this is battle plans like a general in a
briefing room saying you know the airstrikes are gonna be here get me the
satellite Intel I mean when they say it they mean it and so the new issues 2013
the year America dies they're gonna bankrupt the economy they're gonna bring
in by executive order carbon taxes they're already shutting down the power
plants they're gonna get rid of the borders Republicans have already
announced that because the mega banks want it they've done it in every other
region every other country everything you're seeing happen in the EU is gonna
happen here they want to collapse everything they want you poor to totally
control you plus they like it they love living on armored hills outside the city
watching you live in cardboard boxes and watching your children die it's
beautiful to them it makes them enjoy their wealth more when you're poor
there's a word for it it's called total wickedness total evil now here's the new
article total red alert total red alert and I'm gonna explain something to you
no one I listen to mainline conservative talk radio and they're like oh yeah they
want to bring back the old thing where you can't manufacture semi-auto anymore
no no no the bill that Obama is supporting that's introduced tomorrow
when Congress comes back in its public bill says we have the discretion to ban
all guns and make you turn them in if we want it's got that footnote in it now
they don't care what federal courts rule they're gonna do an executive order of
that doesn't work here is the red alert red alert red alert red alert red alert
red alert and I'm gonna have Nemo add to this the point that it's the nationwide
plan Illinois moves to outlaw modern firearms and criminalized owners all
semi-autos or any other guns they want banned in Illinois that's why they
always did the void card every other country first they register then they
take and here it is Illinois state president that's the state president not
some little low-level John Cullerton will reportedly introduce a draconian
bill today in the Illinois legislature that will effectively ban all modern
firearms criminalize their owners and subject their owners to confiscation by
the Illinois State Police yeah that's who they use old veteran has a heart
attack doesn't renew their card day one their SWAT team now they got your list
they're coming for you in Illinois and we're gonna come back and break this
down for you and then get into the fiscal takeover that the Republicans
sold out to of course they sold out it was their job under foreign bank control
we're on the march the Empire's on the run Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other
illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a
revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution recent advances
in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily
to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while
powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as stress
staff pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology
has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions the
Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook if you want an American
company with American products made by Americans here is the cow bend soap
company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years these
all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut
oils that are earth-friendly and safe see them on the web at five star soap
calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog by the one to two months sample
package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now or save
big with a one to two year supply of soaps or all your cleaning needs this
is an amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and you will love
the way real soap makes you feel see them on the web at 5 star soap calm or
call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog we have witnessed two terrible storms in
the east but we are still in the eye of the perfect storm the most devastating
economic condition since the Great Depression America's worst drought in
agricultural history and now the economic results of the presidential
election this perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply I just
doubled down and got even more supplies from each woods direct and I recommend
you do the same it's time to get your own supply for me foods direct I know I
won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food I'm taking
control of my future and you're nuts if you don't do the same go to eat foods
direct.com forward slash Alex to find the specials and you can start with a
holiday gift pack that's normally $80 now under 50 bucks remember I can warn
you but I can't feed you call 800 409 5633 or eat foods direct.com forward
slash Alex would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late or
oh nine five six three three or eat foods direct.com forward slash Alex we
now take you live to the Central Texas command center and the heart of the
resistance rallying Patriots worldwide
you're listening to the Alex Jones show
I want to be clear about this again for listeners who just tuned in for the
first time listing on news stations all over the country I know my broadcast has
sounded radical over the years and some people thought man that guy's crazy am I
crazy now no the elites are out of control
tyranny looks crazy to somebody that's not a tyrant and so I understand why
hearing me report on stuff before it all unfolded sounded crazy but I was
desperately trying to warn people to stop us from getting to this point but
I've always said that once the real tyranny starts unfolding and Ron Paula
said this as well that if we did our job and warn people that once it happened
our credibility would go way up and then we'd have a chance to beat them but
politics now is not like something that even if you're involved that's at a
distance and you know you talk with your buddies at the golf course or around the
water cooler folks it's time to drop everything and get really aggressive
or it's over okay the globalist know that America was really starting to wake
up to him so what do you do if you're a slave master and your slave starts
getting out of line what does a pimp do America it really is the story of a
prostitute this beautiful healthy farm girl thinks she'll go to Hollywood and
be a star she gets there works at McDonald's can't can't get the star job
she wants and they ask her do you want to be in pornography and then pretty
soon she's a prostitute and by the way that's how show business works period
I've never even tried to be in movies but have been offered a few times to be
in some pretty big films by Tommy Pilata and Richard Linkletter and so I didn't
have that experience there but then I got invited to go try out for some other
movies and some of the people associated with the films didn't even know that I
was already an established radio talk show host and already you know on I
think about 15 stations at the time this had to be about 2,000 and I was still
pretty skinny that it looked a lot more attractive than I do now and they point
blank at one of these casting studios asked me if I wanted to be in porn and
I was like are you kidding
and that's just when you're at another meeting people want you to be in a TV
show and then you're walking in the parking lot so my next door goes hey
come on over here and it's a mainline system at that time associated with the
city and you walk in there and there's all these people lined up trying to be
stars and right in front of you they're asking women if they want to be in porn
and they're asking you if you want to be in porn see that's how ubiquitous this
is but I've already gone off into a porn analogy I never told that story
that's how screwed up this is and everybody wants to be a star because
you're nobody if you're not a star let me tell you something once you've been in
movies been around movies they're totally unhappy people it's nothing
it's nothing to be Brad Pitt it's nothing to be any of these people if
there's nothing this is life this is what it is what's rewarding is being
truthful and honorable and having children and raising a family and being
strong the fame the garbage it means nothing but they control people with it
but but but getting back to the analogy of America like a young farm girl from
Kansas beautiful black hair green eyes just perfect complexion perfect
proportions she goes to California because everybody told her she ought to
be a movie star she was so pretty she was so smart and that's just what she
should do five years later she is a heroin addict and a $20 hooker that
nobody even wants to have sex with and then she's OD'd dead at the morgue
that's happened tens of thousands of times in the last 50 years in Los Angeles
alone if she would have gone out had an economy found a man had a business would
have had children would have had a life would have been a grandmother would have
fully fulfilled her destiny of being a wholesome human wrecked destroyed by
Hollywood and you know how those pimps work they tell the young women well we
can get you in movies but first you gotta prove yourself you got to go out
and turn some tricks you're gonna have some sex with some people plus you're
gonna like it they got money and stuff and so the 18 year old woman beautiful
unpilfered might have lost their virginity these women go out and they
try to get into the nastiest forms of sex try to make themselves like it so
that they can then be in movies it's like learning how to be a sword
swallower or a fire blower or something I'm telling you folks this is how it
works I'm not gonna tell you any stories I'm
just gonna tell you that's how it works these women try to learn how to hurt
their bodies how to do things that they don't like so they can be a star and
make $2,000 per film having somebody tear their body open and see that's
America once they get you on the plantation once they get you as a
sharecropper once they get you on welfare in the criminal justice system
once they get you under their control under their socialist health care now
they can tell you hey we got to kill old people to pay for young people how's that
sound young people yeah kill people so I get a job see that's what collectivism
is all about being under people's control where the state controls what
movies are made where the state controls what films are made
and with these evil people because I've run into them and around them and also
history it's it's the enjoyment of hurting innocence it's the enjoyment of
having like cattle cars delivered to Hollywood all the young gorgeous women
of America and men now pile off to walk in where seedy hunchback demonic men and
women sit there and poke at them and prod at them and and say what are you
gonna do
and these stars are told okay clean my house
and do this and that and literally sit here while I do horrible things to you
you know I mentioned this yesterday I'm gonna get into the ton of stuff they do
and the most evil because they control the idea of being stars a fiat nothing
fraud and they control the fiat Federal Reserve Notes they get the whole world
on fake dreams and fake money the whole world by these magicians these fraudsters
these these these these Bernie Madoff Ken Lay types and the whole world is run
by these people now mafia criminals where the very worst rise to the top you
know the film the Godfather is actually based on a composite of true stories
Frank Sinatra you name it it's all in there that's a true story the Godfather
is a true story it's a composite Mario Puzos
and in it it's the story of the old New York Godfather they want to run all
sorts of dirty stuff underage hookers heroin and he says I'm not gonna be part
of it so they shoot him and then they get what they want they get and they say
well I will just keep it in the black neighborhood they're animals anyways let
them lose their souls and that's why those zones have been so
destroyed because they were picked as the red-light district as a way to hurt
those people and the same thing has now been done to everybody
you know when I was growing up we wanted party a party beer we had to drive into
Dallas and going to the black neighborhood we can walk right into a
liquor store if you were 14 years old driving with your 16 year old buddy walk
right into a black liquor store and they'd sell you alcohol and cops would
walk you would watch you walk right out of the liquor store with beer or vodka
or whatever because they were all getting paid off in Dallas Texas
see that's what crimes all about they make things illegal so they can get a
cut of it and anybody that's lived in a crime-run city knows that the naive
people mainly the churchgoers who really think the world is what's going on their
little church they are totally blind to this entire situation but a hundred
times or more I jump in the back of the pickup truck with my older buddies and
we drive into South Dallas you can hear guns going off in the background quite a
few times and people try to mug you and everything else just just just to get
beer so we could have a party and get the cheerleaders over and we drive back
to the rich neighborhood we lived in by the golf course and everybody get drunk
but the point is is that that's just one one hundredth of the stuff that goes on
out there and corruption isn't cute it's it's it's sick it's horrible okay what
corruption is it's a little family-owned restaurant where the organized crime
comes in and says I want you to hire this person for me here and I want you
to pay me 20% all your profits and my guys gonna make sure and you got to sit
there while their thug comes in a few hours a day and tells you what to do and
then the thug wants to have sex with your daughter so the the thug rapes your
daughter one night in the parking lot and you you beat the brains out of the
guy that did it and the police come and arrest you and tell you that you're
gonna go to death row because you killed one of their guys and see they don't
want you having a gun to protect yourself from them I'm gonna get into
the fiscal cliff and open the phones up and everything else but you've got to
understand how this works in America was like a beautiful supermodel that looked
like Wonder Woman those countries and ships we call them women by the analogy
fence and now we're a zombie crack whore in the back of a flat with beg bedbugs
feeding on us and cigarette burns and cuts all over us and almost all the hair
is falling out and she's got double black eyes and the pimp is running a
needle up into her vein to give her an overdose and get rid of her
that's how they get rid of him he's running he's but but see we haven't
quite gotten to that point there's always a point where the hooker goes
I'm going back to Kansas you know she's six months into it she's got diseases
he's had to have an abortion she wants to get off the drugs she wants to go
home to mommy and daddy and he walks in and he knocks her teeth out she falls
down blood coming out takes out a coat hanger and starts beating her and
beating her locks her up for a week in a closet don't don't don't cry just like
Milwaukee when the cops were there Jeffrey Dahmer was authorized to do
what he was doing nobody's coming to help you little kids and nobody's coming
to help you lady and they lock her up in there and have starboard death and he
comes back and says I'll give you some food but you don't you ever try to leave
me again any year later she's dead dead on a dirty mattress and that's what
they're gonna do to America just like they've done to Nigeria and Brazil
they're gonna take us and they're gonna squeeze us out they're gonna strangle
America because they like it they like watching that beauty go out of your eyes
they like putting fluoride in your water and mercury in your shots when global
let's walk into restaurants and see all the disease looking zombie little kids
with the souls already sucked out of them they love it and they're gonna do
it to all of you they're gonna take their time real good on all of you
unless you wake up and realize who they are and that's why I'm here I'm here to
tell you who they are because most people that know this stuff are cowards
and they decide to join the evil they decide to serve this force because when
you are smart enough to know about it you learn about it you know well I'm
gonna play ball the only way to beat this is to not play ball with it now
let's take Illinois famous state millions of hard-working immigrants from
Poland and Germany and Ireland and Scotland went there and Italy and they
took Chicago down with prohibition ten years of the gangsters being
able to make hundreds of millions of dollars a month and that was in those
days equivalent of billions a month and they took it over and it's been their
talent ever since and we're on the radio there in Chicago and when I open the
phones up I first want to give folks there a chance they've taken all your
guns in Chicago now they want to do it system-wide in Illinois
now they want to do it system-wide in Illinois and how's that working out for
you five hundred plus murders last year and people get mugged when when three
four times felons are out there with guns nobody's gonna stop the felons the
highest crime rates are where they take the guns and now Illinois moves to
outlaw modern firearms and criminalize owners Illinois State President John
Cullerton will reportedly introduce a draconian bill today and now it's
happened in the Illinois legislature that will effectively ban all modern
firearms criminalize their owners and subject their guns to confiscation by
the Illinois State Police they're not the Illinois State Police they're the
mafia enforcers the proposed oh yeah when the mafia has been running stuff
for 80 years they wear uniforms the proposed outlawing of firearms was
confirmed by the NRA's Illinois rep according to Robert Farago writing for
the truth about guns website the move coincides with the federal effort by
Diane Feinstein to introduce legislation outlawing all semiotic
semi-automatic firearms and imposing de facto confiscation and the bill will
also shut down John ranges it gets into that and Kurt's adding more to this
article right now at info wars calm red link red alert and I'm telling you
ladies and gentlemen that's why you shouldn't be in to all the stuff that's
corrupt out there because they're gateways when you watch porn you're
aiding them hurting all these innocent young women where they try to make it
look so glamorous most of those women end up dead or in prison look it up when
you when you aid this government you're helping them run murder operations right
now in Africa and Latin America where they come into villages with helicopters
and fire rockets I just showed you the New York Times earlier rockets into
their houses oh you're not gonna hear Angelina Jolie's talk about how that's
bad she goes to those countries and calls for the invasions did you look her
up do you know she's a devil worshiper talks about how much she loves death and
the devil wears a blood amulet around her neck with blood in it take one look
at that woman and tell you she wishes she was a vampire spiritually she is you
notice all the mass shooters son of Sam Ramirez the Night Stalker
the last two shooters New York with the fireman Lanza if you believe that story
all of them admitted devil worshippers all of them devil worshippers devil
worshippers are our problem devil worshippers let me explain something to
you criminals people that are forced into it because oh you relate to class
you're going to juvenile hall now they beat you up you don't join the gang
that's just the muscle of the psychopaths but the real kingpins the
real king rats they need to be dealt with good men are there to stomp the
guts out of the psychopaths politically but if they start the physical fight
with us it's up to us to make sure they can't keep hurting innocent people
it's up to us to stand up against these people and that's what I'm here to do
I'm here to break down for you who the enemy is so you know who's gonna help
those children who's gonna help those women who's gonna help all those people
I am I'm standing up what about you I'm standing up for the kids they're
aborting we're winning that fight politically we can win if we just get up
on our legs get up off our butts we can win we can save the innocence but you
gotta go after the evil this is Alex Jones with five good reasons you should
consider buying a solar power generator number one new climate legislation could
easily double or triple your electric bill number two our new energy czar
wants to control how much power your electric company allows you to have it's
true total government control of electricity in the name of smart grid
technology is coming number three in some areas of the country the power grid
is dangerously overloaded and now new socialist legislation is only
compounding the problem number four dangerous weather is always a threat to
local grids every year thousands of families lose their power from weather
related onages number five a solar power generator provides powerful backup
insurance and peace of mind folks I really believe in the solar power
generators offered by Solutions from Science one of my oldest sponsors you
can get more information at www.my solar backup.com that's my solar backup.com
remember the government doesn't own the Sun so go to my solar backup.com or call
1-877-327-0365 we all know that Berkey water
purification systems are the most trusted name in water filtration as an
authorized Berkey dealer for over six years in serving thousands of satisfied
customers the Berkey guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration
systems the Berkey light systems include a set of self sterilizing and
re-cleanable black purification elements that purify water by removing chlorine
pathogenic bacteria cyst and parasites to non detectable levels and remove
harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides order the Berkey light system
today complete with two black Berkey elements for only two hundred and thirty
one dollars and the Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge with the
purchase of a Berkey light the Berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride
and arsenic filters for only $39.99 that's over 30% off the retail price
call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653 that's 1-877-886-3653 or
order online at goberky.com that's goberky.com today
big business has discovered the preparedness market and that makes it
difficult to know where to go and who to trust my patriotsupply.com is owned and
operated by patriots just like you has the best prices on storeable food
non-gmo seeds water filtration devices home canning equipment survival and
self-reliance books and more my patriotsupply.com has old-fashioned
values and the absolute best customer service in the industry look for the
deal of the day unique affordable survival supplies that fit anyone's
budget get same-day shipping on all orders and free shipping on orders over
$49 call 866-229-0927 866-229-0927 or visit mypatriotsupply.com for
emergency preparedness self-reliance and food independence shop with a name you
know and a name you can trust before it's time to survive it's time to
prepare mypatriotsupply.com
by the way the NRA is reporting we've got links to it in infowarsk.com that
there's a good chance this total semi-auto gun ban banning of shooting
ranges SWAT teaming of gun owners will pass the Illinois legislature and then
it'll take five years to beat it in court federal court you know just ruled
how you can't deny people the right to keep and bear arms you can't deny them the
right to concealed carry their answer is oh really really Mac you heard Al Capone
do whatever we want these people are our slaves they've all got bodyguards the
rest of it incredible article up at infowarsk.com and police all over the
country on record have been training to confiscate firearms for a long time
there's another big article remember we did this six months ago a video with Rob
do a special report US military training to kill Americans that don't turn in
guns and their own army training manual we had the latest on that up at
infowarsk.com Obama would call a military to disarm Americans during
national emergency and we've got a police lieutenant talking about how
they're training for the roll out of martial law now that doesn't mean it's
going to happen they tell the police this to gauge and watch you to see who
says they won't go along with it it's part of a profiling operation but all
over the United States they're setting up quote gang checkpoints now where they
set up highway checkpoints ransack your car and take photos of your tattoos
that's in the Associated Press I'm gonna be getting to that I mean this is just
it's on the homeland security was set up for gun owners veterans conservatives
they're gonna take America down they're gonna bring us into a depression and you
think 50 million on food stamps is bad how about a hundred how about 200 million
even if you don't like the globalist you're gonna go to them on your knees
because they're gonna run your life this is the mafia takeover of America this is
the breaking of America and that's why they report Senate passes deal means
higher taxes on 77% of households and coming up the next hour we have the
clip of Obama pledging nobody under 250 thou a year would have a tax increase
folks he's raised more than 10 different taxes on people different ways but see
as long as you get an Obama phone it's okay he'd never lie to you fiscal cliff
deal one dollar in spending cuts for every 41 in tax increases
and of course Paul Ryan voted for it Romney's owned by the same bank so is
Paul Ryan this is a plan these people are in charge because they are globalist
and only fully waking up to it will save us
you tune into mainline conservative talk radio they're like oh yeah you know the
Democrats will get it going for our guns you know and Rand Paul's like yeah let
them raise taxes that means they'll lose the next election the fix is in in most
areas bud there's election fraud
the Congress engages in insider trading publicly the UN runs around lining up
villagers blowing their heads off to take their property and nobody cares
well nobody's gonna care about you America all these so-called men that
yeah you're about the game yeah you do too well these guys like look at each
other go you know a lot about football you're really manly yeah you're real
manly sport you can have everything you got taken
let's go out to break with Diane Feinstein letting you know how it all
works here she is saying mr. and mrs. America get ready to have your guns
taken here it is California Senator Dianne Feinstein worked for more than a
year to get the assault weapons bill passed in the face of ferocious
opposition from the National Rifle Association she says she got the best
she could if I could have gotten 51 votes in the Senate of the United States
for an outright ban picking up every one of them mr. and mrs. America turn them
all in I would have done it I could not do that and now she's gotten the votes
and Illinois can't wait to pistol-whip every gun owner literally knock your
teeth out and teach you the Mafia runs your life
this is GCN the Genesis communications radio network now that we have moved
into the winter season there is an increased need to support our immunity
and health at silver lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by
providing a full selection of silver based products our most popular silver
based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our 2 ounce nano silver
nasal applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps just released
is our 100% natural silver gel our new silver gel is not based on synthetic
gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface but
rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while
delivering the silver more effectively visit www.silverlungs.com and click on
our store page to find what silver based products are best for you that's www.
silverlungs.com waging war on corruption Alex Jones on the GCM radio network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers
well so does he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from
Austin Texas Alex Jones
we've got a audio clip of a man that said he's a police lieutenant I don't
need to deny that because he sounds credible and I have it all over the news
they're preparing for gun confiscation I'm saying they're getting ready to come
take our guns so now I mean it's just all out in the open we have an article
where the Pentagon admits it but I won't open the phones up for police
specifically if you're training for civil unrest and gun confiscation and
what you're being told only police and then after that every take a few calls
from them folks have been begging to hear from Obama supporters and Obama
supporters can call in normally when the phones are open not many of them um end
up doing it and they seem to call in and go well I just don't like Romney and I'm
like don't you get it Obama was the heir apparent Romney was like the placeholder
the dummy the decoy like a dummy that Obama fought with Obama's a puppet too
but they want him to do it because the left loves it when he orders torture or
wireless wiretapping or murdering people and you know u.s. military invading all
over Africa every African country I mean they think that's really cool because
he's part black and I mean it's just it's cool I mean it's it's like it's I
mean he's I mean his dad was reportedly Kenyan or part Kenyan I mean it's it's
over I mean it he could he could poach the brains of small children and eat
them for breakfast it'd be beautiful because he I mean look he's got melanin
in his skin I mean it's like it's okay
it's trendy I mean it's really cool Obama won yeah yeah we won you know the
people that are into that stuff and if Romney would have won they'd be the same
agenda and you'd have a bunch of Republicans going back to sleep running
around going hey we won we won well Romney wants our guns we'll turn them in
well Romney but see they don't need to play that anymore because America is
more than 50% quote minority now and they've got around 90% of the quote
minorities voting for Obama because I mean obviously he's not a racist white
person and obviously owning a gun means you're in the Klan I mean it doesn't
make any sense but that matter I mean it's true because they said so and so
that is the law law land that we've entered so I want to give the number out
for police officers only just specifically call in about this eight
hundred two five nine nine two three one eight hundred two five nine nine two
three one and congressional fraud investigator in a RAM com for
whistleblower Bob Fletcher will be joining us to talk about all this in the
third hour we'll also have open phones as well make sure Fletcher knows he
knows he's coming on talk about the gun grab and all the tyranny in Congress
right okay he doesn't know that good because he can talk about so much what a
what an interesting person but again not just politically in my gut I'm totally
freaked out because my I have good instincts and they are just like a
firehouse alarm going off I mean it I'm jumping out of bed you know at 5 30 in
the morning now having no trouble not feeling sleepy I could work myself to
death if I didn't control myself because I realize I have actually gone up
against mass murdering total evil criminals who plan a total takeover a
purge you name it because I know going along with them won't save us they plan
to totally gut America once they get the guns they're gonna bring us into total
depression and that's why they're going for this right now and I pray to God
that all the brain numb entranced people out there will break out of their trance
right now and realize the power you have because if you telegraph the message to
the criminals that hey we know your criminal we know your insider traders we
know you work for foreign banks we know your ship in narcotics they do all this
publicly now we know your murderers that run al-qaeda we know you stage 9-11 they
may be forced to back off but if they think you're gonna go along with it the
reason they're so arrogant is they're about to pull false flags I mean I can
just tell you right now false flags are probably in the offing as we speak they
pull the trigger on operations that'll be happening very soon unless we get the
word out 800-259-9231 800-259-9231 police straight ahead stay with us
you prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms but if you don't have a home
security system then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home
protection when you're sleeping who's watching out for intruders and spooks
check out simply safe it's a new do-it-yourself home security system
that is completely wireless go to get simply safe calm simply safe is
independent and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if the grid goes
down you're protected it's completely customizable so you can use it in your
home business boat trailer storage unit or shed simply safe is also ridiculously
easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes so there's no need to let a
stranger into your home if you move or need to relocate you can take this
system with you wherever you go simply safe will stand guard protecting your
property 24 hours a day seven days a week go to get simply safe calm that's
get simply safe calm Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers
the prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse
the globalist model is to shut down societies and starve Patriots out until
they acquiesce to the global takeover that's why we've assembled the most
vital and important preparedness items at info wars shop calm these are items
that I did research on that I personally use you've got the life straw so you can
turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go the Ktor hand crank
generator to charge up key equipment during power outages are out in the
field strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by
Matthew Stein thorough safe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself
during any radiological event and crank shortwave AM FM radios everything that
we've researched and found to be the best is available at info war shop calm
and your purchase makes our info war possible we're getting prepared are you
in full wars shop calm millions of people are going to get sick this winter
from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with
supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution
recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that
can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help
improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every
day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as
stress staff pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new
technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at
several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions
the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
it is certainly an extremely dark day for our Republic Illinois has
introduced legislation the head of their State House to outlaw all modern
firearms all semi-auto handguns rifles I guess revolvers tube and outlaw shooting
ranges it is just an outright statewide ban of almost everything and they've got
the Floyd cards to know everybody in the state who's got them to make you turn
them in total red alert info wars calm also Obama would call on military to
disarm Americans during national emergency that's on all the executive
orders and the training manuals all the proof the military en masse gearing up
with 400,000 auxiliary trained soldiers for gun confiscation here in this
country absolutely insane army manual FM 3-3940 put out in 2010 updated with the
gun confiscation back the main mission now of the National Guard is shutting
down cities taking over communications that's your local radio and TV and
coming down your street just like they did in Katrina as a drill and as ABC
News reported don't turn them in then you pull the trigger and kill an
American that's a quote by the army officer and they've got the clergy
response teams they're ready to tell everybody to turn their guns in there's
Rob dues original report video report that I wrote with him put together with
him miss making the point that I can vet it because I did the research on it 1
million 276,000 views 21 minutes long everyone needs to go see it and the
report is from July 16th 2012 or half a year ago six months ago troops ordered
to kill Americans who not turn in their guns and it's all in the official
manuals even how to deal with your dead bodies and how to process your corpses
how to take daddy to one area of the camp for forced labor where mommy and
the girls and boys go this is the absolute total evil of the foreign banks
that have seized the country and if you're a new listener going this is
scary I run into so many people go man I can't listen to your show it's scary
because I go look it up and it's true aren't you glad we're here on the air
the fact that we're on over 140 stations shows we can beat this as things get
worse I get put on more stations because people go wait this is true we got a we
got to save America why haven't they killed me yet because it'll make
everybody pay more attention to what I've said it'll make everybody listen to
me it'll underline it'll highlight it'll put 15 exclamation points behind
everything I said and look I'm ready okay I don't want to die believe me but
it's in God's hands I am at peace I'm at peace when it comes to being attacked
set up destroyed whatever the case is I've given it to God because there's no
future anyways if we don't beat them okay it's very very simple you know I
liken it to some of the true stories where a ship has capsized there's been a
lot of cases of this and people are caught in the inner bulkheads and the
water slowly rising and there's women and children in there and you've seen
this in movies reenacted and multiple men go and drowned trying to get out and
finally one of them finds a passage out holding their breath five minutes to
find a passage back through and to get rescued and to get people you know in
there to save the women and children or to or to find a blowtorch to come cut
their way through on the top and it's the same thing I am in the tunnel
underwater folks trying to get out of here to get back and cut into the bulkhead
and get people out if I die it doesn't matter I'm not gonna sit here with women
and children as the water rises like a rat hearing them scream and cry I'm in
the tunnel right now folks swimming as hard as I can and and getting out of
this thing means you waking up you are Alex Jones making it to the other end
finding the blowtorch or calling the Coast Guard and getting in there and
cutting through and getting the people out you've got to help me because we're
all together folks you right now are in that bulkhead with the water coming in
and you're like man this is scary yeah we're the water is rising you're like
but it's scary okay it's scary we got to swim out of here but there's all these
different directions we don't know if you're really gonna find oxygen we know
we're gonna die here so I'll go straight you go left you go right you know how
many men are there here let's let's do we got to go we got to go but we could
die look we're gonna die anyways don't you get it
the toll-free number to join us is eight hundred two five nine nine two three one
they're not gonna move slow in the takeover anymore homeland security was
designed and set up the whole time from day one for gun owners conservatives
libertarians that was all going on under Bush the conservative side just wouldn't
pick up on it because it didn't compute then under Obama he announced it because
now it was time for that not because Democrats were in but because the
timeline had been moved up because now they'd shifted into the new paradigm
we're gonna go to Gordon who's a police officer in Indiana here in a moment the
toll-free number for police officers preparing for civil unrest your take on
Feinstein saying we're gonna take the semi-autos make you turn them in the
bills introduced tomorrow going in the Illinois legislature today I mean it's
on the Illinois State House it's on I've got the bill number up at info Wars
calm we've got all the articles about it it's on
and so even if my family is in danger it doesn't matter there's no future form if
we don't beat this the only hope is taking action
it's the only hope we've got and I'm always about attacking on multiple
fronts because we never know what's gonna work the best that's why I say
I'll go straight you go left right somebody go up somebody go down you know
we got to swim out through this doorway in this flooded ship we got to go out
there we got a don't panic hold your breath you can go four or five minutes
but you've got to control yourselves and not have fear because it's the same
thing I've been able to before to swim it's always my mind that makes me stop
I don't know two and a half Olympic lengths back when I was about 25 years
old now I can only do about one and a half links underwater and you just kind
of like almost mesmerize yourself and just relax they got skin divers that can
go down for you know ten minutes but they've trained themselves and trained
their lungs and their blood system so I'm nothing I'm just saying both people
can't swim in a in a small you know private pool 50 yards underwater 30
yards underwater and I liken it to the same thing politically you've got to get
over the fear and realize the greater fear is letting these people win 800 to
5 at 9 9 2 3 1 for police to call in it's now out in the open Illinois says
they're gonna take all the semi-autos and then maybe everything else later
under the Floyd card we told you that was coming get you registered then take
it Diane Feinstein saying we want to take
mr. and mrs. America's guns it's just amazing that all of this has happened
and then coming up I'll get into the fiscal cliff they just use that as a way
to jack up taxes they use that as of course they didn't cut spending of
course it's all expanding of course they raise it on 77% of people in America and
and Obama promised he wouldn't they're gangsters they want your money let's go
ahead and go to Gordon who's a police officer in Indiana what's your take on
all this well I want to say I haven't listened to your show for quite a while
like the Bible says you will not you shall know them by their works I'm a
police officer in Indiana here and I'm also black and I'm I am totally against
this Obama thing about wanting to take a gun I've spoken to spoken to several
officers and also to several citizens black citizens I should say they all say
they're not going to give up their guns out of it it's uh I mean it's it's uh
it's clear that uh that that that they want a total takeover of the United
States and they know they can only do it by disarming us and I for one I'm not
going to go door-to-door trying to take the citizens guns away because it's
clearly against the Constitution what do you think about the state police who are
specifically trained to do this this is going to become a very unhealthy job
yes I was I was a member of our SWAT team here years ago and the newer
members here are actually hooked up with the state police and one officer in
particular actually has a one of those tracking devices embedded in his tooth I
thought it was a joke and as I when I spoke to him found out he really did
have one put in his tooth and I know they make it real elitist I have a
cousin who's in special ops about seven years ago he goes yeah we were in a
briefing with officers 200 of us and they said we're all gonna get chips the
next time I saw him he said don't ask me about it anymore they know I'm talking
to you and it's all classified and he said he won't even talk to me now I
mean he'll say hi and stuff but he acts like I'm a rattlesnake and they all got
microchips yeah the cops are getting him look and they tell you like it's real
elitist like you're gonna get a chip cuz you're elite and they're they're MJTF
thing multi-jurisdictional task forcing the police now they're taking the quote
special units and making them special response to federal events yeah I mean
it's a takeover and and and so this guy got a microchip tell us about that
yes microchip embedded in his tooth and supposedly is what he was the only one
on the team so far so far they've done it and here in the city but uh other
members of this it's like a multi-jurisdictional SWAT team that they
they've come up with in the last I think three years
yeah it's MJTF that's how they dissolve they give the funding to the MJTF and
basically dissolve the counties and cities in the end exactly well listen
you ought to ask him to call back sometime how they talked him into it
because I'm sure it was the federal grant Mexico's done this as well with
their police you can that's MSNBC we guys type in Mexican police officials to
get implanted chips and teeth or in skin it's MSNBC AP Reuters amazing and then
call back in and tell miss tell us how they sold it to him anything else sir I
just I just want to let the American people know let them know that not every
black person is is for this gun compensation thing that they're talking
about like I said every person I have talked to said they are not going to
turn in their gun and I'm talking black black hold on I gotta hear the end of
this and then Eli stay with us we have witnessed two terrible storms in the
east but we are still in the eye of the perfect storm the most devastating
economic condition since the Great Depression America's worst drought in
agricultural history and now the economic results of the presidential
election this perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply I just
doubled down and got even more supplies from eat foods direct and I recommend
you do the same it's time to get your own supply for me foods direct I know I
won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food I'm taking
control of my future and you're nuts if you don't do the same go to eat foods
direct.com forward slash Alex to find the specials and you can start with a
holiday gift pack that's normally $80 now under 50 bucks remember I can warn
you but I can't feed you call 800 409 5633 or eat foods direct.com forward
slash Alex would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late or
09 5633 or eat foods direct.com forward slash Alex hi there my name is Frank
Bates what I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of
trouble I just created a free video presentation at one two three cover-up
calm that exposes the electricity monopolies and government agencies for
what they really are incompetent line crooks that are counting on your
ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high some have called
us a conspiracy others have called it a cover-up and you will be shocked to find
out how deep the conspiracy goes my video at one two three cover-up calm
exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them and how you
can beat them to watch the controversial video the thousands of other smart
Patriots have already seen in the last three months go to one two three cover
up calm and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect your
home go watch my video now at one two three cover-up calm before they force me
to shut it down again that's one two three cover-up calm making the right
decisions is a challenge to investors are we going to see economic growth slide
into a recession or at worst depression hi Ted Anderson from itis resources we
all know when a company acts irresponsibly divesting ourselves in a
move towards safety is prudent when the market becomes volatile US Treasures are
a safe haven but what do you do when the US government overextends itself and
spends beyond its means many investors are turning toward gold as a common
sense alternative to traditional paper investments Midas resources has put
together a powerful book titled 10 reasons to own gold discussing costs
benefits risks featuring full-color illustrations weights and measures the
book is free and can be yours by calling 800 686 2237 paper investments are
dwarfed by gold 6,000 year history discover how gold may be right for you
and your IRA by calling 800 686 2237 whether buying or it's time for you to
sell the book is free call 800 686 2237 hello this is Ty Bollinger author of the
best-selling book cancer step outside the box I want you to know some very
important information in 1985 president Ronald Reagan requested that carnivora
be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the president could
obtain this world-class healer now 27 years later carnivore capsules are used
around the world to keep people healthy now you can protect yourself and your
loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that
instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single normal
cell if you want to stay healthy now's your chance to literally wake up your
critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body
call one eight six six Venus fly or order from carnivore calm that's car ni
vo ra calm that's one eight six six eight three six eight seven three five
one eight six six Venus fly or visit carnivore calm protect your immune
system it's the only one you've got
the globalist took America over a long time ago financially they used our power
our wealth to take over the planet now they want to take us individually down
you know I I have a video and audio up at info wars calm North Carolina police
listen it warns of plans to set up martial law in 2013 that's coming up the
next segment it's our own pastor butch paw of GCN live calm so we're going to
add that to the alt market article that I I didn't find you think they want to
put in the piece they did that it's a syndicated radio host and butch has
broken so many big stories he broke the clergy response team and then we really
broke it big with the pastors and the pastors even got FEMA visits and then
later the media the government declassified their training pastors to
tell people to submit to tyranny but I want to get butch on today or tomorrow
to pop in he had been on a while he's on eight o'clock central on GCN live calm
and syndicated around the country he's a pastor he'll call himself West
Virginia hillbilly but I call him a red-blooded great guy and he he
interviewed this guy and it's it's chilling it's real and what the guy says
is actually in the news in pieces see it isn't just police calling in with this
and then oh well they said they were a cop I already know all this it's just
good for you to hear it now they're telling these police they're gonna drop
the hammer in the next month well they said that back during the election
they're just it's a psychological tactic where they keep saying there's gonna be
martial law or even if you're against martial law it's kind of like when I was
growing up I say I've been in 200 fights of a hundred plus of them were you know
six seventh eighth grade where I got beat up by bullies you know a couple
times a week that's how I got tough so a lot of more like really hardcore serious
fights but you know teeth loose black eyes stuff like that and I just remember
by the time I was in about seventh grade and been in about you know 50 60 fights
some big bully who'd flunked three grades said I'm gonna be meeting you
outside after school you know I wouldn't try to walk around and in the woods and
and you know get home or pick up a bus down the street I'd go right out run
right up and punch him right in the nose and see it's the same tactic martial law
martial law martial law you you know they're gonna attack Iran they're gonna
attack Iraq they're gonna attack Syria you kind of just get to where you're
like well come on and get it done then so it becomes a self-fulfilling prophecy
I'm gonna go to Eli in Missouri who's a police officer we're finishing up Gordon
Indiana anything else you wanted to add about the police and private citizens
you talked to a lot of Obama supporters said all Alex I'm gonna vote for Obama
he won't come after my guns and I said look it's not that Obama's any bad or
good compared to Romney it's that he's who they want and I said Romney was for
banning guns to go ahead yeah actually I didn't vote for Obama I wanted Ron Paul
and a lot of the officers we have on the department who are you know part
military and then you know they go between the military and a police
department they wanted Ron Paul but uh is this a big wake-up call for people
now that it's just openly we're gonna take the guns you know a lot of them I
actually don't know until I speak to speak with him myself you know they
they're not you know they that's another thing this is hardly getting the news
it's getting one tenth the news it deserves it's hardly even conservatives
don't even know exactly I I found it interesting that I'm our lustrous mayor
just recently uh called up for the state police help from the government to
governor to get the state police and the National Guard to come here in the city
to help patrol the city and I found it odd because it's it we're not really
that bad oh yeah all over the country they're saying all the armies here to
help where are you in Indianapolis where are you in Indiana our Gary and now they
want troops and Gary unbelievable god bless you sir I'm sorry go ahead and
now after the Obama thing announcement after the tragedy in a sandy sandy hook
after Obama announcement about the gun now it then it became clear well you
know this because like I said the city isn't that bad off I mean it's bad but
it's not that bad no no that's what listen there are articles all over the
news going oh it's great to have the National Guard on the streets they're
helping sweep for guns and cars no it's great to have the troops on the streets
they're just slowly getting us ready rolling it out god bless you I
appreciate your call stay in touch let's go to Eli I want to hold him over police
officer in Missouri what is your take on all this well I have a couple ideas
about how it's going to be implemented but first I wanted to tell you something
that I haven't heard covered very much other than you you've touched on the
fact that there's ATF rules are not laws but just rules that are asking gunshots
to do certain things for them and one of them that I've personally experienced is
that they instruct the gunshots to send an email to police departments every
time a purchase is made where there are multiple guns purchased so almost daily
especially lately I receive an email every time someone was in the
jurisdiction where I work purchase and then that's going into your threat
fusion Center for the NSA but they use you as the cover stay there I want to
think I knew this was going on stay right there I'm gonna come right back to
you Eli we're on the march the Empire's on the run Alex Jones and the GCN radio
network we have witnessed two terrible storms in the east but we are still in
the eye of the perfect storm the most devastating economic conditions since
the Great Depression America's worst drought in agricultural history and now
the economic results of the presidential election this perfect storm is a huge
threat to everyone's food supply I just doubled down and got even more supplies
from eat foods direct and I recommend you do the same it's time to get your
own supply for me foods direct I know I won't be standing in a bread line
trading my freedom for food I'm taking control of my future and you're nuts if
you don't do the same go to eat foods direct calm forward slash Alex to find
the specials and you can start with a holiday gift pack that's normally $80
now under 50 bucks remember I can warn you but I can't feed you call eight
hundred four oh nine five six three three or eat foods direct calm forward
slash Alex would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late or
oh nine five six three three or eat foods direct calm forward slash Alex
tyranny is here the grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality it really
says that the state is God the United States is now recognized globally as one
of the most oppressive police states on earth this film conclusively proves the
existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being expanded nationwide this
documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an
all-powerful shadow state police state for chronicles the sickening depth to
which our Republic has fallen prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency
dictatorship body scammers sound cameras citizen spies and stage terror and
cameras on every street corner it's only the beginning of the New World Order's
hellish plan the police state isn't coming it's here secure your copy today
info wars calm or see it online in the highest quality at prison planet TV sick
of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and
laughing as you get sick and die start purifying your water with pro pure my
friends I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar
none is pro pure and it's available discounted at info wars calm its
filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth there's no
priming required it's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce
fluoride up to 95% easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity purify
water from lakes streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial
minerals which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that
leaches from the plastic probe here is the best gravity-fed filter out there
it's what my family uses info wars calm already has the lowest price on prop here
but if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10% off
and in full wars calm you can also call to order 8 8 8 2 5 3 3 1 3 9
you walk into this room at your own risk because it leads to the future not a
future that will be but one that might be this is not a new world it is simply
an extension of what began in the old one it is patterned itself after every
dictator who has ever planted the ripping imprint of a boot on the pages
of history since the beginning of time it has refinements technological advances
and a more sophisticated approach to the destruction of human freedom but like
every one of the super states that preceded it it has one iron rule logic
is an enemy and truth is a menace
the answer to 1984 is 1776 right you're listening to the Alex Jones show the
answer to 1984 1776 a pastor Butch Paul Genesis syndicated talk show host pastor
will be joining us here in about 10 minutes we're able to get him lined up
on the ISDN line we're connecting right now and again I saw this story and info
wars calm from alt market North Carolina police lieutenant warns the plans for
martial law I was like I wonder what show that was and I went and looked and
it's pastor Bush and you'd think we need it so we so we've added it to the report
and info wars calm curtain mo is adding it right now it's important to add so
people know where a report came from I see that more and more where the
internet grabs stuff and then doesn't vet it well I can vet pastor butch Paul
and what he's saying is it's all actually in the news they're training
for martial law and gun confiscation and now they're saying and you're like well
that's crazy that'll cause a revolution that's what Homeland Security and all
the spying and all the SWAT teams are for the globalists are gonna bring us
into total depression they can't have you armed they want you to be at the
mercy of the rioting hordes and everything this this is a giant
re-education takeover of America now a gun shop here in Austin over a year and
a half ago gave me ATF letters and they're so intimidated by ATF they said
don't tell anybody this that you know that it came from us because the ATF
swagger Zen threatens people it's like a movie you know when the Mafia comes in
the store I mean they they tell you listen Mac you do we say or you're gonna
be and that in four states but now it's nationwide it was a test outside of law
it's a rule it's total criminality the same folks that did Fast and Furious
the criminals on average some of the good ATF people are the ones that first
blew the whistle they go into shops everywhere now and they say you're going
to send an email to the Threat Fusion Center so I would guess our caller from
Missouri's a detective because those computer files are assigned to the local
regional MJTF Threat Fusion Center that are really illegal CIA NSA bases and by
the way that's now admitted that they're CIA NSA and so they just use you as
their cannon fodder and can tell people oh the local terrorism number is the
local police but then that's all filed into their larger system and see that
way when the globalists are planning a terror attack or something they also
know if local police have gotten on to it see because all the online police if
you're tracking real terrorism and you're filing it with the feds you
that's how you end up getting shot by a quote crack dealer when you're going out
to your car see if they're already gonna run a terror operation a false flag and
you were already on it you're dead
and that's why you always see cops die around a terror attack a few days before
because they'll kill whoever knows about it much I mean dozens got killed before
9-11 FBI agents the FBI deputy director head of counterterrorism O'Neill I mean
they will kill you before they do it so they're also watching to see what the
citizens notice that's one of the biggest NSA functions I can I revealed
this about five years ago with my NSA sources well one of them of course is
former NSA with his sources Wayne Madsen who had to leave the country for a while
because of death threats he was at the NSA that the main NSA thing is not just
stealing patents and watching people and spying on political opposition you know
it's like Nixon don't to the power of infinity but that what they're really
doing is they're watching the local police departments because local police
departments will find out about drug shipments if they're not corrupt they've
got to be called off that case you know if it's a federal shipment of drugs most
of it is federal right to the big banks that run the country and longer the
money publicly our military grows the opium on video publicly so they couldn't
hide it so they said okay we grow the opium move along they ship the drugs in
move along they launder the drug money move along they own the private prisons
owned by the big banks that run the drugs the drug dealers own the the
prisons see the real business isn't just the drugs it's slaves in the prisons
working for 25 cents an hour but I'm ranting and of course a lot of them
deserve to be in prison they're unsavory horrible people the point is is they're
unsavory and horrible a lot of them because since they were 12 years old
they were forced into that culture but sad issue the point is is that see
that's the problem with my broadcast he brings something up as well you're the
only person I've heard touch on this we wrote articles about it but yes then I
give you the rest of the story and I can go on for three hours just on this alone
okay and it's all totally illegal so I'm gonna shut up for two minutes to know
you're a busy man and we got pastor butch coming on here in a moment but we're
gonna air that police lieutenant clip first but start at the beginning with
now gun owners all over the country are having basically a criminal file opened
on them that'll be used for the later confiscation later or to see if they you
know sold the gun to their brother or gave it to their grandson because in the
future it's going to be a felony if you give your grandson retroactively a
firearm that's all been announced go ahead well you're exactly right it comes
in an email form at least when I receive it and sometimes it's so ridiculous
because you'll see you know we don't live in a you know hugely populated
area it'll be someone you know and you laugh up there buying more guns but it
has a person's address it has any prior contact they've had with police then we
receive that and some of us objected to it and the only reason I even read them
is just out of curiosity and out of just so I'll be informed but it's a
surveillance file being opened on someone who is not under the suspicion
of a crime it is pre-crime it is North Korea go ahead absolutely and then the
other thing I wanted to touch on the huge purchase by Homeland Security and
other federal agencies of ammunition had a lot to do with the fact that they knew
this was coming because when you brought it up before they said well here in a
little while you know when they're going to be able to purchase ammo and that
does include police agencies they can't buy ammo just like people can't right
now because there's such a shortage and you know why there's a shortage it's not
really the gun that the ammo buying the military doesn't sell the brass anymore
and because of all the federal purchases the police can't get it either this is
the feds buying it all up because my Intel is it's way more than 1.6 billion
rounds go ahead well and it's true and it's kind of sad because at the low
levels the local police departments that that may actually you know need that for
range training another thing they have very few rounds on hand it's a joke how
little your local police department has they have what's on their officers duty
belts and a few boxes per officer in a locker somewhere and that's it no
whenever I'm at gun shops I see police they're off-duty who come over and tell
me their police and a lot of show me their badge and say I'm here having to
buy ammo to go to the shooting range myself because they won't even give them
the ammo now it's true I mean most most agencies won't give you any to practice
with they won't do some agencies you even have to buy your own duty ammo but
I want to talk about if we have any time about how I envisioned the actual
confiscation to take place they're smart enough to know that there's a system in
place that will allow this to happen without some sort of grandstanding and
going door-to-door just like in any other criminal case if you if there's
probable cause that you have done something they'll just issue a warrant
for you so so you get stopped you have a rifle that supposedly needs to be
grandfathered under the new bill and it's checked for whatever reason by a
police officer they will leave that as probable cause to search your house so
you get arrested on a warrant you'll go to jail at a place where no one sees it
it looks like you're any other common criminal that has warrants for for
whatever reason there's no one to feel sorry for you and no one to take your
side so you just disappeared and they go to your house when you're at home and
take your guns no no that's it I don't know if you've been listening but no
that's exactly how they plan to do it and what they're training the military
for is they're gonna shut up gang checkpoints not sobriety checkpoints
it's already started all over the country and in federal test grounds it's
federal grants quietly for illegal gang checkpoints and they shut up they'll
even have a truck with a heavy gun in the back I actually have the news here
gang checkpoints popping up in Texas and that is out of a WO AI TV and radio out
of San Antonio and what they do is they they just get the police used to it
where they run a gang background they take photos of tattoos they get you out
they search your car totally unconstitutional it's training you for
it and then in the future it's just like the
void cards in Illinois your things out a week they pull you over they go hey
you're Floyd's out you still got guns yeah boom you're going to jail and
exactly they're just gonna pick us up that way you're gonna be pulled over
you're gonna drive into a checkpoint and they'll go we have a record here than a
1989 because they digitized all those records that's going on now you bought a
semi-automatic Remington such-and-such oh yeah oh you admit to it BAM felony
you're gone you're and they're getting money in the new federal law for
expanded federal courts for gun owners more prisons oh yeah they're gonna look
Homeland Security the FEMA camps is for gun owners you can curb that analysis I
agree completely and I also believe that there will be a buyback program that is
put in place it's extremely lucrative money-wise they're probably going to pay
more money than you could get in the market value for guns and they're
probably going to be scaled per how effective they are for self-defense so
the so-called assault rifles you may be able to get $2,000 and so as things get
worse and people are hungry they'll get a lot of guns that way because people
think I my bills are due I can go get two grand right now for this gun and
people will do it I agree let me just stop you that's always been the plan and
I got to go to Pastor Butch and a clip from his radio show a few nights ago but
before we do that just briefly are the other officers around you starting to
get what's happening yes I work in a good department above average in that
regard we just elected a new sheriff in our county who is better than average
perfect but I live I'm fortunate that I live and work in a place that is better
than most but you know everybody should be freaking out right now because it's
not just gonna be take the guns this signifies total hammer drop the end of
America folks they plan a massive re-education takeover god bless you
we're gonna keep pastor Butch about 10 minutes in the next hour and then get
Bob Fletcher on this is breaking but I've got Fletcher coming on because he
was an Iran contra whistleblower and congressional fraud investigator and he
has seen the inside of the CIA assassinations black ops you name it
he's been warning about this for 20 years but I want to play a clip from
pastor butches show the full audio is up at info wars calm because people were
asking you know is this report accurate I went well yeah but we need to tell
people who it is it's pastor butch so that's now been added at info wars calm
but one of his sources a lieutenant McCoy and it was butch that broke the
clergy response team I don't know six seven years ago people couldn't believe
it at the time it was later declassified preachers are being paid to spy on you
and to teach to turn your guns in when they're given the order now it's over a
hundred thousand preachers so we're gonna get butch and and and his info
briefly here I'm probably having back on tomorrow so but but let's go to a clip
from the lieutenant McCoy out of North Carolina totally freaked out because he
says they're telling him it's about to happen in the next few weeks here it is
what are you hearing from from your superiors and what's coming down and
what you're looking forward well they're they're looking they're looking for it
to happen and they're trying to pour it to happen now you said the train and
training to take us down and training to depend sir training training to take us
down and law enforcement in appeared North Carolina has started training
with drones a military-operated drones Wow okay that they started they started
trained with military drones in North Carolina yes sir that's correct by the
way this is all confirmed already several appears are training the forces
to take down the American people yes sir how the forces bothering them well one
of the main things that and with the breaking news that the ATF and the US
Marshals Service is recruiting from law enforcement agencies here in North
Carolina they are yes and what they're planning on doing is they'll get the
local officers in with the ATF and US Marshals Service now they'll be the
payroll will come from the state but the equipment will be issued by the federal
government all except for the vehicle and that would be a totally unmarked
cruiser that'll be issued to them Wow okay in the timeline what do you expect
to happen there the train is gonna start within the next week with the officers
that volunteer to do this and mostly the ones is volunteer or mostly the
droids heads that's what we call them anyhow exactly the ones who are going
home to anything I told to do yes sir and they all pumped up they taken stuff
to build her muscles artificially and it's just unreal I've been in law
enforcement 31 years here and I've never seen anything like it in my life
what do you sense yourself I'm sorry sir so what do you see it's happening
yourself what do you what do you see and so what your time on you scenes well I'm
I figure it's gonna take them about 30 to 45 days to get everything in line
you know we have a our governor here in North Carolina is one of the governors
picked by President Obama to take control under a martial law program Wow
and your personal opinion lieutenant what are you gonna do I'm going home
you going home could take to protect your family yes sir that's what the Lord
wants me to do and that's what he says to do and that's what I intend to do but
you expect some kind of movement in within the next two or three months yes
sir I do as far as I think they'll start to move and they'll start picking out
certain people and making conversation conversations and arrests and you can do
that house-to-house along the road block roadblocks or what it'll be it'll be
wherever they can catch the certain individuals there yeah that's right
catch them at home where they can take their preparedness away from them and do
you have any name you've been given to you yet no sir okay did you think the
higher-ups know who's gonna be yet I think they do yes sir interesting well
attendant if you defense the last time you speak to the public what would you
tell them trust the Lord and be prepared have you been yourself and your family
you tell them to sign about an ar-15 home defense I would say it is and if
you can find one yes exactly that's enough full audio is up at infowars.com
and then we'll also give you pastor Butch's site I'm gonna skip this network
right you know here's the thing folks they plan on this starting a fight okay
I want to explain to the police and military something
I am NOT going to turn my legally bought guns in just because of globalist
criminal mafia Don says I have to but I also want it clear I because I'm an
information person I am here to be sacrificed I am NOT because if they come
to my house and kill me I didn't resist I'm just not turning them in they can
I'm gonna go right to court be a national court case whatever the problem
is they'll probably just kill me and they're gonna sip in special units in to
just kill gun owners and they're gonna call us terrorists and then the foolish
roid head you heard him call them roid head and droid head they're robots they
get killed will be used as martyrs on the news and this is how America falls
and Obama will be called the new Lincoln they've mainly got southern
governors on the special ten governor council to sell everybody out to say oh
look there's governors on the federal council as if that Trump's the other 40
governors it and they're gonna take everything they're gonna take your bank
accounts your pension funds everything they've got force compulsory national
service and communist brigades already set up on a manual set that up I can
play him saying it if you want me to this is how tyranny happens and they
they don't even care if you do if you did all turn your guns and they still
come to your house and kill you and drop guns there they've got special units
that literally hate the American people and want this war now a lot of the
police are good people especially Christians like you just heard that man
and you heard him he's gonna go home and defend his family you know what that
means once we see him killing people in the streets and everything people aren't
gonna wait in their houses and all police that aren't part of this are
gonna have to basically stand down they get out of that uniform real fast
because see you're in Sauron's uniform now you're in the foreign banks uniform
you're in Avicii French collaborator uniform and I just can't my guts I've
told you this for months that I've just I just know it's all coming I mean I know
I don't need to even look at all this I know my discernment is just just I mean
I've got my self in order with God I'll tell you that right now I've made my
peace with God let's go to Pastor Butch paw pastor I tell you this is so
disgusting and it tears my guts out that we're gonna watch the total fall of
America right now but I guess in a way we deserve it the 53 million abortions
and everything else how bad is it gonna get pastor from all your other sources
and lieutenant McCoy well it's thanks have you on day I appreciate it and the
clip you just played he almost got to the point where he asked him how they're
gonna bring it down he said probably through an economic collapse and we're
watching news the news talking about the fiscal cliff and all the things and
not the Senate and Congress is avoided and it's all a show we know it's a show
and this gentleman along with two other sources I have two of my local service
out of Michigan have confirmed everything he's told me and I'm sure a
lot more that they're going economic collapse country probably first to call
strain on that before they move in on people like maybe you and I but tonight
on my program I'm gonna have the lieutenant McCoy on for a full hour to
discuss this in much more detail and I would like to invite you and he on my
show tomorrow can we do that I have to ask him I don't know that I swore
secrets to him who he is waste from except for the state of North Carolina
but I know I know but every time you've had these sources and confirm them it
always later comes out as accurate but but but sure and we'll obviously play
some excerpts tomorrow from you tonight eight o'clock central but yeah talk to
him see if he wants to come on I will do that Alex and you know you and I have
this coming March make me 20 years on the radio and you've been on a long time
to 17 17 and we're not prophets that I won't be people understand this we're
not prophets I'm a Bible believe in I guess you can call me a Bible thumper I
believe the Word of God's the Word of God pain no compromises no no exceptions
but we're not prophets I just take the scriptures I take history and current
events and I can tell you where we are in time and what we're saying we've been
saying that for years it's coming to pass we're not prophets but we're not
fools either we can see what's coming we're trying to warn the people they're
starting to listen a little more than it used to before even people out here that
for years thought I was crazy or something realize hey he's telling the
truth all along and it just breaks my heart we can't reach everyone but they're
one to fight now Alex that's what they're wanting they're pushing for a
fight and they're gonna get one and I know that's the thing I hope all the
all these Royd heads understand you're gonna get a fight yes you are and the
globalist don't care the plan is to wipe all you idiots out but I'll tell you
these Royd heads is just too stupid man I'm telling you I mean they just they
are I've seen one wearing a shirt today and look down here in Summersville next
where I live in West Virginia wearing a shirt that something but don't f with
the cops we're more of a man than you are something like that and I just I
just looked at this cringe you know a few years ago he would been fired for
wearing a shirt like that it wouldn't it wouldn't have been a question but now
this there's no no I want goons they don't want strong smart good man they
want a bunch of crazy goons follow orders unquestionably that lieutenant
McCoy spoke with him a phone a little more in length yesterday before we
scheduled a program tonight and he is very concerned more so than to mention
on my radio show tonight I get more detail but he's very concerned he knows
it's imminent according to him and other sources two to three months is a good
shot of being a possibility this all come together now maybe they're all few
months I don't know we're not gonna put dates on this well if we get the word
out they'll pull back but but but yes right now they're going to DEFCON one so
this is this is imminent we're not talking folks by something 20 years from
now or five years from now this is imminent what is five three months six
months or a year this is coming right now look at the timeline they're getting
ready to pass a physical gun turn in and they're gonna say turn them in and
they're gonna start SWAT teaming and killing people that don't as a way to
try to terrify us and that's not gonna happen people are gonna go out and
engage them and then it's gonna be all the gun owners are terrorists which the
manuals already say a self-fulfilling prophecy well you know Eric Holder back
in 95 said that we have to change their minds brainwash people to believe that
to think different loans that's quote yes and and he did convince me of
something I never bought a gun in my life considered a weapon I own guns I
own several guns I always buy them for fun target practice or hunting I never
bought a gun for a weapon per se but I'm there about a baseball bat for a weapon
either either can be used for weapon but I have considered about guns as weapons
now I didn't do it Eric Holder you were it worked on me you convinced me my guns
are gonna be weapons I didn't buy them for that reason no more no more than
about a baseball bat for that reason but you attacked me I'll defend myself my
family by any means necessary with all the force I have now I'm a pastor I'm a
Christian I don't want to do this I'm begging you folks leave us alone we're
begging you don't tread on us we're not willing to fight but we will by God
stand and fight yeah it's they really want to start a civil war and I'm telling
you the veterans out there are just gonna wipe out the police I mean they're
gonna be wiped out and that is the plan that is the plan to then bring in foreign
troops I mean I mean the police will be wiped out I mean I hope they understand
that I just cannot believe we've got to this point and at first they're gonna go
out and blow up houses and go after cult members and demonize this is not gonna
work and then people are gonna go on the offense defensively pastor and just
cannot believe it and I don't worry the White House will stage some more
shootings I can tell you that so they can go out and fake cry and say well
they told us gun owners you killed the kids you're terrorists we'll be right
back stay there you are listening to GCN visit GCN live
calm today if you want an American company with American products made by
Americans here is the cow bed soap company Alex and his staff have used
these pure soap products for years these all-natural soaps are made from the
highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and safe
see them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free
catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice
as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of
soaps or all your cleaning needs this is an amazing deal you can save thousands
of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel see them on the
web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog
you waging war on corruption Alex Jones on the GCM radio network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
we're gonna get pastor butch and lieutenant McCoy on either tomorrow or
Friday we're lining that up right now and eight o'clock tonight central GCN
live calm nine o'clock Eastern local am an FM certain in some areas of the
country shortwave as well call what's the best website for people pastor
butch called a decision well then go to pastor butch calm to look the stations
were listed on that we are all the country different doll the country in
different stations they can also listen a short way the frequencies are on there
also in pastor Bush calm they won't listen on net the best I go to probably
GCN live calm click on night nine o'clock Eastern listen the program
tonight this probably the most listened to show I've had in a long time and
definitely most important one I've had as pertaining to this police state
situation and what's coming down sure let's get him on again also for our full
audience will obviously play some clips tomorrow but everybody should tune in I
want to crash the Genesis servers but the point is that I mean I don't know if
you have a chance to hear my show I used to be able to listen to yours a lot more
but but I miss it quite a bit but I mean did you hear me two three months ago say
I've never felt like this in my spirit and now we see it all unfolding yes yes
I have nice said the same thing about same time to the power six months ago
there's something coming my gut says it of course we know it's your spirit but
in your gut it's like a dread it's like you're expecting to be mortared or
rocketed like it was an army you're expecting it it's gonna happen you're
just waiting you almost wish to get dope yeah was your spirit ever wrong was your
gut ever wrong when you were in covert operations in Cambodia not very often
though no not very often I've learned I've learned to trust my spirit on that
especially since my Christian and the Holy Spirit does tell me things not very
often though well it just meant the guy aiming a gun at you quit aiming it at
you know when that when the when the bad thing didn't happen exactly that's what
you know that you see you may say a minute ago that's really important if
we get this news out we may delay this for a few months but Alice is going to
come you mean you remember of course William Cooper when Cooper wrote a book
entitled behold a pale horse and in that book he said and he gave the name of the
CIA operation that was gonna do this that would cause shooting and mass
killings in schools that's in his book in 1991 so my website pastor much calm
read it for yourself it's on there this was predicted 13 years ago 12 years ago
no longer than that my goodness has been 21 year yeah 21 years ago so this is
absolutely phenomenal again he wasn't a prophet but he knew I was coming down of
course he was killed for it but he spoke the truth put it in his book and now
we're seeing it happen and most people don't even know what was in the book
because in the most I never read it if they did they forgot about it but then
read it they can see the actual page on my website well I mean I've got other
police calling in with the same info and a lot of it's in the news it's in the
army manuals they're training for gun confiscation it's in the news they're
deputizing local police's ATF it's in the news they bought 1.6 billion bullets
are deploying heavy armored vehicles every town and city they're gearing up
for total war against us in an orchestrated collapse when we're gonna
need guns they're in that collapse they want us totally dependent and I I just
you can look at I know they're gonna stage some more school shootings pastor
well I had two other sheriffs in Michigan a confirm what this gentleman
said plus a state senator confirm the same thing this is that this is a plan
they're all been told the same scenario is coming down
no number for it they're like the lieutenant they will leave and do what
they have to defend themselves but they know it's coming down there they're on
the inside trying to warn us and I thank God for these men and women who have the
courage speak out in time to kiss this this not only can mean their job this
can mean their lives this could be if they this is there's no future for him
anyways there isn't there he's got to put it all on the line now that's what
I'm doing that's what you're doing and and make no mistake he said they're
gonna take out the resistance leaders first yeah in every case they're coming
right for us buddy well you and I both know that we've known this for years it
will be the first taken out that's fine with me if I gotta go the first wave is
fine I don't mind going out then it's in somebody else's hands but we have been
sacrifice yourself so to speak on the air now for a long time warn the people
that we've been scoffed at left at and locked in ridicule but we're still here
and we'll stand to the end all right I'll be listening tonight and get him on
tomorrow or Friday God bless you and we're gonna be staying in contact with
you with my producers to nail this down and make sure this happens so twist his
arm I want to get him on this show okay I'll do my best all right thank you we
got Bob Fletcher coming up to give us his take on this and a lot more and
we're gonna open the phones up for police that want to specifically talk
about this giant ATF gear up millions of people are going to get sick this winter
from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with
supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution
recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that
can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help
improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every
day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as
stress staff pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new
technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at
several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions
the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook we have witnessed two
terrible storms in the east but we are still in the eye of the perfect storm
the most devastating economic condition since the Great Depression America's
worst drought in agricultural history and now the economic results of the
presidential election this perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food
supply I just doubled down and got even more supplies from eat foods direct and
I recommend you do the same it's time to get your own supply from eat foods
direct I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food
I'm taking control of my future and you're nuts if you don't do the same go
to eat foods direct calm forward slash Alex to find the specials and you can
start with a holiday gift pack that's normally $80 now under 50 bucks
remember I can warn you but I can't feed you call 800 409 5633 or eat foods
direct calm forward slash Alex would you rather prepare six months too early or
one day too late or oh nine five six three three or eat foods direct calm
forward slash Alex if you want an American company with American products
made by Americans here is the cow bend soap company Alex and his staff have
used these pure soap products for years these all-natural soaps are made from
the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and
safe see them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for a
free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are
twice as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year
supply of soaps or all your cleaning needs this is an amazing deal you can
save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
see them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free
catalog we now take you live to the Central Texas command center in the
heart of the resistance you're listening to the Alex Jones show
Homeland Security is the foreign banking mercenary army of the six mega banks
that run the narcotics the white slavery world prostitution the drug companies
you name it they are publicly involved in insider trading with Congress they
are publicly involved in a trillion plus dollars a year in narcotics trafficking
500 billion of that in the biggest market in the world the United States
you just look up 376 billion laundered by Wells Fargo and Wachovia they didn't
get in trouble this is a mafia and they want to take the pension funds
everything the end of your standard of living they've stated it but they want
to pose saviors as they destroy you so they're gonna go for the guns they're
telling the Catholic and Baptist churches now you will pay for morning
after an abortion pills Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment
of religion or prohibiting the free exercise thereof they're announcing that
they've got the votes the Republicans are gonna go along with totally open
borders and legalizing 30 million illegal aliens and putting them all on
welfare to bankrupt things further they are announcing that they have changed
the rules the laws to take the pension funds it's all gonna happen now this is
it it's all going to happen and you know I've never got up on air and said that
okay I've said there's a danger of this a danger of that it's because we've been
winning the gun culture has been taking over abortions now unpopular in polls
people are cutting back on abortions they know we're winning so they come out
put Obama back in run a political corpse against him and then say it's a mandate
for tyranny this is their attempt to act confident and do all this and then try
to cause a civil war so Obama can play the part of Lincoln they know it's gonna
be a storm they know it's gonna be a giant shooting war they're ready they're
dug in that's why they've hardened all the police departments police out there
you're smart enough to see all the preparations that are bigger than Obama
this is a long-term program Obama is just the front man for this and now
they're admitting it Illinois's introduced bills with their head head
leader there to openly ban the guns to make you turn in all the newly
manufactured firearms that's up at infowars.com banning shooting ranges
cop-site gangs the justification for unconstitutional checkpoints where
they're pulling a lot of their cars and photographing us all over the country
but centered in Texas Illinois's moves to outlaw modern firearms and
criminalized owners Obama would call on military to disarm Americans during
national emergency and we just talked and played a police lieutenant with GCN
host pastor Butch Paul who has he makes them give him driver's license and stuff
there's a lot of times I end up getting guessed on that he gets because he he
gets these sources and he gets proof of who they are he did that with the
clergy response team seven eight years ago I don't know like it was like seven
years ago two years before he moves us but seven years ago he got the guy's
names I got their names after got him on the show they were training preachers
for during martial law to tell folks to submit now I can play newscast saying
that the during martial law preachers will help tell the public to turn their
guns in just type in clergy response team into YouTube you'll see the
newscast that was like five years after he broke it and he has a police
lieutenant freaked out enough to come on and even use this last name on air from
North Carolina and say in the next week they start the training with the ATF to
federalize the local police we're gonna have checkpoints and arrest everybody
that doesn't turn their guns in now part of that's a shy op to see what police
say no so they can create their criminal brigades of guys that'll say yes and
it's part of scaring all of us look I'm not turning my legal guns and I've never
committed a crime with them I'm not gonna live like places where they've
taken all the guns everybody lives in fear and families get raped and killed
and they only use gun laws against law-abiding citizens in England if
somebody defends themselves with their fists they throw the book at them I know
your criminals I know who you are I'm a talk show host and I'm not turning crud
in okay you got that you got to draw your line in the sand
like Colonel Travis or everything's gone okay all you talkers that say I can't
wait to see a blue helmet all you talkers want a Bob Fletcher here in a
moment all you talkers hell I'm gonna cold dead hand it isn't gonna be the UN
coming it's gonna be your local cops specially picked because they're
steroid heads who I mean I've seen these guys they should be bouncers or
something and even bad bouncers at that they're bugging their eyes out when you
walk by I'm tough you're not I mean my whole instinct says you think you are
you're a piece of trash criminal you're a thug you do good in North Korea
they're goons hundred years ago they'd be in the mafia as a low-level enforcer
there are people that get off on scaring people you don't scare me you don't
scare me you understand that and I'm putting the call out worldwide for
people to get ready all of us are Paul Revere's against your tyranny and they're
gonna smash us up front if they pull this they're gonna kill a bunch of us
they're gonna drag us around they're gonna say we're terrorists on the niche
and then the Civil War starts and I don't want this to happen
I don't want this to happen okay believe me I'm a successful syndicated radio
talk show host who's been in big Hollywood movies and you know gotten to
meet some of the most famous people in the world and have three great children
and a wonderful wife and I'm 38 and got my whole life ahead of me but I know
there's no future if we don't beat these people do you I mean can you get that
through your head and I'm and I've never turned tail and run there's nowhere to
run you know they say there's fight or flight
I fight okay I fight I'm gonna fight and I'm fighting with the info war right now
these are murdering criminals the evidence is they staged Sandy Hook I
want to go to Bob Fletcher I appreciate him coming on today we had a lot of
breaking news I wanted to get him on because he was a congressional
whistleblower an advisor and you know on TV and things during the Iran-Contra
affair he owned a big successful importation export business with toys
and the CIA came without him knowing and said hey let's do business together and
it turned out it was all of operation with generals coming to his toy factory
and using it as a front and and and narcotics trafficking and all the rest
of it he refused to be part of it they tried to destroy they also tried to
assassinate him I mean it's just amazing and he's businessman investigator film
producer speaker and author Bob Fletcher investigations calm and Bob they've been
planning this for a long time it backed off because we were winning because
people are waking up they had Brzezinski admits they're seven to twelve years
behind and putting on which actuary now they're saying because they're in so
much trouble they're gonna try to accelerate the whole program and they've
decided that a civil war will be what brings them into full power that's that's
not my what I'm saying they're now saying he is Lincoln there will be a
civil war he is our God he will crush the states I saw that four years ago
with him saying he was Lincoln I said I think that's what's gonna happen and
that is what's happened now hopefully cooler minds will prevail and they won't
try this but Bob what is your take on everything that's unfolding right now
well first off some miscellaneous random notes that I made for myself for this
morning's program just hit right right on the head exactly what you've been
saying I mean it looks like you've been looking at my nose it's kind of like
well I don't have to do anything cuz cuz Alec has already covered it I mean
verbatim almost word-to-word you you I'm gonna I'm making this assumption you
realize that I myself was one of the primary people in creating what was the
malicious you are the guy and not certainly not taking all the credit
because there's a lot of people involved people need to know that you know what
you're talking about I was doing speaking engagements and what have you
after my crazy situation that you just mentioned being sucked into the middle
of major major governmental corruption you know with illegal arms and drugs
connected to it and all the rest of that stuff which was turned out to be the
Iran contra mess but not just that they were all over the world with the same
people that I was dealing with you know so so what happened was it pro created
itself I ended up being drawn back in over and over and over again every time
for the every like in two years cycles when they had another crazy corrupted
thing up there it was something that crossed my my path so I got dragged back
up into being involved with different senators and congressmen a couple of
them were good and most of them were crooked lying guys but the situation
what had taken place when when we surged with with the and the word militia is
what scared the pudding out of everybody obviously you know that was something
United States never had they never had what appeared to be the word just
constitutes kind of a military connotation so no it had never been used
you know if we call ourselves United Patriots of America we wouldn't have
drawn very much attention but when we started calling it a militia movement a
patriot militia movement you know they went crazy in Washington they we really
scared them to death there for a while and and that was and and that the 10 or
12 years behind in terms of the New World Order's concept and their ideas of
taking our guns and moving into a full one-world government that 10 to 12 years
slow down a lot of that had to do with that militia patriot movement because
they really had to back off because they were openly saying Feinstein was saying
we're gonna take all your guns world government is here we're gonna make you
take shots and all these veterans said we're gonna fight back and they went oh
we're not gonna make you take shots or take your guns you're paranoid so they
went for a while with denying it now they're just trying to force it all
three right now but there's something else it has come up I think and and I
think and it's not you know you're not missing it but a lot of people are kind
of missing it and I don't know that I mentioned it earlier one of my other
appearances with you I'm trying to accomplish and finish up this this last
video I'm putting together which is a presentation that I think sort of and
some of it even gets extremely way kind of out in left field but unfortunately
I'm afraid that it all sort of fits together and but what's going on there's
there's something else out there that has caused the bad guys the New World
Order proponents in all it has caused them to change a lot of directions speed
up some things bypass some other things and then put some of their old concepts
on the shelf and move with this okay I want to break down what you think's
changed in the matrix when we get back with Bob Fleischer weekend by GMO
stressed out about money and blasted by the electric environment hi I'm pastor
Jenny and that was the state I was in back in 2010 then I learned about RNA
drops I learned that 97% of my DNA that scientists have called junk is actually
packed with millions of gene switches that play a critical role in controlling
how my cells organs and other tissues behave I learned I don't have to put up
with disease decay or decline like I'd been conditioned to believe I began
taking RNA drops a 100% natural formula designed to turn on those switches and
provide me with amazing health and joy learn more about RNA drops and order a
free sample today visit RNA free sample calm that's RNA free sample calm or call
toll-free 8 8 8 5 7 7 3 7 0 3 pay only shipping and handling for free 30-day
supply of RNA drops get the information you need and the health you want at RNA
free sample calm hey there Frank Bates here have you heard about the weird
device that could wipe out 280 million Americans this is really scary stuff
defense experts warn that this odd device poses the greatest threat we've
ever known in fact just a few weeks ago former Speaker of the House Newt
Gingrich wrote an op-ed piece for the Washington Post warning about this
deadly threat I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this it may
be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up
that's why my friend just created a free video at weird device calm that exposes
this threat and blows the doors off the conspiracy go watch the shocking video
at weird device calm right now to discover exactly what it is plus
discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack
I'm not sure how long this video be online so go to weird device calm before
it's gone forever again that's weird device calm
hemp usa.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved
detoxification product order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with
vitamins minerals iodine and probiotics and we'll send you our travel size
micro plant powder absolutely free micro plant powder only at hemp usa.org call
9 0 8 6 9 1 2 6 0 8 that's 9 0 8 6 9 1 2 6 0 8 and see what our powder seeds and
oil can do for you only at hemp usa.org only this offer ends January 31st hi
this is Ted Anderson have you ever wondered why banks stock workers
investment advisors won't talk about gold IRAs they've been available since
1986 yet the financial industry won't recognize the value of gold for your
retirement gold is outperformed paper investments yet no word about IRAs if
you would like to have gold for your retirement call 800 6 8 6 2 2 3 7 don't
get left behind by rising inflation and low returns call 800 6 8 6 2 2 3 7 secure
your future and call 1 800 6 8 6 2 2 3 7 hello this is Ty Bollinger author of the
best-selling book cancer step outside the box I want you to know some very
important information in 1985 president Ronald Reagan requested that carnivora
be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the president could
obtain its world-class healer now 27 years later carnivore capsules are used
around the world to keep people healthy now you can protect yourself and your
loved ones in this age of super bugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds
that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell if you want to stay healthy now's your chance to literally wake up
your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in
your body call 1 8 6 6 Venus fly or order from carnivora.com that's car ni
vo ra.com that's 1 8 6 6 8 3 6 8 7 3 5 1 8 6 6 Venus fly or visit carnivora.com
protect your immune system it's the only one you've got
all right ladies and gentlemen let me be real concise about this they're
announcing total open borders the Republicans suddenly say they're all
gonna vote for it they don't care about you anymore because election fraud is
almost total they're announcing that they're just going to massively raise
taxes on 77% of households they have Club of Obama swearing you never do
that it's all about betrayal for every $41 in tax increases there's $1 in cuts
and that's all fake ever this is a program they've done in other countries
now Bob Fletcher we were just talking former congressional whistleblower
insider I ran contra whistleblower who's right in the middle of it that's what
they do when they come recruit people this comes out all the time they just
force businessmen into it or they come and say they're a company suddenly
you're in contracts with them and they go by the way we're firing banks or
we're the CIA and we'll kill you even if you don't do what we say I mean it's
just it's mafia I mean that's all it is is mafia but it's US government national
security and why do they want the guns now you were saying that they're behind
schedule you were concurring that yeah they want to start some kind of crises
but but why now are they just not caring what we think what's the plan
well of course the big problem now is you know that we've we as in everybody
except those of us who are have been in in the front of this thing for so long
you know we've permitted them to do it we've let them get away with it it goes
back and you know unfortunately on my grandfather's shoulders and then on my
father's shoulders and then on my shoulders you know and the the bottom
line is they have successfully gotten away this situation where I mean
anything that they want to do criminally whatever it is whether it's financial or
or something else maybe just political even whatever they decide to do they
just do it which includes killing people that may be gonna come forward and talk
and I'm not gonna get into that but dying core runs child kidnapping
publicly doesn't get in trouble once in the news open insider trading I mean
they are absolute murdering criminals and the way they get away with it if you
can imagine Al Capone if he had the ability to stamp top secret or covert
operations or classified if he had that big rubber stamp that those guys in
Washington have and could just stamp one of his his bank robbery deals and just
say oh you can't interview those people because it is linked to a very important
a government project I'm sorry so then you know put away your lawyers and put
away that you judicial system oh when it came out on the Sandusky thing with the
heads of the university involved they all made them honorary NSA members so
they can't get in trouble no I mean it's unbelievable but so they have
successfully gotten away with that then they as you you mentioned and we all
aware now you know they've been stockpiling bullets I mean they're
buying up bullets and putting in orders for bullets and weapons you know that
would just fill battleships what in the world are miscellaneous bureaucratic
small-level bureaucratic operations doing ordering up ten and a half million
I talked to a police officer where one company of National Guard for Urban
Warfare had three million rounds of bullets there on the small base can you
imagine and so what are we doing about it Chris unfortunately at this point in
time I never thought I was gonna get to the point where I would say this you
know they they got us they got us by the butt they've got a hold of us I mean we
you know I mean I have all the people that were involved originally with the
1990s Patriot movement they so many of them a lot of them have actually been
put in jail as some I think are still in jail random things that they brought in
you know set people up and all that kind of stuff so it's really really reached a
point of it's where it genuinely is going to hit the fan now I don't know I
have a lot of people have a different opinion of this some some folks feel
that it's totally and strictly a financial collapse situation where
they're totally preparing for it to the extent like we know very you know that
upsets me a little bit is a five hundred thousand coffins pre-manufactured
sitting out there in in it outside of Atlanta Georgia I don't know where they
are now they moved them but the the point is when when when the people who
are the theoretical enforcers have gone and ordered five hundred thousand
coffin boxes it by the way could probably handle a two to three or four
people in an emergency situation that should scare the pudding out of the
average American but they seem to not you know nobody's out there I haven't
seen any signs asking by the way we talked about we talked about a purge
during the break because I agree with you I was asking what you think this is
all about you were saying well so it's an excuse to selectively enforce on gun
owners they're gonna make us the new enemy and I concur with you even though
you weren't listening to the show we're gonna come back and talk about that and
then I'm gonna well we'll stay there I got something that's important coming up
we're on the March the Empire's on the run Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and
laughing as you get sick and die start purifying your water with pro pure my
friends I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar
none is pro pure and it's available discounted at info Wars calm its
filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth there's no
priming required it's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce
fluoride up to 95% easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity purify
water from lakes streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial
minerals which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that
leaches from the plastic rope here is the best gravity-fed filter out there
it's what my family uses info wars calm already has the lowest price on propure
but if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10% off
and info wars calm you can also call to order 8 8 8 2 5 3 3 1 3 9 Alex Jones here
with a message to fellow freedom lovers the prognosis for the entire planetary
economic system runs from bad to worse the globalist model is to shut down
societies and starve Patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover
that's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items
at info wars shop calm these are items that I did research on that I personally
use you've got the life straw so you can turn fetid water into safe water
anywhere you go the K tor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment
during power outages are out in the field strategic relocation third edition
by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein thorough safe used by
Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event and crank
shortwave am-fm radios everything that we've researched and found to be the
best is available at info war shop calm and your purchase makes our info war
possible we're getting prepared are you info wars shop calm you prepare by
purchasing gold food and firearms but if you don't have a home security system
then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when
you're sleeping who's watching out for intruders and spooks check out simply
safe it's a new do-it-yourself home security system that is completely
wireless go to get simply safe calm simply safe is independent and off the
grid it runs on battery power so even if the grid goes down you're protected it's
completely customizable so you can use it in your home business boat trailer
storage unit or shed simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in
under 20 minutes so there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you
move or need to relocate you can take this system with you wherever you go
simply safe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days
a week go to get simply safe calm that's get simply safe calm
defending the Republic from enemies foreign and domestic it's Alex Jones
okay I'm gonna open the phones up and probably go into overdrive for police
officers that can confirm what the police officer that pastor butch pause
confirmed his identity in North Carolina said federalizing police for ATF or gun
confiscation training door-to-door highway checkpoints now I have the news
saying we're training the army for that and they're saying they may confiscate
our guns it's official Illinois saying they're gonna ban almost all guns like
Chicago make you turn a man that bill's been introduced by the head of the
legislature that story's up at info wars calm but I want to just specifically for
police officers who are being told the same thing as you heard butch a
lieutenant governor and I can guess which state I know which state he knows
the governor and the lieutenant governor but I'm not gonna say this country so
cowardly now folks that even the heroes do it behind the scenes and the police
you know he talked to two in Michigan confirm their identities and then the
guy in North Carolina and then a lieutenant governor well I already know
I mean I've got articles speak of the devil out of the Carolinas out of North
Carolina it's in my film police state to the takeover from when is it
2000 where they had in the schools deputized local sheriff's under ATF in
the law enforcement program and it said they did anti-gun programs with the kids
for a full semester and and discuss their home life that's part of the grant
actually show the grant papers so I can confirm all of this is going on it's
just good to hear police call in so the public can hear it so 800 to 5 9 92 31
800 to 5 9 92 31 800 to 5 9 9 2 3 1 we're going back to Bob Fletcher here in
just a moment hey the new magazines are in and I saw somebody on YouTube
complaining going why is it $59 for 12 issues and complaining that we're
charging money these are big color glossy thick magazines now we've
expanded them now into the fifth issue and that includes the 12 shipping it's
over $2 per magazine after shipping handling graphics writers I'll be honest
with you and I designed it this way this thing is not making money but it is
getting the word out okay and it will soon we got enough subscribers but we
have to make money to be able to get more info about I did it so there's hard
copies big glossy color things you can give people full of graphics and
editorial cartoons and everything to give people 2013 the year America dies
okay you can buy them in bulk at cost what 10 of them for $14 a hundred it's
even less per copy okay you can buy these at cost in bulk and give them to
people and in fall war store calm but it's designed to wake people up and boy
is it we put a bunch of them out for free on the streets of Austin so again
ladies and gentlemen get it get it out to people now because here's the problem
people don't know what's going on the media is being very quiet they're like
yeah it's reasonable you're gonna turn your guns in with the bill or yeah we're
gonna ban all the guns in Illinois or yeah we did build some FEMA camps there
the average mainline neocon show is not saying anything when the Republicans
pass the biggest you know tax increases ever and taxes on 77% of people let's
call conservative and and and total lies and the point is they're moving this is
it the political whoredom has been threatened controlled fluffed whatever
the issue is into going along with this so they've been told we're making the
move you want to have a seat at the table sit down and shut up so we have
got to lunge to our feet because this is a 50 alarm fire no neocon show is even
making a big deal out of this the only big media outlet not controlled by
globalist that's covering it other than info wars calm and world net daily calm
is drudge report calm okay so a lot of people are like I'll just shoot them
when they come for them they're gonna pull you over to checkpoint and arrest
you and say we know that you've got guns okay this is a way to purge the gun
owners so eight hundred two five nine nine two three one we'll do a little bit
of overdrive with Bob Fletcher whistleblower joining us Bob tell me
what you said off air because you weren't listening today and you said
your notes concurs he won't repeat it cuz I already said it read what's on
those notes about you believing this is a plan to carry out a purge of course it
is this is the cover for them to say we're terrorists they're already saying
gun owners killed the kids gun owners are clan well you know the left is
saying we hope you don't turn them in we're gonna hunt you down we're gonna
form federal militias this is their little Soviet takeover just once they
once they do martial law whatever pretext they utilize for that you know
they have expanded and particularly even Obama in the last couple of years they
have expanded the the martial law capabilities they've upgraded them they've
upset not that it makes any difference because once martial law is in you know
it's it's all over I mean they it gives some carte blanche to do whatever they
want and to utilize any means by necessary they of course make reference
I know you've covered all this and make reference to the American people as being
a you know like it's a chattel product or something like that they call us I
think I have a clip in a UN video from the 70s they call us human resources to
be used and in the US code we're called animals I mean even the new the brand
new upgraded thing that Obama died on have the papers in front of me but the
upgrade on the recent upgrade that Obama did in the last few months actually uses
that same term so they haven't backed off or anything they're still just using
that terminology that you're strictly a an item to be applied to whatever they
have to and they can force you to do whatever they want you to do and that's
very very clear very specific in the brand new executive orders related to
martial law no no it says forced labor it says forced work brigades they can
take your resources Congress is suspended under these executive orders
of Bush and Obama oh absolutely that's a done deal yeah all of that anything that
falls into quote unquote representative government Congress passed a law saying
they're allowed to insider trade but the media said the law banned insider
trading when there was already a law banning it see how they work I mean
nothing to do with what those guys are going to follow up there anyhow but
again and I don't mean to be repetitious but the the thing that bothers me for
example is this huge multinational mercenary operation originally called
Blackwater now it's got to be so gigantic with multi-billion dollar on
challenge contracts with Uncle Sam XE yeah they're so without even being
bidded they're not bid deals for most of them they're training the police
everywhere there's video of them on DEA raids now and when when they when they
get around to kicking the doors and see you'll have like two mercenaries from
who knows Afghanistan or Uganda out at your front door with one local police
officer so that you did so that those two guys don't know it's worse than that
correction Corps of America is now running the public schools in many
cities and in many states and they train the kids literally to how to go into the
private prison which is the new slave labor correction Corps of America is now
in the elementary schools in places like Arizona when they when they go in I mean
when once they do the martial law and then they just tell everybody alright
we want you all to just turn in we're gonna have dump trucks coming down the
street we want you to throw your guns in them and by the way if people think that
sounds bizarre you know we forget even myself and maybe yourself you know we
forget that they did that in Australia already you know they they took all the
guns in England and they killed crocodile Dundee the real guy oh it's a
long time it's a long time ago now they killed 2,000 Aussies they murdered him
yep and they went in and they literally I know we actually had a printed on a
t-shirt that the militia groups had for distribution and it was a t-shirt that
showed a pile that was a hundred feet high and 70 feet across with nothing but
weapons that they had confiscated and their crime rate went up 86% within two
years and has only climbed since and now they're under carbon taxes and they
brought in foreign gangs to literally beat and rape the Aussies who are thrown
in prison or they defend themselves and now they're trying to ban butcher knives
in England people think you know when people hear us talking like this I know
there's a good percentage still out there that says well they couldn't keep
this plan secret how could they do how could they keep this secret in that
secret and everything but the American people have forgotten a thing called the
Manhattan Project all right we for five years in the United States at the high
point of national concerns that there had ever been there for a while back in
1938-39 for five years we worked secretly to create the atomic bomb nobody
knew anything about it I don't know how big of a secret you could get because we
had thousands of people working on that all right but they were still able to
keep it under wraps until boom all of a sudden one day Truman came on and said
we just killed 150,000 Japanese people in about four and a half seconds with a
new weapon and nobody knew anything about it and I'm afraid we're gonna be
caught and interrupt you and interrupt you will go into overdrive we got Joe
Bannister calling in a bunch of other police officers calling them we're gonna
get to them right now this is breaking news they're not actually keeping the
secret it's in the executive orders it's in the military training manuals it's in
pieces of news here and there it's just not all being fanfared and announced so
when they drop the hammer they're like it's like they said they ordered the
body scanners on Christmas Day with the underwear bomber they ordered them a
year before but they lied they just tell the public oh the Army's here to take
your guns we just trained to do this today it's amazing Bob Fletcher ran
contra whistleblower is our guest right now he says he's Joe Bannister I'll
recognize his voice if it is I'm gonna go to Jeff who's a New York police officer
and Joe who's a California police officer and Roman who's a marine but
again I specifically want to know about people that know about the lieutenant
McCoy that's been confirmed by our own GCN host butch paw that that the North
Carolina they are training for mass gun confiscation door-to-door and
checkpoints the training starts next week with special deputized units under
ATF of local police which is the model in which I've already confirmed they're
doing with ATF but the training is nonspecific let's talk to Joe Bannister
Joe is this Joe Bannister hey that's you okay so you're the Treasury agent the
sound of the IRS that found out the IRS was a scam asked him to respond so they
told you resign and they tried to put you in prison for your free speech you
beat them real fast what's your take on this do you have any Intel on the
federalization covertly for gun confiscation absolutely do have a
reliable law enforcement source who told me he personally participated in
training within the last year it was federally funded and sponsored in which
the officers the California peace officers were instructed to shoot to
kill as opposed to shoot to stop and you know law enforcement won't understand
the difference and so the federally these federal agents and federal
military were teaching them shoot to kill and the officers were really taken
aback by that because all of their previous training is about shoot to stop
the threat and that's different from shoot kill so this is these that's what
the feds are training the state and local officers at least in California
you know that it's nationwide it's shoot to kill so I would say that totally
corroborates what your other guests are talking about and that specifically we
have the army manual are they trying to shoot to kill Americans who don't turn
their guns in and including blowing up the houses what are they being told to
shoot to kill training is for they're not told in other words they have this
live-fire training you know where you going well they even had that with the
police and the military quote simulating killing zombies dressed up you know in
Dallas Cowboys jerseys that's the cover you saw that where they are having army
training to kill zombies which is really just mow down citizen training right so
they're not they're not actually putting like John Deere hats on the people but
they are changing their whole outlook in terms of when they're gonna fire it's
shoot to kill and that's such a difference that's a military type
scenario as opposed to a civil law enforcement scenario incredible Bob
Fletcher's on with us right now seeing Feinstein say mr. mrs. America get ready
to turn your guns in seeing them introduce you a gun band hand your guns
in in Illinois they say it's set to pass the military training to mow down whole
crowds of people but using the zombie cover I just showed that mainstream news
article seeing this whole build-up what is your take from being on the inside of
how serious things are
Joe Joe oh well I've got a lot of law enforcement from the past and they're all
freaking out because they can see the federal influence coming in like crazy
into their department so it's it's going to be nasty and what's going to be a
shame is for these law enforcement officers whether to stay or leave and
you know the pressure is going to be on when you start doing illegal and
immoral things as I had to experience myself and many people do it's I'm I'm
really I get that those same chills that you get Alex thinking what's coming oh
it's guaranteed but I mean if 1% of gun owners fight back that's 1.5 million and
I mean I would hide it but again that's the diabolical plan Joe I want to get
you on the nightly news the next few nights to talk about what your sources
are telling you that is really important breaking news thank you let's jam
another call while Bob Fletcher a Bob Fletcher investigations is our guest
will give you his website again as well let him finish up in some overdrive
let's switch police officers been holding the longest let's talk well let's
go to Roman whose California Marine claims he has gun info I know I've
videotaped Marines training for gun confiscations many years ago Roman then
we'll go to Jeff and Joe and then back to our guest real quick Roman what's
your Intel all right listen I appreciate your call your phone's breaking up I
couldn't really understand what you're saying let's go to Jeff in New York says
he's a police officer Jeff real fast what's your take on this do you have any
information on gun confiscation training yes the county that I serve in the
sheriff's department tried to get our small town police department to start
training for door-to-door confiscations and we refused and a lot I think that's
the way it's been going a lot of the small towns is the small close-knit
towns the small police departments aren't gonna go along with us Jeff
excuse me your is so you're saying you guys were told to train and to train
with who for door-to-door gun confiscation our local county sheriff's
department I live in New York New York is still under an assault weapons ban
and very draconian gun laws and oh yeah your governor has said they may ban all
the guns statewide make people turn them in New York Times yes and and and and
who are you supposed to train with the the sheriff's department the sheriff's
department which I'm sure somebody from the federal government has spoken with
them and gotten them to go along and so the federal government's coming in
saying do gun confiscation drill stay there I want to have you Bob Bob
Fletcher's take on this with you then we'll talk to Tom and Marilyn his police
we got Joe and a bunch of others this is just really crazy what's happening
really don't throw away leftovers instead throw all your leftovers
vegetable peels eggshells coffee grounds pizza crusts and more into the Bokashi
if you love to garden and compost but don't like the hassle of turning a
compost bin or this smell then check out the EM Bokashi food waste recycling
system from tarragonics finally a way to recycle all your food and plant waste
safely and effectively and stop using fertilizers the EM Bokashi food waste
recycling system rather than decomposition the Bokashi system uses
fermentation to break down waste so it takes less time to create nutrient dense
humus for crops or gardens with no turning and no obnoxious odors to learn
more and order your Bokashi online visit tarragonics.com and click on the
orange button that's tarragonics.com spelled t-e-r-a-g-a-n-i-x.com or call
eight six six three six nine three six seven eight that's eight six six three
six nine three six seven eight recycle all your food wastes in about six weeks
with the Bokashi food waste recycling system from tarragonics.com tarragonics
life's getting better my name is Josh one world weight is the best in the
market hands down I'm in the US Navy and I live a very active lifestyle being a
vegetarian it's hard getting all the protein I need I tried the vegan protein
powders and I just wasn't feeling any change the meathead supplement store
whey protein kind of worked for a bit but it left me feeling bloated and my
digestion seemed to slow down by some device struck a block I heard a
commercial of one world weight on the radio and it struck my interest I have
to tell you I am so glad I got it I have been taking it for a week and the
results are amazing I don't feel tired when I have to get up at 4 30 a.m. I look
and feel better I recover faster from my two workouts a day when I don't have
time to eat good food I take it and I don't feel the urge to stuff my face for
hours I got up this morning and I looked the leanest I've looked since high
school I can go on and on the best I can do to repay you is buy more and tell my
friends call eight eight eight nine eight eight three three two five that's
eight eight eight nine eight eight three three two five or visit one world WH e
y.com hello this is Ty Bollinger author of the best-selling book cancer step
outside the box I want you to know some very important information in 1985
president Ronald Reagan requested that carnivore be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the president could obtain this world-class healer now
27 years later carnivore capsules are used around the world to keep people
healthy now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of super
bugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond to
abnormal cells only without harming a single normal cell if you want to stay
healthy now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune cells to
attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body call 1 866 Venus fly
or order from carnivore calm that's car ni vo ra.com that's 1 866 836 8 7 3 5 1
8 6 6 Venus fly or visit carnivore calm protect your immune system it's the only
one you've got
it is more important than ever to support this broadcast I've been so busy
the last three weeks with us coming down that I haven't even been plugging things
that fund our operation like the propure water filters discounted 10% with promo
code water at info war store calm the books the videos all of it if you
believe in what we're doing I want to see it continue be sure and support us
at info war store calm or call 8 8 8 2 5 3 3 1 3 9 Bob Fletcher's gonna tell a
CIA story from the assistant of Casey Bob Fletcher investigations calm the
next segment let's go to Jeff in New York we'll go to each police officer
real fast we get to the next one Jeff your take on gun confiscation training
it's it's hard to say Alex I mean like I said my my my department is about 20
officers and we're just not gonna have any part of it do you have any info all
these other departments calling in saying they are getting the training now
um well like I said our local sheriff's department the county that that I work
in they wanted my department to start training with their their SWAT teams for
for entry and it is the biggest thing that happens in our town that we deal
with mostly is you know maybe a bar fight or a DWI but nothing violent
nothing criminal and now all of a sudden they want us to start training on how to
enter houses yeah well if the larger departments it's for gun confiscation
that is confirmed the Army's admits they're training for it they're gonna
have beta tests where they show it everyone's turning their guns in they're
happy that's the SIOP but that's not gonna be real and they're gonna try to
demoralize this it's gonna be amazing god bless you Jeff let's talk to Joe in
California you're on the air police what's your take on this are you getting
that training Alex yes sir privilege yes I just wanted to let you know that I've
been speaking with you for over listening to your program for over two
years now and nobody has ever called in to tell you what I'm gonna tell you
right now there are secret sleep sleeper cells all over the country that are
ready and willing to take charge of the situation and I'm not talking about
kicking people's doors in all right the people that I hang out with all ex
military I spent 20 years in the Navy and I know that I swore an oath to the
Constitution and the only thing that bothers me sir about you is that you
were never in the military so you never swore an oath to the Constitution and I
have my doubts about you being a DoD plant and I want you right now to your
worldwide audience to tell everybody that you are for real because you offer
you talk a lot but you don't really offer any solutions and I'm an action
person about solutions I understand you're you're you're God and then and
John Wayne and I'm nobody I'm on air 17 years you know just nothing but
delivering the goods over and over again and but but but I'm nobody and have no
track record you we don't know who you are had a prank caller earlier now
you're calling in saying their sleeper cells look I appreciate your call we
hear this a lot about the white knights and the good guys and it's all handled
nobody's gonna put a look action I'm calling for states rights I'm calling to
get good people elected to Congress to get a of election fraud I'm saying I'm
Alex Jones I'm not turning my guns in I'm calling for the second American
Revolution and all over the news I know people can't believe I'm still alive
it's called God okay if that's why and and you might get what you want I might
get struck down but you judge a tree by its fruits and that's political
cognitive infiltration that Cass Sunstein talked about even if the guy's
not a fed he probably wasn't they cognitively infiltrate they say go out
in their groups cause in fighting call everybody who isn't a fed okay I'm here
talking about hey Diane Feinstein says she's coming for our guns I'm doing
things to stop this I'm putting out the arguments why this is wrong I'm having a
big effect I'm trying to go to police officers with information I said are you
training for gun confiscation they're calling in and saying yes or yes we're
getting similar training you call in we're trying to get information here you
call in and say I'm full of malarkey we're gonna come back for 20 minutes at
least in overdrive with a plus here I apologize I've been going to calls but
we got to go through these but that's how a sign-off works which you just
heard and saw thank you for listening to GCN visit GCN live.com today now that we
have moved into the winter season there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health at Silver Lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by
providing a full selection of silver based products our most popular silver
based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our two ounce nano
silver nasal applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps just released
is our 100% natural silver gel our new silver gel is not based on synthetic
gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface but
rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while
delivering the silver more effectively visit www.silverlungs.com and click on
our store page to find what silver based products are best for you
that's www.silverlungs.com coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're
listening to the alex jones broadcasting network
it is the second day of January 2013 I am your host Alex Jones Bob Fletcher on
record I ran contra whistleblower advisor to Congress he's got some CIA
stories and tell you in a minute about one of the top folks in the CIA and how
he was able to pretty much start the militia movement to try to resist the
globalist and is one of the guys that helped hold it back about ten years we
also got some other police officers like Tom and Marilyn we're gonna get to now I
don't think that guy was a psyop but he was repeating a psyop see a good psyop
is put out and then other people put it out when you say we have hope we can
restore things but we've got to admit blah blah blah that you know the New
World Order the Federal Reserve that's not a psyop that's a patriot now
sometimes psyops come out been doing the 17 years well really 20 but 17 on air
and they'll for about a year never more than a year put out decent info and then
start in fighting and putting out crazy talk so that and I'd said Hal Turner was
a fed came out he was I mean that was obvious saying kill judges and go after
me and all this stuff and I'm a fed and I'm like that guy's a fed anybody
there's people on air now that's you know call for attacking the Federal
Reserve and stuff folks if I said that the police would be here in one hour
okay how did you deal Bob with with provocateurs and people and what's your
take on that call you just heard where we're putting out you know the mother's
milk info of Liberty Paul Revere and the guy opens the window and says you're a
red coat and I'm like why would I be telling you the red coats are coming go
ahead in a tremendous amount of situations like that people that were
always doing that and trying to say I mean they were always constantly say you
know the that entire Patriot movement the entire militia movement all those
guys up at the very top first off the bad guy said that we were connected to
the Nazis and every other crazy thing and and racist and knowledge and that
was complete garbage with the exception of a couple of yahoos who are always out
there sure I mean you were you were going up against a Reagan and Iran
contrary you're not but listen the point is exactly it isn't about that it's
about they're coming for our guns what are we gonna do and the guy says you're
a DoD plant because you didn't serve in the military I mean what does that even
mean you know people have gone and found my went to Rockwall and went to Austin
and got my yearbooks they've gone and interviewed people I went to college
with trying to prove I'm not who I say I am people think I'm 50 I'm 38 years old
go ahead and we had an awful lot of that constantly and the bottom line in some
cases it simply is a a disgruntled ex-serviceman who by the way I am one
I'm not a did well and yeah disgruntled but not on the wrong side of the fence
or very side the bottom line is we we did guys that felt that if in fact you
weren't in the service that you have no right to talk in terms of defending the
Constitution because you never raised your hand and and and swore to defend
the Constitution but what do you have to point out what I constantly pointed out
to those guys when they would say that I would say hey listen the people that are
the bad guys the president of the United States that's taking us down the toilet
rose raised his hand to protect the Constitution what are you talking about
that has no bearing Bob Bob I've sworn on the altar of God eternal resistance
to tyranny as Thomas Jefferson did I'm not swearing to the corrupt New World
Order that hijacked my country it's asinine my deeds and I'm not here to
justify myself but but it's a total cop-out I work sometimes 18 hours a day
and these people don't have a micron of discernment if they don't know I'm
totally true blue they do stuff like watch police state for and see a thing
where it says submit to tyranny you know with a New World Order badge it's not
subliminal it's clearly on the screen they go that's a subliminal or he has a
pyramid saying New World Order that's subliminal you can't see a subliminal
with the naked eye they use any excuse to cop out and say I'm bad so let me
just say it this way we're gonna break come back into more news and calls with
Tom and others let's just say I'm horrible and bad now let's move on what
are you gonna do to stop copping out okay you need to engage the New World
Order folks we need to expose them we need to get the word out they're coming
for our guns okay all right Alex Jones I'm the worst person on earth okay I'm
not but just whatever fantasy got okay it's true all right now can we move on
now okay you're a bigger man you're a better man I'm a bad man you're a good
man everybody now ignore all that now I'm bad you're good we got it you're
John Wayne I'm crap now let's move on against the globalist
they're the fight they're coming down on us now's the time hundred and ten
percent hello I'm Alex Jones myself my family the info wars calm team want to
relay to you and your families that we aren't intensifying our efforts against
the globalist on every front info wars calm is leading the fight against the
technocrats but we can't do that without your help by getting the films bumper
stickers and t-shirts at info wars calm you will wake up people in your area and
support our operation as we move to the next level we need your help to spread
the word like never before they wish to hide themselves during this
tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness you are the
response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics
dehumanization and ultimate extermination the war is here it's an
info war the spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984 hi my name is Annette
and due to menopause symptoms for nearly two years I suffered severe hot flashes
which prevented me from sleeping all night it was so hard to work because it
continued all day to have the hot flashes from hell I was exhausted and
depleted after only three weeks on one world weight I have no hot flashes and
I'm sleeping normally again I feel energized and strong this is an amazing
product it is a little-known fact that every single cell of your body is
supposed to produce 10% of its protein content as glutathione but due to
toxicity and aging it does not could glutathione be a missing factor in
optimal cell function for your entire body if you restore the optimal
glutathione levels in your cells especially your glands and organs then
as a result your glands and organs work better imagine the quality of life
improvement you might have to order one world way call eight eight eight nine
eight eight three three two five that's eight eight eight nine eight eight three
three two five or visit one world way calm that's one world WHE y.com food
stores check survival tools check weapons and water filters check but what
about a permanent source of cooking power that can run forever without
buying fuel or paying for maintenance introducing afterburner stoves home of
the original patented rocket stove the Kelly kettle and the solo stove
afterburner stoves has what you need and now offers all GCN listeners our
complete preparedness package with the means to cook meals and sanitize water
whether you dig in or bug out cook almost any meal with just a handful of
sticks we already have the lowest online prices guaranteed but if you enter
coupon code GCN at checkout we'll knock off an additional 15 percent and send
you our amazing six-hour solar rechargeable light bulb absolutely free
all for only two hundred and forty nine dollars visit afterburnerstoves.com or
call eight six six seven one six five two one four eight six six seven one six
five two one four afterburnerstoves.com cook hot meals with just a handful of
sticks
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups
you want answers well so does he live from Austin Texas broadcasting worldwide
it's Alex Jones
there's a video we did back in July a special report troops wanted to kill
Americans who do not turn in their guns it's in the official manuals it ties
into all the gun confiscation training in the news that's going on and the
announcements and most guns will be turned in under the Feinstein bill
states are moving in the same direction and you're like well that'll cause a
civil war that's the plan we got one more call from a police officer I got
saying he's a police officer Tom in Maryland and we'll get his take on all
this we had pastor Butch on earlier with the lieutenant McCoy with the gun
confiscation training they're going under with the ATF in North Carolina
that audio and videos up at in full Wars calm right now but the troops ordered to
kill Americans who do not turn in their guns that video is posted in a new
report with the latest info Obama would call on military to disarm Americans
during national emergency and it's got all the proof army manuals provides
blueprint for confiscating guns of quote rioters and dissidents and the
reeducation camp fm3 dash 39 dot 40 how to process you and your family into the
reeducation Center actually uses that term Bob Fleischer congressional
whistleblower I ran contra a businessman who was basically infiltrated and they
tried to use him for operations he helped expose him and then of course one
of the modern founders of the militia to counter it is on with us finishing up
with a caller right now Tom and Marilyn police officers say what what is your
take on this have you gotten any training along this line well I thought
I had two points that I thought would be germane and that you and your audience
would be interested in we went through a very similar time back in the early 90s
when they were talking about doing an assault weapons ban that's what I was
saying I just interrupt Bob was saying that during a break that Alex we can
stop this they did this in the early 90s I want him to respond after you're done
I'm sorry just go ahead sure sure well I suspect that probably as far as police
officers are concerned you'll end up with two groups like we did back in
early 90s we had those who took their oath seriously and had a real problem
with the thought that if a law were passed that would contradict our oath
uphold the Constitution what would we do would we quit like the lieutenant was
talking about earlier would we try to stay on and work and do good from the
inside it was something that we really stressed about now about half of the
other officers didn't take the oath seriously and then they were beholden to
the paycheck and said outright many of them well we're just going to do what we
need to do to keep a job I need to put food on the table it tells you right
away you know who has honor and and who doesn't so as far as we were concerned
of course we didn't know exactly what possible legislation would be it turned
out that with the band we didn't feel that it was something that we had to
take drastic action on but we had decided prior to it passing that if it
was something that absolutely contradicted the Constitution we were
going to start before it even was passed into law with a heavy-duty letter
writing campaign and also the following of lawsuits I think amen we got to file
lawsuits we got to do banner hangs we I keep me in to shoot a video I'm gonna do
it today after the show for the nightly news where I get into solutions but then
I there's so many let me ask you officer and then Bob Fleischer what do you think
the number one solutions are I think just get the word out you know the fact
that the media isn't making a big deal out of this they're making a big deal
about the shooting saying something's got to be done but they're not telling
people it's gun confiscation I mean that's the bill and so I think number
one just get the word out that this is going to be a physical ban that that
would be one of the best ways but we thought the very best way would be to
take action in the form of following lawsuits and writing letters and and
they really go hand in hand getting the word out and getting other people to
realize that it's a serious issue that it's not just another wall and we're
talking about civil rights lawsuits we're talking about and again even if
you don't win them it gets people's attention when you sue them makes them
respond when you file legal action and anyone can do it per se you don't have
to hire a lawyer it only takes your time and your willingness to do what you you
know is right and like I said about 50% maybe a little bit more of the officers
really believed that it was the right thing to do and that it was a priority
what's happening now I mean people you talk to officers you talk to now are
they are they concerned about all this gun confiscation move well the options
that I talk to now are very concerned about the new generation if you will of
police officers we see things being done that we never would have done that we
probably would have been fired for I don't know how they're developing their
general orders or their standard operating procedures whatever they're
calling them now but there's a lot of actions being taken and defended that
we're just appalled at there was a marine killed you can see video of raids
taking place you know when we did a dynamic entry it was just that it was a
dynamic entry and the goal was that no one got hurt and that the warrant was
properly served you look at a lot of what's going on these days and it's as
though they're going in for a shooting match no they want to kill somebody
because that's manly and that's not at all what it's about and in defense of
the good officers can we believe there's still a good number of good officers out
there I can't imagine how they're reconciling the old school if you will
with this new generation well let me tell you god bless you god bless you
sir and the great points you've made I have been around feds and people at gun
shows and stuff and they'll come right over and go yeah Jones we you know what
are you doing here and they look like a guy out of a Hollywood movie who's a
criminal I mean they're like obviously horrible scum and you're like what do
you think you're intimidating me I mean they're gangsters and it just gets my
hackles up at so many levels that we are really a pathetic nation that we put up
with this and most police I see don't act like total thugs but you see units
of them you know where they're like all on roids and shaved heads and wearing
black gloves and gooning at you and I'm the type of person when somebody looks
something like a goon I mean I'm not looking for trouble and that just gets
me like whoa whoa you're trying to dominate me I mean there's such shameful
people that it makes me want to climb up on top of them and show them who you
know you know what you know what a real man is because it's fundamentally
upsetting Bob Fletcher do you know what I'm talking about I mean the sickness of
a goon they're like little arrested kids little arrested of course you know those
are the guys that are selected selected internally and brought forward and run
through the system I'll call them the bad guys run through their system put
them forward and say hey this guy will fit in great for either doing undercover
or doing psychological psych ops to scare the pudding out of some average
citizen you know so they're put over here they get a separate file you know
they're removed and they say hey they call them over and bring bring them up
and say listen Joey we we want to give you a raise and we want to put you into
our special ops over here and it'll be exciting it'll be this it'll be but
don't the globalist cowards know that with the average man somebody acting
intimidating towards them doesn't intimidate you you know the again the
bottom line is if you can you know if you can scare one guy he's usually
whoever he is you know he's gonna drag down another handful of all along with
him some of his friends or family and you know I'm gonna say hey we got to do
this we got to do that when they do this martial law and they go to the first
homes the initial ones where they kick in the doors and they say bring out your
guns and the first guy that says I'm not gonna let you know I'm not I'm not gonna
give you my gun they're just gonna shoot them in the doorway that's right and
they're gonna videotape it and then they're gonna show that on the news and
and I got news that's impressive to the five people that are watching in the
neighborhood and they're all gonna have their guns out on the front porch by the
next afternoon and that's the kindest yeah I predict five and ten percent are
gonna go hunting it's gonna be bad and that's literally part of it oh what I
wanted to mention we talked about a while back I had a very close friend
that had been involved with the CIA going through several different
presidential administrations a very high-level person highly respected the
very fact that and by the way was a lady and the fact that she was involved with
several administrations in the intelligence community shows to what she
was and I asked her one time because it was making me crazy I was watching news
in Los Angeles when I was living there for a while and and there was this huge
a bomb scare situation and it involved helicopters and the bomb squad and all
kinds of stuff and they were doing this live broadcast and everything but then
when I brought it up I think on a television or a radio interview or
something the next day or a couple days later nobody knew what I was talking
about and I said they said it wasn't broadcast they didn't see anything they
didn't know anything about it and I said this was in downtown Los Angeles with
wires and bombs and stuff coming and hanging out of the door of this big truck
and all this and so I asked my friend in Washington I said how is it that United
Press International Associated Press and all of the the middle distribution for
media how is it that they obviously didn't even pass that through and this
is a point in time you know after the Oklahoma bombings and all that stuff in
the Murrah building internet wasn't big yet she said operation mockingbird there
was none so but the point was she simply told me that for several years
progressively the people that were doing the New World Order move on America had
been placing totally prepaid employees at the highest level of management and
these were the guys that would say this story goes out on the public or this
story just stays as a little local thing and so they had totally implanted the
control mechanism and that was how they were able to keep stories from the West
Coast from the East Coast and what-have-you and maintain control and of
course you separately learned about that but that came out in the church hearings
in the 70s about operation mockingbird but now what are they gonna do what are
they gonna do now though they don't control all the talk radio I know they
don't control me they don't control the news sites but still I see stuff where
it's a huge news story you never see it on mainline news that's why they want
the internet kill switch and want to shut down radio with the fairness
doctrine right and basically this I want to point this out to everybody that's
listening also when when they do the martial law there will be no more
internet you can kiss that goodbye that's the internet kill switch they
admit that that's right and whether they've got it in other words whether
they have the quote-unquote legal capability to do that that will have
nothing to do with it it would be an executive order that makes it legal
they're gonna throw the switch and we no longer have our internet even three and
a half years ago with the swine flu you can pull this up White House considered
redirecting sites to CDC it was in mainstream news we can pull that up for
people they actually said Bob they looked at redirecting everything the
entire web or portions of it to a government announcement about to protect
yourself from the flu so they admit they have and notice a few months ago Obama
signed a cyber order but told Congress they can't see it I mean that right
there is a dictator it's unbelievable it has grown and grown and grown we warn
people very specifically in the early 90s people thought we were absolutely
crazy and and and by the way there are also there are still how do you say this
there are weapons and things going on at a high level an extraordinary high level
of technology that we still don't have a good handle on other words we know they
have lasers we know that microwaves we know have a B and C and D and we we have
pretty good exposes on some of that I remember people five years ago saying
the new census would be to mark our front doors to fire missiles at us and
then a few years later they did the census and they marked our doors and
then now they've admitted they are using the marking for drones and they're gonna
use and are using predators and Reapers in our skies and they're gonna launch
30,000 already paid for against us and then police officers are confirming it I
mean it is cuckoo crazy takeover because they want they hate us they want to have
their way with us Bob yeah and it also becomes a bigger challenge you know it's
and and I'll tell you what the psyche of these people who are that's why I
wanted to get you on let me stop you you worked in and around Congress and were
around the intelligence community and blew the whistle on this stuff what is
the psyche because they were bad thirty years ago twenty years ago but now it's
just bull just amazing absolutely off of their rocker say it's I've met these
guys I had one general you know I was involved with a 24 million dollar lawsuit
filed by the Kristic Institute and that was right in the middle of the Iran
conscious stuff actually was prior to by about a year so the actual filings and
it was and basically it was the Iran conscious stuff drugs dope murder
weapons and all of that stuff and all the exact people that later were dragged
through the through the hearings which didn't accomplish anything but those
those one of those generals in reference to myself and other people that were
involved with witnessing he said boy if I was in Vietnam right now I'd blow that
and then he used vulgarity that I won't even use a free three-letter vulgarity
for describing myself and other witnesses and and those guys were in
bed with Pablo Escobar and all the rest no no they're drug dealers now they run
little kids snuff films and then they sit around and actually exactly sit
around and go I'm a veteran I fought in a war I am the good guy they actually
think they're the good guy we put cancer viruses in your vaccines because we're
good exactly they're all because the worst most murderous ones are the ones
that trough their way up to the head of the line yeah the problem is so many of
them started out you know I think they start out okay you know it's that same
old story it doesn't it doesn't help the the end the end product but they start
out doing the thing right it's ever in it next thing you know it's it's money
and drugs and power and the power control this this nut case that came in
and took over my business to use it as a covert front he had several businesses
took another guy for excuse me took another fellow for 13 million dollars a
couple of years yeah that's the thing why because I've studied this in
mainline declassification they come in they say they're doing a merger with a
shipping company then they go hey by the way we're CIA here come the generals
here come the computers we're going to use you as a front and then they don't
even pay you and say we'll just kill you if you don't shut up and then they you
know they have their wives killed they I mean they're just a bunch of psychopaths
that's what they did with me and when I was at the high point of blowing the
whistle after like a couple of years where I actually was having phone calls
on a regular basis from senators John Kerry and other people at my at my work
because I still have to maintain I just have to feed my family I'm in there at
nine o'clock in the morning one day and a guy drove his station wagon right
through my sliding glass doors in Orlando Florida missed killing me only
only because the rear wheels of the wagon hung up on the curb right there
with him oh yeah that's their favorite way is with cars it was just an
accident it was an accident and a week prior to that we run a guy off that was
videotaping the property what he was doing was videotaping the property ahead
of this guy making his erroneous but I'm sure they'll be much nicer once they get
our guns Bob yeah it's unbelievable but but they when we talk about their psyche
the this individual that took over my my business he was so he was crazy and but
and he was but he was successful at what he was doing for the government he was
supplying weapons and helicopters and aircraft all over the world for all of
these variety of you know like if he was still alive now he'd be doing it for
everything that's in the Mideast rate Syrian rebels yes all of it all of that
stuff he would have been involved within Libya and all the rest of that because
he was back then involved all over the world with this stuff and he was so such
a loose cannon you know he carried his stuff like in a paper bag he had like
six or eight or ten passports which of course is totally illegal for anybody
except the CIA different countries names and people and all that stuff big boxes
of money had cash you couldn't imagine the money they believe me I know I have
a let's just say great uncle I that it's really a great cousin but anyways the
whole story is he was an army officer and and and all he's told us was he said
yeah you know I did all this stuff in covert operations so then they bring me
in they go well here's your graduation in the CIA and it was dealing drugs and
killing people in Chicago and he said I'm not and well I'm not gonna he didn't
tell us much more the point is is that the thing is then I know other people
who have done I mean it's this is like it's not like a big deal to work for CIA
it's like working for UPS except they're running around killing people I mean
it's a giant operation worldwide as soon as we as soon as I filed with my lawyer
started to pursue what would have been just standard legal thing really the
contractual thing I couldn't forget it I knew you know what can I do against the
Uncle Sam but I I found a standard legal action started getting information with
my lawyer to simply sue this guy to get the quarter of a million dollars he owed
me which back then was a lot of money okay and I did I get a certification
came from executive orders of the President of the United States the
information that we were pursuing was classified he was talking about my my
toy factory so they basically classified my toy factory for the big rubber stamp
that said secret classified operation no more information will be coming in and
no court will handle your case you know you can't you can't go anyplace if you
got this the CIA tells a local judge and what's incredible Bob is they now are
going to fully gut the country and bring it all down and rob us like a third
world nation Bob pleasure investigations calm amazing look forward to having you
back on very soon they are trying to move on us right now but if we get the
word out like Bob did we can back them off again