Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, it is the 29th day of January, 2013. I'm your host,
Alex Jones. And again, I've told the producers, no guess today, because I want to be able
to play a lot of different clips and analyze them and take your phone calls.
We're going to open the phones up for first-time callers throughout the broadcast today. That's
first-time callers, and I'll give the number out coming up the next segment. And I'm gonna
try again, almost always fail, to go to them early in the shower. If you go up to prisonplanet.com
or infowars.com, our news website, you'll notice some of the headlines.
DHS boss praises trampling a posse commentatis at National Police Confab. They had another
Army Special Forces drill, unannounced, next to a school, terrorizing people in Houston.
The day before that, it was Miami, all part of martial law conditioning. Chinese Communist
Party mouthpiece demands Obama disarm Americans again.
Watson did a great job writing that article, but I think I'm gonna, as editor here, just
make the call that we need to add to that again. But this is the official People's Daily,
just amazing, a subsidiary of the People's Daily. Ron Paul, US action in Mali is another
undeclared war, absolutely.
Houston residents, I mentioned this, rattled by government gunfire and helicopters. And
again, that's powerful, but when you read the actual article, it's the Army, the Army.
Here's the headline out of ABC News, Army drill scares residents on Houston's south
side. Amazing, this stuff's happening every couple days now.
But I thought black helicopters didn't exist. In fact, I was seeing the local Miami TV station
video on YouTube yesterday. I meant to play it whenever it got to it, cuz we've been conditioned
to accept it, I guess. It's not even news anymore. And it showed these black helicopters
flying through the city and firing machine guns and all the rest of it.
And people in the comments are like, I thought the black helicopters didn't exist. Because
back in about 1995, when I first got on air on Access TV, people would call me and they'd
say, man, we just had black helicopters here. They blew up a warehouse. And I'd say, now
those don't exist, come on, cuz the Internet didn't really operate very well then.
But people would mail me, wasn't very prolific then, Johnny on the spot at that point, like
it is now. I would be mailed local news articles out of South Texas, out of California, out
of St. Louis, Missouri, out of you name it. And then I'd go on air just locally on TV
and then just locally by 96 on radio.
And I'd say, here's this newspaper reporting on 100 commandos blowing up the old police
station and this lady had a heart attack. And they actually had the local paper come
out and say I was insane, none of it existed. Again, knowing their audience said, do you
believe the Austin American statesmen, big respected newspaper, or that crazy guy on
the radio?
And so I kinda got obsessed with black helicopters. Not because I was obsessed with the black
helicopters themselves, but I became known by many as the black helicopter man. The media
called me that on hard copy and extra. And Jay Leno called me the black helicopter man
couple times. And so I was like, no, no, the helicopters are real.
So I started going to drills I was tipped off about by the army. So I'd say on air I'd
say army, folks at Fort Hood, next time you're doing a drill with the Fort Benning, Georgia
Night Stalkers or Delta Force or somebody, let me know. Well, needless to say, army special
operations did not like that and that's when the dirty tricks began.
Didn't matter though, I got the black helicopters on tape, you didn't stop me. And now they're
just everywhere. So that's a side issue that's coming up as well. Big sis addressed the big
law enforcement association and said, we're gonna use the army on the American people.
The number one threat is extremist. And she went on to say, the extremists are the ones
doing the mass shootings. So she's blaming constitutionalist for the school shootings
now.
Just an unbelievably degenerate piece of trash.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health. At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver based products. Our most popular silver based products are
the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well
as our all natural silver soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver
gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver
at the surface. But rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the
silver more effectively. Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver
based products are best for you. That's www.silverlungs.com.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die? Start purifying your water with Pro Pure. My friends, I've done
a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is Pro Pure and it's available
discounted at infowars.com. Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required. It's NSF 42 certified. Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride
up to 95%. Easy to set up and use. Doesn't require electricity. Purify water from lakes,
streams, ponds and wells. This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic. Pro
Pure is the best gravity fed filter out there. It's what my family uses. Infowars.com already
has the lowest price on Pro Pure but if you add the promo code WATER at checkout you get
an additional 10% off at infowars.com. You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
He aligns himself with the truth and it's time for you to choose a side. You're listening
to Alex Jones.
There is no turning back on the run. What an enchanting voice. Hard to turn that off.
Monday through Friday, ladies and gentlemen, we are here 11 a.m. to 2 p.m. Central Standard
Time. That's Robert Plant, if you don't know who it is, 1983. The song is Big Log.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, it is Tuesday, the 29th day of January 2013. Again, hard
to believe the first month of 2013 is almost gone. Here's the deal. I run into so many
people who say we like what you're doing with the radio show and the TV show.
We don't know what it is, but you've upped your game. You're more intense, you're more
focused, you cover more news. It's just getting better all around. And I chalk that up to
the times are so dangerous, the shadows are so long, nightfall here that it's got me a
little more focused, a little more serious, though we still have some fun. And of course,
the crew is upping their game as well.
Our supporters have been helping us get the word out. So many new M&FM affiliates, I have
a couple more to announce today, are picking us up. And so we are very, very blessed that
in this time of corruption, for every action, there is a equal and opposite reaction. And
we are that reaction. So the one thing I haven't really gotten better at, and I say this almost
every day, because I'm like in a rut, it's a pattern I follow, is that when I do say
I'm going to your calls, I don't tend to do it.
Because I've got so much incredible news here that I tend to just go off and all that instead
of taking the calls that so many times call in and mention news items I'm not aware of
or that I forgot to cover. And quite frankly, when I'm listening to rebroadcast, I think
that's some of the best and most informative radio we do.
So here's the deal, first time callers today, all three hours, first time callers, ladies
and gentlemen, any issue you wanna raise, any topic you wanna bring up, 800-259-9231,
800-259-9231. We've got a bunch of special reports we're gonna be premiering here on
air as well.
One of them is satirical, speaking of having fun, but it's not fun. I mean, I had an idea
last Friday, and I'm gonna air this at the bottom of the hour. While we were shooting
the news and things at about six o'clock at night, I said, you know what? I've got more
articles of people being arrested or threatened with arrest for bubble guns, Hello Kitty things,
super soakers, bright orange Nerf guns in their front yards, panics, just incredible
stuff.
There's an article today where a guy put on Facebook him holding his one-year-old and
had a BB gun in his hand. I mean, I can't tell you how many family photos we've got
where I'm sitting in grandpa's lap and he's got a shotgun. I mean, everybody's taking
the Old West photos, at least most people I know have been in their houses, they've
got them.
I remember being in Tombstone when I was about seven years old, my parents, and we went and
sat down as a family and my dad had a shotgun and my mom had a pistol in her hand and you
put on the old Western clothes. This guy had an unloaded BB gun, put it on his Facebook
and got SWAT teamed and arrested.
And I read all the time, I know you see it in the news where it's always the same MO,
some old vet lives out in the country where the edge of the city's growing. And they're
cleaning guns in their garage and the SWAT team comes and arrest him and says, he's arrested,
he had 25 guns. They're all legal, but we call this an arsenal.
Well, then how'd you arrest him? It's a hysteria. And I had the idea to have us all get in the
conference room and act like they're having a meeting about the news cuz we do have meetings
about what's coming up the next week and what we think we wanna focus on and ideas.
It's kinda like a newsroom pitch to the editor. We have those a couple days a week. A lot
of times we have them in the hallway. We'll just discuss things we're gonna be working
and ideas. So we did it in one take and it's been pretty popular. Alex Jones goes on Rampage
with bubble gun.
But a lot of people said, yeah, this is really funny. Thank God it's not like this. No, no,
you don't understand. It's based on real people being SWAT teamed for playing with Nerf guns
in their front yard. I mean, I've seen reports where a kid has a slingshot in their backyard
and the police are called, or a little kid says bang bang in the pickup truck driving
by somebody and the police are called.
It's about saying we're all suspects, we're all bad, we're all corrupt. Everybody is under
suspicion except for the government. You see, in a free society, the government is under
suspicion. It's kept small, it's kept on a short leash in a tyranny that is the norm
throughout history. And I make that point cuz it's hard to have liberty.
You better work for it. And you get liberty and you get prosperity, you become decadent
and go back into slavery. That's the only problem with liberty is it produces so much
wealth that, well, people's kids become spoiled brats and then their kids become tyrants.
So we shot this video and a lot of people thought, this is really funny how people are
freaking out about guns, but this is a bubble gun. No, no, no, no, this is based on real
stuff that happened. So I'm gonna air it here on air. It's even more funny with the video,
but I'm gonna air it coming up.
The video is up at infowars.com. It's already rolled off the front page into the featured
news archive or just click the top stories link up at the top of infowars.com and that
will take you there. There's also the tiles up top and it's also in the tiles. In fact,
if you guys punch up infowars.com, it'll actually show people that are watching on television
that they can see that.
Or if it doesn't work on this computer, we can just punch it up right there. Yeah, exactly.
If it ever doesn't work on here, we can just do it in there. It's infowars.com. Okay, anyways,
if you're watching, you can see right here top stories is always a good link to go to
for stuff that scrolls off. That's the featured news archive and the red link is the archive
area right there for all of the news feed.
But we're gonna be playing that piece coming up. Now, going over this, DHS boss praises
trampling a posse commentatis at National Police Confab. That's Janet Big Sis Napolitano.
Chinese Communist Party mouthpiece demands Obama disarm Americans again. This is an official
sub publication of the People's Daily, the official Communist Party mouthpiece. Ron Paul,
US Action in Mali is another undeclared war, no kidding.
Houston residents rattled by government gunfire and helicopters. By the way, by the army.
Here's ABC News, army drills scares residents on Houston's south side. And again, they just
had the army drill two days ago in Miami. So Sunday, it's in Miami and Monday, it's
in Houston. And we're now getting reports of other unannounced army drills where they
set buildings on fire, blow things up.
What they do is they covertly lease a facility. A lot of times it's the police department
or part of it and then they attack it. And in the role playing, they train to take on
the American people. Now, I would tell you this 15 years ago, ten years ago, I would
show you the documents, the proof, people said there's no way that's real.
Now, what's really happening here is you're just being acclimated. They have huge bases,
facilities everywhere. I've talked to the emergency managers who were let in on what's
happening. I've talked to the army officers. I've talked to all of them from every different
angle and facet of this. And it is to acclimate the military, the police, and the public that
it's normal to have troops on the streets.
And we have an article out today by Kurt Nemo, DHS boss praises trampling and posse comitatus
at national police confab. And actually have her remarks printed off. It's also linked
in the article. And she talks about the new threat is gun owners and the same story, the
extremist. And she goes on to say extremist and mass shootings.
So there are no cases of what they call anti-government people in the last 15, 16, 17 years I can
think of. And Oklahoma City was a bombing that was staged where a patriot or a returning
veteran has gone in and shot up a school. But they are now deploying the army. That's
what happened in Houston. It was a drill at a school to fight active shooters as if the
police couldn't do that.
And they are deploying the army of the Kentucky Derby, the army and all these big cities,
the army at the airports, the subways, the Marines. In my film Road to Tyranny, we show
countless clips of this that we shot in the film. I'm just giving you sources to look
it up, the 2007 film Endgame.
I'm in New York, and we're in a restaurant about 10 o'clock at night. And they go, hey,
the army's running around outside. So we go outside, and the army is dancing and partying
across the street with a bunch of professional wrestlers. I mean, it was like clownish cuz
Madison Square Garden was right there, professional wrestlers were getting off buses going in.
And there were these white vans. Well, you can see the video. And they see me and start
cussing, and they've got, I know they're supposed to carry Berettas.
They look like blue slash stainless steel 45s to me. People said, Alex, that's ridiculous.
Instead of just looking at the video, they go, don't say it was 45s cuz they carry Berettas.
I know that. They look like 45s to me. They run over and start cussing and get in my face.
I said, come on. I mean, that's the point we're getting to. We're the Baghdad people.
See, this is an occupation. Now, the average person, that's when the army's used against
us. Now, who's the army training to fight? The veterans, who they know were older and
more seasoned, who are gonna wake up.
So I haven't even gotten to the news. We're gonna go to your phone calls first, and then
I'll just get into all of it. It's all off the charts, and it's all online right now
on mfallwars.com and prisonblinder.tv.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought, to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather a life storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just
in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today, or go to efoodsdirect.com
slash Alex and build your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable
food on the planet. Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods
Direct.
Feeling like there are too many pressures and demands on you? Losing sleep, worrying
about tests and school work, either on the run because your schedule is just too busy?
You may be under too much stress, and it may be affecting your mind. Get your mental edge
back with Neutropic Mind Power from mindregard.com. Neutropic Mind Power is not a drug, but a
natural supplement. Its 12 powerful ingredients are natural and non-GMO, plus it's gluten-free,
wheat-free, and formulated by Americans for Americans by an NSF-certified laboratory.
Neutropic Mind Power is available at mindregard.com, spelled M-I-N-D-R-E-G-A-R-D.com, and comes
with a 100% money-back guarantee. Free your mind with Neutropic Mind Power, a cognitive
supplement from mindregard.com. Mindregard, clearly see tomorrow and yesterday, today.
HempUSA.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine, and probiotics,
and we'll send you our travel-size micro plant powder, absolutely free. Micro plant powder
only at HempUSA.org. Call 908-691-2608. That's 908-691-2608, and see what our powder, seeds,
and oil can do for you, only at HempUSA.org. This offer ends January 31st.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson. Have you ever wondered why banks, stockbrokers, investment advisors
want to talk about gold IRAs? They've been available since 1986, yet the financial industry
won't recognize the value of gold for your retirement. Gold has outperformed paper investments,
yet no word about IRAs. If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns, call 800-686-2237. Secure
your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
Is this the year you finally get serious about your family's drinking water? If so, keep
listening for a special offer from Big Berkey Water Filters. Did you know that over 60%
of municipal water is fluoridated? Berkey water filters distinguish themselves from
many other filtration systems with the capability to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine,
fluoride, arsenic, and disinfection byproducts from municipal water via the black Berkey
and PF line of filters. Then there's affordability. At only 1.7 cents per gallon, Berkey water
filters purify treated and untreated water, even stagnant pond water. Stop and think how
much money you could save by simply reducing buying bottled water and using water filtered
by your Berkey water filter. No need to be constantly replacing expensive filters with
a Berkey. A single set of filters can last for 5 to 10 years. Choose the best size Berkey
for your needs at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com. And right now, all GCN listeners get 5% off
all ceramic filter systems. Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY. That's 877-99-BER-KEY. Or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
Free shipping on every order over $50. Big Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean
water.
You rarely see anything truthful coming out of Al Jazeera, it's the globalist propaganda
front. But they interviewed the president of Iceland, the only country to not collapse
under banker austerity, and they asked him why. And he basically said, we arrested the
bankers cuz it wasn't our debt.
See, they signed us on to 644 trillion, that's a three year old number out of the Washington
Post of the 1.5 global quadrillion, it's 1,500 trillion. And they tell us we owe 16 trillion
and that we're bankrupted. By the way, Governor Rick Perry is set to give a press conference
in a few minutes, calling to give $12 billion in the rainy day fund, I'm gonna cover this
coming up, back to Texans.
That'll just be a free check to everybody, so everybody thinks he'll be a popular guy
to vote for for president. He's a globalist and I'm gonna explain why coming up. Why not
give us the money in the comprehensive annual financial report slush funds? The public doesn't
know that over 70% of the tax money goes to offshore private banks, and you can even get
reports from your own state and local governments on it.
Folks, you're living in a matrix of deceit, it is mind blowing. All right, I promise to
go to your calls, we're gonna take a lot of them today, intersperse with the news and
all the clips. Let's go ahead and talk to Travis in Indiana, you're on the air, welcome.
What's up, Alex?
Hey, buddy.
Hey, I had some friends talking about some explosions that were happening here in Indianapolis
a couple weeks ago. And when I did some research online and looked into it, I found this YouTube
video, I sent it to show tips. I just wanted you to look at it, analyze it, and let me
know what you think it is.
They're having military drills in basically every city, they have about 1,000 a year we
know of. Some of them where they have the Boy Scouts helping do door to door gun confiscation
simulations and I have that on film. And even in the New York Times Renew Listener, I'm
not joking, the Boy Scouts trying to take your guns and do other things now.
But I see in the comment you said military drill sent video, what's on the video?
The video is, it's like some lights or orbs in the sky and then it looks to be some sort
of like a fire trail almost like a missile. And when you hear it, it sounds almost like
a missile and then the impact sets all the car alarms off, the dogs start going crazy.
It's just out of this world.
Yeah, well, send it again to showtipsatinfoawards.com. Sometimes we miss stuff and we don't respond.
Send it again and let us know it's urgent. Thank you so much. I'll look at that video,
send it again right now if you can. Look, since you bring this up and since I got back
into black helicopters because I realized yesterday I mentioned the Miami assault drill
and I mentioned that the army was involved in Houston again yesterday.
I was the leading expert on this. Again, just because my listeners in 95, 96, when I first
got on air, would call in and say, my cousin lives in St. Louis and there were 15 black
helicopters there and they burned a building down. And I'd say, okay, get them to mail
it to me and it would come in the mail and it'd be the local paper.
And it would say residents claim they saw black helicopters and troops. A building did
burn down, but nothing happened. And I'd go, okay, and then people started sending me video
and it's in my films. You'd see black helicopters, guys coming down off ropes, stuff blowing
up. And then I'd cover it and people'd say that doesn't exist.
And then Delta Force crashed in Houston, people got killed. Soldier of Fortune wrote a story
about it. Houston Chronicle said it didn't happen and didn't exist. So it's a way to
see will the media play national security with the military industrial complex? Can
they have, I mean, I've seen drills where they have 1,000 or more Marines in a small
Alabama town walking around in people's yards.
And husbands come out and say, what are you doing? They just put handcuffs on you and
take it to jail. And then that's not in the news. It's all just to see what they can do.
And they've done countless drills. I staked one of these out in Corpus Christi. That did
get in the paper by like 99 or so, they started covering it, cuz World Net Daily was covering
it at the time and no one could ignore it.
And I was feeding World Net Daily videos and photos. Who was their writer then covering?
It was like David Bresnahan was his name. And that's the frustration. You're there,
you're in San Antonio, the police chief says Delta Force came in here with a bag of money
to buy me off. And then I have the video and people say that's not really the police chief.
Or we're down in San Antonio and MPs come up with guns and take our cameras away. I
mean that happened to us.
And then the media says you're insane, it doesn't exist. It's all an acclamation for
martial law. So that they can missile attack or assassinate whoever they want, kill whoever
they want. And everybody's just been taught, hey, you didn't see those black helicopters.
That's a conspiracy theory. That's crazy.
There on the march, the empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
You prepare by purchasing gold, food and firearms. But if you don't have a home security system,
then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection. When you're sleeping
or away from home, who's watching out for intruders? Check out Simply Safe. It's a new
do it yourself home security system that is completely wireless. Go to get simply safe
calm. Simply Safe is independent and off the grid. It runs on battery power. So even if
the grid goes down, you're protected. It's completely customizable. So you can use it
in your home, business, boat, trailer, storage unit or shed. Get simply safe calm. Simply
Safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes. So there's no
need to let a stranger into your home. If you move or need to relocate, you can take
the system with you wherever you go. You aren't always at home, but simply safe will stand
guard protecting your property 24 hours a day, seven days a week. Again, that's get
simply safe calm. Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and
other illnesses. Don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver, a revolutionary
new broad spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology have
resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold
and food poisoning and help improve wound healing. Supernatural silver is safe enough
to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases
such as stress, death, pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens. This new technology
has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times
the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says
silver is our mightiest germ fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder
of modern medicine. Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for
20% off. That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die? Start purifying your water with ProPure. My friends, I've done
a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is ProPure and it's available
discounted at infowars.com. Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required. It's NSF 42 certified. Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride
up to 95%. Easy to set up and use. Doesn't require electricity. Purify water from lakes,
streams, ponds, and wells. This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic. ProPure
is the best gravity fed filter out there. It's what my family uses. Infowars.com already
has the lowest price on ProPure, but if you add the promo code water at checkout, you
get an additional 10% off at infowars.com. You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
We are on the march. The empire is on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
You see, because the public doesn't research legislation or read publications put out by
MIT and Rand Corporation, they just hear a guy saying, hey, there's black helicopters
doing urban warfare drills. And people say, well, that's not true. The media makes fun
of that. That doesn't exist. You're insane. In fact, I happened to come across a Democratic
Party operative radio show yesterday and I was sitting there in the car listening for
about 15 minutes.
And they were talking about how crazy I was and that I believe that the Federal Reserve
is private. And that I believe, I'd mentioned the name, but I wanna give them attention.
That's how small they are. And that I'm tempted to get the author on. They had an author on
with them, who's written a book about how we're all crazy. And that I believe in black
helicopters.
No, I just, I read about, let's not exaggerate. I scan over probably 400 articles a day. I
probably read 100. And every week for 17 years on air, I have been mailed or read a
lot online, mainstream news about urban warfare and black helicopters. And then people sit
there with a straight face going, we define reality.
The Federal Reserve isn't private. There are no black helicopters. There is no world government.
And I'm like, but I have 15 clips of world leaders calling for world government. I have
a whole stack of news here. And ABC Nightline was here two years ago. And I knew they were
gonna say that because they told me some of the questions before they got here.
And I brought them in there. I've told the story 100 times. And I said, here's the clip
of Herman Van Rompuy. Here's Gordon Brown. Here's David Rockefeller. And I showed him
a couple of clips. He goes, I don't need to see anymore. That's a different world government
than what you're talking about.
And that's why then 30 minutes later, we left here to go shoot another interview at a park
down the street. And I said, well, you first said world government doesn't exist. Now you're
saying it's a good thing. And he goes, I don't even agree they're forming a world government.
And that's why I said, well, that's why you're discredited. But see, they edited all that
out.
I said, well, I just showed you all the videos and all their admissions and their definition
of world government. You can't tell me they're not getting rid of posse commentatas to put
troops on the streets. Now it's all happened, you notice. You can't tell me that they're
not going to set up TSA checkpoints.
It's now happening everywhere. You can't tell me they're not going to keep raising all the
different taxes till we're bankrupt. But again, they sit there with confidence as confidence
men and go, there's no world government. There's no black helicopters. And that is so fundamentally
frustrating because if the general public was informed, even when the black helicopters
come and attack your city to condition you.
The media, when they now admit it will go, well, they're just here for our safety. But
they'll never say, I guess the black helicopter people were right. You've all heard the term
black helicopter people. Anybody that doesn't trust government, that's called common sense.
You're a black helicopter person. And if you ever saw one, or one ever flew over your house
has happened to so many people with infrared sensors scanning your home, or ground penetrating
radar, which they now admit they're doing. We knew they were doing it 15 years ago, they
now admit it.
Well, now you're a black helicopter person if you don't like the black helicopter. Before
you were a kook, if you said they existed, but instead of, you were right about everything.
Tell us what else is happening. You were correct, we apologize. Instead, it's your bad. In fact,
you're even worse than you've ever been.
Because people think that if they're just delusional and tell themselves everything
is okay, it's gonna be okay. No, it's not gonna be okay. And I've got Janet Napolitano
saying the number one threat again at the big police chief and sheriff's association
meeting that all the other globalist leadership was at.
The people that have conquered this country through fraud and propaganda, they're brainwashing
the police. And we have it linked in Kurt Nemo's article, DHS boss praises trampling
and posse comitatus at national police confab. Yeah, trampling of the 10th Amendment as well.
And her speech as well, we're merging the federal government with the local government.
We're working together well, and we're now ready to face the number one threat, gun owners
and extremists using guns.
There are no militia patriots. You don't see it anywhere. I mean, what, there have been
a couple, I guess, of events where cops pull somebody over with warrants who says they're
a sovereign citizen and the cops get shot. I guess there have been a couple of those
events, but statistically incredibly rare.
No mass shootings at schools, but she ties it into that. And they got four TV shows now
coming out or airing in the next month where there's militias that are the new terrorists.
It's not Jack Bauer's got to torture people cuz Habib is a terrorist. Well, that's a foreign
or torture him, according to the media.
No, no, no, now it's that veteran down the street. He's a terrorist. So it's a full rollout
with military drills and checkpoints intensifying to a level we've never seen. Armored vehicles,
urban assault vehicles, huge surveillance trucks breaking into our phones, Google cars
driving around spying, Homeland Security grants.
In every major city, putting microphones and cameras in the buses and even in the cabs
with government grants to listen to you and record everything you're doing. Government
grants after the shootings for gunshot detectors that are really shotgun mics to listen to
everybody.
This is happening at an accelerated rate. Let's go to your phone calls. Scott in Vermont,
you're on the air.
Hello, Alex.
Hey, buddy.
Talk to you again. A couple quick ideas to throw at you about Tom Hartman and the Obama
phone lady. It was a great show and I tried to call in with this. My idea was that InfoWars
puts together a video exposing how Obama and our Pentagon and Leon Panetta throw that in
there about how he's admitted that Congress is basically ceremonial, showing how he's
killed over 3,000 innocent people in Pakistan and Yemen, many of them children, with the
drones.
And you can have Michelle come back and narrate the video. And in the name of the video and
at the beginning, she can announce the Obama drone and that funny voice of hers where she
did the Obama phone thing. But that and Tom Hartman, you need to get on his show or you've
had him on your show once before, I think. And you need to do that again and rip into
him about the... He's been demonizing the militia as being racist in origin and twisting
the whole meaning of the Second Amendment and the Constitution.
No, no, they all go off a PR sheet that gun owners are racist, they're gonna kill everybody.
And I'm fully aware of it. I mean, it's the same sheet of music. These guys are going
off talking points. You might as well just get the sheet and repeat it to yourself over
and over again.
Listen, I appreciate your points there. Thank you for the call. Yeah, we're gonna get a
icon of Paul Revere up at the top of infoawars.com the next day or so. It'll be a little horse
with a bullhorn, a tri-cornered hat, minute man riding a horse with a bullhorn. And you'll
click on that and it will take you to infoawars.com forward slash contest.
You've now got three months exactly today until April 30th to get your film, whether
it's a short film or long film, produced and emailed to paulrevere at infoawars.com. And
to then also print off and sign and agree to the contest rules.
And you can win $100,000 first place, but it's not about ideas for us. I'm not gonna
make the film. And I see so many people saying I wish I had a film degree. I don't have a
film degree, folks, and my films have been seen. Let's be conservative. All my films
and special reports, 600 million times. I just said that number and I can't even believe
I just said that number.
And by the way, that's conservative, 600 million times on YouTube alone. 600 million times,
the special reports, the films, all of it, conservatively. Last night I was going through
people's channels that host the show and there were hundreds of them that had a couple million
views per channel, all my stuff.
And then one of our big channels right at 300 million. And then other channels we've
got 50 million, 40 million, 20 million, 10 million, 18 million, 17 million. I mean, it's
just, it's unbelievable. 600 million is a conservative number. So what I'm doing is
I'm turning you loose and the real prize is not winning $100,000.
It's fighting the globalist. Even if you don't win, you win by getting involved. You win
by taking action. You win by resisting. And then the real prize is we're gonna hire crews
or produce crews that has produced films out of the top people. You understand that, folks?
This is a big deal. This is a big deal. This is, who is the next great documentary filmmakers?
Okay, cuz I'll be frank with you. I'm up here a lot of days till six, seven, eight at night
and then I'm working when I get home.
I'm working on the weekends. I'm not complaining about it. It's just that I don't have time.
I will not just make, and I've made some powerful films, but there are clips of this, clips
of that, clips of interviews I did, some scenery. If I ever do another film, I wanna do one
where it's full production and I really, cuz I love film, I really wanna make a powerful
cinematic film.
I'm not gonna sell wine until it's time, as Orson Welles used to say, we will sell no
wine until it's time. I got great crew making many documentaries, making great reports.
We're getting better and better. We're reaching more people. I wanna turn you loose. So go
to mfoawars.com forward slash contest and join Operation Paul Revere now. Let's go to,
I don't know how to pronounce that. Is it Bessemembra? Besimbria in Louisiana. You're
on the air, go ahead.
Hi Alex, how are you? I'm fine, thank you. Wonderful. I don't wanna get tongue tied or
get messed up here, but I just wanted to go back to chapter 12, page 225, and behold a
pale white horse. And the insert right here says, the government encouraged the manufacture
importation of military firearms for the criminals to use. This is intended to foster a feeling
of insecurity that will lead the American people to voluntary disarm themselves by passing
laws against firearms. Using drugs and hypnosis on mental patients and a process called Orion,
the CIA inculcated the desire to these people to open fire on schoolyards, thus inflame
the anti-gun lobby. This plan is well underway and so far it's working perfectly. The middle
class is beginning the government to do away with the second amendment. This book was written
in 1991, okay? The murder of Rabbi Meir Khan, the Stockton, California massacre, the school
shootings in the women's school in Canada, every one of the shooters were all mental
patients on the drug Prozac.
And then after that book was written, it was Buford Furrow, all of them, he had an address
in an Air Force base, was on drugs. About 99% of the time they're on psychotropics and
most of the time they're being handled by government psychiatrists. And yes, a bunch
of these are windup toys. They find a mentally ill person, I'm no psychiatrist. I could go
out in Austin, hypothetically, I'm not saying I'd do this, or they'll spin it and cut it
out of context.
You or I could go out and find a schizophrenic, give them all the money, drugs, whatever they
wanted and convince them to go shoot people, guaranteed. But they wouldn't do a very good
job of it, so you'd have to have somebody there dressed the same to really do the shooting,
then you shoot the schizophrenic in the back of the head.
Or they're so drugged up and you give them amnesics, like Sirhan Sirhan or the Batman
shooter of Aurora, and they won't even remember who they were.
And that's the thing, and that's what I was telling whoever answered the phone this morning.
I just started a new page through my Facebook and it's called America Fights Back. I got
a message from Facebook telling me that if I don't chill out with my tone with the stuff
that I'm posting on my page, they're gonna deactivate my account.
No, no, absolutely, ma'am, and I appreciate your call. Send us a copy of that message
to showtipsatinfoawars.com. Darren McBrain documented this, we've gotten these. We will
send out, we sent out Navy Seals Group's little meme. A meme is, again, just a little photo
with a short message.
And it was, we got Bin Laden, which itself is baloney, but we got Bin Laden and then,
or we got baloney, and then you didn't save us in Benghazi. And Facebook deleted a bunch
of accounts, suspended accounts, and told us you will not send that out. And it was
actually one of our listeners had posted it on our account and sent it out.
But yeah, yeah, mild pro second amendment. Facebook is a joke. People say, well, then
why are you on it? We're using the enemy operation, the enemy combine, the enemy system, the enemy
data relay to jack into their matrix and try to warn people inside of it. And that's what
it is, folks, this is a war.
And if I can seize their weapons systems and use them against them, I'll do it all day
long. This isn't a game. The globalists are hardcore criminals coming down on us. William,
in California, you're on the air.
Hello, Alex. Hey, buddy. Hey, wow. This is, this is fantastic. I finally get to talk to
GI Jones. I just wanted to call you and let you know what a positive impact you've had
on my life. A couple years ago, I had given up on everything, this country, my family,
everything. And I didn't believe you. I've been watching your show for about five years
now. I didn't believe anything you said. A couple of years ago, I started taking your
tangy tangerine.
I started really paying attention to the reports you do. And it's changing my life completely.
And I just wanted to let you know, I'm disabled. I've been disabled since birth. And we're
not all mind controlled drones. We're not all idiots. And I just wanted to tell you,
thank God you're here. And thank you for what you're doing.
Well, thank you, sir. That means a lot to me. Look, I became aware of this stuff as
a mainline libertarian, mainline Republican who was upset about Waco in Oklahoma City.
And then I saw all the urban warfare training, which the media said didn't exist. And I learned,
wow, the media knows this is going on and is lying.
This is a takeover because I'd read history books. I knew what a takeover looked like.
And now we're deep into the takeover. They've already robbed the accounts, the dollar, the
future. The stock market's hopped up cuz it's on cheap dollars. It's really worth about
half of what it was a decade ago.
And this is real. I mean, that's all I can say to people is very bad people are in control.
But there are good people in corporations and government who don't know what's happening.
If we give them the rest of the story, they won't be compartmentalized and this conspiracy
can't succeed.
It is vital to decompartmentalize police, military, bureaucrats, and others. But don't
just count on government. We, in the private sector, have to assault the corrupt system
with the truth. We have to be aggressive. I mean, look, if they're really putting cancer
viruses in the vaccines and deadly fluoride in the water to brain damage us, and if the
White House science czar writes books bragging about it, which he has like eco science, we
should be angry, shouldn't we?
Well, you know what? I am angry. This is a normal response. In fact, the more and more
I think about Piers Morgan, I'm so glad I was mean to him and I wish I would have been
meaner to him. Being nice has gotten us into this position. I wish I would have said more
that he was a hatchet man and a globalist front guy for eugenics.
So God bless you. Anything else you want to add?
Yeah, I completely agree. I just wanted to tell everybody I live on a $900 a month income.
I spend as much money as I can on Infowars.com. Last month I bought almost every one of your
shirts. I bought every one of your hats. Anything. I'm going to join the Paul Revere contest.
I'm going to do anything. I'm considering moving to Austin just to just to be closer
to your operation and do whatever I can.
Well, God bless you, sir. But remember, wherever you are is an important area to fight the
tyranny. And I wish people that didn't have money would not try to support us. It's the
folks out there that still have money. You better support liberty or you're going to
lose everything.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not going to want to miss this exciting message.
Here's why. Our solar generators provide life saving electrical power. And unlike gas generators,
solar generators run quietly, emit no fumes and produce electricity from the sun. So when
the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need. Now, here's the best part.
Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new. We put them
in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new. Each unit comes with
a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe. Don't wait. They go
fast. Go to scratchindentsolar.com. That's scratchindentsolar.com. For the craziest offer
we've ever made, go to scratchindentsolar.com. That's scratchindentsolar.com.
Time and time again. You need to come here and help us. We need assistance, please. Those
we should be able to depend on, let us down. Federal and state and local officials saying
help is on the way, while the folks here in Bell Harbor say show me. Don't depend on the
government to save you. Take action now so that you're prepared for the next disaster
with mypatriotsupply.com. Get the best prices on storable food, non-GMO seeds, water filtration
devices, home canning equipment, survival and self-reliance books, and more at mypatriotsupply.com.
Call 866-229-0927. We are hurting down here and we need help immediately.
More. It's time to survive. It's time to prepare. Mypatriotsupply.com. Mypatriotsupply.com.
Is 2013 your year to achieve more? More vitality, more health, more well-being? Hi, this is
Pastor Jenny. For 25 years, I spent my life's work teaching others how to achieve more.
But in 2010, I got a lesson of my own about RNA drops. I learned that there are millions
of gene switches latent in every single cell of my body that are waiting for an activator.
I learned by taking RNA drops, I can begin to activate that power in my cells and achieve
the more that I desire. I'd like to share what I discovered with you and send you a
free 30-day supply of RNA drops valued at $50 for just the cost of shipping and handling.
Go to rnafreesample.com. That's rnafreesample.com. Or call me toll-free at 888-577-3703. That's
888-577-3703. Rnafreesample.com. Discover the more that's waiting for you.
Come, you masters of war, here to build the big guns, here to build the death planes,
here to build all the bombs. The globalists say that, Chuck, Legoland,
Jabba the Hutt said is anti-Muslim. It's not meant to make sense. It's meant to get you
trained to be guilty whenever they say you're guilty, and to say, do whatever you want.
Raise my taxes, I'm not racist. Take my guns, I'm not racist. Okay, you're gonna arrest
my seven-year-old for playing with a Nerf gun in the front yard? That's reasonable.
A dad poses with a gun, a BB gun on Facebook, arrest him. We got a jury, we'll put him in
jail for something. It's not illegal to film police in public. Still, arrest everybody.
I mean, do bureaucrats and people on their little petty power trips, are you smart enough
to understand that if the globalist will invade Iraq and kill a million plus people just to
control the oil, and actually cut off the supply of it to jack up prices?
There's more than one way to make money off something. Do you think they care about you?
If the government 12 years ago stole the death benefits of the entire military, and it was
a minor footnote in the back of the newspaper, do you think they care about you? See if there's
no checks and balances for the general public, and for other people, there's not gonna be
any checks and balances for you.
There's no lobby for basic liberty. The only reason we still got guns is cuz there's a
gun lobby. And there's money to be made by select corporations off gun sales. The globalist
have always sold weapons to everybody. And so they're kind of schizophrenic on the issue
of guns, because they want total control, but they also like to sell guns.
The only reason we still got a Second Amendment is because our forebearers fought for it.
It's been tribally handed down as a tradition. And you've been active and it's something
you physically understand. You know your gun, you know your rights, so you still got it
to a certain extent. But you don't know about the 10th Amendment, so it's gone. You don't
know about the 4th, so it's gone. You don't know much about the 1st.
You know it's about freedom of speech. I'm talking to new listeners. You know it's about
freedom of religion, assembly, protest, redress of grievances. Government can make no law
respecting religion. That's why Southwestern Indians can take all the hallucinogens they
ever want and nobody can arrest them, because it's part of their religion.
You don't have to agree with it. I don't have to agree with it. But they've got freedom
of religion. So the Supreme Court ruled back in the 50s, the Hopi Indians could take peyote
because that'd been their religion for thousands of years. So how is government then regulating
churches and saying they can't be involved in politics or they can't say they're against
gun control?
That's all a hoax. It's all a giant hoax. It's all illegal to have troops on the streets.
It's all illegal to have warrantless checkpoints. And remember, I told you over and over again
that was coming and I was a kook. It didn't exist, even when I had the documents. Now
it's here. Now will you believe me about the next phase or we lose everything?
I'm gonna come back and go to more of your calls and then I'll get to that Hello Kitty
bubble gun piece we did. It's satire, but it's not really satire because it's what's
really is happening. I'm gonna get to Switzerland and some of the things that are happening
there with the Davos Forum and what the president of Iceland has done to the banksters.
Really key clip there. Big next two hours coming up. Briefly, you heard the last guy
who's disabled and he says, I support the Infowar by buying your ball caps, your t-shirts,
even though I don't have the money.
You know what? I'm gonna tell somebody like that. It's good to get a t-shirt because then
you can wear it and meet like minded people and educate folks when they ask what is Infowars.
But I'm gonna tell you, some of our biggest supporters are people who don't have anything
and we do have great products and things. So if you're gonna buy the products, buy them
from us anyways. But you know what? The middle class, the wealthy people, you're going to
lose everything if you don't start supporting the real media.
And it's up to people like that to buy 100 copies of a film and hand them out or to do
things like that. And they are supporting us. So that's how we're able to do what we
do. But be sure and support us at infowarsstore.com.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just
in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, I've gotten into a cross-section of some of the most important news, but I'm
going to drill into it more in-depth at the bottom of the hour. Then we'll continue with
calls. We're going to premiere a couple of video pieces here in a moment as well and
get into what's happening at Davos Forum. But right now, let's go ahead and talk to
more of the callers here. Let's talk to John in Texas. John, you're on the air. Welcome.
You can't have no power. Folks don't know radio is delayed like 10 seconds, so that
always happens. Or he's listening on an iPhone app or something. Hey, John, you there in
Texas, buddy? You want to talk about drones and terror?
Sorry. Yes, sir. I'm sorry about that. Somebody stopped me here.
It's okay. We don't need to have a long discussion about it. Go ahead.
Okay, yes, sir. I was going to ask you if you saw the Nova special on drones. It was
all aired about a week ago. And I just thought the way they were dehumanizing people by calling
an attack on someone over, I mean, it was in another country, but they were practicing
here. They called the attacks flashes. And I just thought they're dehumanizing people
with that.
Well, no, of course, all the terms were human resources. We're flashes. We're not even the
target. We're a flash in the pan. All of this, and then they've got Prince Harry in the news
every day. He could taste the blood. He loves to kill. It's like a game. He's such a man.
They're training us not to have empathy with each other. So that the new robot armies and
that's not just me saying that the British Ministry of Defense came out and said, yeah,
these are gonna be the robot wars.
Our tax money, it's not just in the sky. It's drone submarines, drone ships, drone tanks,
drone cars, drone trucks, drone insects. This is why government's so arrogant. But they
know our projectile weapons, cuz there's billions of us, hundreds of millions here in the US,
will be able to resist them.
They've done the actuaries. So that's why they wanna get our guns before they turn Skynet
loose on us.
Well, it was actually splash. I'm sorry, it wasn't flash. They called it a splash. And
I thought, wow, they're just dehumanizing the targets while they're sitting over there
for a little while.
I've seen the nomenclature. There's a bunch of terms they use. In fact, a lot of articles
have been written about it. Let me look up. What do they call a drone kill? I thought
it was something else entirely. Go ahead.
Yes, sir. Well, no, they were showing these young men sitting over there in their Air
Force uniforms in these little air conditioned pods. I forgot what Air Force base it was.
But they're just sitting there controlling it like a video game. And they said, oh, that's
a good splash right there. And it was a human being being blown to bits. And they actually
showed some of the videos from I think it was Iraq or Afghanistan. I'm not sure which.
But you know, Nova was just going along like, oh, yes, this is just so wonderful.
But I did have another point. I wanted to ask you if you've ever heard of a man named
Waleed Shubat.
No, I haven't.
He wrote a book called God's War on Terror. And he's a former Muslim terrorist. And anyway,
I just thought he would be a really good interview for you to have him on. He basically the conversion
that he had to Christianity was amazing. I mean, because he was a full blown I mean,
he was, you know, killing people for Islam. But you really ought to read that book God's
War on Terror.
No, I hear you. I will certainly look into it. Thank you for the call. And God bless
you, sir. Glad you got on. For TV viewers, if we punch up my search here, I typed in
autonomous drones. And you can see something new to worry about. Murderous autonomous drones.
Here's Nextgov. Autonomous drones pose no technology changes or challenges for the Navy.
US military test first autonomous drone. Folks, they've had autonomous space plane drones
in the skies since the 60s and 70s.
I mean, this is just ridiculous. But I was reading one out of England yesterday. It's
called the new tyrannous drone, which means tyranny. What a perfect name for it. Just
absolutely disgusting. And again, this cuts the military out of it so that humans can't
say no to carry on an unlawful order.
An 18 wheeler pulls up that's robot driven. The backslides down and 15 combat robots get
off the back. And they've got nerve gas. They've got weapons. They've got lasers. They've got
everything. And the globalists sit back and kill you and your family. And it's autonomous.
It's not even an operator.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now. Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog. Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom
lovers. The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse. The
globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover. That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness
items at infowarshop.com. These are items that I did research on, that I personally
use. You've got the life straw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere
you go. The Ktorr hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages
are out in the field. Strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen. When disaster
strikes by Matthew Stein. TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during
any radiological event. Hand crank shortwave AM FM radios. Everything that we've researched
and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com and your purchase makes our info war possible.
We're getting prepared. Are you? Infowarshop.com. Millions of people are going to get sick this
winter from coals, flu and other illnesses. Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with
Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum anti-bacterial solution. Recent advances
in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent
bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing. Supernatural
Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes
of many serious diseases such as stress, death, pneumonia, coals, flus and other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest
Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is
emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the
promo code silver2012 for 20% off. That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Big Brother. Mainstream media. Government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
We've got an incredible breaking story up at infowars.com right now. Washington Post
report. The new Secretary of Defense nominee Hagel warned Obama about a new world order.
Secretary of Defense nominee pointed to rogue elements within the military. Find out about
that right now at prisonplanet.com and infowars.com. We'll get to it in a moment. DHS boss trampling
a posse commentatis at National Police Confab openly says just the main threat is gun owners
and that that's what Homeland Security is for.
Chinese Communist Party mouthpiece demands Obama disarm Americans again. The official
People's Daily. That is just some of the news. US Army runs drills in Houston. They ran drills
two nights ago in Miami. This is all to condition everyone to accept martial law. Amazing photos
in this article up at infowars.com. Backfire. Seattle gun buyback turns into gun show. Collectors
waved wads of cash at those in line.
Yeah, I've seen some of the purdy shotguns that are literally worth like $10,000 apiece.
I've seen this on the news. You'll see an old woman. It's generally old women when they're
when they're old World War Two vet or Korean War vet husband dies. These poor women have
no idea these firearms. Even old 22s are worth 300 bucks. Gear rifles, 500 bucks. You'll
see him turning in carved shotguns that are worth $3,000, $5,000, $10,000.
And the cops are there salivating. That's why they constantly catch police. You see
it in the news all the time. Shelling gun buyback guns. I'm not for police corruption.
In fact, I hate it. But let me tell you something. I don't blame them. I mean, you're gonna turn
over like an AR-15 that's worth $2,000 to be run over by a steamroller? You're gonna
turn over a purdy $10,000 shotgun because some idiot came and got $100 or a $50 gift
card for it?
I mean, man, I watched those videos of them melting down and steamrolling those guns.
It makes me sick. They are so valuable. And people paid money for those. And I've checked
the MO. A few years ago, Austinites, we ought to find the clip. What's old is new and add
it to this article. Austinites went out. Memory serves, I think it was that guy named John
Bush.
And he's got what, Texas for Accountable Government. I think that, if memory serves that's who
did it. They went out and would try to buy the guns back and actually did. And the police
go, we don't like it, but it's legal if it's a private sale.
Just amazing photos up there. And just extremely painful to watch. Now, a lot of margins total
junker guns that don't even work and people are just getting $100 or whatever. But still,
it's to create the image of guns being handed in.
Yeah, there it is. First ever Austinites outbid police in gun buyback counter program. That
was in February of 2011, so a while back. All right, ladies and gentlemen, now let's
continue here with some of the other news that is coming up.
We're gonna get into five year old girl suspended for terroristic threat to shoot classmates
with pink bubble. We're gonna do that here in just a moment. But first off, let me give
you the toll free number to join us, 800-259-9231. Now, you see the reports every day where somebody's
playing with a Nerf gun in their front yard and the police are called.
A pink, orange, blue, bright colored guns, yellow, orange, you name it. My kids have
all got them. Your children have them probably. Or you read about a kid says bang bang with
their fingers and then the SWAT team comes. Or every day or two, someone talks about,
hey, let's go play with our Nerf guns after school.
And the SWAT team is called and everybody panics. This is the hysteria. People aren't
panicking over going to the hospital where 190 something thousand die a year from infections,
close to 200,000 die from bad drug interactions. 40 something thousand die from car wrecks.
What is it, like 400 and something thousand from alcohol abuse? No, no, all those real
things that are dangerous, huge numbers die from falling and hitting their head in the
shower, dying in the pool.
The pool is, last time I checked, I forget, it's just astronomically more dangerous than
guns in your house. A pool is like super deadly, better have a fence around it. Cuz your little
kids out there, even they're a good swimmer, they fall, hit their head, they're dead. You
pull in from work, your child's dead. A creek behind your house, good way to die, but still
I'm not saying don't live by a creek, I do, it's a good way to die.
That creek behind my house is, you can pull up the numbers. I wanna say it's something
like 70 something times more dangerous than a gun in the house. The point is, it's all
in the world almanac, you can look up these numbers. Being near a water source that's
deeper than a foot deep, people die all the time hitting their head and falling in a puddle.
They are super deadly. The point is, it's total and complete absolute hysteria. FBI
crime statistics gathered from 18,000 jurisdictions, 49% drop in violent crime since 1991. 49%
drop, 21 points of that has accelerated since 07. We've done the official breakdowns, our
videos are up at infoawards.com.
It's called the gun statistics Obama doesn't want you to see. We show fbi.gov, we crack
the numbers right there, what they don't want you to know. So you'd think they'd be, hey,
look, more guns, less crime, no, no, no. They have such hysteria now that you are not allowed
to play dodgeball because it's aggressive, you're not allowed to jog or wrestle during
recess.
Now you're not allowed to even shake hands at most government training centers. These
are the equivalent of medium security presence. And then there's this article, this article
up on infoawards.com from last week. Five-year-old girl suspended for terroristic threat to shoot
classmates with pink bubble gun, with pink bubble gun, with pink bubble gun.
And the little girls said after school we ought to get our bubble projectors. And I've
actually bought these for party favors for one of my daughters when they're friends at
a party. And the girl was brought in three different times with police, was expelled,
and they called it terrorism.
Okay, this is the reality. And now there's a new article that's red linked that just
went up. This is not the one last week. This is the new one this week. Discussion about
toy nerf gun causes lockdown at Bronx Elementary School. What did the Attorney General say?
He goes, we need to demonize guns where people have a phobia of them, literally brainwash
people against guns.
And they know kids are getting into these nerf guns. We have great wars with them all
the time. The only problem with the nerf guns is they break so easily. It's talking
about planned obsolescence to rip you off. Probably about ten of these things for each
child in the last five, six years cuz they're constantly breaking.
The point is, is they have a lot of really fun systems. We play laser tag too. And their
friends come over and play laser tag in the backyard. This is such a hysteria that they're
now pressuring retailers not to sell these. They're now saying, my gosh, the symbol of
a gun.
And they've done this in areas of Europe. They banned toy guns, then they banned the
real guns. Many jurisdictions in the US have actually banned BB guns because there's no
lobby to protect BB guns in the jurisdiction, but guns are legal. You see, cuz there's no
lobby to defend them.
This is a new case. Discussion about toy nerf gun causes lockdown at Bronx Elementary School.
Hysteria, police with assault rifles, helicopters, hunted for non-existent object as parents
panicked. It's always been their plan to get your kids, get them in a public school, have
mass shooter drills, stage mass shootings, provocateur mass shootings, hype up mass shootings
for copycats, and then just create absolute hysteria and fear.
Where you see it all the time where some guy puts his deer rifle in the back of his car,
even in rural areas to go shooting, and somebody driving by sees a gun being put in the trunk.
I mean, that's why no one dare put a gun in their gun rack. You'd be swatting so fast
your head would spin. See how they've conditioned us to, let's hide our guns, while they sit
there and operate and imply that guns are totally illegal.
A discussion between two children about a toy nerf gun caused a lockdown and a massive
armed police response as two elementary schools in the Bronx today. And yet another example
of how hysteria is sweeping American education system in the aftermath of Sandy Hook shooting.
That's artificial hysteria.
Parents rushed to two schools in Fulton Avenue and East 174th Street. And CNN had it and
it wasn't happening again, again, a way to reconjure the fear. Like when a gas main blows
up or a steam main in New York, they shut down half the city and earn fear. Today, after
heavily armed police were called to reports of a gun on campus.
The alarm was caused by a campus aide overhearing a student say something about a gun. It's
the word gun, except government's armed, black uniforms, helicopters, Delta Force raids,
checkpoints, open borders, 57,000 dead, hundreds of heads chopped off a year in Texas and Arizona,
mass death killing. That's no issue, don't worry about a real crisis, killed more people
than died in the ten years of Vietnam, just the last five and a half, six years.
No, no, no, we're gonna skip this network break, cuz I gotta have time to play this
piece and then go to your calls. All of this is going on, all of this is happening. And
it is clear, total, and complete mind control. That's what it is. And that's why, in fact,
I'm gonna do a piece on it.
Will somebody grab me that Lego over there? I can't get to it, thank you, it's right there.
Last week, the Turkish Association of Austria, yeah, it's just right there in the corner.
The door's locked again, I'm gonna have a lock taken off that door, I'm not locking
it. I don't know what keeps happening, but whatever. Anyways, getting back to what I
was breaking down here, they came out and said the Jabba the Hutt is supposed to be
an Arab and is racist.
And there's talk of suing Lego and the Austrian government's very concerned. You go, well,
that's ridiculous. Jabba the Hutt has nothing to do with Arabs and Legos, I mean, what is
this? Or Muslims. It's about, hey, if you don't give your guns up, you're a racist.
You're like, well, I guess I'm not a racist, here's my guns. It's meant to be asinine,
it's meant to be over the top, it's meant to be ridiculous, it's meant to be out of
control, it's meant to be ridiculously sickening.
It's meant to just absolutely get you to do whatever ridiculous order you're told. In
fact, they phased this out because it's sub-politically incorrect. But the Marine Corps, what you
see in films like Full Metal Jacket, most of that was impromptu cuz the guy they hired
to play the drill instructor really was a drill instructor, and in the Marines as well.
And so grabbing their genitals, marching around for an hour, basically masturbating or getting
close to it, saying this is my rifle, this is my gun, this is for fighting, this is for
fun. And sleeping with their rifles, giving it a woman's name, and basically telling them,
you're supposed to, I only wanna get into the secrets of the Marine Corps, it's pretty
weird.
And a lot of it's been phased out the last 20 years. The point is, is it was meant to
be done to just, people didn't wanna do it. They said, listen, you're gonna hump on your
rifle or you're not in the Marine Corps. You're gonna do what you're told, is that clear scumbag?
And if we tell you to go beat people up, we're gonna do it. In the old days of the Marine
Corps, people who didn't play ball, you didn't get beat up with soap, folks, they killed
you.
They'd send you out going over a gorge or something, and they just cut the rope, and
then everybody would be part of the blood cement, the cover up of killing the person
that gave people problems. That's the real Marine Corps, folks. You know why the Marine
Corps has been known worldwide for being so tough, and why even the Nazis feared them?
The Nazis killed people in training too, because that's what you did. The devil dogs killed
people in training. People died in every class generally, okay? You can actually go look
it up historically, it's been leaked.
But anyways, I'm digressing. This whole thing is about mind control. If I tell you to get
your rifle and to start rolling around in bed with it, you're gonna do it, is that clear?
Okay? And it's the same thing. If I tell you you're going to jail or the SWAT team's coming
because you drew a picture of a gun, or you said the word gun, you're gonna happen.
You're not gonna have a Hello Kitty bubble gun. Do you understand that? Do you get that
through your stinking head, is that clear? Do you get that through your head? If we tell
you to walk around in a circle for an hour grabbing your genitals with other men, you're
going to do it, is that clear?
The ancients would say, you will give us your child to be sacrificed. Every culture, the
Druids, the Aztecs, the Babylonians, all cultures, the Greeks had human sacrifice. Most are subcultures
in city states. When you're ordered to kill people, you're gonna do it. And what's the
ultimate thing government can demand?
Give us your first born to be chopped open, to be burned in a fire, to be put inside a
wicker man and burned. The priest class had such control in most cultures, they would
routinely demand a prince be killed or even the king be killed. And again, I know this
all sounds wild, history is wild, history is crazy. Full metal jacket with them walking
around sleeping with their M14, with them grabbing their genitals.
That's what goes on and then some. And again, you're like, well, that's ridiculous. No,
it's about doing what you're told, following orders no matter what it is. Training the
men that if a hand grenade gets thrown, whoever's closest to it jumps on it, so that the rest
of the unit lives. You're like, well, that's suicide. That's kamikaze. Exactly, ladies
and gentlemen, it's total programming.
And the whole culture is a giant reeducation camp. Now here's the piece, if you wanna see
the video as a radio listener, it's up at infoawars.com. We put out an earlier piece
with this last week and people said, they're not sending police for bubble guns. This is
based on true stories. This piece put together by the crew, we did this in one take live
and then added Melissa Melton's comments to the beginning of it. Along with clips of real
newscast where people are getting arrested or detained or expelled for toy guns.
Here it is. Citizens of the homeland. We here at the ministry apologize for the disturbing
footage you are about to see. The extremist Alec Jones has been permanently detained under
the NDAA for an armed rampage with a bubble gun. Such behavior will not be tolerated.
Citizens everywhere are vigilantly reporting other criminals and their terroristic weapons,
such as plastic toy guns, guns drawn by hand on paper. And yes, even the vicious Hello
Kitty bubble gun. Should you see children so armed, be sure to report them and their
parents to the homeland for immediate rendition and reeducation.
Remember citizens, the founding fathers were pig enemies of the state. The people are the
true threat. Government force is freedom. We must thank God for the superstate and do
not worry as we have armed ourselves with over 1.6 billion bullets, fully automatic
weapons and armored checkpoints. The homeland is here to keep you safe. Trust no one else.
Soon we will be one absorbed into the great collective until they continue to be vigilant.
And if you see something, say something. We bring you now this graphic footage of Alex
Jones bubble gun rampage in its entirety. This is Melissa Melton with the Department
of Homeland Security out. Hi, I'm Janet Napolitano, Secretary of the
Department of Homeland Security. Homeland Security begins with hometown security.
You're rolling? Yeah.
Okay. I want to thank everybody for coming here for the staff meeting. Alex will be joining
us in just a few minutes. I'd like to thank my new assistant, Rob Dougal, who's been demoted
for this purpose. Now I have a few stories I'd like to go over, but first, Darren McBreen,
what do you have there? Well, it's kind of interesting that the Chinese
government recommends that our government starts confiscating-
Hold on, I'm sorry I'm late. Look at this. Alex, check it out, man. We've got that office
party and, you know, I gave presents to all the kids at the Christmas party. I think that
office party is coming up. I'm thinking we'll have these as party papers. Check this out.
The bubble touches me. You're going to be arrested for assault. Do you understand me?
Bubbles. Alex, I have this article right here. That's
a bubble gun. A five-year-old girl was suspended after a terroristic threat when she brought
a pink bubble gun, just like that. Was this the weapon of choice for a new kind
of terrorist? Terror by bubbles. The small pink Hello Kitty toy gun is an automatic bubble
blower. But just days ago, when a five-year-old girl said she and a classmate should shoot
each other with bubbles, the school called it a terrorist threat.
What is this, a prank or something? Or someone's going to be having a meeting.
That's a bubble gun. You can't have that stuff, Alex.
Is that a spooky? You can't bring that around, Alex.
That is a fully automatic bubble gun. Listen, Jigar, I know you're joking. There's
no story. All right, look, Alex, hold on, hold on. Let
me talk to Melissa. Melissa, what's going on? I don't know what's going on.
That's a bubble gun. They were almost arrested in elementary school
girl last week for having a paper gun in school. Well, Thomas, this is all about a fifth grader
that brought a piece of paper to class that many say looked like a gun. And it's what
happened next that has her family crying foul. She pulled out a paper gun last week and says
an administrator scolded her in front of the class. Her mom says staff even searched her
with other kids watching the whole time. That's that's what is this about a bubble
gun? The have a kitty thing? Yes. I thought that was a joke. It's not a joke.
This is not a joke. Terroristic threat. The school took this so seriously that administrators
even ordered that the five year old receive a psychological evaluation.
Alex, I'm not going to be subjected to this. It's a detergent. Come on, it's a bubble gun.
If that detergent gets in my eye, I'm in. That's assault. Turn it off, turn it off.
It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. We're going to back that up because we have real
clips of cops where people have bubbles and flowers about peace and love. And the cops
are like, if that touches us, you're going to jail for assault with detergent.
And even some of the cops are laughing. I mean, it's just this mental illness where
the public's bad, the government's good. And so we're actually reenacting what now happens
in America, where I have a bubble gun and everyone is just shaking in fear. Again, you
shake in fear at bubble gums. But whenever black helicopters come out of the sky or there's
a checkpoint, now that's freedom.
You're supposed to be scared of that. That's North Korea. But no, that's a good thing.
But citizens with a bubble gun or a Nerf gun, save me, government. Let's go back to the
clip touches me.
I have a bubble gun. A five year old girl was suspended after a terroristic threat when
she brought a pink bubble gun just like that.
Was this the weapon of choice for a new kind of terrorists? Terror by bubbles. The small
pink Hello Kitty toy gun is an automatic bubble blower. But just days ago, when a five year
old girl said she and a classmate should shoot each other with bubbles, a terrorist threat.
That's about half the report. The end is really the best part, but it's really visual. So
if you're a radio listener, go to info wars dot com. It's in the tiles up there. Man goes
on bubble gum rampage caught on tape. And you can see where they call 911 on me, which
really goes on in the real world.
We're illustrating this, reenacting it for the vicious bubble gun. But foreign banks
running things and saying they're gonna kill the dollar. That's not a threat. Bubble guns.
That's the real threat. Don't be worried about big government. Our founders said be worried
about it. They were bad.
We're on the march. The Empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
Heck of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die. Start purifying your water with propure. My friends, I've done
a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is propure and it's available
discounted at info wars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth. There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95% easy to set
up and use doesn't require electricity purify water from lakes, streams, ponds and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals which is key save money by not buying bottled
water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic propure is the best gravity fed filter
out there.
It's what my family uses info wars.com already has the lowest price on propure but if you
add the promo code water at checkout, you get an additional 10% off and info wars.com
you can also call to order 888-253-3139.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben soap company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Seema camps now being expanded nationwide. This documentary exposes how the continuity
of government program has established an all powerful shadow state. Police state four chronicles
the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen. Prepare to enter the secretive
world of emergency dictatorship, body scammers, sound cannons, citizen spies, stage terror
and cameras on every street corner. It's only the beginning of the new world order's hellish
plan. The police state isn't coming. It's here. Secure your copy today at infowars.com
or see it online in the highest quality at prisonplanet.tv.
You've heard it here. I'm on television so everybody knows it. I believe in the Second
Amendment. I believe in people's lawful right to bear arms. We're going to find the people
who are doing this, take them out and shoot them. No. You take them out, they are traitors
in this country and shoot them. Shoot them dead. I'll pay for the bullet. Challenge
Alex Jones to a boxing match. Show up with a semi-automatic that you got legally and
pop them. I'd love to see that. In uniform. I will not take your shotgun away. I will
not take your rifle away. I won't take your handgun away. Mr. and Mrs. America, turn them
all in. We are back. I am your host, Alex Jones. Thank you so much for joining us. Okay,
let's race through a bunch of your calls right now. Then I'll get to the top story at infowars.com.
Washington Post reporter Hagel warned Obama about New World Order. Secretary of Defense
nominee pointed to rogue elements within the military. So again, they call a New World
Order anything that isn't their system. They want a new system of global government. They
call that a New World Order.
Then Ahmadinejad says, I want a Muslim New World Order, a Shiite New World Order. And
then the Saudis say we want a Wahhabist New World Order. Putin says he wants a Russian
centric New World Order. The communist Chinese say we want a Chinese New World Order. Well,
now they're worried that the military can't be trusted. Remember Panetta? I think I'm
gonna have Steve add this to his article.
Panetta last year wouldn't go to bases around even US officers if they had weapons. Never
in US history has the Secretary of Defense or a top general not wanted to be around the
troops with guns. A little bit in Vietnam, some of the mid-level officers started really
getting concerned with something they could do about being fragged. Wow, just incredible.
We're gonna be getting to that. It's all overwhelming here. We're gonna have news blitz in the third
hour coming up as well.
Right now, let's go to, how do you pronounce that? Reginaldo? Reginaldo. You know what's
happening? I've always had 2015 vision. Undoubtedly, when we move that screen all the way to the
end of the wall, I just can't read it anymore.
So I need to, we've talked about this before. I need a bigger television set with the collars
on it. Cuz see, I could run the collars myself and sit here and hit the buttons, but then
that gets distracting. But it almost gets more distracting if I'm not. Maybe I should
just have the computer put in the front of the table here, like regular radio, and then
I go to the calls right here cuz, or I could unplug that monitor and then that would make
us get a big TV in there.
I don't know. Who did you say it was again? Reginald in Tennessee, you're on the air,
go ahead.
Hello, my name is actually Reginald Cook. And I would like to speak to you about some
of the things you've mentioned because I studied as a barrister in, I suppose you can tell
I'm not actually from Tennessee. Can you guess where I'm from?
I can guess that you're from Britannia.
Well how did you know?
Sounds like your voice, it sounds like a fake accent, buddy.
That's not actually. I'm actually from Sussex. But I've been in the States for 10 years.
Well welcome, welcome, welcome. What's on your mind today?
Well, the thing is, I don't agree with everything you say, but I do agree with certain aspects
of it. That would be that certain peoples are trying to manipulate governments and market
them.
No, no, there's no special interests. That's another conspiracy, there is.
Well unfortunately, I've seen laws change. You see, as I said, I studied to be a barrister,
a lawyer.
Well don't worry, once we turn our guns in, the government's gonna take real good care
of us. They're good people.
This is not what happened in England, actually.
Ah, I'm sorry, go ahead.
Anyway, well the part I disagree with is, of course I understand it, you're an American.
I don't really disapprove of aristocracy and monarchy. I'm a monarchist, sorry. I've actually
met a nice aristocrat as well. Mainly the problem is-
Did they pat you on the head?
No, actually. Why would they do that?
I don't know, that's what happens to lap dogs.
I'm not a lap dog.
All right, I'm gonna stop being mean to you. Look, I get the argument, take UKIP, pro-sovereignty,
anti-new world order, they're royalist. So I can take the little bit of bad with all
the good, because they understand the EU is setting itself up as a new royalty.
They'd rather have the old vestigial monarchy, because at least people think it's British,
and then have some feeling of patriotism, some basic nationalism. So I actually get
the subtleties of all of that. It's just that at the heart of so much of the new world order
we see being pushed, is the Transylvanian royalty that you've got perched over there
in London.
It's not actually Transylvanian, it's actually a German family. But at the same time, there
is British as anyone else that moved to Britain 200 years ago. But that's not the way I called
in. The point is, I think that, and like I said, the accent's a little-
You know the German house they hail out of is originally Transylvanian.
Actually, it's kind of more mixed than that.
Well, it is mixed, but I mean, one of their oldest bloodlines is Transylvanian, and that's
the one Prince Charles says he's most proud of. He says he's Transylvanian in news articles,
and you know he's moved there, and then runs around in the woods.
On the other hand, I have descended from the Stewarts, so I wouldn't concern myself too
much.
Ah, you are a royal.
No, no, because they were kicked out.
So you like Henry VIII?
No, that's the Tudors.
The Stewarts, the Tudors, the Pooters, go ahead.
The point is, I came to America, actually it was 10 years ago, it's not recent, largely
because I saw certain changes in law. And those changes weren't based on traditional
monarchy, they weren't based on traditional British common law, the regular law. They
were based on something I started learning in college.
Called Admiralty Law or Administrative Law, and that's what Tony Blair said in like 1997.
He said, we're gonna quote, get rid of Magna Carta.
What's more than the Magna Carta, they don't even like the monarchy, they don't like anything
traditionally British.
No, cuz that's because they're gonna be the new royalty.
Let me get to the point, please. This is the important part. They don't like people being
British in Britain.
I agree.
They don't like people being American in America. Because, and if I can play the villain for
just a moment, if you don't mind.
No, please do.
Okay, it's very simple. And Stalin even had this done. If I can get you to hate America,
because America's done bad things, and let's be honest, it has done bad things. Every country
in the world has. In fact, individual people have done bad things.
America has peed in the bed.
Yes, so all I have to do is get you to focus on those bad things. In fact, you can do this
on an individual level. And people do this when they reprogram people, when they capture
them in wars.
You see, I don't want you to like yourself. I want you to realize that you're a bad person,
but I can make you good by doing-
No, that's what all this is about. The Homeland Security, the TSA, the Hello Kitty guns being
evil.
It's we're bad, government's good, and you're right. The globalists say they wanna get rid
of all national identity. And even if the British monarchy is parasitic, it is still
a vestigial sign of old sovereignty and must be removed. And I absolutely agree with what
you're saying on that front. You are right.
Because that's sort of the thing. The one thing though, I don't think it's a specific
conspiracy so much as these people actually believe they're helping the world evolve.
It's part of the 19th century progressivist idea. It came out of the 19th century-
Well, no, no, no. They always sell the progressivist idea to get well-meaning people to join them
and empower the inner conspiracy. But if you read the different programs, just intelligence
documents, I don't have to read Illuminati documents that have been made public over
the last 200 years, 200 plus years with people being killed by bolts of lightning or delivering
manuscripts and things like that in Germany. We know that always there's a good claim to
get the good guys on your side.
You wanna keep your friends close, your enemies closer. And so the power structure surrounds
itself with a bunch of people that actually mean well and go out and work for the cover
story. But I'll assure you, the people running this wanna get rid of national sovereignty,
transfer that power to offshore mega systems that have their own global military.
And then they want that, all the nuclear weapons gathered up, so there won't be a big nuclear
war when they release the bio weapon that kills 99% of people. See, they tell their
minions, we're only gonna kill 80%. You and your family may be able to live. They've had
professors talk about this. I hope I work hard enough for the Earth and that I may be
allowed to live when they release the airborne Ebola.
That's the UT professor talking about that and the FBI wouldn't visit him. But the point
is that, and then higher levels, 90% will be killed. And then higher level, it's no,
5% will live. At the highest levels, they talk about killing everyone. And then the
last globalist will merge with the mega computer and become God.
Now I'm not saying that's gonna actually happen. But do you think two New World Order Skeksis
up in their ivory tower, if they actually succeed in this program, merging with cybernetic
systems are not gonna kill each other? I mean, do you really think that?
Well, actually what I really think is that most of what you're seeing comes from H.G.
Wells and Bertrand Russell.
Yep, that's right. They all wrote about it.
I only heard of you three months ago, so I have no idea if you've even covered this or
not. But if you look at the history, when I say progressive, I don't mean the modern,
what came in America around the 20s, I think, 30s. I'm talking about the old 19th century
progressives.
You're getting out of your accent. Listen, I gotta jump. You're an interesting call,
but I promise to get to other people. That's why it's hard to go to calls. They're all
interesting. Oh, boy. We're in so much trouble. I mean, I go look at the general public. They
just go to their job. They just wanna go home and watch TV and drink beer. And I don't blame
you. But you are under attack. Your kids are under attack.
And I just can't believe that it doesn't wake everybody up that the media said there's no
world government, no black helicopters, no TSA checkpoints. I've got articles here I
haven't even gotten to yet. And again, I was aware of this. It's like I'm constantly reminded
by tyranny that I had just forgotten about.
And that's what's so frustrating, is that today I went up to infowars.com this morning
and saw Washington's blog linked up there. And he had boiled down Wall Street Journal.
Let me just actually get the article. Wall Street Journal with quotes. That's why I like
Washington's blog, cuz he adds a bunch of footnotes to it. He's got 15 mainstream and
government announcements. Wall Street Journal, Counterpunch, house.gov with the bill, and
the article's up at infowars.com.
Government to dispose of radioactive waste by putting it in your silverware. Now, 60-something
years ago, they had all this deadly fluoride sitting around. They were at the store. They
had big spills of it that killed entire rivers in Tennessee. It's well known. They're at
the nuclear plants.
So they just started, cuz it's used in the purification of uranium. They just started
putting it in the water. It's all a big joke to the establishment. You go to any elitist
house or read any globalist publication, or they have articles about the Communist Chinese
Party only drinks purified water. They got caught with giant secret farms, where they
can grow stuff in greenhouses cuz of what's falling on the food.
I mean, they ship in dirt from other countries and grow it in greenhouses and have trucks
that follow the elite around and jet aircraft just like the Rockefellers, not to eat what
you're eating and not to drink it while they're telling you, it's good for you. Never mind
all the studies that's gonna do this to you.
Now they wanna take the uranium, which I remember learning like ten years ago, they put depleted
uranium in rebar now. They put it in quick-set concrete. I mean, we're just, folks, it's
so far gone right now. The Chinese executed government officials who got caught going
along with bribes to put melamine in powdered milk.
Here the FDA came out with four years ago during the scandal and said, you know what?
Melamine's not bad for you. When your kids die of kidney failure, they just put them
on dialysis and they're not even gonna do a test to see what's in their kidneys. Now,
if you fed your kid melamine consciously, the cops would put you in jail for life.
But as long as it's from the store, it's okay. And why shouldn't they put radioactive waste
in the utensils you eat off of, which they admit gives you a lot of trace amounts of
it. And they got all this, they tried to pass this twice already in the last decade and
all that's linked to this.
I could spend all day on this one article, and I've got hundreds here. And what was the
other point I wanted to make about this? Yeah, just like it's been well known for 50 something
years that where they get this fluoride, the main fluoride they use isn't just from aluminum
or plutonium purification.
It's from, but you mind them, the uranium out of the limestone deposits that actually
has the phosphates. But the good phosphate goes to be on the cornfield or whatever, the
wheat field, the maize field, the canola field, whatever the case is. The bad phosphate they
can't sell goes in your water.
What else is in the phosphate? Where they mine it. That's why you also get the same
stuff they put in your water from a uranium purification facility that you get from a
phosphate fertilizer facility. Because it's the same, you mine uranium out of limestone.
That's where you get it in Colorado and Florida and other areas.
So here's the fun part about it. They just put it in the water. And it's an absolute
fact. I mean, I saw numbers, you can pull them up depending on which study, about kidney
and also bladder cancer from this. And hey, you know what? We're animals, we're scum,
so we're gonna be killed, globalist or boss.
And I'm a bad man for even telling you about it. I'm sorry I'm an extremist, you're right.
The national talk show host I heard yesterday, so-called liberal, talking about how I imagine
black helicopters in a private solar reserve. You're right, you're right. They're not putting
uranium and plutonium and radon and all that.
You know what, you're right, you're right, you know what? You're right, everything's
fine. Just enjoy your camp. I mean, they're killing us, folks, and they're crazy. The
elite were crazy 50 years ago, but they didn't try to put uranium and plutonium in your stinking
spoons. I mean, and if they can get away with that, they can get away with expelling your
kids for talking about a Hello Kitty bubble projector. Why not?
Darryl and Tennessee are on the air, go ahead.
Good afternoon to you, Alex.
How you doing, buddy?
I'm doing fine. First time caller, long time listener. I am tired of the United States
government infringing our Second Amendment. Because of that, I started a petition on the
White House website. And that's the saying we demand that any infringement of our Second
Amendment be an immediate impeachable offense with absolutely no exceptions.
I agree, Walter Jones, it's time to start the impeachment. Where is the impeachment?
It should be started now. The minute Dianne Feinstein introduced a bill saying Congress
can keep their guns, but we can't. That violates Article 1, Section 9, Clause 8, and a bunch
of others, unjust weights and measures. She should be immediately impeached. I mean, what
else won't we put up with?
I mean, it's almost like we put up with uranium in our water. I guess we do.
Exactly. Well, I have almost 3,000 signatures. I need another 97,000. So we have until February
22nd to try to get a-
Well, great job. Tell us the name of it.
We the people of the United States demand any infringement of our Second Amendment to
be an impeachable offense.
Yeah, great job. We'll get behind that. We've got our own petition coming out. It just got
filed. It's gonna be posted at infowars.com. Wait till you hear about this. We'll tell
you about it on the other side.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book Cancer Step Outside the Box.
I want you to know some very important information. In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested
that Carnivora be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the President could
obtain this world-class healer. Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around
the world to keep people healthy. Now, you can protect yourself and your loved ones in
this age of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal
cells only without harming a single normal cell. If you want to stay healthy, now's your
chance to literally wake up your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that
don't belong in your body. Call 1-866-VenusFly or order from Carnivora.com. That's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VenusFly or visit Carnivora.com. Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
In the U.S., one in every 50 homes will have a break in this year. Burglars call it smash
and grab. Police call it robbery. We call it avoidable. We are Fake TV, a simple electronic
device that can fool even professional burglars. Fake TV easily plugs into any outlet and simulates
the changing colors of a television. To a burglar, it looks like someone must be home
watching TV, so they'll likely move on to an easier target. At only $34.95, Fake TV
costs less than a month of most alarm monitoring plants, and it's perfect if you're traveling
or away from home. Order your Fake TV by calling 877-5FAKETV or go to Faketv.com. That's 877-532-5388
or Faketv.com. Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration. As an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years and serving thousands of
satisfied customers, the Berkey guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration
systems. The Berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable
black purification elements that purify water by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria,
cysts and parasites to non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides
and pesticides. Order the Berkey light system today, complete with two black Berkey elements
for only $231, and the Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge. With the purchase
of a Berkey light, the Berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride and arsenic filters
for only $39.99. That's over 30% off the retail price. Call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653.
That's 1-877-886-3653. Or order online at GoBerkey.com. That's GoBerkey.com today.
All right, here's the deal. We always have a jam-packed third hour, but I have got to
start the third hour and take 20 phone calls in the first 30 minutes, or I am going to
tell Chris in there to put a shock collar on me and basically send me to Gitmo. I want
to take a bunch of your calls, rapid fire. We're going to do that. We've already taken
quite a few today. Then I'm going to get into the communist Chinese government again through
their People's Daily is saying take the American people's guns. A lot of other very, very important
news on that front. And we're going to get to some other special reports. Just a whole
host of issues on the economy. I need to talk about the economy and what's really happening
with the stock market on that front. But I wanted to bring Richard Reeves in here. Richard,
of course, you've seen co-host the show before, who's been a talk show host for about 10 years.
He works here in the office heading up InfowarsHealth.com and really testing and talking to the crew
and other people about which of the 300, 400, whatever it is, the longevity products we
think are the very best.
The problem is there are so many that are really amazing. And I've been on a few of
the products. Aaron's been on about 10 of them and lost 97 pounds and just had a total
transformation. We're now launching a whole program today where Richard's going to make
sure I take all my longevity and do all this. So we'll see what happens with that. I did
it about a year ago for about six months religiously and had amazing effects. Kind of ended up working
18 hours a day again and getting off some of it. We're going back on it. So Richard,
once a week will pop in with us with some of the new products, but also some of the
old products at InfowarsHealth.com. And Richard, in the few minutes we've got, tell us about
some of the products.
Well when talking about some of the old products, I remember back in January 2011 when you had
Doc Wallach on for the first time, talking about Young Jody. And that's when I basically
started every month without fail ordering a Healthy Start Pack or a version of the Healthy
Start Pack. They've got the Healthy Start Pack with the digestive additional ingredients.
They've got the brain and heart. They've also got the Healthy Blood Sugar Pack. So bare
minimum, in my opinion, if you're interested in being prepared for what's coming up, if
our guns get taken away and really the stuff hits the fan, being healthy and prepared is
a big part of it.
The hospitals are killing people now. I mean, we have the worst health in the world. It's
time for all of us to get healthy. It doesn't mean any of us are perfect because everybody's
working hard, but we've got to all try.
That's it. Yeah, we're all working too many hours. We're all overstressed. So the Healthy
Start Pack, bare minimum. But one of the new products that everybody here at the office
really loves, and I know you like it too, is that Root Beer Belly.
I've taken a lot of probiotics. This one has a dramatic. I mean, it really works.
Well, that's great. And the microencapsulation is one of the biggest differences that the
Root Beer Belly has. The probiotics, the good bacteria for your gut is microencapsulated
in this product. And that way, it has a better opportunity to make it through your digestive.
It makes it through the stomach acid.
Through the stomach acid, exactly, to get down in your intestines where it can do the
work that it needs to do. So this is a really good product. The kids like it. It's tasty.
You just sprinkle it on your tongue and then swallow it. It does taste like Root Beer.
And that's why it's called Root Beer Belly. And it's really great. Here's one of the brochures
for it. But the people here at the office, just unanimously, I had a little box like
this open there in my office.
Everybody's always raiding my supplies.
I invited them. Well, I
I'm just teasing.
Well, for that purpose, I actually ordered some extra.
And there's also the Polymer's Plus that I've endorsed.
Right. The Polymer's Plus is the best sports drink, energy drink out there. Totally healthy
with all the B vitamins, the rest of it. The essential fatty acids complex that Wallach's
put out and so many other products at Infowarshealth.com. Tell folks about that little baby right there.
That's what's getting the rave reviews from the tens of thousands of people that shop
at Infowarshealth.com.
That's right, folks. This is called ASAP. It's an acronym for As Slim As Possible. And folks
are really having great success on that. I'm hoping to finally get Alex on this product.
I've been mentioning it to him for two, three months here, but I think finally we're going
to be able to get Alex going on it. And it helps you. It has protein fractions and amino
acids that help support the release of adipose fat. And it really helps you lose weight.
We've had some people.
People can find out more or call and get their questions answered. The phone numbers are
on the site. Infowarshealth.com. We'll be back.
You are listening to GCN. Visit GCNlive.com today.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health. At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver-based products. Our most popular silver-based products are
the 32-ounce nano-silver solutions, our 2-ounce nano-silver nasal applicators, as well as
our all-natural silver soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver
gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver
at the surface. But rather, we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin-nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the
silver more effectively. Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver-based
products are best for you. That's www.silverlungs.com.
Aging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. Big brother, mainstream
media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does he. He's Alex Jones on the
GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, I'm going to your calls in the next segment. That's eight minutes away. We're
going to go to James, John, Brian, Joseph, John and others. I appreciate you holding.
We're going to go fast to your calls, I promise, and then a blitz of news. But I wanted to
get Richard in here for like three minutes once a week just to plug some of the different
products we never talk about at Infowarshealth.com, because these are the best products we put
in one place. You can get discounts there when you sign up to be a distributor. It's
a great business opportunity as well, Infowarsteam.com. But at the same time, I mean, this is the
big group. This is the, it's why I never really endorse vitamins and minerals until I found
these folks, because they know what they're talking about.
And now they went and got a big Clemson University study that they've been talking about doing,
they've been, you know, researching the last year. Tell people what they found just on
the colon cancer certified by a major university. This is Breakthrough.
This is Breakthrough. I tell you, folks, I cannot stress how really important this is.
But here is from a press release, this release a couple days ago, this Beyond Tang Tendering
and Ultimate Classic were administered to healthy human colon cells. There was no significant
death of healthy human cells compared to cancerous colon cells. Ultimate Classic killed 95% of
cancerous colon cells, 65% of cancerous liver cells, 65% of cancerous stomach cells, and
30% of cancerous breast cells.
And Beyond Tang Tendering killed 60% of cancerous colon cells, 65% of cancerous liver and stomach
cells, and 30% of cancerous breast cells.
And by the way, I know we were gonna post this tomorrow, but go ahead and have a don.
Post the Ben Fuchs interview on how to get off Prozac-type drugs. But go ahead and post
that press release with links right after this cuz I wanna send people there. This is
a major scientific study in the laboratory on record. And again, this has already been
backed up by other studies.
They know what mega dosage is of vitamin C and B vitamins and things due to cancer. Linus
Pauling won the Nobel Prize for it. They do not want people knowing this.
No, they don't, you're right. And I don't think I ever recall seeing any kind of a study
result like this where they're talking about vitamin, minerals, supplements actually killing
cancer cells. I don't recall ever seeing-
Here, let me see the Yahoo News press release. Can I see the whole page in the front? I wanna
show people the headlines so they can find it wherever they want. Here it is out of Yahoo
Finance, ladies and gentlemen. Okay, AL International, that's the longevity parent company, announces
results of the longevity clinical research study performance by Clemson University Institute
of Nutritional Research. I mean, this is groundbreaking. And we'll post this right now at infowars.com
and prisonplanet.com. And ask them once it's posted with the video, send it out at real
Alex Jones on Twitter, Richard. I mean, that's a big deal.
It is a big deal, I agree. It's a huge deal and so I can't encourage people enough.
Well, it's what Ben Fuchs said. I lost 40 pounds, and even though it's unadvertised
as weight loss, when I followed most of it for a couple months. Then I got off of it
cuz I'm just not in the habit, my kid's wife are doing it. I do it some. And then I talk
to Fuchs and that's what others say. It's the gut flora, I've gotta totally change that
like Aaron did, or I won't get the full results. So now we're going to go on the full program
here.
Well, anybody's out there that's getting the healthy start pack and not getting results,
the digestive tract issues, you gotta look at it. That's what we've got, Root Beer Belly
is one of the great probiotics that Young Jevity carries. And infowarshealth.com carries,
go to infowarshealth.com and infowarsteam.com to sign up. You can call in and order at 888-789-9277.
That's the Infowars Health product order line 888-789-9277. At bare minimum, folks, you're
already spending money on food and supplements and things like that at your chain supermarkets
and chain drugstores and all that.
You've got to, at bare minimum, be on one of the healthy start packs.
Yeah, this stuff totally blows anything we've seen away. That's why we went out and picked
what we believe in. We've seen the results with Aaron Dykes and many other people who
heard the calls. And it also then funds Infowars operation. We're not funded by the globalist
and taxpayer money and people. We're funded by listeners like you supporting our sponsors
and what we've launched with infowarshealth.com and infowarsteam.com. Give that number out
one more time.
888-789-9277. Also, you can just sign up right there online on the web at infowarshealth.com.
Infowars Health.
All right, we'll be back with your calls.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to supernaturalsilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
You prepare by purchasing gold, food and firearms. But if you don't have a home security system
then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection. When you're
sleeping or away from home, who's watching out for intruders? Check out SimpliSafe. It's
a new do-it-yourself home security system that is completely wireless. Go to getsimplisafe.com.
SimpliSafe is independent and off the grid. It runs on battery power so even if the grid
goes down, you're protected. It's completely customizable so you can use it in your home,
business, boat, trailer, storage unit or shed. Getsimplisafe.com. SimpliSafe is also ridiculously
easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes so there's no need to let a stranger into
your home. If you move or need to relocate, you can take the system with you wherever
you go. You aren't always at home but SimpliSafe will stand guard protecting your property
24 hours a day, 7 days a week. Again, that's getsimplisafe.com.
Coming back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather a life storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all the grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my eFoods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
We are turning our atmosphere into their atmosphere. We are like a natural resource to them. To
keep the planet, move on to another. They want benign indifference. They want us drugging.
We could be pets. We could be food. But all we really are is lifestyle. Our impulses are
being redirected. We are living in an artificially induced state of consciousness that resembles
sleep. We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center and the heart of the
resistance. Alex Jones here back live going straight to your phone calls and then I'm
going to give you some really good news. I'm sure you heard yesterday Gatorade is responding
to a young girl's petition. She got 200,000 signatures to get Gatorade to remove a chemical
BVO directly connected to behavioral problems, cancer, you name it. And folks, they don't
put this stuff in there by accident. I want to explain to you that Bertrand Russell, all
of them, literally hundreds of these guys, all wrote in the 20s, 30s, 40s, 50s, 60s,
like the current White House science czar did, about manipulating things to then create
behavioral control.
It makes you very, very submissive. So we're going to be going over that. But it's an example
of solution, people fighting back. All that and more is coming up. And I haven't gotten
to the Icelandic president at Davos, how he saved his country. It's an amazing short club.
But right now, let's go quickly to your calls. James in Pennsylvania, thank you for holding.
Sir, you're on the air.
Hey, how are you doing?
Good.
The man speaking out in the darkness in the wilderness. Hey, I just like this Constitution.
Like, you know, a lot of people just isn't educated on the Constitution. And I've been
going around just making copies of the Constitution. You know, as far as the Second Amendment goes,
they don't really understand. And a lot of them just haven't been educated on it. Far
as I could see, you know, I talked to some friends and stuff. They don't even know what
all the gun laws is all about and stuff. They just think, you know, to bear arms and to
protect your home.
Well, I mean, here's the problem. And then you can elaborate. The people running the
system and controlling our tax money, Eisenhower said this in his farewell address in 61. Back
then, it was close to 90 percent. Now it's over 90 percent. Eighty seven percent in 61.
Now it's like 93. Last time I checked of all research, public and private is taxpayer funded
and controlled by DARPA.
And there are a bunch of eugenicists at the top of it. A lot of good scientists work there,
but they are able to shape the world and play God. And that's the problem is that these
globalist are bad people. So something can have a good cover story of why it's happening.
But it always fits into something larger that's being set up, not for our own good.
And these autonomous drones and robots and the surveillance, we should not be letting
our money go to this. Our tax money is building our own prison. Sorry, go ahead.
Well, I totally agree with everything you say. Like I said, I've been listening to you
for at least about 12 years. God bless you.
And I mean, I can't really stop. I can't turn my phone off. Only reason I pay a phone bill
is just to listen to you. But like I say, it's like people just isn't educated. You
know, I mean, they messed the education system up. They don't teach the Constitution in schools.
And I'm thinking like the way they have these little Bibles in the hotels and stuff, why
don't they put the Constitution in the motels and hotels at the bedside?
I agree with you, but here's the problem. They've dumbed most people down so far, they
don't even understand the Constitution. There are major studies out. Let's just randomly
show people one. Type in the average vocabulary is shrinking, not just here, but worldwide.
Ours is shrinking the fastest. Young people, they admit computers rewire their brains where
they can't even communicate with humans and have all these fractured thought processes.
And again, this has been scientifically deployed. I mean, they're telling people they just created
autonomous drones last year that make their own decisions. They had pre-programmed drones
like Voyager and Viking and others that went to foreign planets, pre-programmed.
And they had autonomous stuff that was working very well 15 years ago, where you could say
it was truly autonomous. I mean, what do you think that means for the ruling elite that
they're gonna have all these robot armies we pay for that don't even have a human to
say no? It's not even humans even picking the targets or pulling the trigger now. How
bad is it gonna be in 10 years? And again, the people running the show are not people
that are good. I'm sorry, go ahead.
Oh, I mean, I totally agree with you on that too. Like I'm saying this stuff, it's like
a big cloud over the whole world, the whole earth. And people are just totally walking
in darkness. I mean, I don't even know how I even see what's going on. It's like, wow,
you know, every time I'm listening to you, I could see that. I mean, it just opened my
mind up, the whole world is like, I mean, it's just an evil world.
It is, sir, but there's good people in it like you, God bless you. Let me just say this.
The young lady in the United States, in Mississippi, discovered that they had this manipulated,
romanated vegetable oil. You can take vegetable oil, make anything you want. And it's very
bad, according to just countless studies.
She exposed it and because of the public picking up on it because of the Internet, they're
now gonna remove it out of all of the Gatorade, okay? Now, why do they wanna put toxins in
drinks and foods? Most toxins become addictive, your body gets used to operating with them.
So they put toxins in the food to make it addictive, like aspartame and the rest of
it. Now, that's a solution right there.
Well, I'm gonna talk about it after we go to the calls. It's just that I exposed, not
because I'm a hero, I don't like this happening to anybody. I have empathy. If it happens
to you, it can happen to me, that they put radioactive isotopes in the so-called fluoride,
the hydrofluorosolic acid that you drink, out of the uranium mines that are also the
fertilizer mines, same mines, same mines.
They just purify it out, and they put the poison in our water as a big joke and make
us pay for it. Austin's like $1,200,000 a year to pay for stuff that's a toxic waste.
Now, there's a Wall Street Journal article out, and we've got it up at infowars.com,
where I talked about this last hour, that they're putting different radioactive isotopes
like uranium and different isotopes of uranium in, they're already putting them in forklifts
and quickcrete and all this other stuff, the fast-setting concrete.
Now, they're gonna put it in your furniture and your knives and spoons, and so they're
calling for knives and spoons to go all the way. If we can get people to eat off this,
they'll do anything. See, it's all about if we can ban Hello Kitty bubble projectors,
we can ban anything.
See, it's all about how much can they grab, how crazy can it get? Imagine 20 years ago
saying, you'll go to the airport and they'll stick their hands down your pants and put
you on a body scanner, and you'll put your hands up. It's all about you're a criminal.
And it's just amazing that we put up with this. Let's talk to Jonathan or John in Louisiana.
You're on the air, sir, go ahead.
Hi, Alex. I was listening about a year, the last year sometime, you mentioned your uncle
got, took a tetanus shot and almost killed him.
Yep.
It was a similar experience. My doctor, who's a friend of my brother, who's also a doctor,
wanted, he wanted to give me a flu shot and I said, no, I'm not doing that for obvious
reasons. And so he wanted me to take a tetanus shot instead. So I didn't see any harm in
it, so I took the tetanus shot. And it felt like that evening, like I got hit by a freight
train on the side where I got the shot, and I developed a fever that lasted about 12 hours.
Two weeks later, I'm back at the doctor's office with a cardiac problem.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. It causes an autoimmune response. I'm not a doctor, I had brain surgeons
on. It causes brain swelling, that's the headache, and then later it causes swelling in the different
valves of the heart. I mean, that's CDC. And that doctor will tell you there are no side
effects. You know why they had to stop the smallpox vaccinations in 2002 for the military?
Cuz so many died. Remember the NBC reporter took the shot and died an hour later? Had
no heart, your heart, it's not just your throat that'll swell shut with an autoimmune response.
It's your heart does, and I'm sorry, yeah, yeah, same thing happened to my uncle. He
couldn't breathe, had to go to the hospital, swole up, had heart palpitations, brain swelling.
And of course, this was 20 something years ago, and they said it was his tetanus shot,
but sorry, go ahead.
Well, the thing was is I didn't know it, but in a tetanus shot, they throw in a whooping
cough vaccine. I didn't know that.
Oh, they gave you a combo, or yeah, yeah, no, medical stuff's all about deceiving you
now. Yeah, no, they have a lot of triple jabs. So how did it end? Does your heart get okay
after they tried to kill you?
Well, I've been taking Dr. Wallach, well, because of you and Dr. Wallach, I'm taking
the Alex Pack, and when the Alex Pack says, I order it in bulk, they sent me these stiffs
from Dr. Wallach on Hell's Kitchen, just like a radio show that he did or something.
Yes, mm-hmm.
And they talk about, I had type 2 diabetes, and he says, well, you can cure that with
the deficiency of chromium and vanadium. He's got a product for that, I take that too.
And here's the $64 million question, did the Infowars Health products help you?
Absolutely, as a matter of fact, I'm getting ready to kiss off my cardiologist and get
out of the medical program altogether.
By the way, they found the article about the NBC reporter who died of the smallpox shot,
the World Net Daily, the guys actually just put that on screen. No, no, I mean, it's incredible.
Listen, they've tried three separate times to make the military take the experimental
anthrax shot, but it always kills so many people, their own doctors refuse. Listen,
they did an H1N1 variant shot a year before in Europe, five years ago, and it killed,
at one homeless shelter, 23 of the 30 people that were given it, okay?
And then again, the whole hoax is, we're wearing white lab coats, there is no adverse reaction,
don't be a conspiracy theorist. So what did your doctor say after you had all these problems
from the tetanus shot? Did he tell you you were a conspiracy theorist?
Well, no, he was kind of shocked, but I don't think he really knew he was going to do me any harm.
Oh yeah, they always act like that, they know full well what they're doing.
They get kickbacks, okay? They get kickbacks to push vaccines.
My dad's a dentist and he's had offers and said no.
Hi there, my name is Frank Bates. What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could
get me in a lot of trouble. I just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com.
That exposes the electricity monopolies and government agencies for what they really are.
Incompetent line crooks that are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high.
Some have called this a conspiracy, others have called it a cover up, and you will be shocked
to find out how deep the conspiracy goes. My video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth
and shows you the secret of how I beat them and how you can beat them too.
Watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patriots have already seen in the last three months.
Go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect your home.
Go watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down.
Again, that's 123coverup.com.
You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa, where a nicely furnished cabin with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine, and laundry service awaits.
After a good night's sleep, your adventure begins. You're on a golden stag safari for big game.
But it's not Africa, it's Argentina. One-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo, huger, bighorn rams, wild boar, and the biggest stag deer in South America.
All gold medal quality, all the action you can handle. Land rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages, hunting guides, ground transportation included, and more, all more affordable than you can imagine.
The adventure of a lifetime starts at goldenstagsafaris.com. The big game hunting ranch, goldenstagsafaris.com.
Stop the pain from broken, chipped and damaged nails and eliminate toenail fungus with a revolutionary new nail hardener, Nails of Steel.
Just apply one drop of Nails of Steel over natural or polished nails and go.
With Nails of Steel, there's virtually no drying time and it's guaranteed. Try this all natural antifungal and herbal formula for women and men.
Call 816-896-8307 or get free shipping at nailsofsteel.com. Nailsofsteel.com. It's like a salon in a bottle.
We the people grow cotton, we fabric, engrave ink, embed strips and fibers to protect from counterfeit, then carting to a private bank, having it lead back at interest, forcing taxes to service debt.
This capitalism or was Jefferson correct when stating a central bank issuing the public currency is a greater menace to the liberties of the people than a standing army?
Hi, Ted Anderson. I'm placing a silver dollar in a book explains our monetary system. Call for your copy. 800-686-2237.
It's time to understand the system. Call 800-686-2237. That's 800-686-2237.
Digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of toxins. That bears repeating.
Digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of toxins and Pro-EM-1 daily probiotic cleanse is the key to digestive health.
Pro-EM-1 is a powerful liquid probiotic strong enough to cleanse, gentle enough to use every day.
Pro-EM-1 is dairy, wheat and soy free, contains all natural and certified organic ingredients, contains no preservatives or animal products,
supports a healthy digestive and immune system, supports weight loss, improves absorption of food nutrients,
aids in controlling yeast infections, is never freeze dried, and uses three groups of live viable beneficial microbes to cleanse and remove toxins.
Order Pro-EM-1 daily probiotic cleanse at teraganix.com, spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X dot com, teraganix.com.
Or call toll free, 866-369-3678. That's 866-369-3678.
Pro-EM-1, the raw probiotic.
And we are back. I'm going to get into the economy and get into immigration reform as they're calling it.
Totally open borders. Hey, how about Mexico? Let US citizens come there unlimited and give us free welfare and have our kids for free.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's only the US that needs to do that because we need to be bankrupted. The global is starting to completely run Mexico.
Brian in Ohio, you're on the air. Welcome.
Hi, Alex. How are you doing?
Good, brother.
Hey, I got a couple of questions for you, Alex. The first question is what percent of the US military do you think would actually turn a fire on the people that most of them turned up to protect?
I would say about 80%. They've actually done studies, 29 Palms, but many other more modern ones.
When they're sitting around doing a survey and not ordered to fire on US citizens if they're asked if they will, 75, 80, 85% say no.
But in peer pressure, after the evil right wing group has blown up some schools and killed military and there's a propaganda piece,
I would say about 70% will fire on citizens, at least in the first waves, and then it'll all be advertised like it was a great thing they did.
But then people will remember the history of what's happened and folks will start analyzing what went on.
And if it actually gets to that point, it'll be a civil war. And the general public that's awake to the New World Order, they're not going to be going after police and military unless they get in their way.
They're going to be going after globalists. And so I hope it doesn't go there, but the police will probably follow orders, a lot of the military will, to try to protect the globalists and it won't matter at that point.
And I hope it doesn't go there, but the real globalists are going to set off shore while their minions carry this out.
But their entire force structure, the training, the preparation, like in the Cold War, the government trained to fight the Russians.
And we were told on the surface the last 12 years we were training to fight Al Qaeda, turns out the globalists run Al Qaeda, and behind the scenes they were trying to take on We the People.
This is a foreign banking cartel takeover and it's a fact. They train 24-7 to take our guns and put us in reeducation camps.
And there are millions of people who aren't going to go to a reeducation camp. And so there's going to be a war.
And they don't want to have a war where they started and don't have the moral authority. They'll go out and blow stuff up and blame it on us to say we started it.
And so just be aware of that psy-op. And I'm sorry it's come down to this, but they're lining up their people everywhere to launch something very, very soon, I'm afraid.
Okay, Alex, my second question is about the whole banking system. I mean, do you personally have money in a bank account?
Absolutely. I have quite a few bank accounts for the operation because I operate within the system. Individuals can get out of the system.
And I think that's a good way to go for a lot of people. It's your decision to make. I am totally in the system because I'm operating an operation with 50 crew members roughly and infrastructure.
I've decided to be fully exposed to the system so that I can actively engage it, kind of like jacking into the matrix.
But I personally don't have that many assets. The assets I do have are mainly in land and a little bit of backup cash and gold and silver.
Okay, sir. Well, God bless you, Alex, and thanks for accepting my call.
Absolutely. But callers always say thank you for accepting my call. Thanks for getting me on because they screen people so heavily.
Now, we don't screen calls. We get some goofy ones, but we also get some great ones. If you volunteer where you're listening from and what you want to bring up, that's a good thing.
Or I screen calls by saying I'm going to have people call in on this subject, and then obviously people need to call in on that subject.
You don't need to thank me for letting you on the air. Look, don't thank me for fighting the New World Order, folks. I'm just not insane.
I mean, they're putting radioactive isotopes in your drinking water. Our cancer rates are exploding. They're killing us, and they write books like Eco Science bragging how they're doing it.
I'm fundamentally upset about that. I'm risking my life here, not because I'm a hero, folks. There's no future if we don't get out of this.
You've heard my analogy a thousand times. Let's go to John in Arkansas. You're on the air. Go ahead.
Hello. Hey, John.
Hey, Alex. Just a couple of pieces of information there for you. Good job with Piers Morgan there, and I didn't know about you until you went on that show, so that was a great benefit to me.
Oh, yeah. It's not that his show was big. It's that it was on every other TV show in the world. It got huge. I mean, that was big.
Yeah, I caught wind of it on Fox myself. Second thing I was going to throw out there to you is Portsmouth, Arkansas, has got an international guard base, which has been running fighter planes for the past 30 or 40 years.
And they had a general come in a couple of weeks ago, and they're going to take away the manned aircraft and give us the unmanned aircraft now.
Stay there. I want to break this down because it ties into the economy. I'm going to come back to you, then I'm going to cover news, then I'm going to go back to calls.
But John in Arkansas, stay there. Listen, the entire military force is going to go to robots, not just the aircraft. Everything. It's the official plan.
We're on the march. The Empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Food poisoning and help improve wound healing. Supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day, while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off. That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal Ben Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now.
Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com. Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
We are on the march. The empire is on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
All right, I'm going to go through a ton of news here in a moment, but I want to segue into the financial news off of what this caller John in Arkansas is talking about.
And I've seen the reports all over the place where they're talking about, oh, yeah, we're getting rid of the F-16s.
We're getting rid of the F-18s, whatever the case is, and it's all going to drone.
And I'm going to tie that in to the rest of the economy and where this is all going.
But the globalists have said on record in things like Wired magazine with Bill Joy that I've talked about probably 300 times since the April issue 2000,
where he said, yeah, I went to a meeting of a couple hundred top computer company owners and our debate was, do we just give you games and fun things to play and make you a bunch of idiots?
But let you keep destroying the resources or do we kill everybody? And the consensus is we're going to kill everybody.
So I'm just going to tell you that what the Unabomber said was right. Once this technocracy takes over, humans will be obsolete.
And you see, if you read that by one guy who's worth I don't know how many billions of dollars and a top software engineer and everything, you're like, oh, that's one guy.
That's all they talk about. That's what all their books talk about. It's what they joke about.
It's Ted Turner talks about it. Bill Gates, all of them.
And, you know, I see the general public hardworking people in this system who've paid and worked to build this system, but still very childlike.
And they just have no idea that we've we've built the house of the New World Order.
And when they're done building the house completely and they're and they're hanging the paintings up right now, they're you know, they're getting ready to put the vase on the central table and put flowers in it.
And they're turning towards us, the workers that built it. They're like, we don't want you in the house.
And the house is the whole planet. We're like, what does that mean? You see these men in black uniforms?
They're going to escort you. And then they look to the men in black uniforms after you're done escorting him out, shoot him in the back of the head.
You see these robots right here? They're going to escort you. And you know what? The guys in black uniforms are going to go with them because it's a religion of serving tyranny.
Each psychopath worships the psychopath above them. And it's very, very sad. I mean, I know the plan they're trying to build.
They've written countless books and white papers on it. I know where we're going. And the Pentagon said in the 70s that by 2010, you can look this up.
They wanted to convert everything to drones or half the force to drones. And then now they've got reports out.
We're on schedule by 2020. We want the entire combat force to be drone, autonomous operated. And we're talking seven years away.
And they're coming out with combat robots on the ground that have been classified. But now they're declassifying what I was told about by Marine Corps sources.
I mean, folks, I had Marines march in to access television in 1999, one month after I got back from Operation Urban Warrior.
Because they had a family member who had a show down there. I'm not going to say who. They're probably even listening.
And they came in with a VHS that they dumped off as a feed. And they said, we just want you to know you were under surveillance the whole time you were there.
And I said, can I show this? They said, obviously not. And it was a drone watching us, but also simulating killing militias outside of the big public drills in Oakland, San Francisco, where they were doing gun confiscation drills.
They knew we were coming, so they wrote us into the simulation as terrorists. And they had Navy SEALs simulating like they were terrorist militias trying to come up in rubber dinghies and stuff to fight the US military.
I mean, this country's so gone. I mean, that's what I mean. And it's like, can I please show people this? And they're like, no. But that was 14 years ago, and they were calling the drone over us Death Star.
Because it even had the audio chatter of EC2, fly 4000 feet, move into operation, Death Star, Death Star. And it would cut to different feeds of different drones. And they're like, okay, you got to see that. Bye.
We're not all bad guys, but we snuck out to show you that and then took the video and left. The point is, this has been going on for so long.
And they're using our energy and our work. The best analogy of this is, I lived in a middle class neighborhood.
I don't know, seven years ago.
And so many stalkers came to my house. We moved. I mean, I wasn't particularly afraid of them. I mean, my wife and I were just going to have to defend ourselves and air them out if they ever actually came in the house, actually have to defend ourselves, didn't want to have to do that.
And so we moved. But the point was, most of the friends I knew in the area were engineers with IBM and advanced micro devices and things. And they had the two degrees from the University of Texas or the degree from MIT and then another degree.
And they were all there, really smart people, worked their whole life to live in little four bedroom houses. I'd say it was lower middle class because, you know, the idea of middle class is having a nice car. No, I mean, middle class is making $100,000 a year, bare minimum or more.
They'll say that's the upper echelon. $100,000 isn't worth what it used to be. And I'm gonna go back to you, Serge. I just am now kind of on a roll telling the story, at least in my own mind.
And I ran into those guys, all of them, one time or another on the streets of Austin, ran into some of them a few weeks ago on the hike and bike trail.
And when I lived by all these engineers, it was mainly engineers in the neighborhood for whatever reason, they were all training their Indian counterparts who would work for a third as much and who were given visas to come in.
And then the last time I talked to them, the Indians have been let go because they can just build it in China and they've got computers doing the diagnostics running it.
And listen, I get the whole thing of, well, that's just technology humans aren't needed, but the government isn't trying to find things for us to do or having a big space program or having, you know, other things.
They're setting up an agenda 21 just to get rid of human society. And so let me just make the announcement to all of you.
The establishment has said on record that they're going to establish world government, they're going to set taxes to a point that are selectively enforced to consolidate the wealth in less than 20 families and less than 6000 super minions.
That's what Rothkopp at the Kissinger Group calls it in his book, Superclass. 6000 super govers, about 19 families, they're going to consolidate everything and then they're going to set up police state control grids.
And those are just to do the orderly bio weapons releasing. And look, I know most of you won't listen now. I understand that. New listeners, you will when this all happens.
See, I'm setting time bombs into the future against these people. OK, that's all that matters to me is that is that humanity make it out of this.
That which doesn't kill us all only make the species stronger. I understand the decadence. I understand all the fact that humanity is rotting, but the globalist aren't trying to make us stronger with adversity.
They are ultimately selfish and greedy, inbred and very unhappy themselves. And all they do is fantasize and talk about the great time that's coming and the world without us and how they're going to live.
For hundreds of years, and then they can do that, they can live basically eternally, how they're going to copy their consciousnesses into all these other biological androids, how they are going to blast their consciousness. It's not just Ray Kurzweil, it's all of them.
Often to the cosmos and how they will soon achieve godhood will be like a bug and then we don't matter and that they're just going to kill everybody.
And so they've accepted this is the evolutionary curve of humanity. They've decided this is what it is. They discovered genetics because they wanted the keys to this.
They financed all the science, all of our modern sciences came out of eugenics. This is our world.
And I am the obsolete man. You are the obsolete man to them and they enjoy hurting even the best of us. They're not surface eugenics. They want to make humanity stronger, live longer, be better, get rid of the dumb down, get rid of the sick, get rid of the ugly, all the rest of this.
But you always know it ends up being everybody. The truth is just an excuse to play god, play mad scientist and really hurt people bad because they've tried to dumb people down and tried to lower their horizons and tried to make people these addled, mind controlled, and those aren't words, that's real.
In a trance, drooling fools. It's just a horrible, horrible vandalism. I mean, it really hurts me bad to see all the lost opportunity and to see how they've hurt us all and made us all so ugly and poisoned.
And also they can be top dogs. So yeah, they're going to shut down all the military bases when they're done and the bases will be robot factories.
And then your money will be paid under national security into it. Japan's already putting robot police on street corners to surveil people just to get you conditioned to it. The really hardcore combat robots don't so much look like C3PO or something out of.
I'll just put it to you this way. All the stuff you see in the Terminator stuff, that's art imitating life. That's the kind of stuff from my Marine Corps sources and then some others.
Where I was given highly classified information about 14 years ago by a Marine Corps officer.
Who I just happened to run into, and that was the only time and I later looked the person up and indeed it was who they said they were. And man, they got stuff right out of judgment day folks.
They've got like wheeled tanks that are like small, the size of a four wheel with all these guns, and then they'll have like a big skull head on top of it just to scare people.
So it looks like something out of judgment. It's going to be horrible, man. And again, they're going to phase out the pilots. Then they're going to have humans already controlling everything with the computers, watching them learning in a simulator to learn everything.
And then humans are already being unplugged from them, and they're autonomous things that are then programmed by master programmers. And I know I've talked a lot about this.
It's just that the robots that were described to me, this guy told me about a thing that looks like the size of a large Ford truck with a sloped front with a bunch of guns on the front.
With solar panels, but also with batteries in it that can be delivered out of the back of a 18 wheeler.
And then like five years after he told me about this in the Honolulu Advertiser, they showed the thing he described and said that the Marines displayed it, but didn't give details.
He told me a lot of it's just psyops. Like he said, the plan is to start deploying robots that are really just surveillance pods with cameras and stuff because they don't want them to hurt anybody up front.
So they'll mainly just be like a toy, a pre-programmed toy that stays within a little box on the street corner and runs feeds and then makes announcements for humans through it.
Because they want humans to be sold on it and how it's a great thing. Humans will sit back and I was told about this and then happened a few years later.
Where there's a camera on the street pole, but then there's also a screen that has a person's face on it saying don't do that. I'm watching you.
And so humans will now, this is already in Tokyo, they will give orders through the robot.
Like a lot of these globalist bosses have a robot in their office when they're in a different city or different country and the robot rolls around with a camera and stuff on it.
And it oversees everybody and it's the boss. And then a human uses that to have a physical presence through the suit.
And again, they're going to have humans as backup in the combat suits and you see it all in the movies.
They're just getting everybody ready for it. Yeah, well you guys show the new Tyranus drone.
It was something like, just type in danger of robot wars, click news. It's London Guardian, London Telegraph I think yesterday and it shows their new system Tyranus.
Yeah, let's have something called the Tyrant. That's a really good name for it because that's what it is.
And we pay for it, we build it and then soon, just like the IBM engineers and others and Dell engineers and everybody else, they are just rolling all this out.
They go train their human replacements and then the human replacements train computer diagnostic systems where it's just a technician and then the engineers are just out of the game.
But see, that wouldn't be so bad if it wasn't all designed like that, designed to take your job, designed to take your future.
And that's what ties into this. I mean punchupdrugreport.com for folks up there.
While they're busy with reports of Fed's probe for new MLB doping scandal, New York Times A-Rod named in books of anti-aging clinic, CBS on Lance Armstrong.
He'd like to think it's over but it's not. See, let's fry some little people and make you think we're getting the corrupt.
You know, Martha Stewart while Congress insider trades, but look at the Dow Jones Industrial.
$13,960, it's getting close to. $14,000, that's because the dollar's been so devalued it takes more dollars to buy it.
It's a total hoax. But see, everything is a hoax. Fed shut down coal plants, heat capital with coal.
Well, yeah, they're not going to have, you know, they're not going to not have power.
Illegal immigration on the rise again. Yeah. And again, it's meant to bankrupt us.
Payroll tax saps consumer confidence hitting poor Americans.
See, this is all the giant scam. And it's so painful to watch all this unfold and to know it's an engineered scientific fraud that Eisenhower.
You know, he didn't just warn about the military industrial complex. He talked about the scientific and technocratic elite that control it because he'd been around them.
They came to Eisenhower and said, we're going to set up a world government and kill everybody. We have a long term 50 year plan.
Oh, you found Tyrannus. Yeah, go back up to the top of that. I want to read the name of it.
It's named after the Celtic god of thunder.
That may be a different one. Warns of robot wars. Or how do you say that?
Tyrannus.
Tyrannus, which I guess.
Most Celtic god of thunder.
It's all a sick joke. I must have misread it. It wasn't Tyrannus.
Oh, man, help me. OK, I'm going to shut up, caller. John Arkansas, finish up your point.
You just got a whole dissertation on that. So you've got the new robot system there in your area. How are people liking that?
Well, they just announced that they're going to do it. We still got the ATMs here right now, but they said they said the manless planes are coming to get ready for it.
Well, yeah, you can't have pilots making decisions. It's got to be robots controlled by globalist.
What else is on your mind, brother?
He might have dropped off. I put him on hold so he could finish up his point. Anyways, I answered his question. Thank you so much, John.
And again, I get up here and just rattle off all this. I wish it wasn't true. I wish I wasn't having to tell you this.
The plan is to make everything automated, and it's called a technocracy.
The globalists like Zbigniew Brzezinski call themselves technocrats. I mean, they're so arrogant.
They have introduced legislation where the Congress and the government bureaucrats are exempt and can have any guns they want.
But you turn yours in. I mean, come on. We've got to wake up to the full horror.
We've got to remove these criminals and have a public debate about the technocracy.
Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait. They go fast. Go to scratchindentsolar.com. That's scratchindentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made, go to scratchindentsolar.com. That's scratchindentsolar.com.
All GCN listeners are complete preparedness packaged with the means to cook meals and sanitize water.
Whether you dig in or bug out, cook almost any meal with just a handful of sticks.
We already have the lowest online prices guaranteed.
But if you enter coupon code GCN at checkout, we'll knock off an additional 15%
and send you our amazing six-hour solar rechargeable light bulb absolutely free, all for only $249.
Go to afterburnerstoves.com or call 866-716-5214.
866-716-5214. Afterburnerstoves.com.
Cook hot meals with just a handful of sticks.
Hey there. Frank Bates here.
Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out 280 million Americans?
This is really scary stuff.
Defense experts warn that this odd device poses the gravest threat we've ever known.
In fact, just a few weeks ago, former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed piece for the Washington Post
warning about this deadly threat.
I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up.
That's why my friend just created a free video at weirddevice.com
that exposes this threat and blows the doors off the conspiracy.
Go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover exactly what it is
plus discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack.
I'm not sure how long this video will be online, so go to weirddevice.com before it's gone forever.
Again, that's weirddevice.com.
I mean, folks, we need treaties right now to not go to robot systems
because it allows tiny elites to countermand common sense by the officers and do war crimes.
Imagine if Hitler, what about an army of robots?
He basically did, a bunch of people that followed his orders, but this is worse than that.
By the way, Al Sharpton's out. The video's up at infowars.com
saying, you know, you basically don't have a Second Amendment.
But I mentioned this all day talking about the economy.
They're getting rid of the economy to make you dependent on government.
And because of mass production, they can still have robotic-type systems
from farming right through to manufacturing produce the baubles for you.
But it's all done to not just control a country or a culture, to control humans
because the globalists see us as a disease and a cancer.
And you run into all these people, you know, who are well-meaning,
Joe Rogan, Jesse Ventura, they go, well, there are too many of us.
Okay, are you going to kill your family?
You see, the point is, is that this program is going on.
Sure, I see a bunch of lazy slobs out there, a bunch of welfare queens.
That was done to make them weak so they could then be destroyed,
so they could be used as a horde of people to take my rights away
by voting my Second Amendment away.
They bring the illegal aliens in from Mexico, let them vote.
The Republicans are saying, this is how we'll win, it's unbelievable.
Here's this clip from Davos of the president of Iceland
saying, how did we turn our economy around when nobody else could?
Well, we didn't owe this debt.
It was all the foreign bankers' debt they'd had their people sign on.
They arrested the head bankers.
It turned out it was all a fraud, just like in America.
Most of the debt isn't ours. Let's play that clip.
Well, so far, the only bit of hope that's come out of this Davos conference this year
is from the Icelandic president who's standing alongside me, Olafur Ragnar Grimsson.
Mr. President, why are you such a beacon of hope?
Why has Iceland survived where Europe has failed?
What are you doing differently?
I think it surprises a lot of people that four years ago
we were accepted number one of a failed financial system.
But now we are back on recovery with economic growth and very little unemployment.
And I think the primary reason is that we were wise enough
to realise this was also a fundamental social and political crisis.
But above all, we didn't follow the traditional prevailing orthodoxies
of the Western world in the last 30 years.
We introduced currency controls. We let the banks fail.
We provided support for the poor.
We didn't introduce austerity measures of the scale you're seeing here in Europe.
And the end result four years later is that Iceland is enjoying progress and recovery
very different from the other European countries that suffered from the financial crisis.
That's enough.
And the key to the whole thing is
93% of the debt that they were told was theirs was actually foreign banks.
So they just arrested the people.
That's what you're supposed to do. You're supposed to arrest them.
The globalists have signed us onto their debt.
But see, the globalists want our guns to make sure we're really their property
to prop up their debt so they can hold us hostage, saying too big to fail.
We fail if we tie ourselves to this bowling ball and jump into the ocean.
Here's Al Sharpton on your constitution and your guns.
I mean, if you look at the Second Amendment,
it was that you would have militia to protect yourself in case the government came and attacked citizens.
First of all, if the government were to come to disarm you,
you would not be able to use an automatic weapon to defend yourself.
Let's be serious. We're in a world of drones now.
So the Second Amendment would not help you in that area.
We're talking about people do not have the right to unregulated rights.
All right, let's stop right there. There you go.
You do not have the right to unregulated rights.
Folks, see, it's all about the drone.
By the way, the globalists couldn't hold Baghdad.
They couldn't hold Afghanistan. That's another.
But the left, as they're authoritarians, always says,
we got the drones now.
Listen, you can't stand up against us.
So forget the Second Amendment being for the government.
We got more force than you now. No, you don't.
And you don't have the moral right.
Al Sharpton is literally another gutter rat,
just like Chuck Schumer and all these other gangster scum.
A little bit of overdrive and take your calls, but just amazing.
We've got to turn off the technocracy and pull the plug on this thing now.
Thank you for listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents,
which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface.
But rather, we have formulated our silver gel
using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera
to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin
while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.silverlungs.com
and click on our store page
to find out what silver-based products are best for you.
That's www.silverlungs.com.
Coast to coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
Big Brother. Mainstream media. Government cover-ups.
You want answers? Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Alright, taking some calls here in overdrive.
And I hear the stuff I'm talking about on this show
and it sounds crazy, but it's all admitted.
I mean, the globalists are just absolutely conquering us
and they're running this hoax that
Republicans now understand we need to be for total socialism
and open borders and that's what will get the Republicans elected.
Well, good, who needs to get you elected then?
It's all election fraud. It's all scams now.
They just want to convince you to turn your guns in.
I mean, we just got to wake up and we got taken over or it's all over.
Mike in Illinois, you're on the air. Go ahead.
Hey, Alex. Great. I'm glad you're here. Glad you took my call.
I don't know if you're aware of the National Institute of Standards and Technology's
Freedom of Information Act that they just sued for.
They've been on YouTube for about two years, a little bit less,
but I've been doing a lot of troving and searching.
And if you look up the CBS-net dub buyers of World Trade Center
between 340 and 410, you will see the streets of Greenwich and Barclay
full of nothing but exploded automobiles.
Yeah, I don't know what happened to the over a thousand automobiles that got toasted.
We've talked a lot about the toasted cars since September 12th when I noticed them.
And I've talked about building seven, the controlled demolition.
I mean, everybody focuses on mystery. Everybody loves a mystery like toasted cars.
What about the police saying, get back there, bringing seven down
and BBC and CNN reporting building seven had fallen an hour before it fell into its own footprint.
I mean, what about NORAD standing down? What about Panetta's testimony?
Transportation Secretary that Cheney ordered to stand down.
What about the head of the U.S. embassies?
People saying they were ordered to let the hijackers back in the U.S.
and that they were trained at U.S. military bases.
What about Al Qaeda being flown out to safety after the Afghan stage war?
Just amazing.
Oh, no, I agree. I mean, if you take a look at those videos, start trolling through them,
you're going to see how those buildings were on fire for two or three floors
and not on fire for two or three floors.
And as you get to the bottom, there was a CBS cameraman, and I believe his first name was Vince,
that you should probably look up and find out what happened to him and get him on your show
because he'd be the last or the first person.
Well, look, look, look, I mean, we already know what I mean.
Look, the firefighters reported the fires were basically out in both buildings
or people standing, waving their hands with a handkerchief for help.
And then the column right next to him blows up.
I mean, I mean, they blew it sky high, criminal elements working with Al Qaeda,
so Al Qaeda would take the blame.
And then they run the Al Qaeda today.
I mean, it's just we keep just piling evidence on the official story is totally ridiculous.
And we know who had the motive.
Roy in Oklahoma, you're on the air. Go ahead.
Go ahead, Roy, you're on the air from Oklahoma.
Yeah, on the phone because I believe in our amendments and stuff and I ain't giving up my guns to nobody.
I hear you, your phone's not working too well.
Can you talk right into it?
Yeah.
Yeah, that'll work a lot better. Go ahead.
I ain't giving up my guns.
I don't expect anybody else to give up theirs.
You know, those amendments and the Constitution is there written for us from years and years ago,
and we need to stand up for it now.
I agree with you. We got to get aggressive, but here's the deal.
It's not just that. It's taken our money for the drone.
They got drone ships, drone police boats, drone submarines, tiny little drones that they're getting to watch us.
They're spying on us without warrants.
They're converting everything.
Smart meters that tie into all our appliances and control them.
I mean, this is diabolical.
This is a science fiction movie, and it's about to get worse.
We've got to wake up now.
Yeah, they're building drones right here in Broken Arrow, Oklahoma right now.
Look like little helicopters for the police.
I know. It's just hellish.
And everybody's a warrior, and the warriors are going to fight our wives and children.
They're such tough guys, but they're all dead already, too.
They're all taking deadly shots, drinking fluoride.
That's why I can't even get mad at the stupid enforcers, because they're just walking dead.
I mean, that's what I mean.
We're so into this, so deep into the nightmare.
How do you wake people up?
That's why the globalists haven't killed me.
It's all a big program, an experiment.
And they just let me sit here, and they use me as like a radar ping.
It's just all scientifically established.
It's unbelievably diabolical.
Oh, man.