We've got it
Waging war on corruption
It's Alex Jones coming to you live from the front lines of the info war
Every progressive show
As we progress into the future
Each passing broadcast is just getting more and more hardcore more and more jam-packed with absolutely off-the-charts
news and information
It is fortunate that you tuned in to this Sunday the sixth day of
January
2013 broadcast because it's going to be a very important transmission to say the least coming up in 30 minutes a police chief Mark
Kessler is going to be joining us with state level nullification at the town council level
In Pennsylvania, they are moving to get a law passed to mobilize their town
against the globalist and violations of the Bill of Rights and Constitution and the Declaration of Independence gives them that power and
He is coming on the show. We found out he's a
Listener as well. That's good
It's good to know that there's a fellow Liberty Lovers out there across the nation in the world
And that's what my plan and Ron Paul's plan as well has been nullification
at the county city state level
Nullification short of secession, but if we have secession it's not from the United States. It's to have the states pull out of the federally
Occupied New World Order system and to re-upload the Republic and people are hearing that message
There's a bunch of states moving in that direction a lot of towns and counties and cities on different fronts and here's the deal
If 800 plus cities and more than 30 states
Do not arrest illegal aliens for having no insurance being drunk being here illegally
They're above the law because the police can't arrest them for other crimes
They don't arrest them basically for anything except aggravated assault
And then they're not even deported once they get out of prison and you can obviously see that in the news everywhere
That's an admitted fact. I'm not picking on the illegal aliens here
It's that it's a fraud that they're above the law because the system wants an incentive to have them here to drive down wages
Want to know why America is losing a standard of living. That's a big part of it prison labors displacing us
Obviously dollar devaluation too high a taxes make it prohibitive for companies to manufacture and develop things
in R&D here in this country
But my issue is if 800 last time I was like eight hundred and eighty something
It's almost nine hundred cities and towns every big city in the country
almost every small
city and many of the towns
medium sized cities you name it are sanctuary cities and
If
The cities and counties are getting away and the states are getting away with ignoring
constitutional federal law
They're getting away with crime
We can get away with something as constitutional
You know the feds are like oh, no you can't have nullification
Civil war decided that there's no such thing as the states or counties or cities baloney, and it's all about our will
We control our local towns and cities we get people in there that say you know what?
We're not gonna enforce unconstitutional gun laws we catch the money in the commission of a crime of the legal gun
We'll throw the book at them, but we're not gonna pull over
Farmers and find a shotgun in the vehicle and take them to jail it isn't happening
Okay, it's real simple, so we're gonna be talking about that today
That's not even the top story
But it's very important because it ties in a lot of other ways we can resist this globalist takeover by realizing
We do have power and we can say no
there were federal law saying black people weren't human, but the Constitution and the Bill of Rights said they were and
So it took a hundred years, but down the road or a little less than a hundred down the road
Those rights were claimed those rights are there not given by the Bill of Rights and Constitution
Pointed out by it. They're simply signposts like there's Mount Rainier in Washington State
The sign doesn't make Mount Rainier it points at it the Constitution Bill of Rights points at what is already there now
Here's the deal Washington Post talked to the White House. They're talking about executive orders
And they're talking about extrajudicial activity to shut down the Second Amendment
Right here where I live the city's moving to just outlaw gun shows period that's deep in the heart of Texas
We've got a bunch of other really important news as well
They're talking about repealing the 22nd amendment. So Obama can be president for life. Basically stay with us
sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as you get sick and die start purifying your water with
Pro-pure my friends. I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar
None is pro pure and it's available discounted at info wars calm
It's filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth. There's no priming required. It's NSF 42 certified
Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95% easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity
Purify water from lakes streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial minerals
Which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic
Pro pure is the best gravity-fed filter out there. It's what my family uses info wars calm already has the lowest price on prop here
But if you add the promo code water at checkout, you get an additional 10% off and info wars calm
You can also call to order 8 8 8 2 5 3 3 1 3 9
You
We are on the march the Empire is on the run
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
You
My friends we are live it is already Sunday the sixth day of January
2013 and we're here every Sunday 4 to 6 p.m. Central Standard Time coming to you from deep in the heart of Texas
Austin broadcasting world wide not just coast-to-coast on over it's approaching 150 a.m. And FM affiliates
XM global shortwave
WWCR and of course the number one radio show online by every major metric info wars calm and of course
streaming video at info wars news calm and prison planet TV
Okay, let me just mention what's coming up. It's the fullest plate. I've ever had on the Sunday broadcast and and next week
Maybe even more full and more full
I mean the amount of tyranny we're seeing in a week is more than I would see in a in in a year
15 years ago 16 17 years ago on air
just simply
Amazing to see all of this happening
Here is some of the news the 22nd
Amendment HJ res 15 has been introduced to overturn that so Obama could run for a third term
And I went and did a check a bunch of Democratic Party sites like daily costs and others are fantasizing about
Obama for life kind of like Hugo Chavez who by the way they say if they unplug him
He won't be coming back from Cuba
So we're gonna be looking at that also Assad of Syria not a fan of the guy
Definitely a dictator, but a soft dictator
He gave a speech obviously
today and
Said look al-qaeda is being funded by the West to attack Syria. We will fight to the death and it's true
I mean
It's a New York Times you name it that our government is putting al-qaeda in there to attack a country where Jews Christians and all
Muslim groups live in peace
His father was somewhat of a brutal dictator in the Hazi Mubarak stripe, which they call light
So he's a light light dictator, but al-qaeda is just unbelievable
We posted a video up at info wars calm that I'll play later in the broadcast in the second hour of the main brigades
on the suburbs of
Damascus the capital of Syria chanting we blew up the towers. We're coming to kill you America after we're done here and
It's it's even on Arab television stations
It's just unbelievable that and by the way a year ago when they killed Gaddafi
They had signs on BBC saying next stop Damascus. We're coming to Syria
So our government NATO and others the French are leading it. Normally they're anti-war. They're just leading this thing
The French are at the head of this
Well, I've already talked about it a lot. I'm gonna talk about in the second hour
It's just incredible that we were talking about it two years ago with Libya when that started
Almost two years ago in Syria when it started and now it's like yeah. Okay, our government runs al-qaeda. Never mind that
And people send me emails going. Well, at least we got Arabs killing Arabs. You know, this is crazy
Assad hasn't attacked anybody
Assad wears a suit and tie
Women can walk down the street and go to college there and nobody's wearing burkas. That's all ending al-qaeda is chopping
Christians heads off just type in just type in Syrian rebels chop Christians heads off
Stabbing them making father's truck bomber. They kill their whole families and our media has actually run articles saying
Oh, look at the rebels doing a great job
And then there's a backlash in the New York Times pulled a video a few months ago showing this our media thinks we're so
dumbed down they can show al-qaeda chopping a Christian's head off or throwing them off a church top or
Making them a car bomb or they kill their family and our media is so evil
They're like, oh look at the rebels. They're so wonderful
I mean, this is so Twilight Zone. I can't even register it. Okay, and I expect corrupt stuff out of government. I
Mean, I expect all sorts of this
I don't even know what to say at this point because now it's admitted and it's a back-of-the-paper issue
So that's coming up some of the second hour, okay
Hold on to your hats here ladies and gentlemen, because I told you this was coming there is an incredible
incredible Washington Post article posted up at info Awards calm
It's also on the easiest place to find it drug report calm on the left-hand side at least 20 minutes ago
Had it and here is the Washington Post
article White House ways broad gun control agenda in wake of Newtown shootings and
They say in here. We're just gonna have the ATF
Go in and and extra judicially with rulemaking exactly what Larry Pratt of Gunners of America has warned about here in the last month
We're just gonna go in and do it outside of law
Maybe even executive orders and yeah
We're just gonna ban gun shows and ban you giving your son or daughter a gun no more
Giving family a gun or transferring a gun and we're just gonna put giant
You know regulatory taxes outside of Congress on the bullets and it links to all the plans and it's a long
Four-page article with links. I spent two hours on this sucker last night two hours
I was up till about 1 a.m.. On this okay following what they're all saying. It's exactly what we knew it's all their old plans
regurgitated vomited onto us at once
And it is the repeal the Second Amendment that the Huffington Post the Atlantic wire
The economist and then the Chinese government the Russian government all these governments even USA today said what's with all the foreign?
Governments it's bad enough to have Piers Morgan over here lecturing us a redcoat by the way
I'm on his show tomorrow night in person in New York. I thought it'd be fun
But to make a long story short ladies and gentlemen Mike Adams is sitting in tomorrow
He'll sure do a better job than I do. I'm a fan of that guy
But continuing here. It is just off the chart insane. We'll be getting into that
We have a video clip and I remember seeing him say this everywhere, and we even found the text of it
I couldn't find the video
CNS news found it and the videos up at info Wars calm right now
And Obama says look I'm not coming after your handguns your rifles nothing anybody says it. They're a liar. He said that four years ago
And I warned people I said now in this campaign because the fix is in I said he's saying he's coming after handguns and rifles
They're coming after everything the Illinois bill that we barely beat
Last week
Openly made you turn in everything turn it in and everybody's registered there under the void card
That's why you don't want to be registered isn't they always confiscate go through the quote background check
They know you're a gun owner, but it's not registered when you waive your rights
And they said that you know everything's turned in including pump shotguns
Pump rifles people go their pump rifles. Yeah, a lot of pump rifles a lot of good ones out there actually the point is
If you want something reliable, they're actually pretty good some of them the point is is that it banned everything
Except sim except bolt-action way beyond just semi-auto, so it's all here. It's all happening
We know what they want. We know what they're doing. We know what they're after and and by the way
I'm gonna go over some statistics here on air when we come back
From the Centers for Disease Control FBI and US federal government with links to it at info Wars calm
America's biggest killers the chart anti-gunners don't want you to see and
And by the way guns are at the end of the list
With eleven thousand four hundred and ninety-three killed in fiscal year
2011 you always get the numbers a year late and
There you go
But I'm gonna go over all those numbers here on air by the way an estimated seventy two percent of those were gang related
gang members killing each other so take seventy plus percent out of eleven thousand five hundred roughly and
We're now talking about three thousand five hundred or so
Maybe four thousand real deaths from guns folks. There's three hundred and fifteen million people here
Let me just give you one number, and this is a conservative number by the way
Guess how many people die from tobacco use five hundred twenty nine thousand medical errors
195,000 bad drug interactions goes on and on all right see I'm already starting to go to it
We're gonna cover that after the break after we get into these audio clips of Obama's saying
Listen listen when you go home and your friends tell you that I'm coming after their guns
I'm not gonna take anything you got a Second Amendment. I believe in it
We're leaving your guns alone, and the Democrats is very telling are yay cuz most Democrats are gun owners
Almost everybody's a gun owner now every liberal
I know in the last decade has figured out government can't won't protect you watching Katrina and Sandy
And all these other events and and once you go out and shoot again
You're like this is no big deal running a blender at your house. You have to hold it down is more dangerous
Running a egg beater is you know it takes more force. I mean guns are a piece of cake and
once you try one
once you go to a gun you never go back I
Mean it's that simple, and it's not that weird on power trips. We have guns. It's that we're in charge
We feel empowered I sleep so good no
I've got an instant access pistol safe that my kids can't get into right by my bed and one right by the front door
I mean I am ready to defend my family so I sleep good
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses
Don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum
Antibacterial solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria
Viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing
Supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep staph
Pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology has the ability to terminate entire
colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or
Ionic silver solutions the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
Supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
That's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans
Here is the cow Ben Soap Company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and safe
See them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800-340-7091
For a free cash flow of over $1,000
7091 for a free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're
Using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps or all your cleaning needs
This is an amazing deal
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
See them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800-340-7091
for a free catalog
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east but we are still in the eye of the perfect storm
The most devastating economic condition since the Great Depression
America's worst drought in agricultural history and now the economic results of the presidential election
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from e foods direct and I recommend you do the same
It's time to get your own supply for me foods direct
I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food
I'm taking control of my future and you're nuts if you don't do the same go to e foods direct calm forward slash Alex to
Find the specials and you can start with a holiday gift pack. That's normally $80 now under 50 bucks
Remember I can warn you, but I can't feed you call 800-409-5633 or e foods direct calm forward slash Alex
Would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late or oh nine five six three three or in foods direct calm
forward slash Alex
Alex Jones here with a very important announcement for truth seekers
We've carried a lot of amazing
Films and books over the years on the online video bookstore at info wars calm and out of all the titles
We've carried one stands out because it is just so
Chillingly convincing and that's dreams from my real father by Joel Gilbert available at info wars
Calm this film exposes the fraud that Obama is like nothing
I've seen if you want to know who Obama's real daddy is. This is the film for you
Don't forget your purchase supports our broadcast and our growing media network
You'll also find it info war shop calm none dare call a conspiracy by Gary Allen the book that woke me up
We're also carrying behind the green mask you in agenda 21 by Rosa Corey
This book is coffin nails to the globalist takeover the greater good the most professional and up-to-date film
I've ever seen
Exposing the scourge that is vaccines these titles and a lot more are all available at info war shop calm
Coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network
Crashing through the lies and disinformation
It's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network
to quote Thomas Jefferson
The great thing about the Second Amendment is you will only need it when they try to take it away
That is a Thomas Jefferson quote similar quotes by other founders
You know my family fought for the Second Amendment to be created in the Revolutionary War and my family fought
When Santa Anna tried to disarm the people?
at Gonzales and then on into the other battles on both sides and my family were involved in the founding of Texas and
I'm not turning my guns in
Because it's a symbol and we know what it means while the government buys another
200,000 hollow point bullets for the American people on top of the 1.6 billion. They already bought in the last 14 months
We're gonna be going to that report here today government is arming against us and then telling us turn your guns in because we want
To take good care of you
No
They want to be able to do to us whatever they want just like in Mexico
Where they have taken all the guns from the citizens 50-something years ago, and they have the highest crime rate in the world
For a nation the only city that's higher than one of their cities is Chicago where they have a gun ban
Again where the criminals run free in government and on the streets
Right now I want to go to a clip here
And I hope you were listening earlier
The Washington Post has come out and said that they've talked to the White House and that indeed they're going to use executive power
outside of Congress
To basically shut down gun shows tell shops not to sell semianos and and and just prosecute people
Outside of law just have the ATF plan. They have a rule if you transfer guns and things. It's it's a laundry list four-page article
White House ways broad gun control agenda in wake of Newtown shootings very chilling
But I wanted to play the liar-in-chief
Obama this is four and a half years ago
CNF news found this I remember him saying this over and over again that I'm not coming after your second minute
But we have a Biden saying the same thing
But here's Obama saying I'm not coming after your handgun your rifle none of your guns and now that he's not facing a reelection
He's like yeah, I'm gonna take everything here
It is when y'all go home, and you're talking to your buddies, and they say he wants to take my gun away
You've heard it here, I'm on television so everybody knows it I
Believe in the Second Amendment I
Believe in people's lawful right to bear arms. I will not take your shotgun away. I will not take your rifle away I
Won't take your hand gun away, and I will not hire any lobbyists broke all records
I will not sign executive orders to circumvent law
More executive orders and all predators before him from George W. Bush back to George, Washington
I will not have signing statements breaking all the records
But he's got a peace prize so he can put al-qaeda in the countries to chop Christians heads off. I mean it is just amazing
Amazing
Let's go to Joe Biden during the same 2008 campaign saying the same
Thing here is Joe Biden talking about his Beretta handgun after he talks about a shotgun
Which is semi-auto which they would ban here it is I?
Guarantee Barack Obama ain't taking my shotguns, so don't buy that malarkey
Don't buy that Malarkey. They're gonna. They're gonna start peddling that to you. I got two of he tries to fool my Beretta
He's got a problem. I like that a little over-and-under. You know. I'm not bad with it
And he's talking about a very shotgun there the point is is that
There is Biden saying they're not coming after your guns
When he wrote the original assault weapons bill in 92 that they had to water down and we have Feinstein
We'll play it later
We played it last week and throughout the week saying mr.. Mrs.. America get ready to turn in your guns
and
his original bill banned all semi-autos period show
decades later or 15 years later
He's running around saying. Oh, I don't want your guns lying to people
And look some folks say oh Alex as I saw in the comments on info wars calm and prison plan calm
Okay, they all lie big deal see they just got you used to it now
no, whenever George Herbert Walker Bush lied and said read my lips no new taxes and
Then raise taxes. It was over and then of course. We just got something just as bad Bill Clinton William
Jefferson Clinton who I used to think was the greatest liar I'd ever known Obama definitely is better and tells more whoppers
But the issue is is that Obama has raised 14 taxes on the general public
You can just type in its USA today. It's Bloomberg
77% of Americans
That's working Americans
77 percent of the country everybody who works got a payroll tax increase
If you make thirty six thousand dollars a year on average. It's about two hundred dollars a month
$200 a month and and
that's just one tax we're talking about so and
Then there's another 13
Taxes on top of it and fines and fees and all the rest of it and then all those other taxes on people making over
125 thousand dollars a year individually quarter million collectively that all gets passed on to you when you get laid off or
Middle class folks don't come in by goods now there
It is fiscal cliff deal raise taxes on seventy seven percent of Americans tax policy center and analysis and now that's official
Okay, let's go ahead. That's now law. Let's go ahead and go to the clip of Obama saying. I won't raise your
Raise your any of your taxes not your payroll tax not your on on raising them all
Raising everything he said he wouldn't raise
In fact they've had Howard Dean come out and say if you make ten thousand dollars a year. You should pay taxes extra taxes
About two weeks ago. He's looking up Howard Dean says poor should pay more
Oh, yeah, because you want to get the economy going no you know that high taxes shut down economies
You know Kennedy cut the highest tax bracket by 50% the next tax bracket by 30 plus percent and tax receipts
Did what by the next year?
Did they go up 20% did they go up 30% 50 60 70 80 90 they went up over?
100%
More than double the tax receipts you'd think bureaucrats would want money. No they don't want money
They want to bankrupt your butt and get you on welfare. We've gone
from less than 2% of the country on food stamps in the 30s to
Now 50 million people it's doubled the last four years from 25 million
And they're set to double it again the name of the game is takeover. They don't want you uppity having any money
Let's go to this clip of Obama saying he wouldn't raise any of your taxes any of your payroll taxes here it is
And I can make a firm pledge a pledge under my plan no family
making less than
$250,000 a year will see any form of tax increase not your income tax not your payroll tax
Not your capital gains taxes not any of your taxes
by the way they have in the in the now law a
surcharge of what is it three point nine
Percent on all your 401k investments you've already paid taxes on this over and over again now
it's an investment for your retirement or for college whatever for your children, and they're going to tax that and
just I don't know how bad this has got to get here and
And and used to people get mad about this, but and a lot of folks are angry
I mean Congress does have a 9% approval rating
But I got to tell you the 35 40 percent of people in this country that really are Obama supporters
Is about half the people in the country voted and a little more than half voted for Obama?
The 25 30 percent 35 depending on how you look at it because he's got 30 million legal aliens supporting
So that's about 35 percent total
Are you people are just idiots?
I mean you're chumps this guy's a collectivist that wants to bankrupt everything and put America through emergency
Reorganization to make you step and fetch it they want to break your will
We'll be right back in defense of the Second Amendment with a key plan to save the Republic
Tell folks to tune in right now
Now that we have moved into the winter season there is an increased need to support our immunity and health
At silver lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of silver based products
Our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our 2 ounce nano silver nasal
applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps
Just released is our 100 percent natural silver gel
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface
But rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera
To quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively
visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver based products are best for you
That's www.silverlungs.com
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as you get sick and die?
Start purifying your water with pro pure my friends
I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar
None is pro pure and it's available discounted at info wars calm its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth
There's no priming required its NSF 42 certified
Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95 percent easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity
Purify water from lakes streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial minerals
Which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic
Prop here is the best gravity-fed filter out there
It's what my family uses info wars calm already has the lowest price on prop here
But if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10% off and in full wars calm
You can also call to order 8 8 8 2 5 3 3 1 3 9
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east
But we are still in the eye of the perfect storm the most devastating economic condition since the Great Depression
America's worst drought in agricultural history and now the economic results of the presidential election
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from e foods direct and I recommend you do the same
It's time to get your own supply for me foods direct
I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food
I'm taking control of my future and you're nuts if you don't do the same go to eat foods direct calm
Forward slash Alex to find the specials and you can start with a holiday gift pack. That's normally $80 now under 50 bucks
Remember I can warn you, but I can't feed you call 800 for 0 9 5 6 3 3 or a foods direct calm forward slash Alex
Would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late or 0 9 5 6 3 3 or a foods direct calm forward slash?
Alex
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers the prognosis for the entire planetary
Economic system runs from bad to worse the globalist model is to shut down
Societies and starve Patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at info wars shop calm
These are items that I did research on but I personally use you've got the life straw
So you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go the ktor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power
Outages are out in the field strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein
Thera-safe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event and crank shortwave AM FM radios
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at info war shop calm and your purchase makes our info war
Possible we're getting prepared. Are you info wars shop calm?
Coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the alex jones broadcasting network
We now take you live to the central texas command center in the heart of the resistance
rallying Patriots worldwide
You're listening to the alex jones show
Monday through Friday from 12 noon to 3 p.m.. Eastern we're live on the radio. I won't be tomorrow
It'll be Mike Adams. He does a fantastic job sitting in the health ranger of natural news.com
I am gonna get on an airplane
Early in the morning. I'm gonna get on an airplane
Early in the morning, and I'm gonna fly up to New York to be in studio with Piers Morgan
And they've got a bunch of surprises lined up for me
Alan Dershowitz and a bunch of others to sit there and
in Peck at me
But they would do it via satellite and and we were gonna do it be a satellite
And but I thought you know what I want to look that guy in the eyes
And so we'll see if they chicken out boy. They they swore to me. They won't
I've had CNN check it out before via satellite interviews, and I'll get really really upset if they do, but
That political rumble in the jungle is set for tomorrow night
9 o'clock central 8 o'clock Eastern in studio at the CNN command center that I've been in multiple times
So that should be interesting
Speaking of that let me just go ahead and play a clip again of Dianne Feinstein who's bill obama says he's gonna put his quote full
weight my
That's a quote to her last bill. She didn't have the votes for now. She has them
She says to make you mr.. And mrs. America turn your guns in here's that clip
California senator Dianne Feinstein worked for more than a year to get the assault weapons bill passed in the face of ferocious
opposition from the National Rifle Association
She says she got the best she could if I could have gotten
51 votes in the second round of the national rifle association
votes in the Senate of the United States for an
Outright ban picking up every one of them mr. And mrs. America turn them all in
I would have done it. I could not do that the votes weren't here
But that was over a decade ago now her bill says that
Because well a decade ago the American people wouldn't put up with the UN and NATO commanding our military
They wouldn't put up with the NSA spying on the American people without warrants and admitting. It's going after conservative libertarian and
Constitutional groups see the whole homeland system is now for us. They admit it I
Want to play another clip and then for the rest of this segment the next we're gonna go to our guest a police chief
I want to first play this clip from last year, Lubbock County, Texas with judge head. He's the county judge. That's like the county mayor
Talking about Obama's gonna come for the guns that judge had actually read Obama's quotes
And the UN quotes see they've all said over and over again. They want a total abolition of guns
That's in the preamble to the original UN treaty, but see when we're informed when judge head is informed
Or police chief Mark Kessler's informed or Ron Paul's informed
The con artist in corporate mainstream collaborator media they just go to the public. Oh, that's a kook
That's a conspiracy theorist don't don't listen to them. They don't know what they're talking about just listen to us
But see that doesn't work anymore
That's why they're so desperate to bankrupt America now and get our guns now because they know America's waking up
That's why they're trying to get in as many illegal aliens as they can get as much people on welfare as they can they paid
$22,000,000 to ship General Motors to China look it up barely made the news, but it's in the news
vault and Cadillac factories
I believe Cadillacs made in China most of them
Anything they can it's one thing if you move to China
It's another thing of my money paid to move it there
They're not liberals aren't screwing up. They're not liberals. They're authoritarians
they are engaged in economic siege, but here's judge head on local Fox News and
Now other police other county judges mayors are saying the same thing
If 800 cities and 30-plus states can nullify for illegal aliens
When that is a violation of federal and state law and just let them do whatever they want well
We can nullify illegal federal laws when they are unconstitutional
And say our local police under the mayor and under the county or whatever the sheriff. We're not taking people's guns
Okay, but this this this this police chief goes further. They make provisions to defend the Second Amendment. You've got to call these tyrants bluff
Ten years ago Feinstein said oh, I got to get votes to take your guns. We got to get an amendment lady
Constitutional amendment now a decade later. She's like. Oh, we'll just do it with an executive order. That's in the Washington Post
They're seeing what the public does there. They're seeing others a backlash right now
We're gonna go to our guests, but first here is judge head of Lubbock County, Texas
During the election warning of this eventuality coming to a head no pun intended here
It is he is gonna try to hand over the sovereignty of the United States to the UN
Okay, what's gonna happen when that happens? I'm thinking worst-case scenario right right understand civil unrest civil disobedience
Civil war maybe and we're not talking just a few riots here and demonstrations
We're talking we're talking Lexington Concord take up arms and get rid of the guy
Okay, now. What's gonna happen if we do that if the public decides to do that he's gonna send in
You in troops. I don't want them in Lubbock County
Okay, so I'm gonna stand in front of their person armored personnel carriers and say you're not coming in here
Mm-hmm and the sheriff I've already asked him. I said you're gonna back me said yeah, I'll back you well
I don't want a bunch of rookies back there all right
I want that's right
He goes on to say they had to create another unit just to deal with the feds and if every county did that it'd be
Over and people said well, that's that's crazy the feds are God the feds have been taken over by firing mega banks on record
Okay, I'm done ranting our guest is with us this segment and the next
And he joins us, but imagine ten years ago hearing that it would have been crazy four months ago
It sounded a little strange to people now
It's like oh yeah, she know that guy was just more informed than even the general conservative out there, okay?
This is what's going to happen
Okay, they plan on raising taxes now Obama's already calling for more tax increases
Same thing in 1775 eating out our substance
It's reducing us to ruin that was the plan so the British nobility could buy up all the businesses and
land for pennies on the dollar
Was Oliver Wendell Holmes the Supreme Court justice that said the famous justice that said
Taxes are the price of civilization, and that's true to have somewhat of a civilization a small limited government
But what about when the government becomes evil and destructive of those aims which happens all throughout history and and uses
Civilization to destroy us and reduce us to slavery all right. We take you now to police
Chief Mark Kessler in a Pennsylvania a town of Gilberton
That's like Mayberry RFK and the citizens are backing in Pennsylvania police
She proposes Second Amendment preservation ordinance demand a real plan nullifying constitutional gun laws
And he joins us to talk about enact any and all measures as may be necessary to prevent the violation of the Second Amendment
That's right
That's right. Not just say we're not going to enforce unconstitutional laws and act whatever it takes any means necessary
I want to salute you serve for your stand for the Republic, and it's good to have you here with us
Tell us why this came to mind and where this is going. Well. Thank you very much Alex for having me on your show
This came to mind after after yes, and evil shooting and the outcry for everybody to
bad weapons
Hopefully
after three or four weeks of research I came up with the idea for the nullification process and
after several drafts I
planned on
Introducing to the borough council on our next meeting on January 24th
Which I hope they do
pass
Well I hope it I hope it does pass
Why did you I mean did the clock get so close to midnight? Is that why you come up with this plan?
Around the country in particularly in Washington that everybody screaming to
Weapons and they realize that it's not it's not the weapon
That's causing the problem. It's the person behind the weapon
That's causing the problem and until they figure that out. They're never going to solve the problem. It's not the
Law-abiding citizens that are going out and committing these heinous crimes. They're so evil and
Unspeakable it's the mentally ill
Unfortunately they're doing a lot of these crimes and criminals. It's not the law-abiding citizens.
Well, that's right. I mean every day in this country unfortunately every day
I've looked it up or on average every day a mentally ill person takes a butcher knife and stabs their family with it
Do I have to lose my butcher knife because they do that and we're gonna be right back with the police chief
Pennsylvania police chief proposed a Second Amendment
Preservation ordinance we appreciate his courage and his forethought, and this is something that can really pick up steam everywhere
I mean if they let the illegal aliens run free and that's unconstitutional
How about police and counties and cities just pass law saying we nullify
unconstitutional garbage
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses
Don't be one of them protect yourself with Supernatural Silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial
Solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria
Viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing
Supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep staph
Pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria
at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or
Ionic silver solutions the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off that's
Supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as you get sick and die
Start purifying your water with pro pure my friends
I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is pro pure and it's available
Discounted at info Wars calm its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth. There's no priming required
It's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95 percent easy to set up and use
Doesn't require electricity purify water from lakes streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial minerals
Which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic
Prop here is the best gravity fed filter out there
It's what my family uses info wars calm already has the lowest price on prop here
But if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10% off and in fall Wars calm
You can also call to order eight eight eight two five three three one three nine
You prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms, but if you don't have a home security system
Then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when you're sleeping who's watching out for intruders and spooks
Check out simply safe. It's a new do-it-yourself home security system
That is completely wireless go to get simply safe calm simply safe is independent and off the grid
It runs on battery power so even if the grid goes down you're protected
It's completely customizable so you can use it in your home business boat trailer storage unit or shed
Simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes
So there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you move or need to relocate you can take this system with you
Wherever you go simply safe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days a week
Go to get simply safe calm. That's get simply safe calm
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans here is the cow
Ben soap company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and safe
See them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800
340 7091 for a free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as
What you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs
This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars
And you will love the way real soap makes you feel see them on the web at five star soap calm or call
800 340 7091 for a free catalog
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance
You are listening to the Alex Jones show
Coming up in the next hour. We'll look at the economy take your phone calls and look at the White House and NATO funding
radical Islamic groups to invade different countries
I want to show some just some statistics here and then go back to the police chief from, Pennsylvania
Who's introduced a plan with the City Council to have the Second Amendment Preservation?
Act in their area
And again big things have small beginnings, but here's an article at info Wars calm by Mac Slava
America's biggest killers the chart anti-gunners don't want you to see and then it goes directly to fbi.gov
And the Centers for Disease Control their own numbers tobacco use
529,000 conservatively medical errors
195,000 unintentional injuries
118,000 you know slipping in the shower alcohol abuse
107,400 motor vehicle accidents deaths these are deaths by the way all these are
34,000 deaths show you've got tobacco 500 plus thousand medical errors
195,000 unconventional injuries
118,000 alcohol abuse
107,000 motor vehicle accidents 34,000 gonna ban cars because they're dangerous well. Don't worry
They want to make you drive robot cars now. That's the whole Google plan so look out
on intentional poisoning
31,000 758 now gotta ban everything poisonous well everything's poisonous, but you can drink too much
Scope mouthwash and die I'm gonna ban that drug abuse
25,000
Unintentional Falls so that was separate from that
24,792
non firearm homicides baseball bats ice picks butcher knives rocks
16,799 firearms homicides
11,493 in 2011 these numbers always come out a year late, so these just came out a few weeks ago three weeks ago the point is
That you've got a much better chance of falling in the shower
Then you and dying than from a firearm and over 70% of those
11,000 go look at the fbi.gov and violent crime statistics our gang bangers killing each other
Now four thousand still a big number, but but it's nothing compared to everything else. This is a hoax
I want to go back to the police chief sir
You've got the floor here for the balance of the segment
Where would you like to see this go the common sense what you see in your town?
How do we get your counsel to get this law passed?
How do people read a copy of it so other towns can introduce it?
I mean this is what we need to do because you've got all these other cities ignoring things that are the law
Well, how about we have cities ignore things that are unconstitutional? Well?
receiving phone calls from all across the country from Alaska to California
Asking for copies of the alleged proposal. I'm going to introduce the council on 24th of January
From mayors in Chester County, Pennsylvania
to mayors in Bucks County, Pennsylvania
that one copies
of different sheriff's departments all around the country that are asking me for copies they have called and
Gave me great support throughout this whole thing, and I would like to see it spread throughout the entire
continental United States yes
By up by every means necessary and spread the word to everybody and we're not going to stand idle. We can't stand
and
Just let these bureaucrats in Washington
Ram down
anti constitutional law
To the American people it's just not right and I will not my department will not enforce any unconstitutional laws against the Second Amendment
Or the Constitution of the United States as far as I'm concerned for the Constitution of Pennsylvania
Well, I know you're sticking your neck out because you love the Republican your family and our future and obviously
I don't put words in your mouth, but
Guns are the canary in the coal mine. I'd like you to elaborate on that chief
But looking at this it's an example of leadership you do this, and you haven't even put it out publicly yet
Obviously you will see on the city website
And you're already have people all over the country wanting to emulate what you've done
And and that's the essence of this we have to simply stand up as leaders and do what's right and others will join us
but if we just stand here and let the tyranny take over as
Churchill said there may come a time when
We have to stand up and fight because it's better to down our feet than as slaves
Instead of fighting politically early on when our chance for victory was assured
Exactly exactly and God forbid the last thing we want is any kind of violence
hopefully, you know this will be a
Kind of a gateway for other other
other people that believe in the Constitution and other law enforcement officials and just the average citizen that could take it make a
Copy of it
Call me get in touch with me make a copy of it take it to their local law enforcement agencies their local sheriff their local
politicians and
Have them do the same thing that I'm trying to do and I mean I've been contacted by the old keepers
They're there in support of me the Pennsylvania United PA
9 9 12 guys, they're a million members strong throughout the country
They they're backing me. There's just a whole bunch of people
Yeah, folks are just looking for men of honor to stand up and you're doing that and this is what can turn the tide
This is what the anti-gunners are so scared of they know
Actual innocence being killed by guns is incredibly rare. They have the statistics. I've been around them
These are cold-blooded tyrants, you know, all the pro-gunners are always so polite and go what's wrong with these people?
Look at the statistics. They're not dumb. Most of them are tyrants
Sure, you've got people at the grassroots that never grew up around guns that are scared of them
But the general establishment people that want our guns they want them to oppress us and look
I've told the police this and the police aren't stupid
They know this there's a lot of people aren't turning them in and if a Feinstein gun man goes through and they try to go around
Harassing gun owners. It is not going to go. Well and what judge had talked about is going to end up happening
I want to avert that and I agree with you. I think we can
Fix this just by political action. I
Hope so. I hope so out
The last thing like I said, we want if any kind of violent
erupting throughout the country
I know hopefully this sends a clear message to Washington and to the
The media that we're not going to stand idly by and let them confiscate
The Second Amendment or the goal or tamper with the Constitution itself. That's that
We got a band together
Wow
You know, I was looking up your town
Friday I had a caller because we were already covering your report Thursday and Friday and the caller said oh no
Let me give his number out. He's happy to have his number out and I said well wait
Let me get him on and make sure it's okay to give his number out very
You know nice of you to give your number out for mayors and sheriffs or others that may want to get a copy
of it and if you'd like to send us the
The proposed town ordinance or law we would love to post it at info wars comm so you don't get hammered
But if you if you're willing to answer a couple hundred phone calls go ahead and give your number up
So yeah, if they want to get in touch with me, I'll have to our phone number here at the office is five seven zero
eight seven four four
seven nine zero and I'd be more than happy to talk to anybody who wants to copy of the
proposed ordinance and
Well again, I gotta say it I'm not kissing your butt here chief
But I gotta say what you're doing is is is what will save this country and it almost brings a tear to my eye
Because so many people say well, I'll just wait till they come for my guns and we'll have a revolution folks
We that is the last thing we want whoever shoots first loses
We want to stand up politically and use that force to defend our freedoms
Not shoot our mouths off, and I've told people this if you won't politically get involved to defend your freedom
It's talk you will never physically defend when the time comes
Correct that you're right on point there right on point. I can't agree with you more
Well, it's just hope everything goes the way
On the 24th and and I urge the borough the borough
council to take a good long look and a hard look at this proposal and hopefully they'll decide with the
constitution and
We're gonna do five more minutes with the Chiefs and let you get back to your family but start with the ordinance
What is the ordinance basically break down?
It breaks down
basically, I worked at Gilbertson to borough Gilbertson is going to recognize the Second Amendment of the car of the Constitution United States and the
Second Amendment or
the
Constitution of Pennsylvania section 21 the right to keep their arms
in Pennsylvania
And we're not gonna we're not gonna let the we're gonna nullify any state local
or state local
Laws ordinance
Or regulations against the Constitution or article 21
There is the text it's actually in our article
I've seen that but I wanted to double check the text is at info wars calm in the article
Breaking that down very very exciting do five more minutes with us chief
We're gonna come back let you finish up any other points you want to get to
We'll be right back ladies and gentlemen with the second hour, then I'll give the number out. I'll give it out now
It's eight seven seven seven eight nine Alex. That's me Alex Jones eight seven seven seven eight nine two five three nine
Other police military are you gonna stand with this American patriot?
It was simply standing up and defending the rights that our ancestors paid for with blood or will we go quietly?
Into the night with the socialist health care by the way New York Times is reporting when I told you months ago
The new health care bill has now doubled the average insurance premium. I
Mean you talk about a scam you talk about a ripoff
Your insurance premiums have now been doubled under Obamacare because the offshore banks wrote the bill and they own the insurance companies
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers the prognosis for the entire
Planetary economic system runs from bad to worse the globalist model is to shut down societies and starve
Patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at info wars shop calm
These are items that I did research on that I personally use you've got the life straw
So you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go the kator hand-crank generator
To charge up key equipment during power outages are out in the field
Strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein
Thera safe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event and crank shortwave AM FM radios
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at info war shop calm and your purchase makes our info war possible
We're getting prepared. Are you info wars shop calm?
The millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses
Don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum
antibacterial solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria
Viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing
Supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious
Diseases such as strep staph pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic
Silver solutions the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off that
Supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook
Coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the Alex Jones broadcasting network
From his Central Texas command center deep behind enemy lines the information war continues
It's Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
Folks it is a command center. We're just putting out the Constitution if you obey the command
That's between you and God if you don't I feel sorry for you
This country has been wealthy and successful because we had more liberty than other nations
Doesn't mean we were perfect
But we had some amazing founders and I saw a clip of Michael Moore saying how dare the founders
You know people think that's all set in stone. They fought the greatest empire in the world
They trail based liberty that became the model of the planet and I look at the ordinance that you can get an info wars
Calm, Pennsylvania. Police chief proposes Second Amendment Preservation Ordinance Aaron Dykes article Second Amendment Preservation Ordinance
It says prohibitions on federal state local infringement of the right to keep their arms firearms accessories or ammunition
And there's a line in here
It talks about an act ending in all measures as may be necessary people say oh they'll come get us like they're God or something
I'm not Olympus if you simply say no they lose the moral authority and then the gun confiscation never happens if you cower
All Liberty Falls now now I said I want to give you the floor, but you're a polite gentleman. So you're you're you're
A man of few words, but the last four minutes
We've got left other points police chief Mark Kessler of Gilbertson, Pennsylvania that you'd like to impart to our listeners. Oh
I'd like to say I hope everybody gets behind this and my mayor mayor mayor Mary Lou Hannon
She's pro Second Amendment. She's standing behind me on this
She can also push the council into adopting this
and I just really hope the passes and we all got a band together and stand up and fight the
the
Treasonous in the in the
Washington and the elite
It's just everything that's going on right now in the country. I'm really worried about where we're headed in the next four years
it could be very disastrous and
They want to take they're going to start taking our weapons away from us
It's just a very it's the start of a very bad situation within the United States
Hopefully people could stand together
the
Patriots the mothers the fathers the military the law enforcement
These all band together and say enough is enough. We had enough. We're not going to take it no more
We're not going to sit idly by and not and let the government ram
anti-constitutional ball down the throats of the American system
That's right
If we just act like it's some mothership that gives us all the orders it's going to do whatever at once and
Foreign interests are going to come in and buy it off. We have to
It was a famous African American
Statesman during the Civil War to paraphrase
him he said that
the liberty and freedom is not given it is taken it is demanded and
We need the special interest of liberty and the American people and private property and low taxes and freedom
And and and so we've got to get aggressive
We've been taken over because we became passive and it's just common sense we either get involved
Or we lose everything exactly exactly and we can't do that. We can't I will not sit idly by
And let this unconstitutional act that they're trying to get the Congress is trying to pass right now
Not the whole Congress. These are some good congressman
There's good good good senators in the United States, but just certain ones that have this ideological
Anti-american agenda that does not sit well with me. That's right
It won't be what and they guilt us into oh, I mean you've heard it. You're a clan member of your own guns
You know you're an accessory to murder the NRA or lobbyists for these 20 dead kids
It's the government the federal government that made those gun-free zones and the media that
Advertised it as the places for Prozac heads to go kill people
I mean if they want to put blame out there there are light years more to blame than anybody else
Exactly, they should look in the mirror. They really they really need to a reality check
We need to get these people out of office
I don't think that they they're committing acts of treason on a daily basis
And it just boggles the boggles my mind as they as an individual
And as a police chief that these people are in the position of power that they're in what about your other officers
Are they fired up about this?
Yeah, everybody Michael communities pretty much fired up about this that the local communities around me are fired up about it
I've received calls in different
Area chiefs of police that can be congratulate me
Others are good because this is how brush fires in the minds of men start according to Jefferson well
I want to salute police chief Mark Kessler in Gilberton, Pennsylvania
When is your town gonna stand up?
Sick of the globalist you Genesis control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as you get sick and die
Start purifying your water with pro pure my friends
I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is pro pure and it's available
Discounted at info Wars calm its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth. There's no priming required
It's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95% easy to set up and use
It doesn't require electricity purify water from lakes streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial minerals
Which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic
Pro pure is the best gravity-fed filter out there
It's what my family uses info wars calm already has the lowest price on prop here
But if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10% off and info wars calm
You can also call to order eight eight eight two five three three one three nine
Big brother
Mainstream media
Government cover-ups
You want answers?
Well, so does he?
live from Austin, Texas
Broadcasting worldwide, it's Alex Jones
Ladies and gentlemen, I was just talking to police chief of a town up in Pennsylvania mark Kessler if you joined us
He was telling me off-air as he left us that
And he also said some on-air that little short segment
That police chiefs all over the country are calling him and congratulating him for getting a piece of
Statutory law
that can that complies with the Second Amendment of Pennsylvania and the federal Second Amendment to
Simply say we're not gonna harass gun owners. We're not going to confiscate guns. This is unconstitutional order
and by the way
Diane Feinstein and it's in the Washington Post yesterday
They're saying they may use executive orders or ATF rulemaking and I've been warning you about that
But now it's official to just shut down gun shows you name it and I am really ashamed of something
That I have and my listeners to a great extent here in Austin have allowed
Because we're all guilty of not standing up to these people
Have allowed the Austin City Council and the county commissioners
Who are in a story in the Austin American Statesman?
To come out and say that they are set to ban
Gun shows not just from county and city property the big convention centers
They're saying they're set next week to vote the Austin American Statesman reports on a city law and a county law
They're working together to ban gun shows period what's next like San Francisco ban gun shops
This is deep in the heart of Texas
Travis County
Do I have to name drop here that it was David Ayers my ancestor that raised Colonel Travis's son. I
Mean, I've got I've got relatives with counties named after him in Texas and I am ashamed
That that Travis County that bears the name of William Barrett
Travis is set to ban gun shows and they're talking about gun shops. You know, I said that's next they're there
They're starting to talk about that. Here. It is Austin American Statesman city county to consider restricting gun shows
And potentially even curtail them on private property within the city limits. The Austin American Statesman has learned and
It goes on Mike Martinez
Mike Martinez, man, you know Mike can't you just be an American?
Mm-hmm
Mexico has taken all their people's guns. They have the highest murder rate. It's almost 60,000 dead in just last five years
Women men children our own Justice Department shipped guns into Mexico to blame our Second Amendment and got caught
Cuz good be ATF agents blew the whistle and you sit here and call yourself an American. I call you a shameful
Enemy of the Republic and a piece of garbage
You
Physically want to shut down gun shows
Just you people there's no end to you
You know, they were trying to shut down gun shows a few years ago. They were sending an ATF try to set folks up
yeah, I called for a protest of it and then they had a
Local group protest and I showed up at it. They even had provocateurs at it to
Try to go after me
I mean listen, they want to use Austin as a case to break open all of Austin
Texas into the rest of the country and go after our guns. It is it is just absolutely
amazing
To see this type of stuff going on and if you haven't read the Washington Post article
You really should but can we get that flashback cute back up Obama?
I will not take any guns even though it's a state senator. You can find public letters
He wrote as question and answer periods for the Chicago Tribune saying I believe all guns semi-auto
rifles handguns bolt-action single-shot
Everything must be banned and I got Dianne Feinstein saying that too
I've got Joe Biden
when he introduced the first assault weapons ban calling for an abolition of gun ownership in this country for
almost all guns to be turned in the Illinois Statehouse has bills introduced right now and
They've got until what Tuesday to get it done. I warned you last week. They could play possum
They claim they didn't have the votes word is we've got some calls on this from some good sources. They may try to ram it through
Physically making you turn your guns in
Like they've already done in Chicago making it the murder capital of the world at least Mexico doesn't have that crown that trophy that belt
They're just murder capital country-wise
as they took all the guns and
you know, I think all Americans whether your name's John Brown or
Whatever it is, you ought to move down to Mexico, of course
They won't let people move down there. If you're an illegal alien down there. They put you in a forced labor camp, but
Wow
Very very dangerous time and see the globalists don't care whether they're unpopular or not
They think homeland security works for them and they're dropping the hammer on us
Was it Noel in Illinois that you said had some news on the
Bruce in Illinois
Bruce in Illinois, then we'll go to Noel in Illinois and others Bruce. What is your Intel?
It was callers last Tuesday started warning us about the gun grab in emails and Wednesday
We covered it and sure enough
We wrote an article Wednesday that made national news and Thursday the bill to confiscate most firearms including
Pumped shotguns was introduced and then we thought we shot it down Friday
Are you saying other meeting right now and other in session right now to try to get your guns? Yes, sir
Alex on Friday a
the gun ban amendments were introduced into the Illinois House and
In an unprecedented session at two o'clock today
the Illinois House
Judiciary number one committee actually was brung into session to look at the gun ban bill
The Speaker of the House Michael Madigan
He is so confident that the gun ban bill will pass out of committee that at five o'clock today, Illinois time
He is actually going to bring the full house of the Illinois General Assembly the house of the Illinois General Assembly to session now
It originally came out of the Senate and passed committee, but they didn't have a Senate vote
Are they gonna try to pass it in the house first? Yeah, they're doing today in an unprecedented vote today
I mean all the dirty tricks were done out today Alex
This was done so late Friday that even the Illinois State Rifle Association could not get out an alert
Listen my gut told me my gut I said it on Thursday and Friday they would they would sneak attack put it back up
Illinois State Rifle Association impeccable source they say late-breaking alert
And they always sneak this stuff through their criminals next vote on semi-auto ban will take place Sunday shuts down gun shows
Shuts down shooting ranges the bill. I saw even shuts down sit the same bill that makes you turn in pump shotguns
Yes, sir. It's the full ban. They snuck this through they put it on a fast track
It didn't all right looks red alert right now. Give me the top URL
Folks because I want to give out the State Rifle Association actual URL. It's LS
Yeah, go ahead. Give me the our URL
Is ra.org is ra.org
RSra.org Illinois State Rifle Association
Or they got all the phone numbers up there on their front page federal court ruled
They can't bar Chicagoans promoting guns to defend themselves
So they're striking back as any globalist would is just take every gun
We've got my goodness
And they're gonna use this as the model with an executive order the Washington Post reports yesterday
Saturday to just have Obama sign an order taking our guns and his plan is to start a civil war
These people are criminals. I'm sorry. Go ahead, sir
Well, that is what's happening Alex will see the General Assembly with this vote because this is a dirty-tricks vote
If you know any history of Illinois see they're going to they're going to bring the General Assembly
Session in the house tonight at five o'clock, but everybody won't be there
They'll only have the special guys that got the call to be there. Amen
That's what the deal is how they pass the Federal Reserve Act with three senators December 23rd 1913. Go ahead
I talked to Richard Pearson Friday afternoon because I had arranged for him to get on a big national talk radio show like yours
That's the leader of the and in a lot of rivals
Here's the executive director and chief lobbyist for the Illinois State Rifles. I'm so gun crazy
I haven't know the name of all the state groups. Go ahead
Yeah
and anyhow
I talked to him Friday and we knew that there was a chance that they were going to introduce it into the Illinois house
but we didn't know they were going to fast-track it at that time and
Richard had actually left the Capitol and went back to chat. Yeah, when are we gonna stop falling into their traps?
I said Thursday and Friday, they're gonna play possum and people are like stop fear-mongering. I know the enemy's tactics
We've got to call every one of those phone numbers. They're on the website right now nationwide
They want this beachhead to make all of Illinois a Chicago
Mafia command base. Well, that's what they want Alex and they have no respect for the people and I encourage everyone across the nation
To call every member of the General Assembly and tell them how disgusted we are. The amendment is to SB 28
99 stay there caller come back to you
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans
Here is the cow Ben soap company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and safe
See them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800-340-7091
For a free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now
Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps or all your cleaning needs
This is an amazing deal
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
See them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800-340-7091
For a free catalog
Tyranny is here the grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality
It really says that the state is God the United States is now recognized
Globally is one of the most impressive police states on earth this film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps
Now being expanded nationwide this documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all-powerful shadow state
Police state for chronicles the sickening depth to which our republic has fallen
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship body scammers sound cameras citizen spies
Staged terror and cameras on every street corner. It's only the beginning of the New World Order's hellish plan
The police state isn't coming. It's here secure your copy today
Info wars calm or see it online in the highest quality at prison planet TV
Now that we have moved into the winter season there is an increased need to support our immunity and health
At silver lungs. We are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of silver based products
Our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our 2 ounce nano silver nasal
Applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface
But rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera
To quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively
visit
www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver based products are best for you
That's www.silverlungs.com
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east, but we are still in the eye of the perfect storm
The most devastating economic condition since the Great Depression
America's worst drought in agricultural history and now the economic results of the presidential election
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from e-foods direct and I recommend you do the same
It's time to get your own supply from e-foods direct. I know I won't be standing in a bread line trail
I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food
I'm taking control of my future and you're nuts
If you don't do the same go to efoods direct.com forward slash Alex to find the specials and you can start with a holiday gift
Pack that's normally $80 now under 50 bucks. Remember I can warn you, but I can't feed you call 800-409-5633
or efoods direct.com forward slash Alex
Would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late?
Or 0 9 5 6 3 3 or efoods direct.com forward slash Alex
Coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network
From the front lines of the information war it's Alex Jones
That's right from the front lines of the information war
People hear that stuff 17 years ago and go. What are you talking about front lines info war?
I was reading Pentagon public documents about how foreign banks were going to take over America. That was their new boss
Army War College, it's all public and it's not even classified and how they use info war to control us with lies
Doesn't mean the average man and woman in the military is bad. They're great people the globalists that run our military
They're using military mind control
Manipulation techniques on us and I'm done
playing games with it and
It doesn't matter how much fancy propaganda you got once people see behind the curtain doesn't matter how fancy the facade is
It's over and we are on the march. The Empire is on the run
If these crooks in the Illinois state legislature pass a huge gun ban ammo ban most guns
I'll be banned the courts are going to shoot it down. We're gonna keep fighting. We're not going away
But I told everybody I said we beat this too easily on Thursday and Friday not like it's rocket science
They always act this way people like Alex. We had a victory. Come on. Don't don't over Fairmonger and now it's official
We can put the Illinois State Rifle Association
Back up on screen of your radio listener. We have it up on screen at prison planet TV
Late breaking alert next vote on semi-auto bill will take place right now
SB 2899 going back to our guests that alerted us to this Bruce is working as a citizen lobbyist to defend our rights
Thank God somebody is not some foreign banker
You thought you just go to sleep America and keep all your liberties think again
Bruce
When are they voting on this and then if it was in the Senate before?
Will it have to go through the house into the Senate or what's the time frame? What's the order of things here?
Okay. Well Alex the current order is that at two o'clock today the house?
Judiciary number one committee was brung into session and the bill was introduced or filed for that committee
That bill has to be heard in that committee and then like I said earlier at five o'clock today Michael Madigan the speaker of the Illinois
House was bringing the full house to session at five o'clock with the intent that they're going to be there. Hopefully
For that bill to come out of committee so it can go straight to the floor
We're 22 minutes central time into five. This is happening right now. It's happening right now. Yes, sir
Yes, sir
And in our Illinois the history of Illinois is a lot of things bad things happen about midnight
That's right and the way this thing works
as long as
Madigan can keep that committee in session until he can
Brow beat somebody to change their vote and make sure that it passes the committee it will then go immediately to the floor of the house
And this General Assembly in Illinois for a vote
Texas I've stormed the Texas Capitol peacefully the media called it storming
I just marched in with hundreds of people over the TSA the bills been reintroduced to arrest them this time when they grow puss I
Call don't you call for peaceful citizens to go in right now to that committee and to go into those?
the
Representatives offices and let them know it's your capital
I say it's time for Illinoisans to take their state back from the Mafia
Absolutely, Alex. In fact, there's a call out
See that they see the dirty trick about this stunning is the dirty trick about this stunning is it happened late?
Friday so that people actually couldn't rally and didn't even know what's happening
And then you go home to spend one day with your look look
I knew this would happen, but people said oh Alex come on. Let us have a victory that there they are right now
They're introducing the bill
Amendment one it is all happening right now ladies and gentlemen this is insane
Believe that this vote was structured in a deliberate attempt to stop people like you and others from great creating the grassroots
Movement and so that people couldn't go to Springfield and couldn't attend these hearings. That's right. Let me say it this way
Let me say it this way
do you think they're openly introducing bills to take almost all the guns federally and
bragging about it and letting piers Morgan and the Chinese government and the Russian government call for our guns to be turned in with the
UN treaty coming up in March if they weren't planning on doing this okay folks. I know it's unpopular
I know it's unconstitutional. I know when I look in their beady little eyes. They're planning on war
I'm telling you this is it and we can beat them, but people got to admit. There's a fight happening. Well. Yes, sir Alex
I do agree with that now. I do have a slight different take on all this gun control bills
You know remember Joseph Farah when he came on to your show, and he talked about how he was afraid that
Barack Obama and his controllers would line people up and basically do away with them and remember how you played on the air
No, that's what Bill Ayers told Obama in the FBI files was they were gonna kill put 50 million of us in camps and kill us
Yeah, well understand. You know Barack Obama is a hardcore communist, but Barack Obama understands power and
What brocco I believe is happening here is I believe that this is the beginning of a purge
You know if Barack Obama can use the color of law
They're bragging on Democratic sites, this is a way to harass gun owners everywhere
This is how they make us the enemy. This is what Homeland Security's for yes, we'll see this will purge
Obama's critics it will purge his opposition and Obama can in a sense change the demographics in the political
Landscape of the United States and ensure that he and his minions will be in
I don't know why you said we disagree. They've introduced the amendment to making president for life, basically
Hjres 15 federally I totally concur with you
Yeah, I mean to disagree. I mean I have a different take I mean I believe that this gun control situation is literally a purge I
Believe it's the purge of Obama's. Oh, they've actually all over the Democratic sites that we've got an article coming out tomorrow
I told Paul about it mother writers like a week ago, but
Soon articles coming out because I see it everywhere. I sent him a bunch of examples to write an article where they go
We hope you don't turn them in we're gonna kill you and these are big official sites. No this is it these people
This is this is Russia 1948
Now you're right and for those that don't know they kill most people after 48, okay, I appreciate your call
Yeah, and see I'm so busy. I can't keep track of everything guy calls it. He says look it up
I look it up there. It is. I look up the Statehouse website look up the video feed
They're in there debating the bill on the floor of the house right now
They promised they wouldn't reintroduce it on Friday a pack of liars, and I know they're liars
Why did I didn't believe them because I wanted to go home for a day and a half and sit around cook food play with
board games with my children and
Quite frankly go out and shoot my rifle in the backyard because I live out in the country. I mean
But you know what all my neighbors were shooting. I've never heard all my neighbors on three sides of me
Shooting and this weekend. They were all shooting
People get what's going on and again the low-level folks say well, why do you want my guns?
And then the establishment says well for everybody's safety they want our guns to dominate us
Let's jam in a call before we go to break another caller from Illinois Greg in Illinois. You're on the air go ahead
I don't Alex. Thanks for doing what you do. I just like to tell you how crooked this is
I want to underline it so everybody else that's listening can understand
It's so crooked like like the previous caller said you know it's unprecedented
They brought told us they weren't going to do anything
And they brought it in on Friday where they couldn't get the word out now
They've got everybody in there doing their thing and we can't I've been trying to call all day all the voicemails are full
Physically you're gonna physically go to Springfield I
Understand that but that's quite a way from where I'm at and it's not a possibility for me today. I understand
But we're not like for affiliates in Illinois
Everybody needs to get there or the state police are coming to take your guns
You're right. You're right, but it's coming to every other state everybody got to watch it
Don't don't wait like we did
And that's my that's my message. Thanks Alex. God bless you. I hear you it is so disgusting how far our country's fallen
They're getting ready to totally bring us into depression. That's why they want the guns first
Frank Andrew mark Frank Noel ray Greg Spence your calls are straight ahead. I'm Alex Jones
This is defense of the Republic
Alex Jones here with a very important announcement for truth seekers
We've carried a lot of amazing films and books over the years on the online video bookstore at info wars calm and out of all
The titles we've carried one stands out because it is just so
Chillingly convincing and that's dreams from my real father by Joel Gilbert available at info wars
Dot-com this film exposes the fraud that Obama is like nothing I've seen if you want to know who Obama's real daddy is
This is the film for you. Don't forget your purchase supports our broadcast and our growing media network
You'll also find it in full war shop calm none dare call a conspiracy by Gary Allen the book that woke me up
We're also carrying behind the green mask you in agenda 21 by Rosa Corey
This book is coffin nails to the globalist takeover the greater good the most
Professional and up-to-date film I've ever seen
Exposing the scourge that is vaccines these titles and a lot more are all available at info war shop calm
sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as you get sick and die start purifying your water with
Pro pure my friends
I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is pro pure and it's available
Discounted at info wars dot-com its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth
There's no priming required its NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%
Easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity purify water from lakes streams ponds and wells
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals
Which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic
Prop here is the best gravity-fed filter out there
It's what my family uses info wars comm already has the lowest price on prop here
But if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10% off and in full wars comm you can also call
to order 8 8 8 2 5 3 3 1 3 9
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses
Don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum
Antibacterial solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria
Viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing
Supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep staph
Pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology has the ability to terminate entire
colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or
Ionic silver solutions the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to supernatural
Silver comm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
That's supernatural silver comm and like us on Facebook
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans
Here is the cow Ben Soap company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and safe
See them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800-340-7091
For a free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now
Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs
This is an amazing deal
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
See them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800-340-7091
For a free catalog
Coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network
I have sworn upon the altar of God
Eternal hostility against every form of tyranny over the mind of man
Thomas Jefferson, it's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network
It's good to stand for something
You know the old saying stand for something fall for anything
You don't stand for something you're like a leaf in the wind my friends
You know if I had to quantify the New World Order global government all it is is a bunch of Bernie Madoff Ken Lay types
Who in the last 200 years got governments and corporations and companies to borrow money from them out of nothing
And now they've got 1.5 quadrillion in derivatives out there and
Globalism is just a bunch of international crooks only a few thousand of them
Exempt from all the other laws playing countries off against each other
Getting rid of national sovereignty and basically trying to get governments to lobby
Legislatures to raise taxes to pay corporate welfare to them
And now they know we're getting awakes they're like hey how about you give us those guns too
And just sit down there and shut up while we militarize and federalize the police and buy all these weapons and
Billions around to ammo and tanks
Never mind those cameras giving you tickets when you drive down the road from point to point
Never mind your kids being trained to spy on you
Never mind the NSA yeah we'll use drones to kill citizens
Sit down and shut up
You know it's almost a curse to be informed
It's really not a curse
Even if you were a cynical globalist being informed is very good for business
But I spent
I didn't really talk about Al Gore and his current TV
Deal selling out to Qatar in the Arab emirates over in the Middle East
Until I'd had some time Friday and Saturday to study it a bit
And I already knew what was going on but I wanted to make sure you know
That's why I'm so frustrated once I get on air
Because there's just all this research behind it that I could never put out on air
Because of time constraints
But I went and did the research it turns out Forbes already done it all for us
And it's an article titled Current TV
Sold to Al Jazeera for $500 million deal for Al Gore
Average listenership or viewership was 40,000 people an hour
A B-rate AM station in a major city has 40,000 listeners an hour
They're probably charging $100 an ad
Al Gore was charging $10,000 an ad
That was just big corporations kind of giving him you know their donation to put out anti-gun info
And it turns out they're talking about Al Gore
And it turns out they're talking about how it's a foreign run media now here in the US
State run Arab media Al Jazeera
That's bad enough violates a bunch of laws
But the biggest issue of this globalism
Is that he got all this oil money too from it
And he's a hypocrite about that
When he's already been one of the biggest oil men in American
Modern American history and politics
Occidental petroleum
He wants a global
I saw a comment on a YouTube video I did
Saying you mean we pay our taxes to Al Gore
And people said well he owns the software for the carbon trading
No he has a company called Gore and Blood
In London a Rothschild company
That you pay carbon taxes to
Where they trade the carbon credits okay
You pay the money to Al Gore
They couldn't get the feds to ram it through so they got
Counties and cities that were traitorous like Austin Texas to sign on
And yes Austinites
Through different Austin energy programs
Pay money to Al Gore
When you turn your light switch on
That man bear pig fat
Turd of a man
Con artist
I was watching the Beverly Hillbillies with my children
I let them watch old TV yesterday
And they had a con artist episode where this con artist
Comes to their house and
He takes them to sell them the Hollywood Bowl
And then he takes them to sell them the zoo
And he goes I tell you what if you buy these from me
I'll throw in this this highway
I mean Al Gore is that type of con artist
But let me go to your calls I said I'd go to your calls
The issue here is
Carriage rights
If you've got
On average about 5 million viewers a day
It varies in the regulations
You can force your way on the basic cable
But basic cable gets bigger and bigger
Because of that and charge people
On average 56 dollars more than double what it was
When Al Gore is vice president
Honcho the 96 telecommunications act
So he went and twisted arms
They admit this in the article
To put current TV on the air five six years ago
With no viewers
Because he gets an automatic payment
From everybody with basic cable and basic satellite
And now he gets a foreign government purchase
Roughly five times what it was even worth
I mean just amazing
Amazing and that's just one little
One little scam
And it is a scam
I talked about this last week
Congress gets caught inside our trading
They go you know what we'll pass a law to outlaw it
It was already illegal
But they play that little game
That bait and switch
We'll pass a law to make it illegal
They pass a law to legalize it
Talk about crooks
Frank in New York you're on the air
Thanks for holding brother go ahead
How are you Alex?
Listen I just want to thank you
For doing what you're doing for the past 17 years
You've been very knowledgeable
Everything you say is on
But the whole thing this is Alex
This is actually that intervention
This is going to happen regardless of what we do
I hate to sound so cynical about it
But it's going to happen
Unfortunately
Well it is true we've killed
53 million babies and say they're not babies
And we've launched
All these illegal wars and we've become
Decadent and evil
Anytime a country becomes decadent and evil it falls
We'll fall just like Mexico
Just like North Korea
That is our future
You know the Rothschilds actually want to create
Israel I believe you know that as well too
I know the Rothschilds are at the very head
They're at the very head of wanting to create
World government absolutely Frank
My point is
They want to create Israel
After World War II
They funded the founding of it
Correct
But my point is that
Without Israel
This would not happen I know this sounds crazy
But Israel has to happen
For the anti-correct to come back
That's all I have to tell you
No I hear you and you know Israel
Every citizen that wants a gun is issued full auto
And we pay for it with our taxes
But then Israel came out and said
Their foreign minister said take our guns
It's like oh I pay for your M16
And Israel said yeah that's right
Yes and one more thing Alex
Do me a big favor tomorrow night
Can you please kick his ass tomorrow
Piers Morgan I can't stand that
I'm going to be polite
Now with the red coat
But I'm sure I'll let him attack me first
Then I won't physically do anything
He's got a bunch of bodyguards
Anyways and I'm actually afraid of Piers Morgan
I'm being sarcastic folks
I'm flying up there just for the fun of it
So we'll see what happens
Thank you you're on the air go ahead
Well a couple of suggestions
For you and I do hope you will consider taking them
To heart first of all
Every time you mention the whole thing
About the TSA and the police doing random
Searches on the roads and everything
You always forget to state the most important thing
And that is that we actually do have
The right to refuse searches like that
No no we do but the average cop
Doesn't know that and it'll beat your brains out or shoot you
This is totally
Unconstitutional
I like telling Rosa Parks go to the back of the bus
She didn't have to and absolutely
Have you heard they're signing up all over the country
Gang checkpoints where they search your vehicle
I mean this is called martial law
Yes and I know
But we shouldn't be afraid to refuse
Because as long as we have our rights we might as well use them
Whenever we have them so I'm just suggesting
Make sure you point out we do have the right to refuse
Whenever you bring that up
And I also have another suggestion
The whole thing you did
About the TSA week
Has inspired me to suggest
Maybe you do another thing for a day
Like maybe mock Big Brother
Because the fact is I know Big Brothers
Oh no no we don't want to have people go out
And climb up poles and bash
Security cameras with baseball bats
We don't want anything illegal to happen
I mean what would protesting Big Brother week consist of?
Yeah I know
I don't want us to break anything but
No no we should just take cancer shots
Vaccines full of cancer
Let's talk to Mark in Oregon
Mark you got one minute we're going to break go ahead
Hello Alex
Hey buddy
Alex not the main reason I call
I hope you could hold me after the break for a moment
So I could get to it real quick
But I think it may be the main reason that I call
I'm not sure
And I'm not trying to be negative or morbid here Alex
Or to discourage you in any way
But I've heard what you've had to say
About Piers Morgan
You know recently
And I know it to be true
We're going to have Mohammed come to the mountain
Rather than you go to see him
Oh no I love going into the lion's den
Man I love going into the
I don't mean that Alex
I mean this is a very
Accelerated
Event
Framework that we're living in at this time
And I fear for your safety
My brother
You know what Obi Wan Kenobi
Look I got to jump I got to get to everybody
But I appreciate you look look
No more of this stuff
You know what Obi Wan Kenobi tells Darth Vader
Strike me down Darth I shall become
More powerful than you can
Possibly imagine
I am not worried about anything
We have witnessed
Two terrible storms in the east
But we are still in the eye of the perfect storm
The most devastating
Economic condition since the great depression
America's worst drought in agricultural history
And now the economic
Results of the presidential election
This perfect storm is a huge threat to
Everyone's food supply
I just doubled down and got even more supplies
From E Foods Direct and I recommend you do the same
It's time to get your own supply
From E Foods Direct
I know I won't be standing in a bread line
Trading my freedom for food
I'm taking control of my future
And you're nuts if you don't do the same
Go to efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex
To find the specials
And you can start with a holiday gift pack
For 50 bucks
Remember I can warn you but I can't feed you
Call 800-409-5633
Or efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex
Would you rather prepare six months too early
Or one day too late
Or 09563
Or efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex
Now that we have moved into the winter season
There is an increased need
To support our immunity and health
At Silver Lungs
We are committed to meeting your needs
By providing a full selection
Of silver based products
Our most popular silver based products
Are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions
Our 2 ounce nano silver
Nasal applicators
As well as our all natural silver soaps
Just released is our
100% natural silver gel
Our new silver gel
Is not based on synthetic gelling
Agents which quickly evaporate
And leave the silver at the surface
But rather we have formulated our silver
Gel using the natural skin nourishing
Chemistry of aloe vera
To quickly penetrate and nourish the skin
While delivering the silver more
Effectively
Visit www.silverlungs.com
And click on our store page
To find what silver based products
Are best for you
That's www.silverlungs.com
So even if the grid goes down
You're protected
It's completely customizable
So you can use it in your home
Business, boat, trailer
Storage unit or shed
SimpliSafe is also ridiculously easy
To install yourself in under 20 minutes
So there's no need to let a stranger
Into your home
If you move or need to relocate
You can take this system with you
Wherever you go
SimpliSafe will stand guard protecting
You. Go to www.getsimplysafe.com
That's www.getsimplysafe.com
You can turn fetid water into safe water
Anywhere you go
The Ktor Handcrank generator
To charge up key equipment during power outages
Or out in the field
Strategic Relocation 3rd edition by Joel Skousen
When disaster strikes by Matthew Stein
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security
To protect yourself during any
Radiological event
Handcrank shortwave AM-FM radios
Everything that we've researched
And found to be the best is available
At www.infowarshop.com
We're getting prepared
Are you?
Infowarshop.com
Coast to coast
Direct from Austin
You're listening to the Alex Jones
Broadcasting Network
Live from Austin, Texas
Broadcasting worldwide
It's Alex Jones
All right, we've got dozens of calls on the board
But Mark, Frank, Noel, Ray, Spence, Jeff
I'm going to get to at least you guys
Mark, make your other point real quick
Go ahead
Okay Alex, and just quickly in passing to my other point
When you get on Pierce Morgan's show
If you would please bring up the gross inconsistencies
Around the Sandy Hook shooting
Indicating it's a government black op
And perhaps discuss false flags
False flags in general
I think it hit it really good
I really do
Alex, my main point
Is that John Moore
And he says eight other public
Figures who have very high level
Competential sources
In various US federal
Government agencies
All agree across the board
That the scenario is to occur in March
Where we have the perfect storm
Of the gun grab
Having gone on for a bit
Or commencing
Financial collapse
Martial law and then civil war
Well I hope that's not the case
And if we get the word out
These tyrants won't be able to do this
But they didn't set up homeland security
And all the tanks and armor
And anti-gun training to play deadly winks
Frank in Louisiana, you're on the air Frank
Welcome
Yes Alex, we have to remind these traitors
That they are literal traitors
You can't legislate away the bill of rights
And we have to remind them
That you're in violation of your
Article 6 oath
Supreme contract
To we the people
And by the way we were watching
The live Illinois Statehouse feed
And when the bill came up they went
Let's go to closed session
And they turned the video feed off
To take their guns
I'm sorry go ahead
Well they're in violation of the Article 6 oath
Which when that contract is broken
You didn't default to that contract
We don't have to do anything
Hey this government is not legitimate already
They say our military is under
NATO UN command last year
And they have to be
Reminded that the right of the people
Clause followed by the infringement clause
Says we have a right
From God as declared
The declaration of independence
Which is organic law still cited on the
First pages of the statutes at large
That's right our rights don't come
From government or even the constitution
Of bill of rights they come from God
They're unalienable
They're unalienable they're on record
Great point Frank anything else?
Well one thing that you might
Just put into the thought process
Is we have to ask the government
Why are you charging us a heavy progressive
Income tax it's forbidden by the
Rules of direct apportionment in the constitution
Didn't have it until 1913 it's all
Paid to the private federal reserve
It's the foreign federal reserve sucking us dry
They brag they're foreign
They call us dumb slaves
To the public find out what the Goldman Sachs
And people say about you
Let's talk to Noel in Illinois
Shite of the treachery go ahead Noel
Yes before my
Comments on the gun grabbing
Anyone in Austin I highly suggest
You go to the Austin Hilton Convention
Center at 745
Tonight T. Boone Pickens
Will be speaking at the annual meeting
Of the American Meteorological Society
And heck go protest all week
That's right they're having a big weather
Notification chemtrail meeting here in Austin
The next two days we're going to have reporters
There you make your point on the guns
Okay Mike
Madigan his daughter Lisa Madigan
The attorney general of Illinois
Lost an embarrassing suit when
The courts ruled that Illinois can't have
Concealed carry so it's no surprise
That they're doing this at such
Rapid speed yeah the answer is
Oh really courts say you can have a gun we're just
Going to take them all we're going to jump down to Ray
In California they're also trying to totally
Ban guns there now the few that are still there
Open gun bans being pushed by the
Globalist who are arming with the teeth against
Us and all have bodyguards and their own
Special licenses go ahead
Ray
Go ahead welcome
Hi I just wanted to say
I'm more concerned about
Bio Holocaust and subsequent nuclear
Holocaust that is probably going to run with
This gun ban thing that's going on
Well we got a federal government
That injected black people with syphilis and
Gave foreigner kids polio
And it's all irradiated our soldiers
So how dare you say the government
Would ever do anything corrupt or illegal
That's impossible I mean the government
Is run by foreign banks that are
Eugenicist and say they want world government to
Cut off resources and kill us I mean
That's loving Ray I appreciate
Your call Spence in Missouri
Spence you're on the air welcome
Good lord Alex I'll tell you what you're hard to get a hold of brother
Hey let me tell you what
Thanks for giving me no more life
I'm meaning that
Jokingly okay
Hey listen I was going to tell you again
Thanks for getting me on the air I'm going to make it quick
You know where I live up here I think I've
Talked to you once before just for a brief moment
Just south of the big 72,000
Square footer
Hey listen they've blocked off
All the caves around here with bars
They've put concrete
Up around them
They're blocking all the highways with cables where you can't cut
Across they're digging in against us
They're cutting it the foreign occupation is here
And the cops are dumb enough to march
Off against the American people holy mackerel
Real quick on the gun man
Listen I have I hope you
Don't mind I started
Just a small website to try to get people
Informed around here
Because just
And I've used a little bit of your information
On there please go to it check it out
It's called
ThePatriotPage.com
We're trying to get people
I've owned to your show
And I'm trying to buy the magazines from you
I'm trying to get everything I can
In hardcore literature I've ordered
All of the discs
I want to get this stuff tangible
So that we can produce this
I've got an IT department
I employ probably 20 people
I'm sick to my stomach with this crap
No I hear you Spence
And God bless you I appreciate your call
Speaking of magazines
Absolutely you know he's saying
Where you've gained your life
Realizing that we're all focused on football
Entertainment, TV
All these petty things
While global corporate combines
Are coming in taking over our government
Socializing the public to make us dependent
While siphoning and skimming
Off the money overseas
We sell the magazine at cost
They're almost sold out the January issue
Just six days into January
Is almost sold out
2013 the year America dies
The last issue came out two weeks
Before the shooting in Connecticut
And said this man wants your guns
And broke down he would use executive orders
To go after your guns
We know our stuff
You can buy these in groups of 10 up to 100
At cost or get a year subscription
And get the next 12 issues at info war store.com
We have the best water filtration systems
Discounted gravity fed systems
You name it
Like propure 10% off with water code
Again the code is water
Again that's info war store.com
Or info war shop.com
Or 888-253-3139
Let's talk to Jeff
In North Dakota
You're on the air Jeff go ahead
Hey Alex how are you doing?
Good
Hey I've been spending about the whole entire day
Trying to get through to these Illinois
Reps about this gun ban
They've just turned their phones off
Yeah they're mafia
I finally did get through to somebody
Sid Matthias' secretary
Or something
She told me the bill did not get called
And I thanked her for the
Information but then you just reported
That they did call the bill
And they went into committee
Well they change stuff all the time
But according to the Illinois state rifle association
And we were watching it and they brought up the bills
A group of bills including that one
And they said we're going to closed session
And cut the video feed
Well you know maybe there's still
Time for us to get some voice in on that
Well my point is
We now have Dianne Feinstein on record
In fact you are up to end the show please
All of them saying Mr. and Mrs. America
Get ready to turn your guns in
They want our guns, the question is why
What do they have planned?
Total implosion, collectivization
Of America
Well give Pierce Morgan
A piece of my mind when you see him
You know what
The last time I flew to New York to be on TV
It was The View
And that was a couple years ago
And they were like okay satellite we really want you to
Fly here and I went no I'm only doing
Satellite and then I thought you know what
I want to be in person talking to that guy
And the first they're like
You'll be alone with him talking and
Now we're going to have you know this guy
Dershowitz or whatever, whatever
I don't care, I'm going to go in there with some
Common sense facts
It'll be the biggest audience they've had in a while
I mean CNN's only got about a half
Million viewers now the derivative of
It the YouTube videos other news picking
It up that'll be tens of millions so I'm
Happy to do it I'm going to fly
Out to New York and
Do that interview
The TSA tries to stop me
Give them a good heads up then I'll just
Do it via satellite oh yeah they I walk
Up and go where are you going what are you doing
And I'll go you know who I am that's right
You're a troublemaker such a free
Country that I'm treated like a convicted
Felon doing a perp walk
At a super max I mean it's just
This whole culture is about
Training you to be a slave
Felix in New York you're our final caller
Go ahead
Thank you Alex just two quick things
First of all my mom just suggested
That you wear a
Don't tread on me either shirt
Or maybe a flag
Because
And secondly I was just
Wondering what time is
Is it being taped or is it going to be live?
I wouldn't do it if it wasn't live
It's 9 o'clock central 8 o'clock
Eastern it's not that I mean
I mean Jesse Ventura goes on there
A lot of other folks on there it should be an interesting
Interview I mean I called for his deportation
So he'll say how dare you
Try to violate my first amendment and I'll say you're trying to
Violate my second amendment you're a foreigner
I'll source the Supreme Court ruling
They'll have
You know Dershowitz come flapping out there
Mr. Torture I mean it's all incredible
Hey Mike Adams tomorrow
11am central 12 noon
Eastern info wars dot com
The big weekday show and I'll be back Tuesday
And Ron Paul's coming up during the week
As well on Wednesday
In the Republic ladies and gentlemen
We'll be right back.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east
But we are still in the eye of the perfect storm
The most devastating economic condition since the Great Depression
America's worst drought in agricultural history
And now the economic results of the presidential election
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from eFoods Direct
And I recommend you do the same
It's time to get your own supply from eFoods Direct
I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food
I'm taking control of my future
And you're nuts if you don't do the same
Go to eFoods Direct dot com forward slash Alex to find the specials
And you can start with a holiday gift pack that's normally 80 dollars now under 50 bucks
Remember I can warn you but I can't feed you
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoods Direct dot com forward slash Alex
Would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late
409-5633 or eFoods Direct dot com forward slash Alex