Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, this again will be one of the most jam-packed transmissions we've
ever engaged in and one of the most important. They are openly announcing at the federal
and state level, and we're gonna go through some of the audio clips, they wanna physically
ban guns and make you turn them in.
We told you that was coming months ago. That's always been their goal. But they're like,
hey, you got a second amendment, you got a right to turn them into us. And hey, Obama
can use existing statutory interpretations with his executive order. So you're wrong
to freak out. That's what they're saying on CNN and MSNBC, that he's going to use executive
orders to curtail your second amendment.
And they're saying, we're just gonna tell the gun manufacturers they can't manufacture
these. That's our power under executive orders. And we're just gonna tell gun shops what they
can and can't do outside of law. We'll call it rulemaking. That's what they've already
been trying the last two years.
Now they're politically just gonna try to ram it through. I also have another article
here out of CBS News where they're announcing that they're getting together $20 million
to begin with from rich megabanks and globalist. Guys, I am that to you, but it may not have
come through cuz I didn't see it.
It was a CBS News article that had Bill Clinton video in it about a national plan to raise
money to pass laws at state level. The point is they're bringing a bunch of money to come
after our guns. They're at the White House right now twisting the arm of the NRA president
to go along with all this.
This is serious, very, very, very, very serious. Now, Doug Hagman is coming up in 30 minutes
and I have not talked to him since I got back from New York. He has talked to his DHS source
who told him that indeed we were under surveillance and was feds, not Bloomberg detectives.
Well, they look like, cuz I've seen Bloomberg's quote detectives like the mafia around him
multiple times in New York covering things. They look like New York detectives to me.
A lot of times they're under the feds. They all looked exactly like they were brothers
or something. I mean, it was just absolute archetype, Goodfellas types, but you could
tell they were cops, like something out of a movie.
And they were in the hotel, they were following us, all this. But I was reading what Doug
Hagman put out on his website. He's gonna be joining us 30 minutes about it. And I didn't
tell anybody what motel or hotel we were staying in. It was a little boutique hotel scene and
put us in. I didn't tell anybody there was a Starbucks catty corner to it.
I didn't tell Hagman this. I didn't tell listeners this. Nobody told anybody this. I hadn't gone
through all the details. In his article, his federal source described it all and that they
were planning to cause a confrontation. That's what my gut told me. I was like, they wanna
cause a confrontation, stay away from them.
So I would literally just turn and walk the other direction, hail a cab, get out. I'd
be walking back, more of them. I mean, they were definitely, and you'd see them, they'd
be looking at a cell phone, looking around. And I mean, they weren't even good at it.
They'd be talking to their sleeve and I'm not looking at you and then start following
you.
People were like, well, go confront them. And we did get one of them on video when we
were coming out of CNN. Well, two more were coming and I just sent a cab and got out of
there because they planned to cause a confrontation. Gotta know when to hold them, know when to
fold them, know when to walk away, know when to run.
You never count your money when you're sitting at the table. They'll be counting enough for
counting when the dealing's done. And the money I'm looking for, the treasure I'm looking
for is liberty. That was another reason I was real angry when I got in there. I was
under the weather, hadn't had a lot of sleep and a bad mood.
And I think overall we did a good job getting in their face. I got sent a little text message,
I ought to get him on the show about it. Billy Corrigan, listener of the show, friend, he
said Alex, you broke people's hypnosis, could have done a better job. John Rapport said
the same thing.
And people said, man, that was really calculated and good how you made that big scene. It was
just I was sick of it. And I was sick of them going, yeah, have him sit out front. Yeah,
look what he's wearing.
I'm like, you're gonna make me look really fat. I mean, it was just they were a bunch
of wolves. I wanted them to know I wasn't gonna sit there and play nice with them. And
so that's what happened. But it's just a huge broadcast today, totally jam packed on so
many fronts. We're gonna launch officially the transmission on the other side of this
quick break.
That's Thursday, the 10th day of January 2013.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At e foods
direct we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm
by having a supply of food on hand after Hurricane Sandy. Danny from New York City wrote almost
all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able
to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one
day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what Alex
has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your
food supply. It's the best tasting non GMO long term storeable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on e foods direct.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog. Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom
lovers. The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse. The
globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover. That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness
items at infowarshop.com. These are items that I did research on that I personally use.
We've got the life straw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go. The
Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out in the
field. Strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen. When disaster strikes by
Matthew Stein. TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological
event. Hand crank shortwave AM FM radios. Everything that we've researched and found
to be the best is available at infowarshop.com and your purchase makes our info war possible.
We're getting prepared. Are you infowarshop.com? I was trained in firearms. I carried a concealed
weapon. I made the determination that if somebody was going to try to take me out, I was going
to take them with me. If I could have gotten 51 votes in the Senate of the United States
for an outright ban, picking up every one of them, Mr. and Mrs. America, turn them all
in, I would have done it. Defending the Republic from enemies, foreign and domestic. It's Alex
Jones. I'm only a man just like you. And I am a soldier of the Republic. And I'm doing
the best I can in French warfare at point blank range against these globalists. For
17 years. And all I ask is that you stand beside me. All I ask is that you recognize
that we're living in total tyranny. You read the headlines today, it sounds like 1984.
I was walking by the bank of televisions we have in there in the newsroom. And I looked
at the lower thirds, and it was police to take blood nationwide without warrants at
checkpoints. And then I'd walk back by and it would be predator drones to be operated
by the UN worldwide. And then I walked back by and it was drones to be armed in the US.
And then I walked back by and it said, Alex Jones, revolution coming. It's just totally
bizarre. How crazy things have gotten. And I got in here about an hour before showtime
this morning and they handed me a email from Doug Hagman of the Northeast Intelligence
Network who runs a nationwide famous private investigation outfit that doesn't work for
the feds and state and local government.
And he described how I was surveilled in New York. And what happened where, things I haven't
even talked about. Because even though I've mentioned being tailed and harassed, it's
quite frankly kind of embarrassing that I ran. But I did it cuz my gut said, get out
of here, they wanna set you up. They can drop something on you, they can stab you, whatever.
And it was clear that they were tracking us by our cell phones. Because whenever I come
around a corner, they'd be looking at the phone and then look up and then walk into
a wall and then start tailing us.
They were following us. Just like when your wife knows your number, she can track you
exactly down to the foot of where you're at. You're driving down a road trying to find
something and your pin is blue, it's moving. Where you're going is the red pin down to
feet. Those systems were designed and put into phones by the Telecommunications Act
of 96. And not only could I tell they were what I've seen New York detectives look like
in videos where they're tailing Luke Rudowski and harassing him.
And when I've been covering events and seen Bloomberg surrounded by them, I knew because
I'd walk around a corner no matter where I went. And there'd be guys getting out of a
car and then going like this and they're looking at their phones. Or I'd walk around a corner,
there'd be guys looking at their phones and looking up.
And then if you looked at them, they'd say, hey, hi, Alex, big fan. And then it'll give
you a dirty look. And then you're walking in, they've got the guys there, you're walking
out, you tell security, I don't wanna go out this door. Bloomberg's people are out there.
And the guy's like, you're going out this door. I go, but that's a mall entrance. It's
right there, I can see out the door. And he goes, I'm not opening that for you. And you
could see the glass out into the mall.
And I said, I wanna go over there. And he said, I'm not gonna open that door. I said,
fine, get your camera rolling. So we started to go out the other door and got one shot
of a guy you see talking into his windbreaker. And then he turns as we walk out, and he sees
the camera and puts his face in the wall.
People say, well, why not confront him? I look down the street and two more of them
are coming up going, that's him. And I'm like, whoa, cops aren't this confident unless they're
about to set something up. And I just said, please, God, let there be a taxi, cuz taxis
never stop.
And I went like this and a taxi stopped. We got in and got out of there. And do the review
and the tape, I said, try to get some footage. I mean, and again, we get to the hotel, now
the street's blocked off, little bitty boutique hotel they put us in. There's a Starbucks
right there. And we went, got our bags, went and got a cab, and said, go to New Jersey
because that's where our flight was out of anyways.
That's where the main direct flights out of Austin go to Newark. Went to a hotel, got
out of there. And that happened, and then Doug Hagman, I haven't even told one-tenth
story, sends me an email saying, this is what my federal source said. This is what they
did to you. Good thing you didn't go to the Starbucks across the street because that's
where they were gonna set you up with a woman who's gonna come up and get in your face.
And then they only use selective video of me saying get back or whatever to make me
look like I'm attacking a woman. And they've tried that before, folks. I mean, this is
right out of movies, which is based on the real story in JFK, where the district attorney
Garrison goes in the bathroom at the airport.
And the guy starts running in the stall trying to have sex with him, and then he runs out.
And then the police are like, hey, stop, but by then he's already gone. And see, if you
haven't lived this, ladies and gentlemen, you don't know. And you've seen the footage
of us tailed, and then they go ahead and pull us over in Canada, and it's cops, or they
arrest us, or Bilderberg Group Security is talking to their lapels and following us,
getting in the car, speeding after us, Secret Service questioning us, Bohemian Grove.
I told you that I went with History Channel and that they got arrested, and I jumped in
the river and swam off. And later, six months later, they air the piece. And sure enough,
there's the video of it. People are like, well, where's your footage? I'm sorry, I jumped
in the river.
I mean, I wasn't going to jail with the police. I mean, this is the real life I live, okay?
It's real. And I know for those of you that have not been on the front lines as a real
journalist, I'm not trying to make it Gonzo journalism, where I'm the story. Believe me,
I want nothing more than to not be here and to not have to do this.
I want nothing more than to just live in a free country. You know how creepy it is to
have multiple people, including an ambassador's daughter on Piers Morgan two nights ago, talking
about how great it would be to see me shot and killed and how I need to be popped. And
those security people, their little CIA style FBI suits at CNN, I'm telling them, I want
to go out the mall entrance, because I've seen that, and I go, I want to go out in the
open mall.
And they go, no, you're not, you're not, you're not. And I go, no, I want to go, okay, okay,
we'll go by there. And I go, okay, there it is. They go, I'm not opening that door, because
I have to open it for you. And I went, come on, and the guy just laughed. He goes, no,
you're going out there. And he was really excited, you're going out there.
And he walks out, and you see, again, some guys turn this way, and this other guy walks
in the wall, and I walk out and more are coming. And then he was trying to stop me. We're starting
to go to the cabin, he goes, wait, wait. And I go, what? And he goes, give me your badges,
or little paper badges that have to be, and I just threw it at him.
But the point is, and then he's looking as I drive off like, I mean, it's just trash.
They all want to play Mafia. Well, you know what, I got there, I covered it, I got the
information out. We're going to analyze and go through the little bit of footage we do
have. Do put some of it out. The first night he was back, actually. But this is the type
of stuff we deal with.
And I have been so busy fighting the globalist. Since I got back, you'll have to bear with
me that everybody's got these incredible chest colds right now. And I've had this one for
weeks. I thought it was just allergy related, but actually had a fever last night. So I'm
not complaining.
I just want you to know I am under the weather here. If you hear the wheezing and stuff on
air or occasional coughing, it's just too important at times to not be here. John is
with the chest colds where you've got to focus just not to go into a coughing fit on air.
But Hagman's joining us coming up. I thought I would play first a clip just to remind you
that after this happens, they come on the next night and talk about how they want to
pop me.
How great it would be to see Piers Morgan in a uniform killing me. Because that's their
fantasy, the state, the power, the uniform. We're gonna execute you like somebody in a
ditch in Nazi Germany. Let's queue up. Buzz Bissinger says, popping, and they agree, clip
number three.
And then we're gonna go to a compilation of Rob Dew that he aired last night of Doug Hagman
from the 27th saying they're getting ready to go after even physically pro gun groups.
And then tied into Conan O'Brien attacking me, putting a gun in my hand with a computer
animation and all the rest of it. But here is Buzz Bissinger, here it is.
But what do you need a semi-automatic weapon for? The only reason I think you need it is
Pierce, challenge Alex Jones to a boxing match, show up with a semi-automatic that you got
legally and pop him.
I'd love to see that, in uniform.
I'll borrow my brother's uniform.
I don't think guns are worth more than the answer.
There you go, I'll borrow my brother's uniform. And then there's the part about, we hope his
kids don't get killed one night. We hope his kids don't kill him really, I hope they don't
get killed. And on and on and on and on and on.
And-
I don't want Alex Jones to get the phone call at 3 o'clock in the morning that one of his
children have been shot and killed by somebody who shouldn't have a handgun or a rifle or
a automatic weapon. I don't want him to get that.
Yeah, thank you for talking about my kids in the same episode. I mean, a five year old
would understand exactly what all this is about. And then I get this, I mean, Doug Hagman
definitely has the sources, he says, cuz the sources I have send me a Homeland Security
document or a tip.
But I mean, Doug Hagman on the East Coast, I mean, he describes what happened here. I
mean, sure, there are a lot of Starbucks in New York and things, but I mean, he described
that there was a Starbucks right by the hotel and that's where they were planning to confront
me.
I mean, imagine we show up and the streets are blocked around our little hotel, a little
boutique hotel. And there's more guys out front and I walk in, there's more guys inside.
These weren't guys in dark suits that were the bellman or the hotel security. They had
eyes for you know who. And it just went on and on. I was like, wow, what are they planning?
What were they planning?
Well, he says he knows that all his DHS sources, they were gonna get into a confrontation with
me. And my gut was don't let them get in a conversation with you. They're gonna set you
up somehow. Whether it was drugs or say that crackhead shot me, I don't know. But man,
they were so angry and these guys were looking at me like they wanted to kill me.
And again, this is what they want to do to all of us. They hate the fact we've got guns
and they can't just go around arresting us all. You notice they're all saying gun owners
are the new terrorists, conservatives, libertarians, new terrorists. That's all the homeland security.
And if gun owners cower to this, if we get into this, it's over. This is a mafia takeover.
That's what the new world order is. It's an organized crime syndicate takeover. We've
got all the clips where they're announcing, yeah, we're gonna go after your guns.
And no, the president can't take your guns with an executive order CNN said this morning.
They can use existing rulings with an executive order to take your guns. Just amazing spin.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at e foods
direct. We hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm
by having a supply of food on hand after hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York city wrote, almost
all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my e foods just in time to
be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than
one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what Alex
has done. Call 800-409-5633 today, or go to e foods direct.com slash Alex and build your
food supply is the best tasting non-GMO long-term storeable food on the planet. Call 800-409-5633
or e foods direct.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on e foods direct. American
gardeners and fellow Patriots make the right choice with your money, time and your family
food supply. Choose 100% pure heirloom seeds in the survival seed vault from my Patriots
supply.com. Why spin more? The survival seed vault from my Patriots supply.com is only
$37.95. It includes 20 varieties of pure Hardy, easy to grow heirloom seeds. Yes, only $37.95
that's 70% less than our competitors. You could buy three survival seed vaults for less
than one of theirs. The survival seed vault from my Patriots supply.com includes detailed
planting and seed saving instructions and ship same day. Plus all orders over $49 ship
free. My Patriots supply.com is American owned by Patriots like you passionate about freedom
and preparedness. Call now 866-229-0927. That's 866-229-0927 or discover more emergency preparedness
items when you order at my Patriots supply.com. Choose the original, choose the survival seed
vault at my Patriots supply.com. hempusa.org has a newly designed website and a new and
improved detoxification product. Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins,
minerals, iodine and probiotics. And we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder
absolutely free micro plant powder only at hempusa.org. Call 908-691-2608. That's 908-691-2608
and see what our powder seeds and oil can do for you only at hempusa.org. This offer
ends January 31. Hi, this is Ted Anderson. Have you ever wondered why banks stockbrokers
investment advisors won't talk about gold IRAs? They've been available since 1986 yet
the financial industry won't recognize the value of gold for your retirement. Gold is
outperform paper investments yet no word about IRAs. If you would like to have gold for your
retirement call 800-686-2237. Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns
call 800-686-2237. Secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237. Is this the year you
finally get serious about your family's drinking water? If so, keep listening for a special
offer from big Berkey water filters. Did you know that over 60% of municipal water is fluoridated?
Berkey water filters distinguish themselves from many other filtration systems with the
capability to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine, fluoride, arsenic and disinfection
byproducts from municipal water via the black Berkey and PF line of filters. Then there's
affordability. At only 1.7 cents per gallon, Berkey water filters purify treated and untreated
water, even stagnant pond water. Stop and think how much money you could save by simply
reducing buying bottled water and using water filtered by your Berkey water filter. No need
to be constantly replacing expensive filters with a Berkey. A single set of filters can
last for 5 to 10 years. Choose the best size Berkey for your needs at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
And right now all GCN listeners get 5% off all ceramic filter systems. Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY.
That's 877-99-BERKEY or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com. Free shipping on every order over $50. Big
Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean water.
We're back live, Alex Jones here. We're going to get into all the attacks, the talk of executive
orders, Cuomo, getting all excited, saying we're going to get their guns. Yay! Well,
I thought I wasn't supposed to get excited. I thought I wasn't supposed to get in their
face. You know, we're told sit down, shut up, be gentlemanly while we are basically
gang raped financially and politically by the New World Order.
Our forebears went to war over being disarmed. Imagine some of these ninnying mainline conservatives
that are like, Alex shouldn't have gotten in his face. Well, our country wouldn't even
exist if people hadn't gotten in the red coat's face. We've gotten here by laying down and
becoming comfortable with basically anything.
Let me tell you, have you noticed no other national TV has wanted me on? Even though
Piers Morgan's ratings doubled to a million from 500,000, his highest ratings ever the
night after I was on. Next night 800 and something thousand, it's already dropping. You think
they'd all want me on?
They were crying, they were panicked, they were hyperventilating because they want to
keep you in an NPR trance. Smart guy Billy Corrigan sent me a text message, he said,
right after it, he said, you just broke the hypnosis best I ever saw. I didn't even intend
to do that.
But that's what it did, it breaks the comfort zone, it gets us up, it gets us awake. They
use the Lord of the Rings analogy like when Wormer Grimewood has got the King of Gondar,
or the King of Rohan is in a trance and he's like, I'm old, I can't fight the evil. And
Gandalf breaks the spell and says, arise.
And then the weakness leaves his eyes. We need to pray to God to break this spell the
globalist to put over us, that's what it is. We need a pep rally for liberty. That's why
they wanted to intimidate me and set me up because they know they're finally going from
he doesn't exist to this guy has a giant audience, tens of millions.
We've got to stop him, he's dangerous. Glenn Beck saying the same thing, cuz they all come
from the same area wanting to act like there's separation between these groups. They're factions
of the same sewage line. And here is a compilation of clips from Doug Hagman on where this is
coming up in a minute, from the 27th.
And then everything he talked about coming true with Colonel Bryan, 28, putting a gun
in my hand on the show like I was shooting him. I mean, this is the type of stuff that
he said, that's funny, but it's the image it sells. Here is Hagman talking about what
was coming in the future, here it is.
My source told me pretty much exactly what their plans are and what their contingency
plans are. They've got plan A, B, C, and D, whereas one of my sources calls that a no
single point failure. So they're gonna come at us on multiple levels. It's just not gonna
be the legislative level.
It's going to be through executive orders, through global initiatives, through health
initiatives. It's really an insidious situation.
If the president is going to act, there are executive orders, executive action that can
be taken. We haven't decided what that is yet.
And they're not only coming after the guns, Alex, they're coming after the mouthpieces.
They're coming after the Alex Joneses of the world and Doug Hagman's and others who speak
the truth.
But tonight, I'll go head to head with a man who actually wants to deport me for having
these very views.
They are going to marginalize us before they take us down. They're going to make us look
foolish, to make us look like fools on the internet before they pull the plug, obviously.
Now the two men debated gun control. I'm not 100% sure, but I think Alex was the one who
took the pro-gun position.
And I'm here to tell you, 1776 will commence again if you try to take off firearms. We
will not relinquish them. Do you understand? Stalin took the guns, Mao took the guns.
No one's taking away all the guns, according to my source, the very first people to be
rounded up.
The very first targets, if you will, on the radar of this regime are the people that are
speaking the truth about what's taking place. Alex Jones, Doug Hagman and others like us
who are getting to the heart of the matter, we are the targets for not only the censorship,
but for what's coming after that.
What's coming after that is the actual, the physical part of it to take us out of the
fight before it really begins.
Challenge Alex Jones to a boxing match, show up with a semi-automatic that you got legally
and pop them.
I'd love to see that, in uniform.
There you go, and if you're a radio listener, we were putting articles up during that Fox
News YouTube gun enthusiast shooting death spurs hunt for suspect. He owned a gun making
factory, FPS Russian, he was the guy behind it all, tied down in a chair, shot in the
back of the head.
Some evidence is coming out, tortured, no guns or money taken. Another top manufacturer
of firearms who was going public, exposing government, drugging of the kids being behind
it, he is dead now. And it looks like some more deaths are developing. We're going to
be breaking all this down, ladies and gentlemen. If this continues, it's not just a pattern,
we know what's going on.
We're going to talk to Doug Hagman straight ahead. He has a federal source that knew exactly
what they were planning to do to me in New York.
We're on the march. The empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Lots of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad
spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver
solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning
and help improve wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day,
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as stress, death,
pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the ability to terminate
entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal
or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ
fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go
to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off. That's
SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die? Start purifying your water with ProPure. My friends, I've done
a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is ProPure and it's available
discounted at infowars.com. Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required. It's NSF 42 certified. Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride
up to 95%. Easy to set up and use. Doesn't require electricity. Purify water from lakes,
streams, ponds and wells. This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic. ProPure
is the best gravity fed filter out there. It's what my family uses. Infowars.com already
has the lowest price on ProPure but if you add the promo code WATER at checkout you get
an additional 10% off at infowars.com. You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cow
Bend Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog. Crashing through the lies and disinformation,
it's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are live and we are broadcasting worldwide. And we're gonna go
through some clips here. We've got Doug Hagman of the Northeast Intelligence Network on the
line with us. And I got an email from him today and it's up on his website right now.
Kurt Nemo is gonna be posting it at infowars.com and getting it out to folks. And we're also
gonna give you his website so you can go look it up for yourself, but it's homelandsecurityus.com.
And that night when I went on Piers Morgan, the first two or three times somebody pops
out of a doorway and says, hey, I'm a big fan. You're just walking down a random street
and they look just like a undercover cop. And one time you see the gun on their side.
You're like, okay, but then when you start seeing guys in your hotel looking at you like
they wanna kill you and they're obviously off duty police or detective types. And then
when you notice you're being followed or you notice they're out front CNN and when you
come out, they're out there. We even have some footage of one of these guys.
It gets really crazy. And my gut was, and my dad never calls me, not when I snuck in
Bohemian Grove. He knew I was about to do it, not when I'm at Bilderberg. My dad called
me and said, you know what, I think you oughta watch your back and get out of New York as
quick as you can. I said, well, it's funny, we're flying out of New Jersey in the morning.
I'm gonna go ahead and just go to another hotel there. I'm leaving now. So that went
on.
Then the next night, and I've played this clip at Nauseam. We'll play it again coming
up here in a few minutes. I am simply watching the next episode of Piers Morgan. And one
guy says, man, gee, I hope his kids don't get killed some night. And I'm thinking, that's
not a veiled threat.
Well, that was creepy the way they said that. And then they go to the next guest, they go,
yeah, you oughta get a gun and pop him, shoot him. And then the other guest goes, yeah,
and you can wear a uniform. And Piers like, I'll get my brother's uniform. I guess he's
in the military or something. And it's just all bizarre.
And then these tweets, people say they wanna kill me and all this stuff. The point is,
is this really went on. I've been all over the place. I've gone in Bullhorned Buckingham
Palace in the Parliament. I've gone and been there when there's mass arrest at the DNC
in New York. I've gone and been covering the DNC in Denver.
And guys run up and start screaming, kill Michelle Malkin with video shooting from in
front with a guy right behind me. I'm like, why is he behind me screaming, kill Michelle
Malkin? Well, it was so they could put it out instantly on the wires. The news just
went with it.
It was a setup saying I said, kill her. So I've learned about dirty tricks. And thank
God we had our own footage later, put it out showing I wasn't saying that it was guys behind
me by the grace of God. They tried to destroy me with that. It was like the headlines were.
The end of Alex Jones, he says, kill woman. Now we were in a boutique hotel CNN put us
in. And I'm checking into this thing at like four o'clock in the afternoon Monday, and
I'm looking around me.
I'm looking around me. And I see, I mean, have you been to enough events to cover stuff,
you know what detectives look like. And you know what they look like in New York City.
And you know what they look like when they're undercover. They stick out like sore thumbs
with windbreakers or sports jackets and they're looking at you.
You can tell they're accustomed to authority and doing whatever they want, especially in
New York. And if you say something to them, they're like, hey, how you doing? I mean,
it's ridiculous. Or you walk out the door and they see you and start talking in their
sleeve and then turn and then walk into a wall.
I mean, yeah, absolutely. In fact, if you're a TV watcher, he's gonna roll some of the
video on one of the guys. As we leave CNN Center, I'm like, hey, start rolling. I see
one of them. Dude turns the camera on instantly. And the guy talking into his sleeve, he then
goes back. I don't know if dude got it, but he starts walking into the wall.
As soon as he sees the camera, he turns and walks into the wall to get away from the camera.
And then there are two more guys coming up. So I hail a taxi. You can even see it. See
the taxi? That taxi's pulling up with the grace of God. I hail it and get in as more
guys dressed just like him.
I imagine you're walking around town and these guys come out of doorways and go, hey, Alex,
how you doing? Obviously, always looking down at their cell phones. You say, well, some
of them could have been listers. Yeah, maybe one out of the seven or whatever. And then
it's not on tape, but he turns, his dude starts going over to him for a second and walking
into the wall.
And I said, dude, I remember doing that. I said, dude, come on. I'm like taxi. And see,
I'm looking back right there at two more guys coming up the street dressed just like him
so they can all recognize each other. Okay, and then I look down the street and I see
the taxi. I hail it, it stops, I get out of there. Unbelievable, and you see me right
there looking back.
And dude was gonna confront him and my instinct was, get out of here. Normally, I'll confront
him. I'm like, wait a minute, they're turf right outside. Why are they doing this? Boom,
it happens. Okay, that said, Doug, I'm gonna give you the floor to roll. I want you to
go through the entire write up that your source gave you, what this signifies, and I'm gonna
play some of the clips here, okay?
I wanna play some of the clips here, but I'm gonna give you the floor till we go to break
in about ten minutes. Because if I ever start interrupting, I'll just interrupt. I want
you to go through your story because here's what happened. Sure, there are 100 Starbucks
in New York or more.
I was in a little boutique about ten blocks away from there, no Starbucks around, right
on the corner. We come back, the road is blocked around the hotel suddenly. There's more of
these guys out there. I see people looking at me out the Starbucks, and I said, this
is a setup.
And dude's like, yeah, let's get out of here. I don't know what they were planning. But
your guy, from everything he said, now I know you're 100% for real. Because there's stuff
in here I didn't tell anybody. But because, quite frankly, it sounds crazy, but I knew
I had to get out of there, so I shot the video before I left the hotel, picked my bags up
and left.
So Northeast Intelligence Network, law enforcement, certified, 30 years, private investigator,
working with the feds, the state, you name it. Doug Hagman, you were here with us a week
and a half ago, on the 27th and 28th. You said they're gonna start targeting us with
dirty tricks, but also physically.
Now there's been prominent deaths with the number one gun show in the world that was
pro Second Amendment, the guy that runs it, killed execution style, others being killed.
What is happening, Doug Hagman, you have the floor.
All right, Alex, well, thank you for having me. And I gotta tell you, I was quite surprised.
I did catch your appearance on Piers Morgan. I had no idea where you were staying. I had
no idea what your itinerary was, who you're with, or whatever.
We have not talked until now. Exactly, exactly.
I couldn't get a hold of you yesterday, go ahead.
Yeah, I was away yesterday. And when I had contacted my DHS source, the individual who
had given me the information, I appeared on your show with last time. And he said, I wanna
tell you something that I found out is very disturbing. And if you could relay this to
Mr. Jones and the gentleman that he was traveling with.
Now, apparently, you were traveling with another individual. I don't know. My information,
direct information from you is zero. And in terms of the situation is kind of spotty anyway.
So I'm not exactly certain other than what he told me. He said, look, here's the deal.
He said, your itinerary, Alex, your itinerary, as soon as the wheels were down in New York,
you were under active surveillance by at least two federal agencies.
One of the two being the Department of Homeland Security. Three men teams of surveillance.
We don't know how many, I was not told how many total agents were involved in this, but
you were under active surveillance. But not only just covert surveillance, because that's
normal surveillance. This was a bumper lock type surveillance. And I wrote a textbook
on surveillance that's used for law enforcement training as well as college courses for Homeland
Security.
So I understand the different types of surveillance we're talking about. But bumper lock surveillance
is where you make your presence known to the subject you're following. And the words from
my source were this. The instructions to the teams were bumper lock him, make it obvious.
Do whatever you can, just make sure he knows. Handle him as a hostile. Which tells me that
they wanted you to know that you were being followed, at least during part of the operation.
Now from what I sense and what I had deducted from my conversation with my source, there
were a couple of different operations going on here. The first of all was the attempt
to psychologically intimidate you. Now from what I understand, and again, I don't know
if you recorded it, I don't know what time, if it was live or whatever, but some of this
happened before the surveillance happened, obviously before the interview as well as
after the interview.
But the bumper lock type of surveillance, the physical intimidation, was especially
before the interview. And I suspect that would be to destabilize you, to kind of keep you
off guard. And that's what that was. But you had three-man teams actually, three-man teams
of operatives following you around. Now the other part of this, the other side of this
story, and this is something that didn't shock me, didn't really surprise me, but alerted
me, and I alluded to this in our interview the last time we spoke, was you were going
to be set up, Alex, and that's the long and short of it, you were going to be set up.
It's important that you were to know that there was a woman by a Starbucks. And again,
I don't know where you were, I don't know if you passed a Starbucks or if you were in
New York City. But apparently, you were to be accosted by or have some sort of physical
altercation with a female in front of or near a Starbucks. Now I know that they're prolific
in New York City. I guess it wouldn't be a stretch, but nonetheless, if one was close
to the studio or your hotel or whatever, I would imagine, or however, if you pass by
one.
With the intent, Alex, to make you look to embarrass you, in other words, and there was
a video surveillance too, let me just reinforce that. In addition to the obvious overt bumper
lock surveillance, there was a video surveillance. So the intent of this female was to accost
you in a way that you would have to push her off or do something to get her away from you.
That would then be on videotape or on disc, on security camera, covert surveillance, footage
taken covertly, and then used against you to marginalize you, to show that you were
a violent man, to show that you're out of control. And the fact that it would be a woman
makes it even more hideous.
And then that's what my source told me. That's with respect to your presence in New York
City. That's also my understanding. And I don't know this for a fact that this also
was interstate, or yes, interstate, and also may have involved another state, New Jersey,
where they crossed the state lines into New Jersey as well. But the fact of the matter
is the orders for surveillance came from the higher levels of DHS. This was a DHS sanctioned
operation.
This is not an NYPD thing. Now, it's possible that the NYPD-
Okay, I mean, they just look like NYPD detectives I'd seen. They didn't look like feds. I mean,
they look like scary guys.
Oh, I'm sure they did. And it's also possible too. I did not get a lot of details. The contact
I had with my source was pretty short, pretty narrow in terms of information, pretty abrupt.
But that's the bottom line, that this was a DHS headed operation involving at least
one other federal agency. And by the way, there was coordination. And I don't know,
I'm not familiar with CNN or their security staff, but there was coordination there with
building security as well.
Oh, no, the guy was laughing at me. I said, listen, I want to go out. I saw a mall entrance
because it's built onto a giant mall. I said, I want to go out there. And they said, no,
you're going out there and really enjoyed shoving me out on the street with one guy
that turned and walked into the wall looking right at us. Two more guys, by the grace of
God, I got that cab. My instinct said, get in the cab, get out of here.
You did well. I mean, follow that little voice, but you did well because had you fallen into
any one of these traps that they had set up for you, things could have turned dramatically
different for you. And this is one thing too, that the high profile people, the gun owners,
the people that speak out, the proponents of the second amendment, the proponents of
the constitution, we are in trouble. We are targets for this kind of thing. And people
think, oh, this doesn't happen. No, it happens all the time. Well, not all the time. It happens
more than you think. And it's sanctioned activity because what better way, what better way can
they take us out of the fight by marginalizing us by push a woman or you're caught doing
something. They take the video and edit it so it looks
a little bit different. And what I have seen are clips from the late night show that you'd
shown where you had a gun in your hand. Shooting people in there.
Yeah, it's ridiculous. So you know the capabilities obviously of what they're capable of.
Why do you think the next night they came on and make cryptic statements about my children
being killed at night and then cryptic statements about how they all want to shoot me and kill
me and how much fun it would be? I don't have any direct information on that.
So what I would say would be speculation. But once again, there's a destabilization
factor to keep you off focus, off target. And we see this happen to others a lot. When
you're fixated on a target, the most vulnerable thing, the most vulnerable you can be is when
they start talking about your wife, your children, your parents, if they're elderly, they do
this and they do it intentionally and maliciously with the intent to get you focused on something
else and to even perhaps intimidate you into silence.
This is not by accident. Those comments, for as many people, and it's funny because you
could have someone in a studio, and I've seen this happen before in other situations, you
can have somebody in a studio that they're told to say something about, oh, just go ahead
and make a joke about, we know he's got kids or make a joke, we know he's got a family.
Go ahead and make a joke with the family, if you can fit it in there. It's done by design
and it's done to intimidate.
No, that's exactly what they do. And so why does your DHS source reach out to you on this
because they were concerned?
Absolutely. My source is a God-fearing Christian man. He knows what's going on. He doesn't
like it. He understands that there is a need for security for the United States, but there's
not a need for this out-of-control, tyrannical, gun-grabbing police state that we are involved
in.
What do you make of SPS Russian, the head guy behind it being killed execution style,
tied down in a chair, shot in the back of the head, nothing stolen from his factory?
I gotta tell you, Alex, the first time I heard about it was yesterday. In fact, when I heard
part of your program, I gotta tell you, I'm very concerned about this. I do think as we
talked earlier about the purge, I think that there is a purge taking place.
And as some of the more high profile people, they will set examples. They will take people
out.
And they canceled three gun shows that were top shows on Discovery. Another top manufacturer
died very mysteriously. I've got that article out of Military Times. I mean, this is starting
to get a little crazy. If we see a couple more of these, we know it's like a Clinton
deathless type deal against gun owners.
This is a globalist mafia we're dealing with. And if they can't get it legislatively, or
if we won't go along with an executive order, I guess they think they're just gonna start
going after us.
And they think that they can get away with it. The hubris behind these people is something
to be reckoned with and to be recognized. But that's also indicative of their weakness
as well. We have to understand that these people are psychopaths. I mean, really, they're
real psychopaths. The way they think, and people might think I'm crazy, but the Luciferian
satanic agenda, that mindset, folks, that's real.
It is. Stay there, investigative reporter and investigator.
Hi, this is Alex Jones. Did you know that the global elite are now storing non-hybrid
seeds in secret storage vaults near the Arctic Circle? Did you know that in a real meltdown,
non-hybrid seeds could become more valuable than silver or gold? It's true, seeds have
outperformed even gold and silver before in this country, and it's possible they could
even happen again. So our friends at Solutions from Science have put together the perfect
mix of non-hybrid seeds. They call it a survival seed bank, and it can produce an endless supply
of nutrient-dense food for you and your family. And here's the best part. These seeds have
not been genetically modified in any way, and you actually get enough seeds to plant
a full acre crisis garden. So visit them today at survivalseedbank.com. That's survivalseedbank.com.
Or give them a call at 877-327-0365. That's 877-327-0365. Remember, in a real crisis,
non-hybrid seeds are the ultimate barter item. This is Alex Jones for survivalseedbank.com.
We can buy GMOs stressed out about money and blasted by the electric environment. Hi, I'm
Pastor Jenny, and that was the state I was in back in 2010. Then I learned about RNA
drops. I learned that 97% of my DNA that scientists have called junk is actually packed with millions
of gene switches that play a critical role in controlling how my cells, organs, and other
tissues behave. I learned I don't have to put up with disease decay or decline like
I'd been conditioned to believe. I began taking RNA drops, a 100% natural formula designed
to turn on those switches and provide me with amazing health and joy. Learn more about RNA
drops and order a free sample today. Visit RNAfreesample.com. That's RNAfreesample.com.
Or call toll-free, 888-577-3703. Pay only shipping and handling for a free 30-day supply
of RNA drops. Get the information you need and the health you want at RNAfreesample.com.
You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa, where a nicely furnished cabin
with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine, and laundry service awaits. After
a good night's sleep, your adventure begins. You're on a golden stag safari for big game.
But it's not Africa. It's Argentina. One-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo, cougar, bighorn
rams, wild boar, and the biggest stag deer in South America. All gold medal quality.
All the action you can handle. Land rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages,
hunting guides, ground transportation included, and more. All more affordable than you can
imagine. The adventure of a lifetime starts at goldenstagsafaris.com. The big game hunting
ranch, goldenstagsafaris.com. They don't want to see us tonight. All they want us to do
is keep on pushing us higher. They don't want to see us live together. All they want us
to do is keep on killing one another. All they want us to do is... Here's another song.
I saw Sheriff John Brown coming down the street with a gun in his hand. You know that song?
I shot the sheriff. What was I to do? He drew on me. See, we're supposed to just bend over
to all this. And the American people aren't going to do that. And I'll say this on air.
I probably in hindsight, I watched Larry Pratt last night destroy Piers Morgan. And at the
end, he said, you're not my friend to him because he knew he'd been beaten. I wish I
could do that more. And sometimes I've gone on shows and been very calm.
But when you're got a chest cold, when you're angry, when you've just been messed with on
the street, by detective after detective or whatever they were popping out of the dark,
and you see all this, just the disgustingness of it, you get angry. And you know what, when
we need to get out of our coma, I know a lot of limbing Americans sit there and they see
somebody like me getting angry and they go, that's scary.
You know what's scary is the drones in our skies and the NSA spying on us. And people
don't even think I snuck into Bohemian Grove because they can't believe anything real was
done. They can't believe I made films that have been seen, some of them 40, 50 million
times online. I mean, I'm real. You're real. We can beat these globalists. But be honest,
Doug Hagman, about, as you said, my performance on air, I think overall, like Billy Corgan
said, it shocks people out of their hypnosis.
I think overall it's gonna be positive, cuz folks can say, hey, makes gun owners look
like aggressive people. Folks, our founders tarred and feathered people before the revolution.
Our founders killed people that tried to take their rights. I'm not calling for that. What
would they think of our founders today? I mean, I simply was there saying, look, I'm
off the script.
I know you want our guns to enslave us. Knock it off. And plus a foreigner here lecturing
us and putting out tweets about how Americans are stupid scum and how he's conquering us.
I mean, I'm angry at him. I'm angry I gotta risk my life up against these people. I'm
angry they act like they care about us all day when they're a bunch of authoritarians.
Doug, your take on this.
One thing I have to say, Alex, I can guarantee you this. I do a radio show with my son every
night and we were talking and one of the things that came up was this. When you said Piers
Morgan, the hatchet man for the new world order, I can guarantee you that phrase will
be remembered and remembered throughout television history.
I can guarantee you that numerous things that you said will be remembered. But how many
people for the next guest, I believe it was Sheriff Joe Arpaio, how many people remember
what he said? Not too many, but how many people remembered what you said? All the viewers.
So was mission accomplished in that respect? I believe it was.
Exactly. They were crying, fuming, melting down. He looked like he'd had his blood drained
and none of the national TVs invited me on. I mean, if I'm so discrediting, why not have
me on?
Sure. And you know, the anger issue, at what point? What's it going to take for Americans
to get angry? I mean, we're seeing our mothers, our daughters, our aunts, our grandmothers
being fondled at the airports. We're being treated like slaves. We're being physically
molested. We have women, our wives. I mean, we're the men in this country. Where is the
anger? It's easy to sit behind a keyboard to develop beer mussels, virtual beer mussels
behind a keyboard, Alex. It's simple for somebody to do that. Sit back here and second guess
anybody, second guess you, second guess me and say, well, you know, whatever. But the
bottom line is this. We need to be angry. We need to show that anger. And the anger
is a righteous anger.
Well, it's more than that. We're getting to the end of the line here.
Yes.
Okay. I mean, there's two lights in the tunnel. One's a trend that's going to run us over.
The other's a juncture. And we got to get, I mean, I know my life's on the line. I know
this stuff's real. I know those detectives are real. I know the death threats are real
and I'm angry. I know Piers Morgan works for the new world order. I don't like it.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action.
Tyranny is here. The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality. It really says
that the state is God. The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most
oppressive police states on earth. This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret
network of FEMA camps now being expanded nationwide. This documentary exposes how the continuity
of government program has established an all powerful shadow state. Police state four chronicles
the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen. Prepare to enter the secretive
world of emergency dictatorship, body scammers, sound cameras, citizen spies, stage terror
and cameras on every street corner. It's only the beginning of the new world order's hellish
plan. The police state isn't coming. It's here. Secure your copy today at info.wars.com
or see it online in the highest quality at prisonplanet.tv. Waging war on corruption,
Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. Big brother, mainstream media, government cover ups. You
want answers? Well, so does he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live
from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, we got five more minutes with Doug Hagman joining us. You don't understand, ladies
and gentlemen, you know, Rob Dozle. I think we're being followed by those guys. Those
guys are cops. And I'm like, yeah, they've been at the hotel since the time we got here.
You know, you're in a hotel checking in, you're tired, you don't feel good. You wanna go lay
down for an hour. And then there's guys, obviously police, looking at you.
You're just like, hopefully they're just in here for some reason. Then you notice they're
talking into their sleeves cuz they all get into secret. Just a note, people ever wanna
be quote spies? The really good ones are like old ladies and stuff and aren't sitting there
talking into their sports jackets. I mean, it's so ridiculous.
They all get into these movies. They think they're 007 or something. That's not how the
real world works. I'm an agent of the Republic. I'm a vestigial left over of Americana, just
there desperately in my own ham-fisted way trying to fight these people. And look, man,
I don't do the best job a lot of days, I told you that.
You can analyze it, either say it was a great victory or a great defeat. All I know is I'm
stumbling into the arena, man, after a lot of hard battles already exhausted. I'm like
a quarterback that's been in 12 games in a row and has got both shoulders blown and my
knees blown.
And I'm there getting run over. And people are like, look at him down on the field stumbling
around. Hey, man, there's a war going on. That's all I can tell you. And I think the
course is to get upset and get in their face. And that's what scares the system so much.
They'll try to spin getting upset is bad. And it is bad to some people out there that
have been limingized. But Doug Hagman, Northeast Intelligence Network, any other points you'd
like to add about what happened and what is happening?
Do you think talking about this will stop them from trying to set me up?
Well, it can't hurt any Alex. I mean, their agenda is what their agenda is. They're out
to marginalize anyone who is speaking out proponents of the Second Amendment, the First
Amendment, speaking out against tyranny, speaking out against the truth, what they're doing
in the shadows. We need to keep doing it. You need to keep doing it. We need to pray
for you, Alex, because you're at the tip of the spear. And I think we all need to play
our zones or particular positions.
But you know, you can only last so long out there at the tip of the spear by yourself.
We need reinforcements. We need to back you up. We need to back each other up. We have
to realize that we're all in this together. I don't want to be trite, but you know how
they say if we don't-
Hang together, we hang separate.
Exactly. And that's what it is. These people can be intimidated back into submission. They're
trying desperately to fulfill their objective.
They're trying to bully us. We have got to righteously get them back in line.
That's right. And I think too, Alex, just in my personal opinion, we're fighting a spiritual
battle as well in addition to the earthly battle. And I think we have to recognize that
this is pure evil what's going on out there. And it's just we need to not only fight on
a practical level, but we need to pray on a spiritual level. Certainly our prayers are
with you.
Well, my gut told me just get away from those, because I'm usually the type that just confronts,
but I thought, well, they could set me up with something. I mean, what do you think
they might have been trying to do? Just drop something on me or what?
I really think the issue with the Starbucks, again, I don't know the geography where you
were if there was one around you.
There was a Starbucks right on the corner and they blocked the streets off around the
hotel and there were guys watching when we even came up.
That bothers me the most, because I think that whatever they had planned involved getting
you on videotape, perhaps shoving, like I said, shoving a woman or bear, or it would
have appeared that you were bullying a woman. And that bothers me because if they can set
you up in that fashion, they can set anyone up.
They did that with Michelle Malkin. Yes. Well, yes. They had guys because I wasn't as sophisticated
even five years ago at the DNC. Like why are these guys standing behind me screaming? And
they were, we caught them on, we got the tape going, kill Michelle Malkin and then they
left with her.
We need to be aware of our surroundings all the time. You need to be extra special.
No, I'm going to have to get, I'm going to have to go to the security route now. That's
it. I mean, it's obvious. I got it. Doug, thank you so much. Gerald Cilente coming up.
Thank you, Doug. We'll check in with you more soon.
All right, sir.
God bless you.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health. At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver based products. Our most popular silver based products are
the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well
as our all natural silver soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver
gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver
at the surface. But rather, we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the
silver more effectively. Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver
based products are best for you. That's www.silverlungs.com.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to www.supernaturalsilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's www.supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Alex Jones here with a very important announcement for truth seekers. We've carried a lot of
amazing films and books over the years on the online video bookstore at info wars dot
com. And out of all the titles we've carried, one stands out because it is just so chillingly
convincing and that's dreams from my real father by Joel Gilbert available at info wars
dot com. This film exposes the fraud that Obama is like nothing I've seen. If you want
to know who Obama's real daddy is, this is the film for you. Don't forget your purchase
supports our broadcast and our growing media network. You'll also find it in full war shop
dot com. None dare call a conspiracy by Gary Allen, the book that woke me up. We're also
carrying behind the green mask you in agenda 21 by Rosa Corey. This book is coffin nails
to the globalist takeover. The greater good, the most professional and up to date film
I've ever seen exposing the scourge that is vaccines. These titles and a lot more are
all available at info war shop dot com. Crashing through the lies and disinformation. It's
Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
We are live, ladies and gentlemen, now into the second hour. It is the 10th day here of
January 2013. And the national media said how horrible that I pointed my finger at the
Brit over here in America telling us to get rid of our Second Amendment and told him 1776
would commence.
Well, Ron Paul was on yesterday. We're gonna play it later in the hour for Gerald Salente.
He agreed. He said, I've always said it's the line in the sand. It'll cause a civil
war. I'm not calling for a civil war every day you've heard me. I want to stop this from
happening. They want to persecute us. They want to come after our guns because the guns
go, it all goes.
They're already saying they wanna raise taxes again now. They're already saying they wanna
cut benefits again. We're going into austerity, the same blueprint they've used in Europe
that Gerald Salente has warned about for so many years. Here's the McClatchy newspaper
headline as new fiscal cliff nears, Democrats seek more tax increases.
Before we go to Gerald though, I wanna just say this. Yes, watching Larry Pratt last night,
we're gonna play this in the next hour, skillfully, calmfully destroy Piers Morgan was powerful.
And that is how I would have rather have done it. But I get angry sometimes and we will
make a lot of lemonade out of the lemons, but I don't even think it was lemons to begin
with.
That's how they try to spin it. Notice they're not inviting me on other shows, national TV
shows. They were freaked out because they knew that was gonna make big news and get
people out of their coma. As a lot of top media people I've talked to on record, off
record, they said no, that was history making because it shocked Americans out of their
days.
At first, it's uncomfortable to somebody under hypnosis though, to be shocked out of it.
And that's what we got. A lot of people were negative up front, but now it's getting more
and more positive. That said, I'm always the person to second guess myself. It is what
it is. But I could have gotten to more points. I probably went too far yelling at him into
the second segment, should have done less of that.
But it doesn't matter. They're going to misrepresent no matter what. The point is, we're in a coma.
When are we gonna get angry? That's why I love when Gerald Cilente comes on. He gets
angry sometimes. Cuomo's all angry in this new speech we're gonna play. We gotta get
these guns, they're hurting the kids, get them.
I was like, yeah, or they're like, don't raise your voice. That's so animalistic. They want
us to sit down and shut up. I think we've been way too meek. Did I go too far? Maybe.
But the point is, they're demonizing gun owners one way or the other. I wanna play this clip
of them talking about how I need to be shot. And then the other guest and the host talk
about dressing up in a uniform to do it like it's okay when the state does it.
Here's that clip.
What do you need a semi-automatic weapon for? The only reason I think you need it is, Pierce,
challenge Alex Jones to a boxing match. Show up with a semi-automatic that you got legally
and pop him.
I'd love to see that. In uniform.
I'll borrow my brother's uniform.
There you go. And he says he'll borrow his brother's uniform. Pierce agrees. Again, if
I or Gerald Cilente or Ron Paul said anything remotely close to let's kill somebody with
a rifle, it would be like it was the end of the world.
And then with other people, I mean, folks get arrested all the time for joking around
about bars. Hey, I wanna shoot that guy, blah, blah, blah. Yeah, Bob, let's do it. I'll help
you, I'll get the bullets. Conspiracy to commit murder, boom. People are like, we were just
joking, doesn't matter, grand jury just indicted you.
These people are on TV knowing nuts are out there. They know when they hype up these school
shootings where they victim disarm, it advertises that's the place to go. And so I got into
all of that probably overcompensating as I was under the weather.
Never had, I thought it was an allergy, but it's actually a fever last night so that a
chest cold. But the point is, is that it was so disgusting I blew up. Now Gerald wants
to get into a bunch of economics today and a bunch of other big issues that are happening.
But I wanna get his take on this. And of course, the news website that you've absolutely got
to visit over there is trendsresearch.com.
Gerald Cilente is an American trends forecaster, publisher of the Trends Journal, business
consultant and author. He's made a lot of incredibly accurate predictions, not just
about events, but major trends. He's been on every major television news show you can
imagine in the world, trendsresearch.com, subscribe today.
Okay, Gerald, break down your take if you want on the overall open assault on the Second
Amendment and how it ties into everything else. And your take on what happened with
Piers Morgan.
Well, first of all, I wanna say and I wanna make this 100% clear. I am 100% behind Alex
Jones on his stand against the government, imposing any more legislation, rules or regulations
to take our guns away from us. I am totally opposed to what they are doing and I totally
support your belief in what you're doing to protect our rights. So I wanna make that really
clear.
And as I look at this issue and as it evolves and devolves, the politicians are doing nothing
more than using this for political capital. These are a bunch of inepts and incompetence
that have failed at everything that they do. Now, all of a sudden, the fiscal cliff is
out of the news and the official jerks who have been officially incapable of doing anything
to solve the major problems are now grabbing on this gun control issue.
And as you pointed out, they're all shooting off their fat mouths coming up with their
solutions on how to solve the problem. As I look at the problem, this is what I see.
300 million guns out there. What are you gonna control? It'll be as ineffective as prohibition.
It will be as ineffective as the war on drugs and it will be costly to everyone and in the
not only financially, but raping us more of our rights from us, which they love to do.
They are the DC gang, the greatest rapists of human rights in the history of the United
States. They love to rape us. So they're going to be totally ineffective.
Number two, as you well know, and I know that you have the facts down on guns and who uses
them and where they come from better than virtually anybody out there. And as you well
know, Alex, most of the crimes that are committed using guns are committed by the criminals,
the gang bangers, and the other slime out there in society.
And what are, where did those guns come from? No, no, no. They didn't come from mommy or
daddy's closet where they weren't locked up. Those are unregistered guns. Those are black
market guns. Hey, maybe they're even the guns from Fast and Furious. Who knows? So then
the other issue becomes there is a no argument for them to be imposing more rules that are
not going to work. So I support your strong stand on we, the people should be able to
protect ourselves. And as you pointed out and you show those little weenies, I love
that guy Dershowitz on there.
You know, if I was around Alex Jones and I would be afraid that he would come after me
with a gun. Hey, take it easy, Alan boy. If Alex Jones came after you with a feather duster,
that will knock you over. So these little guys, these little boys out there that are
telling us what we should do to protect ourselves their way on.
Absolutely. I want to get your next take on that. We've got breaking news, Gerald. And
this continues. There's a lot of evidence this could be provocative. Shooting outside
Bakersfield, California, where we have a 50,000 watt affiliate. California school shooting
two reportedly shot at Taft Union High School near Bakersfield.
At least two people were shot. That's how Sandy Hook started was two at Taft Union High
School in Kent County, California. This morning, as the suspected shooter has been taken into
custody, according to local media reports, let's pray to God nobody dies. Let's pray
to God. It's time to arm these schools now, folks. They're advertising a minute.
ABC News in Bakersfield said the incident happened at 9 AM. That's just minutes ago,
their time. This is incredible. Gerald Cilente, what's your take on that?
Well, my take again is what are the other issues that you keep talking about? What kind
of psychotropic drugs are these people on? What kind of society, a cruel nature of society,
a culture of cruelty that we had? Who are these people that are committing the crimes?
What drugs are they on that they wouldn't answer you when you brought it up? That each
one of these, there's records of them showing how many people on psychotropic drugs are
killing this.
How about the new guy Obama just nominated for the CIA, who, as I understand, is so much
in favor of, quote, enhanced interrogation techniques. How about torture?
Well, that's like Dershowitz. Dershowitz wrote a paper saying torture should be normalized
and they should just torture us whenever they want.
So that's what I'm saying. It's not about-
I mean, he's the one that's creepy. I mean, we've been out to dinner and stuff. We're
just normal, nice, calm guys. These are the weird, creepy monsters that think torture's
good.
Exactly, so what I'm saying is, whatever happened just now is another American tragedy, but
it has to do with the entire culture of cruelty. No, you watch all those violent video games.
No, no, it's not gonna affect-
Cruelty to animals, people are into that now, that's like chic.
Exactly, so what I'm saying is, no, they're not gonna affect everybody violent, but people
on the edge that become over consumed with them. Again, the drugs, no one is talking
about the psychotropic drugs. This is not a gun control issue, it's a mind control issue.
And the minds of Americans, pick up the paper today. Go look at the last study that just
came out. It has nothing to do with this, but everything to do with it.
Gerald Salente, Gerald Salente, we gotta go to break. We'll come back and talk more about
this in the economy, trendsresearch.com, and you can get their quarterly magazine that
is an absolute must read for everybody right there at Trends Research.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought, to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather a life storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just
in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration. As an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years and serving thousands of
satisfied customers, the Berkey guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration
systems. The Berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable
black purification elements that purify water by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria,
cysts and parasites to non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides
and pesticides. Order the Berkey light system today complete with two black Berkey elements
for only $231 and the Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge. With the purchase
of a Berkey light, the Berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride and arsenic filters
for only $39.99. That's over 30% off the retail price. Call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653.
That's 1-877-886-3653 or order online at GoBerkey.com. That's GoBerkey.com today.
Making the right decisions is a challenge to investors. Are we going to see economic
growth slide into recession or at worst depression? Hi, Ted Anderson from Midas Resources. We
all know when a company acts irresponsibly, divesting ourselves in a move towards safety
is prudent. When the market becomes volatile, U.S. treasuries are a safe haven. But what
do you do when the U.S. government overextends itself and spends beyond its means? Many investors
are turning toward gold as a common sense alternative to traditional paper investments.
Midas Resources has put together a powerful book titled 10 Reasons to Own Gold, discussing
costs, benefits, risks, featuring full color illustrations, weights and measures. The book
is free and can be yours by calling 800-686-2237. Paper investments are dwarfed by gold's 6,000
year history. Discover how gold may be right for you and your IRA by calling 800-686-2237.
Whether buying or it's time for you to sell, the book is free. Call 800-686-2237.
Hey there, Frank Bates here. Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out
280 million Americans? This is really scary stuff. Defense experts warn that this odd
device poses the gravest threat we've ever known. In fact, just a few weeks ago, former
Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed piece for the Washington Post warning
about this deadly threat. I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up. That's why my friend
just created a free video at weirddevice.com that exposes this threat and blows the doors
off the conspiracy. Go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover
exactly what it is, plus discover the number one way you and your family can survive this
deadly attack. I'm not sure how long this video will be online, so go to weirddevice.com
before it's gone forever. Again, that's weirddevice.com.
Yeah, magically, these school shootings just started right as Obama isn't facing reelection
or honestly says he'll use executive orders. And if you look at the shootings out in Aurora,
definitely had government involvement. The guy was paid under a DARPA program that was
in mind control, and that's back of the paper.
I mean, you can't make this up. I mean, Operation Northwoods, US government called for staging
shootings in movie theaters and on the streets to blame their political enemies. Operation
Gladio declassified, our government did it all over Europe. We know about it cuz the
Italian government declassified. They worked with NATO and the US government shooting up
schools and things to blame political groups they didn't like.
It happened in every major European country. They're running Gladio, in my historical researched
opinion. And now if this isn't gang related in Bakersfield, and my God, they could start
announcing dozens of dead just like last time when they said it was one or two and then
it was two shot right now.
I pray to God this isn't, but either way, they're hyping it, they're advertising, school
shooting, school shooting, school shooting, school shooting. They know with copycats that
when they do TV shows about young girls cutting themselves, suddenly more girls cut themselves
and then more cut themselves and then more. When they did death education in public schools
starting in 1990, suicide increased.
Teaching 10 and 11 and 12 year olds how to commit suicide, they never even thought of
that. It's like an option. You see, when they started advertising death by cop, people started
going out and pulling more guns on cops to get killed. It's called advertising. If people
ran $1 million of advertising on a local TV station saying it's fun to go to the corner
of Washington and Liberty and beat yourself in the head with a hammer.
There would be people that went to that corner and beat themselves in the head with a hammer.
There are some people that's suggestible. Most of us aren't like that. When somebody
jumps off a major building, the police always station people there for the next three days
because somebody always shows up. And the police in the old days would call up the media
and say, please stop reporting on this.
When we had real terrorism in the 60s and 70s, they had policies where they did not
report on it at one time. Because when you report on it, it causes more of it. Gerald,
I know I'm ranting and I've got you on here to talk. And we're gonna play some clips coming
up with Ron Paul and moving to other issues that are very important.
But I mean, the way they're hyping school shootings as an epidemic, it's going to cause
copycats to go in there and do this. They know exactly what they're doing. I mean, I
went and took a few courses in media theory at a community college and they talked about
this. I mean, certainly the masters running the media know what they're doing.
But I agree with you 100%. It's advertising. And if this was buried on the back pages of
the New York Times, these incidents, rather than promoting them, they would have a very
different impact. For example, they just killed, quote, 10 militants over there in Pakistan.
That's not a front page story. It's a tiny little thing. It was a front page story. Obama
sends more drones to kill people that had been tried, never had went to court, never
would charge with anything, against the Geneva Conventions and kept doing it over and over
again. It would become news. So I agree with you.
As we were going out of the break, and I'm talking about what's happening to the country
on a broader level and the breakdown of the culture and all these people on psychotropic
drugs, new study just came out. America, USA, USA, we're number one. We're number one. Guess
what? New study just came out. We're in infant mortality. Yeah, we're near number one.
And narcissism. Narcissism, yeah, but the other one was, out of the top 17 nations,
we rank last in longevity, and we're ranking last in as far as people being healthy of
mind and body. And by the way, I was just thinking, any legislation that is being passed
now, what they say to stop this crisis from continuing, I want to see studies being done
on it. I want to see studies being done that what they're proposing is in fact going to
work rather than them stealing my money, hiring a bunch of their flunky friends to make money
on these new programs. Hey, remember that one they used to have in front of all the
schools? Dare, dare. Yeah, that'll keep kids away with drugs. Who are the people making
money behind that? So what I'm saying, Alex, before any new legislation is passed, there
should be cost benefit analyses done as to if this is going to work, how it's going to
work and what it's going to cost.
And your point that you keep making, do not stop making it. They are advertising this.
They are promoting it. It's what prestitudes do. They're standing out there and they're
hawking it like any good prestitute would do. So they are creating the culture.
Long segment coming up with Gerald Salente. The Drudge Report had this up yesterday, but
I'm going to cover it after Gerald leaves. This is the most powerful article I've ever
read on the Second Amendment. Americans never give up your guns from Pravda, from Russia.
And it is powerful, ladies and gentlemen. It's still actually up at DrudgeReport.com,
the middle column. We've reposted it at Infowars.com. And here's the bad news. Biden has just announced
they're going to confiscate all guns that aren't registered. So that's coming up.
Here on the march, the empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather a life storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just
in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu, and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad
spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver
solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold, and food poisoning
and help improve wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph,
pneumonia, colds, flus, and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the ability
to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness
of colloidal or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says silver is our
mightiest germ fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off. That's
SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
We are all in the arena doing the best job we can to fight the globalist. Depending on
how you look at it, I probably could have done a better job on Piers Morgan. I'll say
this, if they ever let me back on there, I will try to show the opposite side and be
very, very calm. Let me take five or six Valiums beforehand. I'm joking, I've never even taken
Valium and I'm told that's what people take to calm down.
But I was just angry. I'm sick of the lies. I know they're opportunistically trying to
disarm us. They could care less about a million dead Iraqis in the Lancet Journal estimate.
They could care less about hundreds of dead kids a year. When they kill innocent people,
they just call it collateral damage. They could care less about fast and furious thousands
of dead people that this White House shipped guns into Mexico. Their own memos came out
to blame the Second Amendment, and it makes me mad.
And I'm just sick of everyone kissing their butts. And Larry Pratt went on there and destroyed
him last night. We'll play it last hour, but he won't make the news anywhere. Listen, they're
not having me back on other shows because they know it's breaking people out of their
spell. Sure, they're gonna spin it and say, look, this guy just credits gun owners because
that's one angle, and with some people it will.
But the overall thing, it scares them for the sleeping giant to awaken. Trendsresearch.com
is Gerald's excellent site. We'll go to that and talk about some of the new trends coming
out after we finish up with guns here in a moment with Gerald Cilente. But first, I wanted
to get his take on Ron Paul.
I brought up my quote of you're gonna trigger a new 1776, which I don't want physically.
Gerald and I have talked about a velvet cultural revolution of liberty versus their cultural
revolution of tyranny, a culture of Americana, quality. We're gonna talk some about that.
I'm clear, I don't want violence. Believe me, I'm one of the first they're gonna go
after. But that's why I'm like, don't come for the guns, it will cause it.
And Piers is like, and like after the show, they're like, he wants some violent revolution.
You idiots don't get it. You're going to trigger it. You're going to draw first blood. You're
going to push it and push it and push it and push it and push it.
And I brought this up and Ron Paul said, well, I haven't used those words, but I say this
is the line in the sand. This could cause a revolution. Here's Ron Paul. So you think
I was right then telling Piers Morgan if they try to confiscate the guns, it will start
1776 part two.
Well, I don't know whether I'd put them in the same words, but I think I said something
very similar to what you're saying.
Well, God bless you, sir. I hope we can get you back again in a month.
Bye, guys. Very good.
What are any other websites that are important to plug? Just campaignforliberty.org.
Do that. And then we'll be listing some new things there because we're making some other
web page. I'm going to have a a home page. Unfortunately, I didn't have Ron Paul dot
com.
So I'm going to have to have Ron Ron Paul's home page dot com. That'll be coming up, but
it's not ready yet.
All right. Big announcements coming soon. We'll talk to you and say hi to the family.
God bless you, sir. Thank you. Right to talk to that man during this dark time. I told
you executive. They're getting us ready to see if we'll take it. Ladies and gentlemen,
this could be it.
All right. There is that clip with the audio off, but it doesn't matter for radio listeners.
I have the news here. Bakersfieldnow.com. Bakersfield school officials take part in
shooting survival training. This is January 9th. They just had a drill at the school.
Now, whether that copycat did the shooting now there or whether that's used as a cover,
we know in North was other documents they use. They use drills as the cover for the
real shooters.
And I'm telling you, ladies and gentlemen, they're so confident. I believe they're staging
and provocateuring these and you're going to see a bunch more shootings. That's why
they're so confident and why he's told fundraisers Biden will get the guns by the end of January
and they're training local police federally for forced gun confiscation.
And Biden hints at outlawing unregulated private guns and saying that you can't have guns that
aren't registered. Well, that's what Dianne Feinstein's bill says. Gerald, let me ask
you the question here, because it's very, very important. Again, I don't want a violent
revolution.
But I'm not going to a FEMA camp either. So defensively, we have a right to protect ourselves
in the duty. What do you think is going to happen if they physically start trying to
confiscate all the semi-autos as Feinstein's bill says? And if they go out and start SWAT
teaming people and calling them terrorists who don't turn them in, what do you think
as a trans forecaster who's been so accurate, what do you think's going to come out of that?
You'll see the same kind of thing that happened during the prohibition. And it'll be another
industry that the government creates. It'll accomplish nothing and it'll be a failure.
When you just read that statement by Biden, were you reading that out of a comic book?
They're going to confiscate all unregistered guns? I mean, come on. Where are you going
to find them? In the unregistered gun dump? I mean, it's an oxymoron. How are you going
to confiscate unregistered guns? They're losers. Everything they turn, they do. They turn to
failure. And going back for a moment, by the way, on two things. One on the Piers Morgan
show about the revolution. I believe there's going to be a revolution, but I've come up
with something very different. And we're going to be announcing it within a few days and
I want to be on your show to talk about it more. Gerald Cilenti's Four Rules of Peace.
That's right. Am I in favor of guns? You bet. Do I own them? You bet I do. If I'm going
to have some crazy person blowing through my place like that woman did who was protecting
her children in the attic, what was it, in Georgia, and shot the intruder as the intruder
was going to shoot her, I want to have the will, I want to have the wherewithal to protect
myself. If I see society breaking down, let's say what happens, a nuclear power plant goes
berserk, and people turn into animals, and they try behaving like deranged, rabid animals,
I want to have a weapon to protect myself. No kidding, exactly, as portions of the population
degenerate because they don't know how to work, everything's always been given to them,
first by their parents, then by the culture, plus the jobs are shipped overseas. As all
of this is happening, we have a right, a duty, a responsibility. Of course. And the other
thing, Alex, when they made, after you went off the air, and they sandbagged you there,
with that guy Dershowitz, they would talk about, oh, he's making this New World Order.
I want to make this clear to everybody. The New World Order is not a conspiracy theory.
It's a fact, and I could prove it. The New World Order is the banking order. That's right.
They are the ones responsible for so much of what's going on in society today. I could
pick up a piece, and we'll take it in the break, I'll get my assistant to get it, from
the CEO of UBS, saying how arrogant they were, and how they shouldn't have been so greedy,
in nice white shoe boy language. You look what's going on over in Europe. Instead of
them reporting on all of the prostitute news that they do, they're not talking about the
horrors that people are living through in Portugal, in Spain, in Greece. The people
are taking to the streets. You say, Alex, that can this be a tipping point? I don't
know what the tipping point is, because the tipping point, they never see it. They will
continue to rape us until their sickest desires have not been fulfilled in one area, as when
raping us of our constitutional rights, and then they'll do something else. They never
learn. Look, have they learned from Vietnam? Did they learn from Iraq? Have they learned
from Afghanistan? No, I got it. Let's open up 35 new bases in Africa. Yeah, we'll come
up with a name for it. They never learn.
You're right, and they know though, they have learned something from history that people
will resist them later. So they're buying 1.6 billion bullets. They're digging in, they're
militarizing, they're surveilling, they're calling peaceful protests, terrorism. Publicly,
they're demonizing the entire Bill of Rights and Constitution. Meanwhile, they are erecting
all these new taxes.
Now, you originally were gonna come back on this week, and we appreciate you doing that
because I know you're a busy guy, to get into the big trends coming up that we didn't have
time to get to last week. Let's shift gears out of the guns now, and this Bakersfield
thing looks bad.
Another shooting at a school, a government training center, and they had a drill there
two days ago of a mass shooting at the school, practicing taking the kids to the sports stadium.
And they've actually done that now. This, again, just absolutely programs the youngsters
to think about this, and that this is an option.
They lose their girlfriend, they put them on Prozac, and they don't know what their
name is. Well, get a gun, I mean, this is unbelievable. But Gerald, shifting out of
the guns now, because you offered, you said I can come back and finish cuz we're out of
time. All the big trends that are coming up other than the disarmament, I mean, that's
one of them.
Why are they pushing so hard to disarm us right now? Because they know, I was reading
with the Chinese government starting to hoard food and weapons for itself against the population.
Governments everywhere are digging in, how does this tie into it?
That's exactly it. And that's exactly what we're writing about. There's an economic collapse
going on worldwide. They know, you pick up today's New York Times, or yesterday's, one
of the days, one of the members of the Federal Reserve Board from Virginia saying that all
of this quantitative easing is not going to solve anything. They know that the game is
going to end. And you know my say, when people lose everything and have nothing left to lose,
they lose it.
And I firmly believe that with the National Defense Authorization Act, with the wiretapping,
with all of the surveillance going on, as you pointed out what they did with the Occupy
movements, with the FBI, the CIA, the NIA, all of them watching everything that we do,
and I'm not a conspiracy crazy. I'm seeing it as I'm watching the world collapse around
us and I'm saying they're preparing for the collapse here. And so they want to have it
so that they can control us. Again, just like they infiltrated the Occupy movement and every
other movement. They're going to do it again because we're going through an economic collapse
here. In fact, Switzerland, I used to call them the money cockroaches of the world. They
are now printing more money and a leverage of GDP to printing money higher than any of
the other countries. The new guy they got in there in Japan, Abe, the new prime minister,
first thing he did, they're printing more money through the Bank of Japan. You look
what's going on over in Europe with Mario Draghi, former vice chairman of the Goldman
Sachs gang. What is he doing? OMT, ongoing monetary transactions, in white shoe boy language,
in real language, keep printing money. Oh, gold, by the way, Alex, pop up $20 today.
Why? Because they're depressing it and if anybody doesn't think the game is rigged,
then you're a moron to think that they don't rig things because after all, didn't they
rig the interest rates with LIBOR? Aren't we finding out all these inside deals that
are going on? I'm making the point because it all ties together. There's an economic
collapse. The only way they're keeping it going is by printing this cheap money and
in the meantime, devaluing our currency. If anybody travels out of the United States and
goes to an affluent nation, your dollar isn't worth a dime, ladies and gentlemen. What's
going on is that this is part of the greater collapse and then you start putting the other
pieces together. Hey, drought conditions going on. Can't bring barges down the Mississippi.
Food prices going up. Oh, shortages. Hey, over there in Brazil, big problem. Can't get
any hydroelectricity. Why not? Things are drying up. Don't have the water. So you keep
putting this all together. The government, the nation is too big to operate from a central
location. What I would like to see as part of the next revolution is secession. I don't
want a gang of 535 telling 315 million people what to do. I don't want a guy like Biden
or boner. I don't want a person like Reid or McConnell. I don't want these losers who
have created nothing but misery and hardship for all of us except their friends to keep
destroying the nation. And when you look at the Bill of Rights and when you listen to
our founding fathers, this is the time for me for one of the big trends that we're writing
about the secession progression. You notice how they push that out of the news. You notice
how over a million people signed up for it and no one's talking about it, but it's going
on in Spain. It's going on in Italy. It's going on in Scotland. It's going on over 200
countries around the world. The nation is too broken to fix and it's too big to be operated
by a mafia, a Republican and Democratic crime family.
You can't reform criminals. No, you don't reform the mafia. We need a new system and
that's what I'm going for.
By the way, last week they had kicked him out. They had indicted some of them. I remember
three, four years ago we were told Iceland's bankrupt. The 400,000 people of the country
who are some of the wealthiest capital in the world, they now are all bankrupted. And
then it was reported by Reuters and others, just amazing information last week that they
actually arrested them.
Now at first we were told all the debt was the Icelandic peoples. It was something like
$50 billion. Then they said, okay, it's only 10 million, please pay it. Turned out 90 plus
percent was not even their own national debt. It wasn't even their own socialism, which
it wasn't. It was foreign British bank debt that their criminal government had signed
them on to.
They protested and refused the system and sabotaged it any way they could. And went
on strikes for a year until they took the government over, they stormed the banks. And
then now they've arrested the people and they're going to prison. And the bankers are trying
to do dirty tricks to them now.
But the point is, at first England said, we're not gonna let flights out of Iceland come
here saying you're illegal. We're gonna seize your citizens' bank accounts, cuz a lot of
Icelanders use British banks. So they just counter-suit them. The mafia of the British
cartel, the biggest in the world, tried to say, our debt is your debt.
And the Icelanders said, you can literally go to Hades. These nice well-mannered folks
actually reverted back to being Vikings. Can't we follow the Icelandic model? Isn't it the
way out? Isn't that the key?
Absolutely, again, you're going to be receiving the Trends Journal next week. Another great
trend we have is the Great Awakening. It was a great awakening in this country prior to
the revolution. You read it in the works of Thomas Paine.
Part of the Great Awakening, first it began as a religious revival. And people realized
that their salvation was in their own hands. It wasn't from a hierarchy of a Church of
England or anybody else. That you're responsible creating your own destiny, and you leave this
life in the way that you choose to leave it by the deeds that you do on Earth. That was
the awakening. It then became a second part of it, just as no longer genuflecting to the
head of the Church of England.
Hold on, this is key. We're gonna come back and get into this. That's right. And that's
why they're setting up all this tyranny worldwide, as Brzezinski wrote in his new book. They
know the Global Awakening is happening. Gerald Salente predicted it six years ago. Brzezinski
confirmed it this year. We'll be back.
This is Alex Jones with five good reasons you should consider buying a solar power generator.
Number one, new climate legislation could easily double or triple your electric bill.
Number two, our new energy czar wants to control how much power your electric company
allows you to have. It's true. Total government control of electricity in the name of smart
grid technology is coming. Number three, in some areas of the country, the power grid
is dangerously overloaded. And now new socialist legislation is only compounding the problem.
Number four, dangerous weather is always a threat to local grids. Every year, thousands
of families lose their power from weather-related onages. Number five, a solar power generator
provides powerful backup insurance and peace of mind. Folks, I really believe in the solar
power generators offered by Solutions from Science, one of my oldest sponsors. You can
get more information at www.mysolarbackup.com. That's mysolarbackup.com. Remember, the government
doesn't own the sun. So go to mysolarbackup.com or call 1-877-327-0365.
In the U.S., one in every 50 homes will have a break-in this year. Burdlers call it smash
and grab. Police call it robbery. We call it avoidable. We are Fake TV, a simple electronic
device that can fool even professional burglars. Fake TV easily plugs into any outlet and simulates
the changing colors of a television. To a burglar, it looks like someone must be home
watching TV, so they'll likely move on to an easier target. At only $34.95, Fake TV
costs less than a month of most alarm monitoring plants. And it's perfect if you're traveling
or away from home. Order your Fake TV by calling 877-5FAKETV or go to faketv.com. That's 877-532-5388
or faketv.com. Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book Cancer Step Outside the Box.
I want you to know some very important information. In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested
that Carnivora be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the President could
obtain this world-class healer. Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around
the world to keep people healthy. Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in
this age of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal
cells only without harming a single normal cell. If you want to stay healthy, now's your
chance to literally wake up your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that
don't belong in your body. Call 1-866-VenusFly or order from Carnivora.com. That's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VenusFly or visit Carnivora.com. Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
The Genesis Communications Radio Network proudly presents the Alex Jones Show because there's
a war on for your mind.
Ladies and gentlemen, here's the issue. We've got Gerald for two more segments. Really appreciate
him joining us. They came out and announced we're going to have an executive order, which
they'd said quietly before, where we can just ban semi-autos. And people said, no way, that's
unconstitutional. So then CNN, I was watching them today before the show started back there
in the coffee area, was going, it's just an executive order to use existing laws, but
it's how we implement them.
This isn't unconstitutional. Don't be paranoid. They played a clip of Limbaugh saying this
is a tyrannical takeover. And I saw another newscast criticizing Drudge for putting Hitler
and Stalin up there. Well, they used executive action to take guns. That's what this is.
See, they're always, don't be radical, don't be radical. They're the ones that are radical.
And we've got to rise to their radicalness with our base rock common sense and say no.
Now Gerald Salente is covering something here of the utmost importance. And it is so important
for you to support Infowars.com, to buy the books, the videos, the magazines, the propure
water filters that blow the competition away, fluoride filters, all of it, Infowarshop.com.
I haven't even plugged that today. To go there, the Buy the Pro Gun t-shirts, the Infowars
t-shirts to meet like-minded people. To go to trendsresearch.com and subscribe there
as well.
Because even if you think you know all this, this is the type of magazine, the color magazine
with great graphics and everything that you wanna give people, executives, teachers, preachers,
the police chiefs that can really wake them up. You can also sign up for the free trends
alerts there at trendsresearch.com. But now is the time to support those of us.
And that's why I wish Glenn Beck wasn't attacking me and folks because I want to work with everybody,
okay, who wants basic liberty, left, right, center, libertarian. If you want basic bill
of rights and constitution, and if you realize we've been hijacked by foreign mega banks,
I'm your friend. I wanna work with everybody. None of us are perfect. All of us can be arm
share quarterbacks, but we better financially support Infowars.com.
We better support Gerald Cilente and his trends research. You better spread the word about
these broadcasting local AM and FMs because they won't always be here if you don't support.
Now is the time. Gerald, get back into your great awakening.
Yes. And then after the religious part that people understood that their salvation was
in their own hands and their own mind and spirit, then it became as well, we're not
going to genuflect to the crown either. These people do not have a royal bloodline. They
have not been ordained by God to rule us. And that's the works of the Thomas Pains and
others that people revolted against the tyranny of the nobility. Well, guess what, Alex? It's
the great awakening 2.0. They don't ride around in their coaches and knock everybody over
like they used to when the royalty arrived. Now they have their SUVs, their motorcades.
They closed down the airspace, closed down the highways. Every one of these creeps. Now
they have their jumbo jets. That's their new coaches. And they salute to the surfs down
below they wave. It's a new royalty. It's the royalty that Mark Twain so despised. It's
the royalty that Jefferson wrote in his letters, how disgusting and how deranged and immoral
they were when he was over in Europe. We have a new royalty. They are our senators. They
are our congressmen. And our kings and queens have become the presidents and prime ministers
who, by royal, eat it. Our executive order will tell the rest of us surfs what to do
and how we should obey them. Because if we don't, they have the goon squads to make sure
that they do. Unbelievable. Stay there. You are listening to GCN. Visit GCNlive.com today.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook. Waging war on corruption. Alex Jones
on the GCN radio network. Big brother, mainstream media, government cover ups. You want answers?
Well so does he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network. And now live from Austin, Texas,
Alex Jones.
Up on screen of your TV viewer, I have an image of Thomas Jefferson next to Nancy Pelosi,
Harry Reid and some of the other little globalist minions there. And imagine 235 plus years
later, these tyrants are trying to destroy what Thomas Jefferson helped get into place
and he was the main architect for those that don't know.
They are literally still trying to get rid of something that our forebears fought with
blood, sweat and tears and a lot of work to put into place. And that's why they spend
all day demonizing it. And I was just thinking about Gerald Salinas. I'm at the old royalty
that discussed to Jefferson and others. And then here is the new royalty saying by executive
decree, we'll do whatever we want. We'll spy on you. We'll kill you. We'll disappear you.
We'll have the goons come after you. We are right back in that same position. And it's
just amazing.
Absolutely amazing. Gerald Salinas, we got four minutes left. You got the floor.
And again, you are a voice of the great awakening. I mean, if anybody doubts it, you know, they
haven't been tuning in so much. And as I am and others, Dr. Paul Craig Roberts, Ron Paul,
nothing has changed. There is a new royalty. I'm not making this up. Do you ever see these
people? Everywhere they go, there's red carpets and a bunch of flunkies either saluting, depending
on the country you're in, or dressed up in some moronic uniform.
And I'm saying to myself, who's paying for this? And then Obama bows to royalty. But
who's paying for this garbage? Who's paying for all of these flunkies to get dressed up
in this uniform? I have a business. Get to work. What are you doing over here to salute
me when I walk in the door? Do they salute anybody? Here he comes. Roll out the red carpet.
Nothing has changed. Look how they talk down to us. Look how they tell us what we must
believe, why we should believe it, and how we should behave. There's a new Great Awakening.
The Great Awakening 2.0 is going to precede the Second American Revolution. And again,
not one of guns and armies, but one of the mind and the spirit, the heart and the soul,
the dignity and the respect of the individual, not what we should be saying and taking orders
from our masters.
I agree with you. When you talk about royalty, the red carpet was for royalty. They even
have the guards around them holding up standards. They're telling us we are the emperors, we
are your owners, and they act just like old royal dictatorships. And they say they're
above the law, they're immune, you're a slave, they twist it all. And then they take old
ladies' houses, you see it in the news all the time, for some unpaid tax they can't pay
so that these guys could have $15 billion in the bank.
Exactly, the new royalty. Here's a quote from Thomas Paine. To the evil of monarchy, we
have added that of hereditary succession. Yeah, one Bush, another Bush, another Bush,
a Clinton, a Clinton, a Kennedy, a Kennedy. And as the first is the degradation and lessening
of ourselves. So the second claimed as a matter of right is an insult and imposition on posterity.
For all men being originally equals, no one by birth could have a right to set up his
own family in perpetual preference to all others forever. And that's what they have
done. It's their seat of power. They have become the royalty. They are in charge. They
know what's best for us.
Amazing. Gerald Zalenta, I hope to speak to you soon, trendsresearch.com. I'm Alex Jones,
one of the followers.com. We'll be right back with the main radio transmission, 11 AM to
2 PM central every day. Find all Gerald's material and videos at his trends research
site. We'll be back.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health. At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver based products. Our most popular silver based products are
the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well
as our all natural silver soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver
gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver
at the surface, but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the
silver more effectively. Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver
based products are best for you. That's www.silverlungs.com.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At e Foods
direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my e foods just
in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting non-GMO long-term storeable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on e foods direct. Alex
Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers. The prognosis for the entire planetary
economic system runs from bad to worse. The globalist model is to shut down societies
and starve patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover. That's why we've assembled
the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarsshop.com. These are items
that I did research on that I personally use. You've got the life straw so you can turn
fetid water into safe water anywhere you go. The Ktor hand crank generator to charge up
key equipment during power outages or out in the field. Strategic relocation third edition
by Joel Skousen. When disaster strikes by Matthew Stein. TheraSafe used by Homeland
Security to protect yourself during any radiological event. Hand crank shortwave AM FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com
and your purchase makes our info war possible. We're getting prepared. Are you infowarsshop.com
live from Austin, Texas, broadcasting worldwide. It's Alex Jones.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, we are back live here today on this Thursday worldwide
transmission and I want to go through the different laundry list of clips that we have
here today. In fact, guys, I had my list. Here it is. I want to first give out the number.
If you heard Doug Hagman on earlier from Northeast Intelligence Network or you just heard Gerald
Salente on the broadcast or you want to give your take on them saying they want to use
executive orders to take our firearms.
That's the issues we're mainly talking about. Or the Democrats are proposing even more tax
increases now that they just got the other tax increases through. And this is how it
works. Once they get you to the cliff, they start raising taxes once a year, then it's
three times a year, then it's ten times a year.
And then you're paying 80% to 90% is the IMF World Bank model of everything you do in different
taxes and the streets aren't fixed, sewage is everywhere, but almost all your money goes
to the government. They're like, yeah, but their tax receipts go down when they do that.
They don't care. In fact, they want to make you poor.
And so McClatchy newspapers reporting that. There's a really creepy article. Could Alex
Jones revolution actually happen out of Yahoo News? And it goes on to admit the government's
arming against us and building up and that it's creepy. And if they try to take the guns,
there may be a revolution.
But it also tries to discredit me. Look, it's not Alex Jones' revolution. I know a few months
ago I said, get ready, this is it, they're coming after us. They're saying they're gonna
use executive orders to take all our liberties. I can tell by their bearing and the propaganda
and all these new shows coming out on ABC, NBC, CBS, that the fix was in for Obama.
And that they are gonna demonize gun owners. I mean, they don't have four new shows on
broadcast TV. And then a couple I know of on cable that are now out or coming out where
gun owners are terrorists and the US Army hunts them down and infiltrates them. And
it puts them in situations where the gun owners are always bad guys.
It follows total Homeland Security scripting where they say gun owners, veterans, returning
vets, libertarians, conservatives are the enemy. And then their training, the real trainings
for this war going on for a decade, even before Obama got in. And now they're just going,
public with it. And so I mean, you'd be a fool if you didn't know they're not spending,
let's be conservative, 50, 60 billion a year for this domestic takeover.
And buying 1.6 billion bullets and deploying armored vehicles in every area and creating
dissonant list because they're not gonna come after us. They're gonna hammer down. I mean,
it's horrible. I wish this wasn't the case. And they mean to break this country. They
mean to bring this country completely down.
And I just pray to God to open the eyes of this country. I pray to God to open the eyes
of police and military, which is starting to happen. But they select goons out of these
forces and put them in these special thug units. And I've looked in their eyes. They
really can't wait to hunt us down. And good luck. I mean, you may get the first few of
us, people like me. But man, all you're doing is just really setting up for something bad.
And not just on this plane. Going after people that really do love liberty and are good guys
is bad mojo. Reap what you sow, karma, whatever you wanna call it. And this is really bad.
This is the worst scenario I could imagine. And it's not a game. It's not about entertainment.
It's time to get freaked out. Glenn Beck said, I'm spooky, I'm scary.
I'm dangerous. No, I'm covering the spookiness and the dangerousness that's already there,
bud. The time of wearing designer sweaters and being a cutesy and being into being a
rich guy, it's over. Look, you either leave the United States and try to run to where
rich people live if you're rich.
And just hope they don't get you later or you stand and you get the word out now. Okay,
cuz if we wait till they blow up some federal buildings and blame us, we're in deep trouble.
And I can tell you, I see all the signs. That's like I told you back days after Obama got
elected. I call for the second American Revolution, a restoration. There are a lot of revolutions.
Most of them aren't physical. I said before they, before the establishment, gets physical.
We have got to just absolutely overwhelm them and let them know we're on the watch and that
this isn't gonna work. And that means not letting those of us on the tip of the spear
be intimidated.
All of you that have a platform have got to turbocharge. I gotta give credit again, DrudgeReport.com
yesterday showed Hitler and Stalin and said Obama is trying to become a dictator with
executive orders. And look, if you have an executive order, I wanna play the Ron Paul
clip here in a moment, the HD one we now have, talking about the martial law is the first
clip we're gonna play or the line in the sand.
Ron Paul's like, well, it is dictatorial and it's going a dictatorial direction. But Obama
was elected, yeah, through fraud. It doesn't matter, Hitler was elected. I actually disagreed
with Ron Paul only slightly. He said, well, we're going in the direction of a dictatorship.
No, we're not. And I know he understands, he's real smart. He knows the public doesn't
get that.
They think as long as you're elected, you're not a dictator. If you got elected and overthrew
your office and did things outside of the office, like saying the UN's over our military
and I can sign executive orders and take your guns, that is dictator. Hitler was elected.
A lot of dictators, Hugo Chavez was elected. And there was pure fraud. The guy has not
been reelected. Fidel Castro was popular at first. This guy's still a dictator. The
point is Hitler was elected.
And Ron Paul said, well, we're going in the direction of a dictatorship. No, the office
of the President is becoming dictatorial, that is true. And it is going into dictator
territory and then it goes the rest of the way very, very quickly. But Ron Paul said
when I said, is 1776 not about to happen again?
Won't that be the line in the sand out of 100 plus million gun owners? Won't there be
1% that stands up or more? That's a million people fighting back. And he goes, yes, I've
always said that's the line in the sand. That's what's gonna kick this off. I mean, I'm not
saying, hey, Piers Morgan, there's gonna be 1776, we're coming to get you.
I'm saying do not hit the red button, buddy. Just like Larry Pratt told him last night,
we're gonna play that clip. He said, listen, I would tell Obama don't make the mistake
King George III made, don't come for the guns, it will happen. And Larry Pratt said, so you're
for revolution.
Or Piers Morgan said that to Larry Pratt. Larry Pratt said, listen, I'm telling you
what's going to happen. It's like don't run out on I-35 with 80 mile an hour, 18 wheelers,
back to back going down. Don't just stand there when one drives by and jump out in front
of it and think you're not gonna get run over.
What, are you gonna run me over? What, are you threatening me? No, idiot. Listen, don't
do this. Don't do this. Don't do it. Don't do it. 800-259-9231, 800-259-9231. And it's
not that we're, people are like, well, Alex, I know bad times are coming.
We're just gonna have to turn the guns in. We know it's tyranny, we'll have to bide our
time. Look, Biden, our time's over. They're getting ready to raise taxes again and again
and again. You're like, well, that'll bankrupt things. That's the plan, Jack. There's gotta
be a time, people are like, well, this is scary.
I'm not the one making it scary, Glenn Beck and Rush Limbaugh. I'm not the one making
it scary. They did, they did it. Okay, I'm following the Bill of Rights Constitution.
The globalists call us counter revolutionaries. They're involved in the revolutionary change.
They're the ones coming in doing this. They're the ones bringing in globalism. And excuse
me, I am an honorable person trying to do the best job I can, pouring out my very substance
to really historically try to do the right thing and back these people off.
Because again, I'll be honest with you, if they were just a corrupt group that wanted
to run stuff, I'd still be criticizing them and fighting them. Everybody has this feeling
of unease. Everybody says, yeah, we agreed things and we knew that we get bad and now
it's happening because God's warning you, folks.
These are nasty mass takeover FEMA camp, reeducator, total takeover types, and it's all on record.
But the mainline conservative talk show hosts all attack me and say that isn't true when
it's all on record. The army manuals, the FEMA camps, the emergency centers establishment
attacks. I'm giving you names of things that are public.
Let's go to the Ron Paul clip. Here it is, 800-25. So you think I was right then telling
Piers Morgan if they try to confiscate the guns it will stop.
Just stop it. I'll go to the clip here in a moment. I just want to give the number out.
It's 800-259-9231. Sorry guys, I said go to it and sort of give the number out. Let's
go back to the clip now. Here it is. So you think I was right then telling Piers Morgan
if they try to confiscate the guns, it will start 1776 part two.
Well, I don't know whether I put them in the same words, but I think I said something very
similar to what you're saying. Well, God bless you, sir. I hope we can get you back again
in a month. Very good.
What are any other websites that are important to plug? Just campaignforliberty.org. That's
the short clip. And there's a full clip right before that that we should probably hear on
the nightly news tonight. The full clip's up on info-words.com where he talked about
the line in the sand being the gun. So there's a full part. Okay, so we're gonna play that
later once we find that because it's so important.
Sure, we'll go ahead and play it now. Go ahead. Will you turn in your semi-autos?
Well, I might not even have anything to turn in for that purpose, but I don't think the
American people will. I've always assumed that the line in the sand may well be drawn.
If the federal agent marches in unannounced and they say, well, give me your gun and give
me your gold, I don't think we'll do that calmly. I think the American people will highly
resent it and resist.
Yeah, I mean, this isn't a game. We've got radical Marxist hired by foreign banks. By
the way, it is the most incredible article I've ever read, and I will read this after
I take some calls. This Pravda article that we've posted in full, and probably used to
be the total Soviet mouthpiece, now it's the opposite, probably used to be known as a joke
of lying media.
And it comes out and says, the banks that have hijacked your country put Stalin first
Lenin in here and took our guns. We were just like you, we all had rifles and shotguns.
And we fought back, we were the White Russians and they killed us. And Pravda says, the same
banks. I actually got tears in my eyes reading it this morning. I saw it yesterday and didn't
read it. And I know the history is true and here are the Russians, the Russians saying
you're run by big banks, they're gonna take your guns, they're gonna kill you.
Your banks did this to us in 1917, America, watch out, they're gonna put you in camps,
they're gonna kill you. I mean, it is incredible information. I'm gonna read this on air, it
is so incredible.
Hello I'm Alex Jones, myself, my family, the Infowars.com team want to relay to you and
your families that we are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front.
Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats, but we can't do that without
your help.
By getting the films, bumper stickers and t-shirts at Infowars.com, you will wake up
people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level. We need your
help to spread the word like never before. They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic
battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination. The war is here. It's an info war. The spirit of 1776 versus
the mindset of 1984.
My name is Stephen Heuer. After 22 years of nutritional counseling, I've observed that
most brain malfunctions have at their roots some form of toxicity and brain damage. So
whether it is poor memory, poor focus, lack of creative thinking or more serious matters
like inability to focus, speak normally or remember things, the emphasis to getting one's
brain working optimally needs to be on detoxification. One World Way supports your body's number
one means of detoxification, which is glutathione production.
My name is Angie and my son has suffered from borderline autism and constipation. I got
him on One World Way and in two months his constipation is gone. He has become friendlier.
He can carry on a normal conversation with me and he has made his first friend. He's
doing great and he looks forward to taking One World Way every day. He could offer him
a present or a cake and he would prefer the One World Way.
Go to oneworldway.com. That's oneworldwhey.com or call 888-988-3325. That's 888-988-3325.
hempusa.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine and probiotics
and we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder absolutely free micro plant powder
only at hempusa.org. Call 908-691-2608. That's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder, seeds
and oil can do for you only at hempusa.org. This offer ends January 31st.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson. Have you ever wondered why banks, stock workers, investment advisors
won't talk about gold IRAs? They've been available since 1986 yet the financial industry won't
recognize the value of gold for your retirement. Gold is outperformed paper investments yet
no word about IRAs. If you would like to have gold for your retirement call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns call 800-686-2237. Secure
your future and call 1-800-686-2237. Hi there. My name is Frank Bates. What I'm about to
tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble. I just created a free
video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity monopolies and government
agencies for what they really are. Incompetent line crooks that are counting on your ignorance
and fear to keep your power bills criminally high. Some have called this a conspiracy.
Others have called it a cover up and you will be shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy
goes. My video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat
them and how you can beat them too. Watch the controversial video that thousands of
other smart patriots have already seen in the last three months. Go to 123coverup.com and
discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect your home. Go watch my video
now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down. Again, that's 123coverup.com.
I want to say something to everybody. I want to thank those of you that have prayed for
us. I want to thank those of you that have supported us. I want to thank all of you that
have put up with me over the years because you know, in your discernment, I'm just doing
the best job I can. And I don't think I always have the answers. In fact, I know I don't.
I make a lot of mistakes and I'm just fighting as hard as I can. And that's all I can do.
That's all I can do. And I get very angry at the globalist because I know who they are.
And I, at a selfish level, I'm very mad that it's in my blood and that I can't help but
resist them. I mean, I've tried to think about before backing off and I just, it just feels
so horrible that I just can't do it. And then I realized things are just going to get worse
and then I get really angry because I'm not backing off. My ancestors didn't back down.
I'm not backing down. And the only reason we've had wealth and liberty and freedom and
lived the longest and had the most money was because our ancestors were meaner than rattlesnakes.
And a grizzly bear. And acting like a bunch of sheep, you're going to have wolves come.
And that's all I can say. I mean, we act like a bunch of cowards and bow down to government
like it's royalty. We're going to get treated like slaves. And that's why I'm so angry.
Is because I realized I've been around about all this and then some and it really is upsetting.
I know why people want to think things aren't as bad as I say, because then you'd have to
do something about it, wouldn't you? And I know there's a lot of you out there doing
a lot and you can't get through to me and you try to call and I whatever and you get
mad at me because you've got an idea that would fix everything.
Look, I'm totally overwhelmed. Okay, I can't do it all. And I try to take time off. I try
to rest. I try to not get angry. And I did probably need to take a vacation. I'll be
honest with people because I never take off. Any race car has got to pull over and get
its oil changed and get new tires on it and stuff. I'm only a human.
But I do appreciate all the prayers and things. But I told you, I feel this quickening coming
and see it building the last few months and now you see it all happening. My gut now it's
ten times what it was a week ago. It's just man, we're in trouble. And I just want to
turn things around.
I just don't want us to be taken over by pure authoritarians. Jacobson just gave me an article
about searches the examiner reports as liberals proposed gun control, Google searches on Hitler
gun control spike. One of the top searches yesterday because Drudge told it like it was.
When I saw this yesterday, I said that's the spirit. Putting Stalin and Hitler up there
where Obama was talking about using executive orders to take our guns.
Why is that so powerful? Because you've got to be radical in the face of their radicalism.
You've got to tell them where this is leading. Because they are radicals and they tell us,
don't be radical. Don't be radical that discredits you. No, you're the radicals and extremists
in defense of liberty is no vice, as Barry Goldwater said.
Laying down to charity is not golden, it's yellow. Silence isn't golden, it's yellow.
Like somebody pee in their pants. That's what cowards do and they get real scared. They
fall down. Don't hurt me and pee on themselves. I'm not gonna do that, man. I don't know how
to do that. Let's go to phone calls. I'll come back in the break, take more. Let's talk
to Glenn in Michigan. Glenn, you're on the air, go ahead.
Hey buddy.
Alex, it's a privilege to be on the phone with you. You can count on our prayers up
here in Michigan. And I just want to tell you, I want to encourage you, what you're
going through and what's happened reminds me so much of what happened, the situation
with a family member of mine who was Thanksgiving. I'm a little nervous, sorry Alex. But I'm
a reluctantly confrontational person. I've had to confront a member of my family that
I love so much, an alcoholic. And I prayed about what to say. And to be honest with you,
God gave me words to say to him, but it came out very brutal. And really wrecked our Thanksgiving,
if you want to say that. The family was mad at me, but that guy has given his life to
Christ and he has got a drink, so.
Absolutely, you did an intervention. Instead of watching your brother or whoever it was
drink themselves to death. It was like an intervention with Piers Morgan. They were
crying, none of the national TVs invited me on. They're totally freaked out, because they
all know it's about enslavement. And I'm like, look, you don't care about these kids, you
want tyranny.
Watch it, you're on notice. And that scared a lot of mainline conservatives, cuz they
all deep down know where this is headed. Hey folks, only admitting how real it is, is gonna
save us. I hope everybody gets that. My pastor has told me for years when you speak the truth
to somebody and confront them, it's like holding up a mirror to them and showing them what
they're like.
And it shocks them. And I agree with you, God bless you, brother. I gotta jump, we got
more calls coming up, but you're right. No, I mean, that's a lot of people say that it's
like an intervention. It was shocking. A lot of people didn't like it, because they are
in trances. Folks, you need to get angry. That's the beginning, like Howard Beale says
in network. First you've got to get mad. We're on the march. The empire's on the run. Alex
Jones and the GCN radio network.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad
spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver
solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning
and help improve wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as stress, death,
pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the ability to terminate
entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal
or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ
fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go
to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off. That's
SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action.
Tyranny is here. The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality.
It really says that the state is God.
The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most impressive police states
on earth. This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps
now being expanded nationwide. This documentary exposes how the continuity of government program
has established an all powerful shadow state. Police state four chronicles the sickening
depth to which our republic has fallen. Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency
dictatorship, body scanners, sound cameras, citizen spies, stage terror and cameras on
every street corner. It's only the beginning of the new world order's hellish plan. The
police state isn't coming. It's here. Secure your copy today at InfoWars.com or see it
online in the highest quality at PrisonPlanet.tv.
I don't have to tell you things are bad. Everybody knows things are bad. It's a depression. Everybody's
out of work or scared of losing their job. The dollar buys a nickel's worth. Banks are
going bust. Shopkeepers keep a gun under the counter. Punks are running wild in the street
and there's nobody anywhere who seems to know what to do and there's no end to it. We know
the air is unfit to breathe. Our food is unfit to eat. We sit watching our TVs while some
local newscaster tells us that today we had 15 homicides and 63 violent crimes as if that's
the way it's supposed to be. We know things are bad, worse than bad. They're crazy. It's
like everything everywhere is going crazy so we don't go out anymore. We sit in the
house and slowly the world we're living in is getting smaller and all we say is please
at least leave us alone in our living rooms. Let me have my toaster and my TV and my steel
belt and radios and I won't say anything. Just leave us alone. Well I'm not going to
leave you alone. I want you to get mad. I don't want you to protest. I don't want you
to riot. I don't want you to write to your congressmen because I wouldn't know what to
tell you to write. I don't know what to do about the depression and the inflation and
the Russians and the crime in the street. All I know is that first you've got to get
mad. You've got to say I'm a human being. My life has value. I want you to get up now.
I want all of you to get up out of your chairs. I want you to get up right now and go to the
window, open it and stick your head out and yell I'm as bad as hell and I'm not going
to take this anymore. I want you to get up right now. Get up, go to your windows, open
them and stick your head out and yell. I'm as bad as hell and I'm not going to take this
anymore. That's right. I'm your host, Alex Jones. We'll get to your calls. I want you
to do this prompt article. We have some more clips that I want to play right now, but that's
why they're so scared and that's why they're trying to say, oh, that's a losing tactic
to get angry because I'm not here to make you love me.
I'm here to get you to realize you're being usurped. I mean, they are cold bloodedly hammering
these dead kids deaths to get our guns to enslave us. They're going to come and take
our guns. They're going to raise our taxes again and again. They're going to reduce us
to absolute despotism. They're going to eat out our substance, the power to tax and the
power to destroy.
I'm angry about that. I don't want to have to flee the United States. There's nowhere
to run. I know who these people are. And we're never going to get out of this if we don't
get angry about it. And all of you that have decided to serve the system, I mean, come
on. You think you've picked the winning side and oh, so what, we're going to have tyranny.
You're idiots. Do you know what real evil is? Because you've signed on to it.
And I think if you really knew what's going on and what's at the head of this thing, you
would not want to be under its wings. I mean, I'll tell you right now. And I know a lot
of you are dumbered in dirt out there that support the system or you're childlike and
you like to have fantasy that Obama's your friend and the government's your friend. No,
it's not. The only reason this tyranny hadn't taken over quicker is there's good people
outside and inside the system.
Let me read to you this Pravda article or at least part of it because I saw this yesterday,
didn't have time to read it, read it this morning and it just blew me away. Because
I know everything in this article in the first five or six paragraphs is absolutely true
and documented. These days, this is written by Stanislav Mission, who by the way, boys,
you want bonuses, get me Stanislav on with an interpreter, whatever it takes.
Might speak English, a lot of Russians do. These days, there are few things to admire
about the socialist, bankrupt and culturally degenerating USA. But at least so far, one
thing remains, the right to keep and bear arms and use deadly force to defend oneself
and possessions.
Yeah, it's the only beachhead of liberty really left right now. And people are clinging to
it and it's actually growing the movement and awakening. And they hate the statistics
that areas that have guns have lower crime rates. They hate that. If they don't kill
our gun movement, it's over, okay? I don't need their supercomputers to look into the
future. I can historically, culturally, and with the brain God gave me, look for it.
And of course, they even say now what I've said, that they've got a nippus in the bud.
You don't get, you've already lost globalist. This is not gonna be like Russia. This will
not be like China. This will not be like other areas. By the way, the Russians did give one
hell of a fight. And if you don't know the history of that, the White Russians, nothing
new with white people, folks. They were all white. Some of them are Asian on the East
side.
The point is, they were the pro-Zarists. And you can say what you wanted about the Zars.
It was medieval, and it was a dictatorship of royalty. But people had private property
and the poorest people could feed themselves, and they could have guns, and they were treated
with respect. They starved to death, more than 50 million of them shot, killed, worked
them to death in just the first few decades, and they killed another 15 million after that.
And if you look at the globalist takeover model, as this article points out, it's designed
just off this Stalinist, Leninist takeover. See, that's what I tried to say earlier, folks.
If this was just good old boy corruption, I wouldn't be risking my life to fight them.
I'd just be saying it's wrong and exposing it. And I'm here desperately trying to get
you to realize that even if they wipe me out, God forbid, or bad things come in the future.
Listen, knowing this information could stop them down the road from really bad stuff.
They wanna cut all the food and water off, that's what they're setting up. They wanna
kill millions of us. And I mean, I've got the FBI's own testimony where they were in
there with Obama's handlers. And they were in there saying, we're gonna put 50 million
in forced labor camps, we're gonna kill 25 million of them.
I mean, this is their plan, now they've set those up. They'll collapse things and advertise
it as good though, you have to understand. And there's all these sickos and wannabe sadists
who wanna run these things. And I mean, I'm sorry, I am not gonna go in there, okay? You're
gonna have to pay for it. And America knows you're coming. They didn't sell 10 million
guns last month, and now it's gonna be on track even more this month cuz people don't
know.
They know who you are, their gut knows who that you are. I'm gonna shut up, let me get
back to this. These days, there are a few things to admire about the socialist bankrupt
and culturally degenerating USA. But at least so far, one thing remains, the right to bear
arms and use deadly force to defend oneself and possessions.
This probably comes as a total shock to most of my Western readers. But at one point, Russia
was one of the most heavily armed societies on Earth. This was, of course, when we were
free under the czar. Weapons from swords to spears and pistols and rifles and shotguns
were everywhere.
Yeah, in fact, you weren't a man unless you carried a pistol. Common items, people carried
them concealed, they carried them holstered. Fighting knives were the prominent part of
many traditional attires and those little tubes, Chris's, crossing on the costumes of
Cossacks in various caucus and peoples. Well, those bullets were for rifles, that's why
it's part of their dress.
You always see them with the bullets on them. Various armies such as the Poles during the
times of troubles, or Napoleon, or the Germans, even as the czar estate collapsed on the way
to World War I and Wall Street money. Found that holding Russian lands was much, much
harder than taking them. And that it was no easy walk in the park, but a bloodbath on
its own.
That's right, that's why when the West tried to collapse Russia at the end of World War
I, they couldn't do it cuz they had guns. And Napoleon couldn't do it, he'd beaten everybody,
but he couldn't beat the Russians, because their citizens would sit there and snipe you.
So Western banks on record declassified congressional hearings in the 70s, sent 25 million in gold
in with more than 10,000 New Yorkers trained with rifles with Lenin to take over. And they
took over Moscow, and then our media said, Uncle Lenin has taken over, he's a great man.
And then they went in and just killed everybody. Because it was the government, they got the
central government under control, it wasn't an open outsider.
See, if you can't realize that, you can't beat these people. Various armies such as
the Poles during the times of trouble, or Napoleon, or the Germans, even as the czar
estate collapsed with the weight of World War I, and Wall Street money. Found that holding
Russian lands was much harder, let me see a document cam shot of this, I'm gonna show
folks this article.
Was much harder than taking them, and taking was no easy walk in the park, but a bloodbath
all its own. In holding one faced an extremely well armed and aggressive population hell
bent on exterminating or driving out the aggressor. This well armed population was what allowed
the various white factions to rise up, no matter how disorganized politically or militarily
they were in 1918.
And waged a savage civil war against the reds that went on for more than 15 years off and
on. And that's why finally when Stalin had wiped them all out, then he killed 50 million
people. Once he'd gotten full control, it took him decades to kill everybody. And they've
got the same plan under agenda 21.
That's why you can't have a garden in your front yard or backyard. This is all a Russian
takeover because it was a banker takeover. American money did that to the Russians. It
should be noted that many of these armies were armed peasants, villagers, farmers and
merchants protecting their own. It had not been for Washington's clandestine support
of the reds, history would have gone quite differently.
Just like our government funded just now in 49, that's not declassified. He killed over
80 million people, depending on which number you look at, 60 to 80. Moscow fell, for example,
not from lack of weapons to defend it, but from lying guile the reds. 10,000 reds took
Moscow and were opposed only by some few hundred officer cadets and their instructors.
Even then the battle was fierce and losses high. However, in the city alone at the time
lived 30,000 military officers, both active and retired, all with their own issued weapons
and ammunition. Plus tens of thousands of other citizens were armed. The Soviets promised
to leave them all alone if they did not intervene.
They did not and for what we were asked afterwards to come register themselves and their weapons
where they were promptly shot. And the Russians go on to explain to them they are murdering
liars, they are about to do to you what it does. That's right, you study the Russian
Revolution and then you look at the Trotskyites who finally Stalin double crossed the Lenin
Trotskyites and sent them over here to Mexico and the US.
They took over and became the neo cons. Go look it up, the founder of it, Crystal's dad
was a top commie general. And they said, okay, we got kicked out over here, we're gonna come
over here, we're in so much trouble. They're gonna follow an exact Soviet blueprint. And
it really is just hard to deal with.
I understand why a lot of you can't believe this is happening because it's so horrible.
Folks, they wanna break us forever. Okay, the Russians were just as armed as the Americans.
They beat Napoleon and they beat the Reds at first until our government sent a bunch
of armed US citizens over there that knew how to shoot.
Army veterans and people, it's just so evil. As you know, American citizens helped take
Moscow. And see, as soon as McCarthy, it's now been declassified by the Russian file,
said, our army runs the Soviets. My gosh, he was destroyed but in one day. When he was
being used to just persecute liberals and people and set up a police state, see, they
used the threat they created to take our rights over here as well.
Just like in episode three, the emperor becomes the emperor by staging attacks against his
own bases. See, that's a child's movie, explain to you how false flag works. Now, the globalists
this time are gonna use Muslim extremists as the pretext to have the cover of the takeover.
But then the real manuals, which are now public, are all about gun owners. The whole thing
is about checkpoints, grid points, locking down the food, coming and getting our guns.
I mean, they plan it. And they're gonna call him Lincoln, they're not gonna call him Lenin.
Obama will be, you better remember the day you heard all this, cuz if we don't beat him
politically, this is what's gonna happen. They're gonna call this Lenin-esque takeover
Obama, he's their man. They plan on making him a full dictator, there's no doubt now.
They plan on making him the new Lenin, that'll be what he's called privately. They're gonna
call him Abraham Lincoln. And I knew this was coming because of the build up and all
the other points whenever they were advertising him as the new Lincoln and all these movies
and TV shows.
And I said, they're going to say that he's gonna crush the states and the right wingers.
And now that's in daily costs and others, they go, you bet he's Lincoln, we're coming
for your guns, get ready. And they're talking about federal militias that are gonna round
us up. You see, they want our guns cuz they fantasize like Piers Morgan agreed. He said,
I'm gonna get in a uniform and I'm gonna blow Alex Jones' brains out.
And the media is like, you bet, kill Alex Jones. But there was nobody outside harassing
me, no, no, no. They just said they wanna kill me on TV and talked about my kids, hope
they don't get killed. And I'm not even, listen, I'm not worried about myself or even my family
cuz they have no future if we don't beat them.
My flesh says just leave the country. I've warned you, I've done my part, I've been on
the front line, bye, I'm out of here, I'll broadcast from Switzerland or some other place.
Not that they're perfect, but get out of here. I'm not doing that, I'm staying, I'm going
all the way up against these people and I pray that God reprieve us.
But you know what, the White Russians weren't aborting 50 plus million babies. The Russians
were pretty moral people, folks, about as moral as you could get, culturally. They went
to church like 15 hours on Sundays and two hours a night every other night of the week
and everything else.
I mean, hard working people. And they were turned over by our filthy government and foreign
banks to be murdered and butchered. And now they wanna do that here to us. And it's just
so horrible. It's so horrible, they're gonna do this. They're gonna call us terrorists
and they're gonna set up a Soviet takeover of America.
The Red Terror is gonna come to America. That's what Homeland Security is, is the Red Terror
force. Mike and Mash here on the air, go ahead.
Yeah, Alex, I got an article for you to pull up titled Linsky, L-I-N-S-K-Y, Linsky taking
new slant on gun control. Here in Massachusetts, a state rep, David Paul Linsky, he wants to
introduce legislation that calls for liability insurance for gun owners, storage of assault
weapons at only gun clubs, can't have them in your home.
No, no, that's the plan. It's British style. That's what the commission's gonna say. Biden's
already saying it. Everyone must re-register, quote, as a new background check. You can't
give your son a gun. Any guns given to you by anybody else will be retroactively illegal
and they're gonna make you go get, quote, insurance on them. Yes, that's the plan.
Yeah, and you know what? I just got off the phone with the staffer for the state rep and
she confirmed it's not, the bill isn't written up yet, but they're working it out. But she
confirmed that they want insurance. They want storage of assault weapons in gun clubs and
they want full mental disclosure that you have to sign a waiver before you apply for
your license so that the issuing officer can get any mental health screening.
And that just reminds me of Brandon Robb. It's a total gun purge, you know?
No, listen, they're coming. What did I say two months ago? Drums, drums in the deep,
they are coming. I mean, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom. I can hear the drums. I can see
all the signs. Now they're at the door. We're now here, okay? And they're not just gonna
shoot up schools.
They're gonna blow stuff up and blame it on us. I mean, folks, this is it. And listen,
a lot of you are just gonna go along with it, listen to Glenn Beck and sit there and
they're just gonna talk, be nice and not say the government's bad. They're going to take
everything. This is a Soviet 1970 takeover. I've studied their battle plan. It is a Soviet
takeover. The Rothschild Rockefeller banks wrote the Russian takeover plan.
This is their plan refined. Look at the plan in Libya. Look at the plan in Syria. Look
at the plan in Iraq. They're doing it here. They went to all, I'm sorry, go ahead, sir.
Yeah, if you wouldn't mind, I'd like to give out the phone number for people to call in
on this guy.
Well, listen, listen, I believe in your voice sounds good, but I've always got to check
numbers before we give them out on air. People can call in with the wrong number to some
old lady and then we're in deep trouble. Email me the number, we'll look at doing that. We're
trying. And again, by the end of the show, I've got this chest cold or whatever it is.
So it's hard for me not to have packing attacks. I'm not as eloquent as I normally am. The
Russians and the previously Russian run government run Pravda is saying, do not turn your guns
in.
They're planning a red tear that your own banks financed. We've seen this before. Don't
turn them in. And by the way, they're going to tell the police and military to turn their
guns in. That's in the 7277 State Department plan. After our guns are taken, yours are
taken.
Hi, this is Alex Jones. Did you know that the global elite are now storing non-hybrid
seeds in secret storage vaults near the Arctic Circle? Did you know that in a real meltdown,
non-hybrid seeds can become more valuable than silver or gold? It's true, seeds have
outperformed even gold and silver before in this country, and it's possible that could
even happen again. So our friends at Solutions from Science have put together the perfect
mix of non-hybrid seeds. They call it a survival seed bank, and it can produce an endless supply
of nutrient dense food for you and your family. And here's the best part. These seeds have
not been genetically modified in any way, and you actually get enough seeds to plant
a full acre crisis garden. So visit them today at survivalseedbank.com. That's survivalseedbank.com
or give them a call at 877-327-0365. That's 877-327-0365. Remember, in a real crisis,
non-hybrid seeds are the ultimate barter item. This is Alex Jones for survivalseedbank.com.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box. I want you to know some very important information. In 1985, President Ronald Reagan
requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the
President could obtain this world-class healer. Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are
used around the world to keep people healthy. Now you can protect yourself and your loved
ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond
to abnormal cells only without harming a single normal cell. If you want to stay healthy,
now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders
that don't belong in your body. Call 1-866-VenusFly or order from Carnivora.com. That's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VenusFly or visit Carnivora.com. Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got. Don't throw away leftovers. Instead, throw
all your leftovers, vegetable peels, eggshells, coffee grounds, pizza crusts, and more into
the Bokashi. If you love to garden and compost but don't like the hassle of turning a compost
bin or the smell, then check out the EM Bokashi Food Waste Recycling System from Tarragonics.
Finally, a way to recycle all your food and plant waste safely and effectively and stop
using fertilizers, the EM Bokashi Food Waste Recycling System. Rather than decomposition,
the Bokashi system uses fermentation to break down waste, so it takes less time to create
nutrient-dense humus for crops or gardens with no turning and no obnoxious odors.
To learn more and order your Bokashi online, visit Tarragonics.com and click on the orange
button. That's Tarragonics.com, spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X.com or call 866-369-3678. That's 866-369-3678.
Recycle all your food wastes in about six weeks with the Bokashi Food Waste Recycling
System from Tarragonics.com. Tarragonics, life's getting better.
By the way, you know what? You just heard me break down. I need to do more eloquently
in some special reports, but you've heard me say this many times. It's the Soviet style
1917 Red Terror takeover. And sure, the Soviet Union didn't come till later. You know, technically
it's just a Red's takeover. Red Terror would be the proper term. And again, you're saying,
well, are they communists? What are they? It's mega banks. It's the same very banks
that did this, that always wanted to take down Russia because it wasn't controlled by
their system. And then Russia kind of got away from them for a while under Stalin. He
double-crossed them. And then Gorbachev was a globalist agent. And then now they're trying
to merge the EU with Russia. It's just a horrible situation all around. Let's take some more
calls. I appreciate you holding. Let's talk to a Heretic from Washington and
then we'll go to Chris and others. We'll do some overdrive. Go ahead, Heretic. Okay, he's
gone. Let's talk to Chris in Oklahoma. You're on the air. Go ahead.
Hey, Alex. How's it going? Good, buddy.
I just wanted to call in and give people kind of a mindset into somebody who is actually
a conflict schedule weapons. I was with the 45th Infantry Brigade and Delta Company, first
the 279 during Hurricane Katrina. We were really the first boots on the ground. And
keep in mind, we were an infantry brigade and we were called there for security. Saving
lives would have been nice or whatever, but that's just not what we do. And when we come
up to your house, it's just a hell of a scene. It's just like something out of a movie. It's
five trucks. Everyone departs. They stack right on the outside of the frame of the door
and then they come through. Well, every now and then we would knock and yell, does anyone
need any assistance? But that's how I'm booting in the door.
Well, that's the psych warfare thing. We're here to assist you. I mean, that's all. This
is not an attack. And this happened on record. Again, this is the training. This is the test.
I think you called a few years ago and told the whole story, didn't you?
Yeah, it was a couple of months ago. I called in and I was talking to Rob, the health ranger
it was. Okay, so finish your story. I mean, describe
to people, yeah. And then ABC News said if someone resisted, you killed them.
Yes, sir. What happened, I was called up in the middle of the night and literally at 2
a.m. I reported to the unit at 4 a.m. We were told immediately that there's news reports
and reports on the ground that people are firing at rescue helicopters. The city is
descended into total chaos and we're gonna come in there and put our boot up some butt.
Yeah, exactly. Notice the cover story with you at society.
Now we're gonna go find and shoot in helicopters later made up. We're just gonna go take everybody's
guns at their houses. Yeah, we're going to secure the city at any
and all costs. We'll meet aggression with aggression. And that's how it was to be done.
And we're like this, right wing terrorists just nuked the major city. All of them are
to be killed on sight. They don't turn the guns in. We're gonna round up the troll makers
as well. You're the willows and you're dead. Hail Obama, King of Earth. Sorry, go ahead.
Oh, sorry. They used that whole situation. I figured this out later. I'm not in the military
anymore. And this plagues me every day that I went around and actually did this. It didn't
occur to me till later what I was what I was doing. I know it sounds like an ignorant cop
out, but no, no, no, no, no. You just walk up and suddenly you're being
groped by TSA. You just walk up one day and they say, take your shoes off. You walk up
one day and they say, go get in the ditch and they shoot you in the back of the head.
But I mean, look, they are planning this and then they're going to call gun owners terrorist.
And then I hope people understand they plan a red style takeover. If people submit to
this, it's over. If you could imagine what this, you know,
the geoengineering and things that go on, whatever you could say about Katrina, it happened.
And it's just that emergency situation where everybody's hyped up. You know, my whole unit
is is on fire to do this mission. And me as a young soldier who had had some disciplinary
problems, I'm eager to prove myself. You know what I mean? I'm eager to show that I'm combat
ready and I'm ready to go. You know, I just did it. I didn't. I wasn't there to exactly.
I mean, I think we should all just turn our guns into Obama and have one hundred percent
tax and all live in forced collectives like Mao did. And I think 80 million of us should
be killed by Mao. And I think Mao is God there. Now I can be on Piers Morgan and I can be
popular. We have a guy claiming he was a Piers Morgan audience member. Stay with us.
Thank you for listening to GCN. Visit GCN live dot com today.
Coming back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At E Foods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, Almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my foods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared ten years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on E Foods Direct. Coast
to coast, direct from Austin. You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network. Big
brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does he. He's Alex
Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones. All right,
folks, we're now into overdrive here. We've got a fellow who says he was a previous audience
member. They didn't have a studio audience when I was there, but they do sometimes. Derek
in New Jersey. That was a scary last phone call. Then we got James. We'll try to cram
in. But real fast, Derek, what's your story? Hey, Alex, how you doing? Good. Hey, I was
an audience member back in September when Jesse Ventura was the guest. I was actually
one of the audience members. I got to ask him a question. That was the first audience
member. Getting a little nervous. My experience on that show was that they filled the audience.
You can't really see it from the angles that they shot it at, but they filled the audience
with people, interns, people from other floors. They were pulling people out of the street.
They couldn't fill the entire audience, all the seats. There were a bunch of empty seats.
The guy next to me who asked the second question about the Navy seal book, they pulled him
off the street. I swear this happened. They pulled him off the street because we were
talking to my brother and I. My brother even pointed it out to one of the producer people
who comes over. He said, oh, you're pulling people off the street. She gave him a snide
remark and the guy, they said, here's your question. They handed him the car. They said,
they went through it. They practiced it. I was right next to the guy and they said, here
you go. Here's what you're going to ask him. And he asked him the question. They didn't
even get to the other audience members that were picked to ask questions.
Sir, they had people on a rooftop in Atlanta with a green screen saying they were under
nerve gas attack. I mean, have you, no, I mean it's CIA and they're not even, did you
notice that how, how the place looks shabby and was rotting. It was disgusting. I actually
used that bathroom. It was, I couldn't believe it. Wow. So you, you, you saw the poop on
the walls. It was terrible. They, they, yeah, before, before the show went, they said, if
anyone needs to use the bathroom, come with us. My brother went to, it was, I couldn't
believe it. You sound credible. We can go to the last Ventura interview and see if it
matches your voice and people will do that later when this goes online.
Describe the layout of the Piers Morgan set. When you come in out of the hallway, how was
it laid out?
Well, the way he had it set up there was kind of like a round table. So everyone was sitting
in the middle. Before you go in the studio, what's, what's right outside the door. They
brought you in.
Yeah, it was like a cruddy white walls or the ceiling was caved in. It was terrible
lighting. There was, I mean, it looked like you were in a, I mean, it looked like they
bring the trash through there every day, but what was the layout? What was the layout of
the, of the green room? And then the, what was beside it?
Well, we just, I just went to the restroom. It was through the, through the doors and
I didn't quite go past through the green rooms.
It was white walls. By the way, that's not the common restroom. I'm talking about the
green room restroom was dirty too. I appreciate your call, sir. Good to hear from you. Let's
talk to James in Minnesota with vital info and XM listener. Go ahead.
Hey Alex, this is James. Thank you so much for taking my call. A long time listener.
First time caller. I just want to say that I do hereby solemnly swear and affirm that
I am prepared to die for the public. I am prepared to die for Liberty. I'm a us infantry
army show army soldier. I am prepared to die in the defense of this Republic. And I stand
on that.
What do you think about the Russians saying, don't turn in your guns. Like our military
did, you know, under the state department memorandum after they get our guns, they have
the general army stand down and turn their guns in.
Oh, absolutely. I mean, that's, that's what they've done in every, every communist revolution
is always a purge of the military after they're done being useful idiots after they're done
using us to enact their agenda, they murder us. And I'm telling you right now, everyone
listening to this, everyone who can hear my voice right now, you are in the military.
If you do not stand against this, you will die. They will murder you. You are their enemy.
They hate you. Now look, I have, I have a message of tragedy and hope. I, I have seen
the enemy and I have looked into his eyes and I know who he is, but I know how to defeat
him.
And I'm going to share that with you right now. Are you prepared? All right. Last night
I spoke with tier one special operations officer. He looked me square in the eyes. We're going
into extra overdrive. This is too important. We'll go to more calls as well. Don't hang
up. Don't hang up. James folks, I've studied history. I know this attack pattern. That's
why I keep telling you what's coming next. I guess I just got chills. This is a red Soviet
style takeover by mega banks, not the Russians.
Joe Biden is, is leading the fight against the technocrats, but we can't do that without
your help. By getting the films, bumper stickers, and t-shirts and info wars.com. It will wake
up people in your area and support our operation. As we move to the next level, we need your
help to spread the word. Like never before, they wish to hide themselves during this tectonic
battle between the forces of freedom and darkness. You are the response to the globalist war.
technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization and ultimate extermination
the war is here it's an info war the spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984
preparedness is simple when you have the right stuff and with the looming threat of economic
collapse and possible service interruption it's time to get the best in class preparedness stuff
at disasterstuff.com disasterstuff.com has been serving smart preppers for over 15 years with
quality products like berkey water filters disasterstuff.com is the official berkey in-stock
shipping center and as always free shipping on all berkey products stock up on water barrels and
accessories get country living or wonder mill grain mills Excalibur food dehydrators
hattler reusable canning lids sun oven solar cookers emp bags to protect sensitive electronics
and don't be without your life straw personal water filter all from disasterstuff.com preparedness
is simple with the right stuff from disasterstuff.com freedom through self-reliance and personal
responsibility fight back this cold and flu season with the world's best garlic extract
ali-c why ali-c because it helps your body fight viruses bacteria and fungi ali-c has been
scientifically proven in double-blind studies using low doses to greatly reduce the number
severity and duration of common colds ali-c contains 300 milligrams of stabilized allicin
the active ingredient in crushed garlic studies show ali-c is effective against mersa bacterial
fungal and viral infections one tablet of ali-c has the equivalent of 40 cloves of garlic ali-c
supports your body's resistance to all types of conditions and can help lower high blood pressure
and high cholesterol so boost your body's resistance to infection with nature's best
garlic extract ali-c for more information and to order ali-c call 877-888-7126 or go
to garlichealthproducts.com that's 1-877-888-7126 or go to garlichealthproducts.com for your ali-c
today from his central texas command center deep behind enemy lines the information war continues
it's alex jones and the gcn radio network so they announced yesterday they were going to use
executive orders to ban semi-autos other things and because it was a huge backlash they came out
today i saw on msnbc and cnn both globalist channels collaborator channels saying nobody's
going to take your guns through executive orders the executive order only activates interpretations
of existing laws so the new thing is yes a dictator would use executive orders to take guns
our executive orders only interpret laws that already exist that's what we've said they could
use some street sweeper legislation to expand to all semi-autos and then claim under rulemaking
you got to turn them in that's what larry pratt said a month ago on the show they can also harass
with rule making the gun shops and make it impossible and make them you know well under
atf rules you got to have 50 million in insurance they in fact they said they're going to target
manufacturers with rules so and again they're just getting you ready where they have the moral
high ground where every time there's a mass shooting that they advertise and and and hype
up with copycats that it's your fault you collectively have the guilt you did it like
you told larry pratt yesterday he said don't you feel anything for what's happened don't you feel
any empathy like he's done it and i would have said i wouldn't have been so mad of course he
didn't bring that up to me because i knew he'd say something like that i plan to say you mean
you're the ones that made them victim disarmament zones and advertise it's the place to go kill
people i did get that part out you're the ones you're the ones using 20 dead which is terrible
but statistically very low probability why don't you use all the other horrible stories out there
because you've got an agenda now i want to shut up go back to your calls james in minnesota says
he's an army infantryman and he wanted to get into talking to some people last night in the
military and what he was hearing he's listening on xm james go ahead hey alex thanks for uh going
back to me hey you better recap what you said recap what you said and then cover it all right
last night i was uh speaking to a friend of mine this guy is tier one alex this is u.s army special
operations this guy's been in he's seen it from every angle and i just asked him straight up i
said hey um if it comes to it are you seriously willing to look me in the eye and kill me and he
said this to me he saw you right to my face and the face of my wife he said yes i would i would
come to your house i would kick in your door and i would kill you to take your gun and the moment
he said that to me the you know god just revealed this to me in a glorious flash light this is how
we are going to defeat these people alex we're going to call their bluff we're going to turn
their threats back on them i haven't i had this idea for a campaign we're going to call it we are
the dead we're going to have a massive facebook campaign we're going to get people who are willing
to stand with the public with republic we're willing to stand with democracy we're going to
get them to delete their facebook pages in mass if they want to treat us like unpersons but they
want to dehumanize us we're going to pull out from their system we're going to reject them
i want to get a massive advertising campaign going i want t-shirts i want bumper stickers we are the
dead we are the 1.5 million if one percent resisted 1.5 million who would die if these
laws are enacted we're going to call their bluff and i want 1.5 million patriots to march on
washington dc in mass and we're going to stand there in a silent protest and at the stroke of 12
we're all going to light candles and we're going to blow them out one by one and we're just going
to stand there well that's powerful you should shoot a youtube video describing your idea no i
mean that's what i've done on air is i've i've said okay i'm not going along with this and that's
why i got morgan's face is because i've had to go across that line i'm public they've now made me
the poster boy to take down when they blow up stuff you better believe they're going to blame me
and they're going to try to get all the other cowards out there who are libertarians or whatever
to then come criticize me and and when they do that they're benedict arnolds
okay our forebears went through this you know don't be so angry at the new world order don't
get in their face don't you know go along don't don't say you know that's what this is coming down
to and listen i've had the calls i've talked to a lot of military folks where they said their
commanders are like yes we will kill americans they don't turn their guns in so now it's gone
from it'll never happen to we're going to kill the americans i mean it's total treason and oh
by the way it won't be sob stories for us that are dead and i just want the military and police to
know once this starts i i mean it they just have no idea and usually militaries throughout history
usually do this and then they're called out as well i mean i i don't know what it would be like
if this guy looked at you and said i'll come kill your family i mean he's been psychologically
profiled and chosen for this so he i mean i guess there's no order he wouldn't follow just anything
he'll do it and alex this is why we have to call their bluff look i'm telling you man well what
did you say to him when he said this i i just i just said well you know what if if a faceless
corporate fascist regime means more to you than the lives of of human beings then the lord bless
you and keep you that's all i could say to him that's all that's honestly all i could say to him
because yeah these guys think being evil is manly and and it's the opposite i mean i mean alex look
i'm telling you we're not the best but we're all that's left i want to work for you man i want to
come to austin i want to make this a reality i want one point five well well here's the issue
if you try to have people march on washington they put provocateurs and it would never even
the point is we need a million marches in every town and city every day with banner hangs and
people doing youtube videos and other ideas and people saying i'm not turning my guns in this is
about despotism and you know drudge putting up the fact that hitler wanted the guns and stalin
one of the guns we need to call them what they are authoritarians using dead kids for their agenda
i appreciate your call i mean i think most of the military i talk to aren't going to go along with
this but uh the ones that they're going to put in command are and i've analyzed it it is a vicious
takeover plan and a lot of people say man you're scary i guess you're just cowards then because
you know i'm telling you what i really think it is so we can face it and i i i mean my instinct
my gut my intellect everything points towards resist this get back in its face or it wins
my fear is letting them take over so i'm running around like a chicken with my head cut off
trying to warn people and as radical as this show sounds we're getting new affiliates in fact
here's a couple of them every week khnc 1360 am the lion port collins colorada 10 000 water
and that's one we're featuring that's been an affiliate uh and wjnl 12 10 am
traver city michigan 50 000 watts thanks to pd and gm and the great stations and i think those
are two stations we already had so this is this is a station in focus this is not the new affiliates
that that list is somewhere else but i need to have the affiliates in focus thing once a week as
well uh but but it's it's all very very exciting i just came in and said hey here's some new
affiliates and that's actually the new stations in focus deal um but we have gained several new
affiliates this week as well the point is the broadcast is steadily steadily growing here
let's talk to chris in california uh wants to talk he's listening on xm chris what's your take on all
this and man i think that this is all something that you predicted from the beginning i'm a one
year listener first time caller and that piece of garbage going back is always preaching about
doing your homework and doing your research and last night i did my research and went on youtube
now you've been talking about this since july 25th 2001 i mean you called 9 11 on the spot
you know you you know we got i i appreciate everything you're doing alex and and uh i'm
getting my mother my brothers my friends everybody's getting into the show i'm trying to
get them on info wars this is all you know i'm ready man i never thought anything like this could
be possible my last time i was hoping it wouldn't but well no i mean it's a foreign banking takeover
to label all gun owners as terrorists and then and then the gun grabbers is sweet people that love
children and they're sending men in black uniforms to get our guns it's their excuse to start a civil
war so they can then like the regs uh take over i mean that's their plan and and listen i i just
really quick i think that it's going to be quite as simple as i don't think obama knows that he
can't take our guns yet but this is all a setup and i think what did what python was saying yesterday
i think the setup is they're just going to make it more difficult for people like you and i
to take to carry our guns around you know more gun no gun zones and that so when that happens
that's when they're going to be able to confiscate the guns because all of these
movies are going to start shooting people and blowing people up and blaming on people like us
who you know just wanted to they're going to make it more difficult for us to defend ourselves well
god bless you let's go to eric uh in canada real quick go ahead hey alex first time call i've been
following you since 2004 and you're awesome um i gotta tell you since all of this stuff has been
going on and after watching what happened on pierce morgan the other night um me and my wife
are going out to start buying guns and i don't know if you know what canada is about but we
we don't have a very big gun population up here but as much as this stuff is going on state side
this stuff is going on canada side to uh the idol no more movement which is being held by the natives
so on and so forth you know alex i gotta tell you my friend you know we will stand there we
will stand in front of you we will not allow these guys to take you down and from your brothers from
the north i swear to god we're here for you guys well that touches my heart and again i'm certainly
an imperfect vessel to be right up at the tip of the spear we're all up there together i'm trying
my best thank you for the support uh they're going to demonize us they're going to use all of this
weird cultural revolution uh you know emotion stuff they're going to say we killed the children
we blew up the federal buildings we nuked the city we assassinate you know i mean i've told
you everybody they're going to do horrible things and then say it's our fault and they've said gun
owners are nazis gun owners are clan gun owners we collectively killed those kids no you did you're
a bunch of scum trying to scapegoat us to disarm us because they can't have us armed when they
fully implode the economy so they're racing to get our guns god bless you sir and i appreciate
you're from canada all right well i tell you we've got wmqm listeners in tennessee we've got
all sorts of folks calling in but i'm going to go into retransmission now because i've already
gone 20 minutes into overdrive and again i'm under the weather so it's hard for me to talk
with this chest cold but i thought was just allergies so i'm gonna go work on some things
for the nightly news coming up tonight seven o'clock info wars.com prison planet.com a lot
of key info the dean of the doug hagglund interview is coming up with the homeland
security confirming source that they are stalking me and again they do this to make me sound crazy
when i talk about it and then also try to intimidate me because they know the general
public just does not understand the stuff you see in movies so much stuff i've seen in movies
that's based on real stuff that goes on so please pray for us
all right that's the doug hagglund things coming up stay with us