Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is the 14th day of January, 2013. We're gonna be here live, Lord
willing, for the next three hours. And again, I am your host, Alex Jones. We do not have
any guests today except for the Obama phone lady.
And she is going to be in studio with us. She is here in Austin, Texas. If you go up
to infowars.com or prisonplanet.com, you can see there that it says, Obama phone lady comes
to Texas. And this is amazing because she's one of the most virally viewed and downloaded
videos ever.
And it's not just that what she's saying is ridiculous about free handouts from the government.
I know she's listening right now, she's a very sweet lady. It's that she's very funny.
And she's exactly what I thought she would be like when she flew in last night at about
630.
Her plane was late, flew in out of Cleveland via Houston and then to Austin, Texas. And
her husband is exactly what I imagined him to be like. Just really nice, funny, smart
people except childlike when it comes to trusting government. And she's just as funny and just
as charming in person as she is in that video.
That's only about a minute long, where she talks about you on social security, food stamps,
you get Obama phone. Everybody in Cleveland got Obama phone. Well, ladies and gentlemen,
we took her and her husband out to dinner last night and has had a great evening with
them.
And quite frankly, I haven't really hardly seen my children the last few days. I've been
drinking so much over the weekend. And I wanna go home and see them tonight. But I also wanna
take Obama phone lady out to dinner. You know what I'll do? I'll have my wife come meet
us for dinner.
And we'll take Obama phone lady and her husband. And we're gonna tell you her name and everything
here on air. In fact, if you don't know who Obama phone lady is, let's go ahead and cue
that up with audio. Can we cue that up and play the audio here in a moment?
So, people are asking, why have you gotten Obama phone lady here? Well, number one, I
said to listeners, there'd be a $5,000 bounty for whoever got me a hold of her. That's some
good English there, that there would be a $5,000 bonus for whoever got us in touch with
her.
And then if we actually got her on air, $5,000 bounty. And I gotta talk to the guys that
actually ran into her at a store and did this and obviously asked them if they want any
of that bounty to go to her. But we flew her down here and she is here. And so in about
an hour and a half from now, if we cover news and take your calls, we will have Obama phone
lady here.
And you notice last night when I picked her up, the video is up on infowars.com that I
wore a sports jacket. And you notice I'm wearing one now because I've got butterflies. This
is a big deal around here and I'm not joking. It's like the eagle has landed, okay? This
is the kind of stuff we get excited about.
I was not even excited about going on Piers Morgan, didn't even have butterflies. I didn't
wear a sports jacket. For Obama phone lady, I think I'll go put a tie on. I ought to put
some diamond cufflinks on. In fact, I'm wearing a short sleeve shirt, that's not respectful
enough. That's actually all I had back there in my wardrobe, I sent stuff away to be cleaned.
Anyway, she's coming. You may even get her husband in here with her. He's a character
too, but it's a big deal. And I'm telling you, this woman could be ready for standup
comedy on HBO right now. So who wants to manage her out there is the big question. We'll be
right back, ladies and gentlemen. Stay with us.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad
spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver
solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning
and help improve wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as stress, staph,
pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the ability to terminate
entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal
or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ
fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go
to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off. That's
SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to supernaturalsilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
There's an old saying in Tennessee, I know it's in Texas probably in Tennessee that says
fool me once, shame on you. If you fool me you can't get fooled again.
He aligns himself with the truth and it's time for you to choose a side. You're listening
to Alex Jones.
A man's got to have a code, a creed to live by, John Wayne. And I tip my hat and take
a toast of coffee to John Wayne from my John Wayne coffee cup that I bought at his favorite
place in the world, Monument Valley, Utah, where he shot so many of his first westerns.
Mm, absolutely delicious. Thank you so much for joining us on this Monday edition worldwide
broadcast the 14th day of January 2013.
Wow, where to begin? Where to start? If you just tuned in to the broadcast, coming up
in the flesh and I'm still pinching myself that this isn't a dream. People on the YouTube
video that we posted late last night that Rob Dew and John Bowne did a great job getting
up even though he didn't get back from dinner with Obama phone lady till about 930.
They stayed up late to edit down our picking her up at the airport and taking her out to
dinner and some of the enjoyable antics that took place there. Don't worry, they'll be
full behind the scenes videos in the days to come and she's gonna be in studio today
with us on the radio show.
And then I think I'm gonna take her out around Austin today as well and shoot some more footage
weather. And a lot of people are obviously freaking out saying it's like reality is folding
in on itself. She goes out and talks about Obama gave us a phone, he's gonna do more.
Everybody in Cleveland got Obama phone. And it's not just that the video is obviously
ridiculous, the dependency and the idea that government's there to give us freebies.
But that she does have an electric personality. And I think this could be a story of somebody
who literally takes that flash in the pan 15 minutes of fame and turns it into something
bigger. I see her as a kind of a Sam Kennison style comic, because she's very funny in person,
very witty. But again, also tough love here, I told her this last night.
She's like, well, my son says you're a Republican, you're a big conservative, you're pro gun
and stuff. I don't really have the Internet, so I don't know. And I came anyways cuz so
many people after they heard I was coming on or was thinking about coming on said, yeah,
you gotta go on the Alex Jones show in her community.
And a lot of folks she knows said that I was a good guy. And I was honest with her. I said,
look, it's ridiculous that you want a free phone from the president and that that's your
idea of winning somehow when they take your whole future away with dependency and then
basically give us baubles. It's like a free toy and a happy meal.
But the fact from a sociological perspective, or a psychological perspective, as a sociologist
or as someone studying culture, that she is kind of the archetypal person who really thinks
the government cares about her and wants to help her get a leg up. There have been some
people in government that have tried to help folks.
There have been good people that have worked through government to help people. But the
controlling driving force of government is domestication, enslavement, and cultural destruction.
And no one can argue with the numbers of what welfare and big government has done, not just
to the black community, but communities across the board. And so it is my hope, and I'll
just be honest with you here about this, is that it is my hope to stay in contact with
Obama phone lady, and we'll give you her full name and stuff on air when she joins us.
And to try to basically maybe even have her as an auxiliary reporter. I haven't even told
her this yet, I'm just saying it all on air. And to try to educate her and inform her about
how we're all being inserted into a matrix like prison. So I wanna reach down to the
matrix like Morpheus to her a Neo.
Because as Eric Blair, aka George Arwell said, if there is any hope, will you guys print
me Orwell quotes, I meant to do that. Orwell quotes on the only hope lies with the proles.
And even though I don't subscribe to the communist ideology, the globalists are using communism
as a template of control. And it's the general public, George Arwell talked about, he actually
wrote nonfiction books on this subject, that obsess over lottery tickets or get rich quick
schemes or a hope and a prayer.
But just if Obama gets in there, he's gonna fix everything cuz the President can get it
done. And this woman really hopes that he's gonna turn the economy around. This woman
works for $8 an hour and can't live on that and I don't blame her in Cleveland. She goes
and cleans houses all day for $8 an hour, no one could live on that.
And they take taxes out of it, and she didn't even understand that. She didn't even understand
why her paycheck's getting smaller with the payroll taxes. I mean, let me tell you something,
my wife and other people in my family when they heard that she was coming to town last
week, they said, listen, Alex, you're mean, you don't get her on your show and make fun
of her.
And I said, what do you think, I'm an idiot? I don't wanna make fun of her, sure, it's
funny at one level, and she knows it's funny. My goal is to actually show this lady who's
actually an interesting human being and has a lot of spirit, a lot of heart, a lot of
guts, who's got real potential.
I guarantee you, ladies and gentlemen, you take somebody like that lady and you put her
on the frontier, you put her in adversity. You give her real opportunities to have a
future and to build a better world and to not be dumbed down by the television in this
sick culture, she would be an unbelievably powerful individual. I can see the potential
there.
And that's what makes me so bad about The Collectivist, is that they know human potential
and they wanna shutter it, they wanna shut it down. While telling us big government is
about getting Obama phone lady to her highest potential. And that is not the case. And if
you don't know who Obama phone lady is, can we cue that up one more time?
She's the lady who was one of the most viral videos last year. I mean, it's been seen,
let's be conservative. There's probably 50 million views in one form or another out there,
8 million here, 5 million there.
Keep Obama in president, you know, he gave us a phone.
He gave you a phone.
He's gonna do more.
How did he give you a phone?
You sign up and you on full stamps, you on social security, you got low income, you disability.
Okay, what's wrong with Rami again?
Rami, he sucks. Hey.
You got Obama phone?
Yes, everybody in Cleveland, low minority got Obama phone. Keep Obama in president,
you know.
By the way, I put a $5,000 bounty out to find her. And I was surprised, cuz we have listeners
in every city. We're on a couple of stations in Ohio, lot of listeners in Cleveland. And
no one could find her until a listener ran into her in a store months and months later.
And guess what? The Democratic Party took her, same amount of money. She was working,
you know, paid canvasser. So we now know that. And they stuck her at a desk job and told
her stay out of the public eye. And then they lied to her and said, because you're just
too effective.
I mean, see, I'm not gonna lie to this lady. I told her it's hilarious what you did. I
don't agree with the dependency. I think if you play your cards right, and if you go to
some small time comedy clubs and get under the right person's wing, you can develop comedy
pieces and probably become very famous. She's got natural talent. And there's nothing I'd
like better.
By the way, I didn't tell her this to get her here. I told her this once I was with
her in person. But I told her it'll take hard work. She's not gonna go right to the top
immediately. She's funny. And my instinct about her, she's exactly what I thought she'd
be like. Exactly what I thought she would be like.
And her husband was exactly what I thought they'd be like. And just really funny, interesting
people who are, again, smart at many levels, but also still buy into the fake dream. And
that's what this is all about, the fake dream of, you go to a casino, you're gonna get rich.
You buy a lottery ticket, you're gonna win. You get Obama in, all the problems are gonna
be fixed.
And I was sitting there talking to her last night. I know she's listening. I should just
leave it all and let it be fresh when she gets here. She's like, man, I voted for him,
voted for him twice. Things gotta get better. Obama's gonna get in trouble. If things don't
get better, honey, things aren't gonna get better.
This is Agenda 21 designed to destroy you. They don't bring in 30 million illegal aliens,
so you've got a future. And they don't bring them in so they get a future. They bring them
in to drive down the wages and make us poor as a political tool of control. And they also
understood that, well, Obama, like Nixon, he can just pump some money out there.
They understood Obama's got the printing press to turn up on high. And I said, have you noticed
prices have gone up? Notice the packages of potato chips and ice cream have gotten smaller.
Have you noticed that in almost every area, things are going up and up and up in price?
And they're like, yeah, we have noticed that. We just can't pay our bills. Her husband works
as a plumber 12 hours a day. She works as a maid for $8 an hour. And again, no one's
ever taught her anything entrepreneurial.
No one has explained to her that the maid service she contracts through, I bet money
is getting 20, $25 an hour for. And all she's got to do is go hang up signs all around the
area that she wants to target, saying she'll come clean houses. And she'd get all that
clientele for herself and double or triple her money, just like that with pieces of paper
hung up on the wall.
No one is teaching these people anything. They don't teach any of that in school. They
don't want you to know that. Anyways, it's going to be a study of can we help somebody?
But it's not like the Eddie Murphy movie where they make a bet that they can't help somebody.
I know that we can probably try to help this lady and help others by her example. We'll
be right back. Stay with us.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought, to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
We can buy GMOs stressed out about money and blasted by the electric environment. Hi, I'm
Pastor Ginny and that was the state I was in back in 2010. Then I learned about RNA
drops. I learned that 97% of my DNA that scientists have called junk is actually packed with millions
of gene switches that play a critical role in controlling how my cells, organs, and other
tissues behave. I learned I don't have to put up with disease decay or decline like
I've been conditioned to believe. I began taking RNA drops, a 100% natural formula designed
to turn on those switches and provide me with amazing health and joy. Learn more about RNA
drops and order a free sample today. Visit RNAFreeSample.com. That's RNAFreeSample.com
or call toll-free, 888-577-3703. Pay only shipping and handling for a free 30-day supply
of RNA drops. Get the information you need and the health you want at RNAFreeSample.com.
hempusa.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new Micro Plant Powder Gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine, and probiotics
and we'll send you our travel size Micro Plant Powder absolutely free. Micro Plant Powder
only at hempusa.org. Call 908-691-2608. That's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder, seeds
and oil can do for you only at hempusa.org. This offer ends January 31st. Hi, this is
Ted Anderson. Have you ever wondered why banks, stock workers, investment advisors won't talk
about gold IRAs? They've been available since 1986, yet the financial industry won't recognize
the value of gold for your retirement. Gold is outperform paper investments, yet no word
about IRAs. If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237. Don't
get left behind by rising inflation and low returns, call 800-686-2237. Secure your future
and call 1-800-686-2237. Is this the year you finally get serious about your family's
drinking water? If so, keep listening for a special offer from Big Berkey Water Filters.
Did you know that over 60% of municipal water is fluoridated? Berkey Water Filters distinguish
themselves from many other filtration systems with the capability to significantly reduce
dangerous chlorine, fluoride, arsenic and disinfection byproducts from municipal water
via the Black Berkey and PF line of filters. Then there's affordability. At only 1.7 cents
per gallon, Berkey Water Filters purify treated and untreated water, even stagnant pond water.
Stop and think how much money you could save by simply reducing buying bottled water and
using water filtered by your Berkey Water Filter. No need to be constantly replacing
expensive filters with a Berkey. A single set of filters can last for 5 to 10 years.
Choose the best size Berkey for your needs at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com. And right now,
all GCN listeners get 5% off all ceramic filter systems. Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY. That's
877-99-BER-KEY or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com. Free shipping on every order over $50. Big
Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean water.
We're going to get into the news and open the phones up here in a moment. But first,
here's from page 60 of 1984 written by George Orwell. If there was hope, it must lie with
the proles, that's the common working class. Because only there in those swarming, disregarded
masses, 85% of the population of Oceania, that's England and the US, could be forced
to destroy the party ever be generated.
The party could not be overthrown from within. Its enemies, if ever it had any enemies, had
no way of coming together or even of identifying one another. Even if the legendary brotherhood
existed as just a possibility it might, it was inconceivable that its members could ever
assemble in large numbers in more than twos and threes.
Rebellion meant a look in the eyes, an inflection of the voice, at the most an occasional whispered
word. But the proles, if only they could somehow become conscious of their own strength, would
have no need to conspire. They need only to rise up and shake themselves like a horse
shaking off flies.
If they chose, they could blow the party to pieces tomorrow morning. Surely, sooner or
later it must come to them to do it, and yet. And he goes through the strength of the proles
watching this grandmother out there hand washing the clothes in the slum. And the strength
of her sunburned face, and her big muscular shoulders, and sound of children giggling.
But the proles wouldn't spend their time studying how government or business worked. The proles
obsessed all day about lottery tickets, and lottery systems to win, and get rich schemes,
and pornography, and mindlessness, and entertainment put out by the party.
Big Brother didn't even need to police the proles. They were just dumbed down, and obsessed
with petty garbage, and didn't even exist. The party, the English Socialist Party, which
is really a Soviet party in the book. This is what George Arwell, aka real name Eric
Blair, who'd worked for the communist, and worked for MI6, and worked for OSS, and worked
as an imperial policeman before that.
And lived in the slums on purpose for years, contracting tuberculosis in Paris, and also
in London. Wrote a bunch of non-fiction books and essays, amazing stuff. I've read basically
all of Arwell's writings I could find in a period in my life when I was about 20. I learned
a lot through him not having to actually go live in a slum with people with tuberculosis.
He came from a well-to-do kind of establishment intelligentsia family.
And he thought communism would fight the ills he saw. And then he discovered, wait a minute,
fighting in the Spanish Civil War, that the communists were just as bad as the fascists.
They were just criminals, using a governmental term, a political term as a cover. And then
he went and worked at the BBC in propaganda. And the character Winston Smith is Eric Blair
at the BBC, one of their top propagandists, taking truths and rearranging them and smashing
them.
And then he discovers the British government is funding Hitler, that they'd funded Hitler.
Didn't run Hitler, they helped creating, helped put him in there. It was like a wind-up toy,
like one of these mentally ill mass shooters. They give government funds and have a government
psychiatrist and then, they go and attack.
And the book talks about government-sponsored terror, how the government itself was firing
missiles into London every day, randomly, just to scare people. And now everything else
was squalor and rack and ruin, but the giant, pyramidal-sized buildings that look like something
out of Blade Runner, with black helicopters coming in and out of armored command bases,
flying around, looking through your windows and your television screens, watching and
listening to you.
That is now a reality. They just haven't gone to the physical end of it yet. And here's
the good news, they are in check. And if you know chess, that means we've got them, we're
closed to fire, we're closed to beat them. Because the average gun shows out there are
reporting 10,000 people visiting them, organizers shocked as 10,000 attend gun show.
Piers Morgan is now chickened out of a debate he called for, part two, round two. Senator
Schumer is saying they'll just use executive power to basically lean on. This is what they've
already said they do, that's why we told you this was coming. Executive orders, rule-making,
and just tell Walmart and others not to sell semi-autos, and have the ATF come in and make
basically nickel and dime them and white glove inspect them till they do it.
You're saying, well, how do we have them in check? Doesn't mean we've won, they've still
got some moves. But I mean, we're up against them, we're right on their tail. They're not
on our tail, we're on their tail. When we come back, I'll explain to you why, go for
some news and then take your calls. But coming up at the bottom of the next hour, one hour
away, you will be transmitted.
We're on the march. The empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought, to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health. At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver-based products. Our most popular silver-based products are
the 32-ounce nano-silver solutions, our 2-ounce nano-silver nasal applicators, as well as
our all-natural silver soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver
gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver
at the surface. But rather, we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin-nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the
silver more effectively. Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver-based
products are best for you.
In the councils of government, we must guard against the acquisition of unwanted influence,
whether sought or unsought, by the military industrial commons. In Dallas, Texas, three
shots were fired at President Kennedy's motorcade in downtown Dallas. One man did it. First
reports say that President Kennedy has been seriously wounded by this shooting. It is
a big idea. A new world order. I thought that didn't exist. It was almost as if there were
planned implosions. It just pancakes. Either you were with us or you were with the terrorists.
And later you gave them, time Feinstein loves us. I also believe in a lot of gun owners
cut on. Vacationant got all falloc the police and guards. It is an uncomfortable job to
for what the central banks do.
And for me, give me liberty or give me death.
Live from the Infowars.com studios, it's Alex Jones.
Yes, sir, I am he and it is the 14th day of January 2013.
And if you'd like to talk about all the incredible news taking place geopolitically, domestically,
the economy, by the way, start sending your questions in at Real Alex Jones on Twitter.
And guys, will you start printing me or ask Christie, who helps run the Twitter account
does a great job.
Maybe ask her to print off questions for Obama phone lady.
Show that when Michelle, that's her first name, so that when Michelle is in here in
about an hour from now, we can also have some of your questions for Obama phone lady who
we've flown down to Austin, Texas, to really have the archetypal Obama supporter here in
studio with us.
And by the way, we've had archetypal Bush supporters on before, who thought it was conservative
to get rid of the Bill of Rights and were pro torture.
So they're just as nonsensical sometimes as well.
So we look forward to having her here just because we hope to try to be able to change
her mind.
And it doesn't mean we want her to go support Romney.
No, Romney sucks to quote Obama phone lady.
The point is, is that it was a rigged game.
So that is coming up if you just joined us.
Yes, you heard me right.
This is not a joke of the video of her arriving to Austin via aircraft is up on prisonplanet.com
and infowars.com.
In fact, have we tweeted Obama phone lady videos out?
I don't think I've even done that.
Will you guys tweet that out for me?
Cuz it's hard for me to walk and chew gum.
I've come here to do two things.
One thing is to kick butt and the other thing is to chew bubble gum and I'm all out of bubble
gum.
To quote, to paraphrase Rowdy Piper, okay, I'm being silly.
The point is, I wanna send out a tweet that Obama phone lady discovered, Obama phone lady's
identity discovered.
It's kind of dictation, I'm dictating the tweet there.
Okay, you can tell I'm excited about this, even though we've got a lot of bad news and
some good news here.
And we're gonna be going over.
By the way, this shirt sold out, this shirt sold out, but they had a feeling it was gonna
sell out.
And so there is a truck coming, but tomorrow with more of these.
So you'll basically should be able to get it by next week.
Get your order in now.
We've never had a t-shirt sell like this.
It is a come and take it AK-47 with the Texas come and take it, Texas Revolutionary War
segment.
It says come and take it and inside of the AK-47 is the right to keep and bear arms shall
not be infringed.
And then it says infoawars.com handsomely on the back.
And we've got women asking for a woman's design, that'll take some time, but we got smalls
for women.
Yes, we're going to come out with some shirts for women, people been, I get requested on
the street all the time.
I never tell my folks, we gotta come out with women's shirts, and with the same messages,
but that are more contour form fitting.
My wife has said this, and so we've got to do it.
So there I'm multitasking here on air.
If you want the come and take it shirt, get your order in now.
And of course, we also have the second best selling, Victory or Death with the rattlesnake
on it.
Very powerful, we also have a camouflage one of those, not just the black on red one.
It's all up at infoawarsstore.com and your purchase of the books, the videos, the T-shirts,
all of it makes this broadcast possible.
So they're all up there on the site right now, be sure and get it today.
And again, continue to spread the word about the transmission.
I'm certainly risking my life, my treasure, my name, everything else in this fight.
So I'm not saying the least you can do, we appreciate your support.
And the point is, this isn't a game, we shouldn't take this platform for granted.
That's why I'm working so much harder than I ever have, because we've got to make hay
while the sun shines.
We've got to engage the globalists while we still have a lot of freedom left.
Now, I told you before we went to break that, people are always saying, you never give the
number or the address out.
You're right, not everybody's on the internet or wants to order via the internet.
You can call and order any T-shirts or propure water filters discounted with promo code WATER
ALL of it, 888-253-3139, 888-253-3139.
And you can also write to us here at P.O.
Box 19549, Austin, Texas, 78760, P.O.
Box 19549, Austin, Texas, 78760.
I give that out so rarely that I don't even have it memorized.
So P.O.
Box 19549, Austin, Texas, 78760, and we've had that address now for about six years.
So that'll give you an idea.
A lot of survival stuff, the best quality stuff out there.
We've got the very best essential oil systems put out by our friends over at Interfood.
We've got the Army Ranger style black caps, it's come to the Oathkeeper style in fullwars.com.
Okay, I'm done plugging.
I just haven't been plugging much the last month.
I've been so focused on defending the Second Amendment that I haven't even been midair
refueling our news operation system.
Cuz we're not like the mainstream media that gets government bailouts and tax exemptions
and then tries to overthrow the Republic, tries to get your taxes raised cuz they get
the corporate welfare bailout money.
They're subsidiaries of banks that do.
We just sell products we believe in.
And of course, the media says that's horrible, that's evil.
How dare us, how dare us, how dare us, how dare us, pay our own way, promoting high quality
products at great prices.
It's totally immoral.
And that's what they always say at CNN, you name it.
They always say the same thing, they say I'm evil.
And every time the national media comes to interview me, they go, how dare you make money?
This is a pretty big operation, you got a lot of crew members, you got a lot of equipment
here.
You're making money, that's bad.
I'm like, well, did you fly here, first class?
You did, didn't you?
You're in New York, aren't you?
How much you paid a year?
Oh, a million dollars, read off a teleprompter.
You're here lecturing me.
Anyway, side issue, just amazing how they play these mind games with us.
Here's the toll free number to join us.
It's 800-259-9231, 800-259-9231, and we'll get you up and on the air.
Well, that high def camera's so good, you can even see the dust on top, the live on
air right there.
No, that's okay.
It's not your job to clean in here.
I think we do have a cleaning crew.
I don't think they ever come in here though.
I guess because they see it as like the big studio.
Oh my gosh.
There's like a dead fruit fly over there or something.
We're to start here, 800-259-9231, on any issue you wish to discuss, I got a couple
of news items.
I want to hit them and then we're going to your phone calls.
And let me just show folks in the document cam, hey, hey guys, we got a camera mounted
in there.
Can we punch that up for viewers?
Here, come on over and say hi to folks.
No, no, just right there in that microphone.
Hello fans, Obama phone lady here.
How's that audio, Genesis?
Show today.
You better open your phones in your head.
Hey, can you give a shout out to everybody?
No, go ahead.
I'm going to give a shout out to everybody here in Austin, Texas.
I'm on the Alex Jones show.
I'm the Obama phone lady representing Alex Jones here today.
And I love that guy.
He's funny like me.
Oh my goodness, there's no doubt, and I'm not just saying this, you could do voiceovers
immediately.
I'm going to work on your radio station before I leave here.
I think you might.
Have you heard the news?
I'm going to officially offer you on air, at least an auxiliary paid job as a reporter.
All right, hallelujah, yes, thank you.
I also want to make sure you like the terms, I'm going to work it all out, but I'm very
glad you're excited.
I'm excited about that, I need a job.
Darn it, May, Obama, you see what you've done?
I'm moving up in the world, you're going to do your job, I'm going to set you down.
What do you think of the rest of the crew?
I love the crew.
You got your kids out, anytime you can go to work and bring your kids, that's the job.
That's what I'm trying to get to.
That's right, well, don't give out too many of our security issues, but yes, no, my son,
I'm just joking.
Jakari, what do you think of all this, Jakari Jackson back there?
This is quite a deal for me, Michelle and I have something in common, we just made a
YouTube video and somebody liked our voice enough to give us a job, so I can relate to
her on that.
Thank you, Jesus, well.
He's the man, he's the man, but Obama with the man with the plan, but we're going to
see what he's going to do.
If he don't do the right thing, I'm going to be the woman with the plan, Michelle Obama
and Michelle Dowery.
That's right, ladies and gentlemen, all right, you think I'm joking, she's here, some people
still think I'm joking.
I mean, I think everybody is more freaked out about you being here in a good way than
when I've had movie stars here walking around in the halls.
And I got the blood of Jesus, baby, I'm here, all right?
All right, we're very excited, ladies and gentlemen, she is in the house.
I'll tell you, guys, why don't we get her some lunch or something, or take her back
in the green room, because it's so exciting to have her here that I can barely even operate
right now.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, I'll tell you what, Michelle, run in here real quick.
Run in here real quick, Michelle, come on in the studio, come on, we got to give people
a taste of this right now.
Come on right around here.
That's right, no, no, come on right over here by my microphone, you're just going to pop
in for a moment, okay, come on in.
We've got the camera right over here, say hi to folks right there.
Hello, folks.
Let's go to this camera right here, guys.
Hello, folks, I'm here today, the Obama phone lady.
Here she is, here, here, talking the mic, oops, go ahead.
I'm here today, you guys, I'm here in Austin, Texas, I'm at the Alex Jones show, I want
you guys to represent, I'm here, the Obama phone lady, I arrive, I'm ready to get it
going on, let's do it.
All right, we'll see you in here in about an hour.
Good job, there you go, ladies and gentlemen.
That is proof of life, as they say, all right, absolutely, ladies and gentlemen, there she
is.
Okay, now let's shift gears into the really, really bad news.
And again, guys, I hear another mic open now, whatever's going on, okay, got that mic shut
down cuz you get that taken care of, you know what I'm gonna do?
They're moving ahead right now with draconian moves, where they're just gonna tell, as I
told you, gun manufacturers, you can't manufacture this, no law, they're just gonna say it.
They're moving ahead with telling shops you just can't sell guns.
And Chuck Schumer has announced that, the article is up at infowars.com.
New York has tentative deal on gun control, they're just gonna throw anybody they want
in the nut house, no judge, no jury, you're just going to the nut house.
And Rahm Emanuel is announcing in the Washington Post what he said years ago, they'll just
put you on a no gun buy list, no judge, no jury, no proof, no nothing, you just disappear.
Like Brandon Robb, the Marine, who criticized Obama.
And so we are going to be discussing all of that today, but let me just go ahead and go
to your phone calls right now here, ladies and gentlemen.
Let's go ahead and talk to Dexter in Maryland.
Dexter, you're on the air.
Yeah, your phone's really, really low, brother.
Is that an Obama phone?
Is this a little better?
Yes, sir, go ahead.
Okay, well, first of all, congratulations for Piers Morgan interview, that was epic.
I do believe he'll have you back around too, who could be so desperate for ratings, and
it would be huge.
But what I wanted to talk about was Sandy Hook.
I'm somebody that believes that there's some fishiness there, and I'd like to go through
a couple of things.
I'm not sure if you've seen all these things yet.
First, have you seen the video where the little girl's father comes out, like the first guy
that came out to give an interview?
Yeah, he's laughing and smiling, and he says, do I read off the card?
And then he turns the camera and then breaks, and then sits there and looks like he's forcing
himself to cry.
And then it looks like bad acting from the worst soap opera you've ever seen.
But people act strange under incredible pressure, so none of us know what he's going through.
So my prayers go out to him and his family.
But yeah, a lot of people are investigating the whole thing.
Well, one thing that's weird about him is that his daughter, by the end of the day,
she had a Facebook page up that was a tribute that was already looking for money.
It seems kind of odd that so quickly, just a few hours after-
Well, listen, here's the deal.
I appreciate your call, bro.
Look, I don't know about that, and I'm not going to talk about parents of dead kids,
okay?
And see, I don't know if that's true.
That's something I haven't seen.
And so it's just, I'm not gonna talk about somebody who lost his daughter.
Yes, there wasn't the AR-15 inside the school, yes, it was in the car, yes, there were multiple
shooters outside.
Mainstream media, RT has attacked me, saying, five-year-olds said they saw multiple shooters.
No, it's on footage from the surveillance cameras, from the helicopter they put on the
news, showing them arresting people in the woods dressed like the supposed shooter.
And the whole thing's suspicious, okay?
And I'm not trying to jump on you, caller.
It's just that there are a lot of reports out there, a lot of people questioning the
whole thing.
But I'm not going to sit there and go after the dad.
It's just, I'm gonna let other people do their own research, I'm gonna leave it at that.
Jessica in Canada, you're on the air.
Hi, Alex.
Hey.
I just wanted to, you did a great job with peers, and I just wanted to bring you up to
date on a couple of things that are happening with Agenda 21 here in Canada.
Tell us about it.
Well, one, our environmental commissioner here in Ontario has decided that food waste
is an environmental problem.
And I just noticed that the UN has taken up this issue, so they're coming after our food,
Alex.
No, no, they're going to, they've already done this in England, and they're going to
tax you for everything that goes in the trash can.
And they're going to have RFID on all the products that is scanned, this is already
happening in London, to track, and they'll give you $3,000 fines for every attraction.
It's already on the books in several Florida cities.
And they go, don't worry, we'll never implement it.
Kind of like they put it on the books under federal grants, start taking blood without
warrants 15 years ago, now they're doing it.
So you're absolutely right, Agenda 21 is a total surveillance grid where all the appliances
track you, and where they tax you to the point of total bankruptcy.
It's to make sure you stay poor.
And that you have to go on government subsistence so they can then shoot you up with deadly
vaccines.
Have you looked into Idle No More, because it looks like the Tides Foundation is radicalizing
our natives up here.
Yeah, it's everywhere, the Tides Foundation is involved in a ton of stuff.
Did you have anything else you wanted to add on the agenda 21?
Nope, this is on Land Use Planner, and I've been fighting this for eight years.
Well, good job, you give them hell.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the President could obtain this world-class healer.
Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally
occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune
cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VenusFly, or order from Carnivora.com, that's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A dot com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VenusFly, or visit Carnivora.com.
That's your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
Big business has discovered the preparedness market, and that makes it difficult to know
where to go and who to trust.
MyPatriotsSupply.com is owned and operated by Patriots just like you, has the best prices
on storable food, non-GMO seeds, water filtration devices, home canning equipment, survival
and self-reliance books, and more.
MyPatriotsSupply.com has old-fashioned values and the absolute best customer service in
the industry.
Look for the deal of the day, unique affordable survival supplies that fit anyone's budget.
Get same-day shipping on all orders and free shipping on orders over $49.
Call 866-229-0927, 866-229-0927, or visit MyPatriotsSupply.com for emergency preparedness,
self-reliance, and food independence.
Shop with a name you know and a name you can trust.
Before it's time to survive, it's time to prepare.
MyPatriotsSupply.com.
We travel so much, and having a fake TV, well, it gives added peace of mind.
Burglars look for houses that appear to be easy targets, but fake TV can fool even professional
burglars into thinking someone is home watching television.
As a recent widow living alone, it gives me great peace of mind to set my fake TV near
a window and know that passing motorists and pedestrians will think someone is home watching
TV when I'm actually away from home.
Fake TV easily plugs into any outlet, just like a light on a timer.
And they're so easy to use, you just plug them in and they're ready to go.
Plus, they're so affordable that we have one upstairs and downstairs.
Fake TV is only $34.95.
Order your fake TV by calling 877-5FAKETV or go to Faketv.com.
That's 877-532-5388 or Faketv.com.
Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
And he decides who to free and who to blame, everybody won't be treated all the same.
There'll be a golden letter reaching down when the man comes around.
We are back live.
The hairs on your arm will stand up.
Hi, I'm Alex Jones, your host.
Let's go back to your phone calls.
George in Texas, you're on the air.
I noticed you called in about gun control, you volunteered.
Are you excited that they're trial ballooning executive orders, ATF rulemaking, or just
Chuckie Schumer ordering Walmart and others to stop selling semi-autos?
I mean, they're really trying to see if they can just sell us on being dictators.
Yeah, I absolutely agree.
And I first wanted to congratulate you on your appearance with Piers Morgan on CNN,
the state-run media.
And I believe you did exactly what it takes.
I think they're scared because you broke the spell.
And I think this rush and this barrage of legislation, all the draconian legislation
that's coming out, I think it's very clear that you forced their hand.
And I don't think they were ready.
I think it's too early for them and that's why they're so upset.
Well, I don't think I did it, but I'm certainly part of it, and so are you.
We're all together in this.
But earlier I said I would get into the victory, get into what's positive.
I haven't really done that yet, but I've already said it before, 10 million guns sold last
month.
They're talking about more guns sold this month.
They're saying soon everything will be sold out.
There won't even be bolt action 22s.
Everything is going to be sold out.
The ammo is selling out everywhere.
That's the real vote.
America knows the government is criminal and can't be trusted.
America knows we're going into a depression and the state run media lies.
And we've talked about what to name the corporate globalist trader media.
That's it.
It's state run media.
That's the best term for it.
And we're dealing with a global corporate fascist state that uses socialism at the grassroots
to control us like flypaper.
And there is a revolt.
People are waking up.
And that's why they're trying to act all confident and we've got a mandate for socialism now.
Obama wasn't really reelected.
They had that thing fixed seven ways to Sunday, running him up against that political corpse
Romney election.
But even the evidence shows even though Romney was a dead horse, still he really beat Obama
of the election fraud evidence shows and not that that would have been good.
He's globalist as well.
They just think Obama can con people better.
I'm sorry, I'm ranting.
No, no, no, no, you're good.
And you know, I'd like to make two points with you.
I'd like you to explain to people just what a semiautomatic weapon actually is, because
I don't think a lot of people realize that it includes pistols and handguns.
I think they associate it with fully automatic and they associate it with assault rifles
and they don't understand exactly what.
Well, Feinstein has called for even revolvers to be banned before, but technically a semiauto
is pull the trigger once a bullet fires, pull it again, it fires again.
And they obsess over full auto that's worthless for actually killing people if you wanna be
selective about it.
That's what the military doesn't use full auto, unless it's a heavy machine gun with
big boxes of ammo in emplacements to take out large numbers of infantry.
Or sometimes even used on the ground to mark targets in a primitive way for aircraft that
are coming in.
They use tracers to mark targets and do other things, but that's another issue studying
military warfare.
The truth is, when they say ban semiautos, you don't need assault rifles and they show
a scary looking black M16, why people think that's scary, I don't know.
And then they are saying, let's just get rid of these, when really it gets rid of almost
all guns, almost all shotguns, everything.
Most guns are semiauto and they wanna get rid of them, but their new bills even get
rid of pump shotguns.
So I mean, they're coming for almost everything, does that answer what you wanted me to do?
No, yeah, absolutely, and if I could, I'd like to tie that into an article you just
had run yesterday on the death of Aaron Schwart.
Yeah, stay there.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support, and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Raging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, we're taking your phone calls ahead of Obama phone lady joining us in studio.
Now I'm going to have a serious talk with her.
And sure, we will have her on as a example of collectivization.
And at the same time, though, that she's a smart lady and has humanity in her, like all
of us do, and then hopefully I can get through to her about Obama.
So that is coming up.
But Georgia and Texas, yeah, Obama killed this critic found dead in New York City, prominent
American blogger, and the guy that really headed up killing SOPA, the Internet takeover,
found hung.
And they were trying to put him in jail for 35 years for downloading some MIT policy papers,
research papers that taxpayers paid for, and posting them for the public to have.
Talk about military industrial complex, so they say, he committed suicide.
That's what they'll do.
They'll indict you, say you're depressed and kill you.
Listen, if I ever get indicted, I'm going to fight it forever.
I will never commit suicide.
And what they do is, even though the DC madam sat on my show, she never committed suicide.
And then I knew behind the scenes she was being followed, being harassed.
And I even had her condo manager on saying he was friends with her and that he even gave
me her handwriting.
It wasn't her.
They put out the suicide note, wasn't even close.
A totally different handwriting and that she was being followed by men, was bringing stuff
over to her mothers.
She killed her and her mothers out in the shed.
And she said, I'll never commit suicide.
And then of course, somebody says, I'll never commit suicide.
They have a quote, friend, someone who doesn't even really know them, always comes out in
the news and said, shit, she told me she was gonna commit suicide.
So that's what will happen.
If they ever kill me, they'll have a friend come out and say, Alex told me he was.
And that person, that person was told by the killers and paid by the killer to do it.
That person, that's the person involved, okay?
You understand that?
Cuz that's a bunch of baloney.
If I was diagnosed with cancer, I will go with Darth Vader level surgeries and everything
else.
Alternative, you name it, okay?
I'm gonna go out of this world kicking and screaming and snapping like a crocodile, okay?
Let's just get that straight.
I'm going all the way, okay?
Darth Vader level medicine, brain surgery, you name it, lungs out on the table, open
heart surgery, whatever it is, I'm doing it.
Let's get that straight.
I'm never gonna commit suicide, never, never, never, never, never, never, never, never,
never, never, never, never, never.
And I would never murder, suicide my family.
That's one of their other favorites, just to wipe out a whole family.
Never that ever happens, God forbid, knock on wood, pray to Jesus, it won't happen.
And you know I was killed.
Real fast, your comments on that, George?
I'm glad you said that, cuz this is really a personal issue for me.
The similarities between myself and Aaron Swartz, this is George from Austin.
I was out at the drone mob event, you had me in studio.
I did the drone peaceful protest, and I actually just made a video and uploaded it saying the
exact same thing.
I took a cue from you after the Piers Morgan show, yeah, I saw your videos when you're
in the hotel, you're being followed, I saw the security guy.
And so I felt I had to make a video and post it up on YouTube saying the exact same thing.
I'll never commit suicide, I love my life, I love my country, and I believe the solution
to this is just to tell the truth, wake people up, political commentary, and you know, it's
really sad that I'm in fear that I could end up in the exact same situation.
And so I posted that video up on YouTube, and I don't know if you would allow me to,
but I'd really feel a lot safer if your listeners could go take a look at it.
Sure, what's the name of it?
This is your video, it's YouTube.com slash Young Truthers.
All right, listen, I gotta jump, but listen, folks, the number one cause of death is automobile
accidents.
Well, not anymore now, it's suicide, people killing themselves, then it's cars.
You're risking your life every day driving with cars going 70 in this lane, you're going
70 in this lane.
If you hit it's 140 mile an hour, you're dead, I don't care how many seatbelts you're wearing,
you're dead 99% of the time, okay, you're dead.
I drive on roads where people die every week, okay?
And I still do it cuz I like to drive, folks, take their power away, you're gonna die anyway
someday.
Let me tell you, they keep killing people like this, folks aren't gonna put up with
it, and I'm not calling for that, but New World Order folks are the ones better watch
their butts.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarshop.com.
These are items that I did research on, that I personally use.
We've got the life straw, so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out
in the field.
The strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen, when disaster strikes by Matthew
Stein.
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Hand crank shortwave AM FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com
and your purchase makes our info war possible.
We're getting prepared, are you?
Infowarshop.com.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu, and other illnesses.
Be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold, and food poisoning, and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day, while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases, such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus, and
other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
To the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die, start purifying your water with ProPure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research, and the best gravity filter out there bar none
is ProPure, and it's available discounted at infowars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified.
Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%, easy to set up and use, doesn't
require electricity, purify water from lakes, streams, ponds, and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
ProPure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on ProPure, but if you add the promo code
water at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, again, thank you so much for joining us.
It is the 14th day of January 2013 on this Monday edition.
And coming up after we take more phone calls and cover more news, we are going to have
the one, the only Obama phone lady on the broadcast.
And if you don't know who the Obama phone lady is, perhaps this will remind you.
She's the lady who talked about Obama gave us a phone and he's going to do more.
Obama phone.
Keep Obama in, president, you know.
He gave us a phone.
He gave you a phone.
He's gonna do more.
How'd he give you a phone?
You sign up.
You sign up and you on full stamps, you on Social Security, you got low income, you disability.
Hey, listen, okay, what's wrong with Romney again?
Romney, he sucks.
Hey.
Hold on.
Obama.
You got Obama phone?
Yes, everybody in Cleveland, low minority, got Obama phone.
Keep Obama in, president, you know.
He gave us a phone.
He gave you a phone.
He's gonna do more.
How'd he give you a phone?
By the way, guys, that's enough.
We are playing her out of the studio and she's right there sitting behind him.
And I gotta be honest, I mean, I'm getting goosebumps here and butterflies.
Ma'am, can you please go to the green room?
You're such a big star and I'm not joking for whatever reason.
I'm having trouble continuing the broadcast here with you in there.
Do you get that chocolate shake I got you?
She's awesome, absolutely awesome.
She's right there.
I see you, this is incredible.
She's already in command.
She's, all right, you can stay there, that's fine.
I just, it's, man, it is distracting.
I tell you, this is a real fringe benefit.
It's like caviar, being able to have, that's one good thing about my job, I get to meet
interesting people.
And we've had a lot of famous people in this building, but I tell you, nobody like Obama
phone lady, which by the way, the Democrats, she was working for them.
They went and put her on the desk job after that viral video you just saw.
So, but we're gonna break that blockade here on air today with the Obama phone lady, but
actually get down to the core of what this lady really stands for.
And again, I sent the link out to the video when she was on the show at Real Alex Jones.
Just go to Twitter, forward slash, Real Alex Jones, you wanna find the link to the video
last night of us hanging out around Austin, Texas, that video now obviously going viral.
And we're going to print, again, dozens of questions that listeners are sending in for
her.
She'll be with us for an hour and a half while we take phone calls.
We're gonna have her in studio and she's gonna do more.
She's gonna answer your questions.
She's gonna describe why Romney sucks and why he sucks bad.
So let's go back to your calls.
You know what?
Let me get one news item before I do that because I'll never get to it if I don't.
Right here on the document cam if you're watching on television, radio listeners just search
New York has tentative deal on gun control.
And that's out of the Associated Press.
And they're going to have mental health law that allows for civil confinement of people
determined to be a threat to others.
And they're saying that if you criticize the government, that's a sign of mental illness.
They're saying wanting to own guns is mental illness.
And here is a article out of the Washington Post today, where again, the so-called liberals
or really the authoritarians, they dictate reality.
They say that when I went on Piers Morgan, that that was wrong, that I got in his face
and that it was abnormal to yell or raise my voice.
Now Governor Cuomo raised his voice when he said we're gonna get the guns last week,
started yelling and screaming, everybody was cheering.
Well that's okay, that's okay because he's calling for our rights to be taken.
But when I said listen, don't try to take the guns or it'll cause a civil war, do you
understand that?
Ron Paul agreed with me two days later last week.
Just search Ron Paul says, Second Amendment is the line in the sand, attempt to take guns
will cause civil war.
Well, that's bad too.
But when you read this article, whom does Alex Jones represent?
They play this game of saying, mainline conservatives, Alex Jones represents you and this is bad.
You're discredited now, your Second Amendment's discredited.
It's a total mind game.
It's like them saying, there are no bills that take any of your guns, it's a conspiracy
theory.
Though this bill does take your guns, it's no big deal.
You're like, you just said you don't take my guns.
But because they're the boss, they're on the throne, up above us, in the clouds, okay,
you've introduced 11 bills that some of them even take pump shotguns federally and they're
at state levels.
And you've got state reps calling for door to door gun confiscation, mainstream news
covered that yesterday.
All of this is going on, the military training manuals for confiscating guns, all this is
happening and they go, nobody wants your guns.
Nobody's coming after your guns.
And when that tank was slamming into the Waco church, and they had troops behind it firing
their M16s into the building, the flare footage is clear.
They were saying, this is not an assault, come out with your hands up.
And there's footage of Davidians coming out with their hands up, you can see their body
resonance heat, the flare footage, and they just shoot them, they fall down, and the tank
runs over them.
But they said, this is not an assault, come out with your hands up.
And when they would come out, this is too big of a distraction now, my son and Obama
lady together, hey, hey, hey, hey, everybody out of the studio, seriously, out, out, okay?
Yeah, that goes to my son, okay?
It's a circus out there, man, I can't focus, there's all this stuff going on out there.
Well, talk about chomping at the bit to be on the radio, that's my son.
What is the point I was getting to here?
They are selling everyone that they control reality.
And so number one, if so-called conservatives don't agree with what I say, that's fine.
We're not collectivist, I don't speak for you, you don't speak for me.
But everybody's got to, we've got to be nice and turn some of our guns in, and we've got
to not raise our voices, and we've got to, yeah.
How's that work for people that are constitutionalist, conservatives, libertarians, whatever you
want to call it?
I mean, Romney was for Obamacare, he wrote the thing for banning semi-autos, for open
borders, for carbon taxes, should I keep going on here?
And that's who they ran so he would lose, like a rigged Don King boxing match, I mean,
come on, folks.
And so I get up there and I go, listen, stop saying you don't want our guns, and stop saying
this is about kids, this is about authoritarianism.
You're on notice, don't start the Civil War, is that clear?
You're a mouthpiece for globalist criminals, and I'm putting you on notice.
That's exactly what, in fact, I wish I'd have been more hardcore, instead of even responding
to anything he was saying.
Now that hindsight's 20-20, I should have done more.
Paul Revere wrote through the countryside when they came for the guns, saying to arms,
to arms, the British are coming, the redcoats are coming, one is my land, two is my sea.
Our forebears went out and killed people.
I'm not calling for that, I don't want that to start, I wanna fix this peacefully.
But if so-called libertarians and conservatives can't handle somebody going, listen, you twit,
go back to your country and stop telling me to turn my guns in.
If they can't handle it, then may your chains set lightly upon you, lick the hand that feeds
you, crouch down and lick the hand that feeds you.
Will you guys print me the Patrick Henry, liberty or death speech?
I mean, why does New Hampshire say liberty or death on the license plates?
Why do we get a tear in our eyes at the Star Spangled Banner?
What's that song about?
It's about people on a fort under bombardment, not giving up.
It's about ragtag farmers and people taking on a military that had defeated the Spanish,
the French, the Dutch, the Portuguese, you want me to keep going here?
I mean, the British Army a few years later beat Napoleon.
And our ancestors literally had to go bushwhack people by the end of the war to get ammo.
And they don't want you knowing about that, I'm up here just saying, hey, man, don't come
to my country and tell me turn my guns in and tell us collectively as gun owners that
it's our fault somebody died.
It's your fault for making that a gun free zone.
It's your fault for advertising the place to go kill people as a school.
Well, that really got to them.
They were going pull the plug when I said that they were no, no, no, cuz they know that
they know for their their hype in school shootings every single day on corporate New World Order
globalist run traitor media, hoping mentally ill people go into schools and shoot people.
I mean, they are hyping copycatters like it's going out of style.
And I put them on notice, man, they're trying to get more kids killed.
They're the ones that set the whole thing up.
They know full well that the drug inserts on those drugs, by the way, I've got Samjay
Gupta, whoever he pronounces him the brain surgeon, Gupta and Tom Ridge.
I saw a natural news article today, always great reporters, but I didn't see where the
links were to Samjay Gupta and Ridge saying drugs are probably the cause of these shootings.
So I went and searched what they said, it might have just been an oversight.
And I actually found everything they said, I actually found the transcripts and the videos.
I've got those, I told Paul Watson to add links to it.
So good for that former head of Homeland Security.
And what's going on with Tom Ridge?
That guy has got like a conscience.
He wrote a book saying Bush put out fake terror alerts as the pretext to take our liberties.
And now he's come out and said, we gotta look at these drugs.
That's the main unifying issue.
I mean, good job, former head of Homeland Security Ridge.
By the way, the head of Homeland Security is a puppet, folks.
They usually don't even know half of what's going on.
This is an outside shadow government, not the front guys, you see.
And I'm not saying Ridge is a perfect guy.
I'm seeing signs, though, that he's got a heart and a soul, and that's all I'm looking
for.
All right, we'll take some more calls and get Obama phone lady in here.
And the point is, is that they're telling you what is acceptable behavior.
They're telling you what reality is.
They're telling you, you killed those kids collectively, so you have guilt.
And that makes me angry.
And they're trying to get more kids killed, okay?
Now what would George Washington do?
Would George Washington cower, appears Morgan?
What would Thomas Paine do?
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e Foods Direct.
We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration.
As an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years in serving thousands of satisfied customers,
the Berkey guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration systems.
The Berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable black purification
elements that purify water.
By removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria, cysts and parasites to non-detectable levels
and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides.
Order the Berkey light system today complete with two black Berkey elements for only $231
and the Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge.
With the purchase of a Berkey light, the Berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride and
arsenic filters for only $39.99.
That's over 30% off the retail price.
Call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653.
That's 1-877-886-3653 or order online at GoBerkey.com.
That's GoBerkey.com today.
What's going on with food prices?
Have you noticed how your favorite ice cream is now 14 ounces instead of a pint?
Round trip air fares into nine major cities has increased 44% in just one year.
Ask your 18 to 25 year old what it costs to buy some nice fashionable jeans, $300?
And yet not one person in a hundred realizes these prices reflect government spending and
Federal Reserve Bank dollar printing.
Gold in the last 10 years has increased 450% while the dollar's purchasing power is declining
daily.
My name is Daniel Larson.
I work at Midas Resources.
To learn more about how gold and silver can protect your dwindling purchasing power and
your IRA accounts, call 1-800-686-2237, extension 134.
That's 800-686-2237, extension 134.
Daniel Larson, 800-686-2237, extension 134.
Hey there, Frank Bates here.
Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out 280 million Americans?
This is really scary stuff.
Bates experts warn that this odd device poses the gravest threat we've ever known.
In fact, just a few weeks ago, former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed
piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat.
I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up.
That's why my friend just created a free video at weirddevice.com that exposes this threat
and blows the doors off the conspiracy.
Go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover exactly what it is,
plus discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack.
I'm not sure how long this video will be online, so go to weirddevice.com before it's gone
forever.
And that's weirddevice.com.
Coming up, we're not going to be fighting, though, but we are building it up the eye
of the tiger.
The Obama phone lady right here in Austin, Texas, rising up the thrill of the fight is
the eye of the tiger.
In fact, we'll just re-intro her with this again, kind of like her royal entrance whenever
she comes on the broadcast.
It's the eye of the tiger.
There it is.
Oh, yeah.
It's the eye of the tiger.
Let's go ahead.
Everybody, you know you love that song, even though it's cheesy.
Everybody knows when they're driving along, they turn this up.
We're playing that off YouTube.
It's not doing it justice.
Here it is.
Crank it up.
Hey, she rose to the challenge.
Put her down here to be with the crazy Texan.
All right, Billy in California, you want to talk about Satan?
Go ahead.
You're on the air.
Thank you, Joan, for having me on right now.
You bet, buddy.
Yeah.
Just just want to talk to you about Jimmy Fazil.
They just recently found out in the UK articles, the UK articles that he was involved with
for satanic ritualism, which is a really big shock, not to not to us, of course.
But no, David, I said over a decade ago that he was a pedophile and a Satanist, and that's
on record.
And he said about a bunch of other people, you know, David, I worked at the BBC.
You can say what you want about the guy, but, you know, like George Arwell, he worked at
the highest levels of the BBC.
And of course, Sevelle.
Yeah, you're right.
That's now coming out the Satanism.
Yep.
Yeah, basically, I was hoping, I know you do talk about this, you know, often about
how Satanism is involved in this, and I was wondering maybe if you could do a future show
really focusing on how deep Satanism has gone, you know, whether it be in Nazism, in the
past, and how it's led America down this path of darkness, and just really showing
people that, you know, we really need to understand that we're dealing with some super high
level, dynamic activity here as it leads America down the path of destruction.
Well, I mean, you could take one look at Jimmy Sevelle.
I mean, I can tell pretty much if somebody's a real Luciferian, because they look like
that in the eyes.
I don't care if they're black, white, who they are.
That's a guy that hung out with a royal family like no one else and hung out and quote supplied
things.
He would brag.
I supply special things to government parties.
And see, they don't trust you at the highest levels of government now, because here's the
news, folks.
They don't just hurt the children, okay?
If it all comes out on this guy from my sources, they don't just watch snuff films, and we
know that's a huge industry.
They produce them.
Let's put him back on screen.
International Business Times, Jimmy Sevelle's satanic sex ring claim, star worship the devil.
And all these top reporters are coming out and saying, yeah, he would just brag about
worshiping the devil, how he was with the royal family.
This is a guy who could get into the royal palaces, had his own keys and stuff.
Nobody got that.
And I mean, that's who they are.
That's who we're fighting.
I mean, I sit here and that's why I should be so serious.
I joke around and stuff because I can't be serious all the time, or I'd go crazy.
But I mean, yes, we're dealing with Satanists that want to torture children to death.
I mean, that's who we're fighting.
That's who runs the government.
And if people don't get that, there's no future.
Yeah, yeah, just basically when I talk to people about this stuff, that's eventually
where I lead them to, and they don't wanna believe it.
And then when they find out for themselves, they're like, wow, this is really happening.
It's really in front of myself.
I want people to learn to see the look.
Punch it back up.
You see that guy?
I have been to the court cases.
I've covered it with a CPS.
Half of them look like that.
Men or women, black or white, they look just like that.
When you're possessed by whatever demon is in those people, that's what it looks like
on your screen if you're a TV viewer.
If you don't know who Jimmy Savelle is, just search engine it and get ready.
And let me tell you, ladies and gentlemen, that is a demon of hell, a demon of hell.
And the only reason this is all coming out right now is the EU's blackmailing the British
government to bring down England and put them into the EU.
Yeah, you didn't know that's why this is all coming out right now?
Even more even may come out.
They may come out on the news someday and say, yeah, we chop kids' heads off and drink
their blood as it sprays out of their, you know, stump.
They'll be like, well, that's good, but I don't want to do that.
Well, you're an extremist, you know, because the Aztecs cut kids' hearts out every day
when the sun came up.
And if you didn't think that was normal, they'd kill you.
You're like, but that's crazy.
No, when you're in the devil worshiper kingdom, you're crazy.
See those of us that don't like all this and are like, hey, you're not getting my guns,
devil worshippers.
They're like, you're mentally ill.
We're going to have to put you in solitary.
We're on the march.
The empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e foods direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York city wrote, almost all of the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today, or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting non-GMO long-term storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e foods direct.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben soap company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at fivestarsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at fivestarsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarsoap.com.
These are items that I did research on that I personally use.
We've got the life straw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages are out
in the field.
Strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein.
Barrow safe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event and
crank shortwave AM FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarsoap.com
and your purchase makes our info war possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you infowarsoap.com
Michelle Dowry is in studio with us, ladies and gentlemen, and we'll queue up the Obama
phone famous audio video here in a moment for folks.
So new listeners who don't know who she is can get a idea and be reminded.
But when she flew into town last night, there were people at the airport taking photos shooting
video of her.
Also there were people when we went out to eat who were coming over wanting to take photographs
with her.
I mean, that's the power of YouTube.
And it wasn't just that it was somebody on there saying I want Obama to give me something.
There's plenty of videos like that.
It's that she was interesting and she was funny.
And so people ask why did you bring Obama phone lady down to Austin, Texas to be in
studio with us?
And her husband as well, who we've had a chance to hang out with, Harvey.
We brought her down here because she's a phenomenon.
And I guess the way she disappeared from being an obvious Democratic Party canvasser disappearing
that they had put her up in an office and that is indeed what she told me last night
on video.
And I thought, hey, let's actually hear from the person, the real person, not just a short
clip.
Let's see what she really stands for, what she really believes in, just from a sociology
perspective to really understand what is in the mind of someone who really thinks Obama's
a great guy.
There are a lot of people that think Mitt Romney was a great guy.
I didn't like Mitt Romney either.
Her son thinks that I'm a Republican because I don't like Obama.
Whenever a Republican gets in office, people think I'm a Democrat because I don't like
it.
When Republican presidents are torturing and wars and all this, I just marvel at how when
somebody's guy is in office, be they Republican or Democrat, they suddenly switch off their
thinking process.
And if the other party was doing that, they'd be upset.
But because it's seen as their guy, well then everything is great.
But here is the Obama phone lady clip.
Here it is.
You got Obama phone?
Yes, everybody in Cleveland, low minority, got Obama phone.
Keep Obama in president, you know.
He gave us a phone.
He gave you a phone.
He's gonna do more.
How'd he give you a phone?
You sign up, you're on full stamps, you're on Social Security.
You got low income, you disability.
Hey, listen.
Okay, what's wrong with Romney again?
Romney, he sucks.
Hey.
Obama.
You got Obama phone?
Yes, everybody in Cleveland, low minority.
Okay, now she's gonna be with us for the next hour and 20 minutes, maybe even into overdrive.
And yes, ladies and gentlemen, I know we've got callers on other issues holding, but you
can address your question to myself.
And of course, to Michelle Dowry, who is here in studio with us.
But first off, Michelle, I wanna commend you for having the courage to come down here.
Describe that thinking process and how that happened, and then tell people a little bit
about yourself.
Okay, you fans, my name is Michelle Dowry, I live in Cleveland, Ohio.
I work for the Obama campaign.
The campaign was over November 11th.
I went out and campaigned for Obama to get voters in to vote for Obama.
One thing I liked what I did, this was like my second year campaigning.
You know, he won this the second four years, the first four years I did it and it's the
second.
A lot of people didn't know about voting.
They thought if you had a warrant for your arrest, you couldn't vote.
I explained to them that had anything to do with it.
Some people wanted to vote, thought if they go get an ID that the police will get them,
no.
We had people that wasn't from this country, but they had foreign IDs, which they've been
here two, three years.
They need to go change it over and get a state ID to vote.
It was very nice, very interesting what I did.
When you talk about people, US citizens that have been out of the country?
We had people that was from overseas, a few of them that didn't even have Ohio state ID
and been here two, three years.
So I explained- Were they US citizens?
Yeah, they were not from Ohio.
But they were US citizens.
They were US citizens now, but they didn't even take the effort to get their state ID
yet.
So I opened some doors for a couple of them people too, because once I told them how you
had to have a state ID and a vote, they went and got a state ID and they voted.
Let me be honest with you.
The first thing that pops in some listeners minds and the first thing that pops in my
wife's mind was, the Obama phone lady, don't be mean to her.
Obviously, I'm not here to get you here to be mean to you.
In fact, contrary to that, I would like to try to see if I can communicate with you and
actually show you the fact that Obama is just as bad as the Republicans, probably even worse,
and that he does not have your best interest at heart and he's an incredible liar.
But again, that's my view.
Tell us why you like Obama.
I liked Obama.
I had seen him last year when and some things have went on by me being a minority and didn't
know no better.
I know he really didn't set the phones off.
Once I spoke on that on YouTube, they showed me that it was passed, but when Obama got
an election, it was Obama phones.
That's how-
Well, they radically increased the funding.
Right.
But he didn't put that bill out for us to get the Obama phone.
That was Clinton, right?
Yes.
Okay.
Did you know that my mother now calls her phone the Obama phone?
Well, everybody in Cleveland calls them Obama phones.
If you look on, and this is weird-
No, we just call cell phones Obama phones now, period.
Well, that's not-
It's like people don't call search engines search engines, they call them Googles.
Well, I never knew about it till I applied and I got one.
So they are called Obama's phone.
He got the name for them, but he didn't-
How many Obama phones do you have?
One.
But my sister has four or five of them, so that's what really pressed me to get them
because I work, my sister don't work.
She have no kids, she got four or five, she got three or four Obama phones and don't pay
a bill.
Here I am, I got Revo and I pay every month.
Now expanding on that, do you see the danger of people getting to where they're dependent
on the government?
Yes, I do, even myself, but I'm coming out of it.
Well, you've got a job.
Yes, I got a job, I started the day after Christmas, 26th of December.
My issue is obviously government at some levels needs to be there as a safety net, but government,
and I can actually after the show today show you some of their statements, about 100 years
ago said, we need to take control of society, we're going to do it by making people dependent.
And they didn't set up welfare and stuff to help people, they set it up to control people.
Right, right.
And that's true.
I've seen that with my own eyes in Cleveland, in Ohio.
They set it up to control you and have some where they can feed back and get you right
in.
I'm one of the ones, I got a child that I get child support for.
And by me getting the child support, here it is, the child is 10 years old, the dad
been working off and on, and we're not getting any money.
And I'm asking the child support people, what you mean?
Here he is working.
We need to send the channel news people in there because here he is working and he keeps
saying they're taking the money out, but we ain't getting none.
And we haven't got any, he's 10 years old.
So here I am right now, where's Obama now?
Like one thing, I'm glad he won the elections, but I want to see what he going to do.
You told me that last night, what do you expect Obama to do?
What could he do?
He could do a lot.
He's staying with the plan on the 25th of January, but is he going to do it?
And I know they keep saying it takes time, it takes time, it takes time.
Only thing I've seen he did, they passed the election and people calling Obama phones,
but for others in Ohio, I haven't seen him do too much.
He haven't even put up his office on Lee and Harvard, he's supposed to be rebuilding it
and everything.
You haven't did that yet.
Let me ask you a question.
Have you noticed prices have gone up on most products?
Hell yeah.
Oh yeah, prices, gas, cigarettes.
Do you know what the private fellow reserve is?
No, I don't.
Well, this country was taken over in 1913 by offshore European banks, and they've been
devaluing the dollar ever since, but most of the devaluations happened in the last 15
years or so.
And Obama has got the printing presses turned up on high, but all that's doing is devaluing
the dollar.
So the president really can't do anything for the people long term.
Anything he does do will end up being turned towards bad.
That's the problem with big government, that's why it doesn't work.
I heard that too.
Did you know that in communities, in the black community, that quote illegitimacy, that is
the parents getting divorced or the dad never being there, was less than 10% back in the
50s and now it's over 90%?
Yeah.
I mean, the state has taken over, but it's not just the black community, it's happening
everywhere now.
Right.
I mean, it's like a plague, wherever government takes over, so I mean, what will more government
money do?
Well, what I look at it is, well, what government money do is nothing, it's not doing anything.
Here I am as a living sacrifice and they haven't did anything to me, feed us and get bigger
and bigger with the food stamps, father's cash, they've been stopped the cash.
So he's not really doing anything right now.
But how do we go from being able to feed the whole world 50 years ago to where we can't
even produce our own food now?
See, globalism is poverty.
The policy is poverty, they want to make you poor so that they can control you.
Do you know how horses got domesticated?
Do you know how pigs got domesticated?
Do you know how cows got domesticated?
No, I don't.
Well, it's the same way we're becoming domesticated.
You simply set up an area and start putting food out for them, then they get used to eating
it, then you put a fence up around it but leave a gate open, then they start going in,
then you just go close the gate one day.
Then you make them come to you when they're starving to get the food.
And pretty soon you're on a spit being basically roasted.
That's being sent off to fight illegal wars.
Here's an example, to get welfare, in a lot of states they try to force you to take vaccines.
Do you know folks that are on welfare?
Yes.
Do they tell you that you've got to take vaccines?
No.
They don't?
Do you take vaccines?
No.
You don't?
Why?
Vaccines?
Yes.
Fascination shots?
Yeah.
Because I had all my shots.
What would you say if I told you that they put all sorts of deadly things in those shots?
Well, that's now.
I'm a little older, so I won't need no vaccination shots.
Well, they are starting to try to make adults take them.
Do you know about the Tuskegee experiments?
Where they put them in animals or something?
Hold on, I've got my phone going off here.
Got my Obama phone going off right here.
Anyways, now we're having a serious interview here all of a sudden.
You were pretty wound up last night, so was I.
I am still wound up.
Look, I've got so many questions here that I could ask.
I know we've got so many callers on so many fronts.
Let me just give you one example right here because I'm not here to beat you up because
you're an Obama supporter.
I mean, I get the argument of, well, the Republicans, they're torture, secret arrest, wars, lying,
corporate welfare, banker bailouts.
At least Obama says he wants to help me.
My issue is, did you hear how they paid $22 billion to ship General Motors Cadillac and
Volt plants to China?
Now, I mean, it's one thing if they left the country.
We paid to make them leave.
And there's hundreds of things like that.
Did you know Obama, Congress wouldn't pass a law that he's shutting down our coal power
plants and power prices are going up everywhere?
You know why that is?
No.
People, I don't know.
No, I don't.
My point is, Obama is a front man for some very dangerous criminal organizations.
Have you heard of the New World Order?
A little bit, I heard you talking.
Okay, these are people that want you dead.
Have you heard about the tens of thousands of experiments killing US troops, killing
foster children?
Yeah, I heard about it.
Yeah, I mean, they admit, they want you to know all day, we're the government, we kill
you.
Right.
Did you hear about the thousands of black people injected with syphilis?
Yeah.
That's Tuskegee.
Right.
And the reason I raised that, not cuz you're black, but because people have heard of that.
That was a 50 year program, okay, and nobody got in trouble for that.
Right.
Did you know the UN gave millions of kids in India vaccines last year and 60 plus thousand
of them got paralyzed?
I mean, those kids are never gonna run and play again, they're paralyzed, a lot of them
died.
Now, did you know they put that in the back of the paper like it was like they were talking
about the price of gasoline or something?
Now, why would the government put US troops in chambers and nerve gas them to death?
Guys hadn't done anything.
Right.
Black, white, kill you.
Mm-hm.
Why would we trust them?
In a way, I really don't.
As I'm a living sacrifice now here in America, and I did all this work for the help with
Obama.
You got paid a dollar sign nice and everything, but four years ago, he said what he was gonna
do and he still ain't dead, why is it taking so long?
He said the mothers that like me got kids, a 10 and a 15 year old, how should if I don't
have a job just getting food stamps, how could I live, how could I pay my rent?
You know, and these are people that press for you to win.
You know, and then I look at him like he'd be in a black president, at least he looked
out for the black minority who got you in this chair.
You know, cuz even with me doing what I did, you know, by being a lot of big shot white
guys around, they didn't really want to see me go from canvassing on the streets to an
office job.
Do you know right before it was over, they gave me that job in office maybe a week or
two at the last minute after I had already walked five or six miles?
Well, see, here's the thing, you're a really nice lady.
The way you described it to me, tell folks, I mean, tell us how they called you in after
the Obama phone video went viral.
I mean, describe that because you told me last night.
Okay, well, when I got the job that I was doing walking in the field service, they called
me in the office and they was like, do you know how you showed your ass?
You know how I really talked to the cameraman and I said what I said.
And I said, I said the first thing came to my heart.
And he was like, do you know that Obama didn't get the phone?
It don't matter.
You are walking around, even you, the job that I got, the phone you gave me say Obama.
So if this is all what we see and know, this is what people think of that.
And then you told me they put you in the office.
They gave me an office job.
So that you wouldn't be on the street.
That I wouldn't be on the street.
And then what did they tell you about that?
Well, when I got in the office job, they told me they didn't want me on the street because
I had so many voters for Obama.
You know, I was really going out there talking and knew because at the end of the day, turning
your paperwork, I got over 75 to 100 people.
But do you really believe you did such a good job, we pulled you off it?
Right.
But I don't believe that.
I believe they pulled me off because he was full of stuff too.
Well, but see, the difference is here with me, Michelle, is I'm talking to you straight.
Right.
See, I don't see you as a human resource to be used.
I see you as a real person who has incredible potential.
Right.
And I want you to know that I have Margaret Sanger and all the documents where they said
about 100 years ago, they said, we're going to go in and take over the black community.
We're going to hire their leaders and we're going to get abortion legalized so we can
kill these people.
The Democratic Party exists to put you six feet under.
The Republicans are a bunch of gangsters too, but the Democrats, a modern Democratic Party
is designed to kill black people.
We'll be right back.
Okay.
All right.
You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa, where a nicely furnished cabin
with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine and laundry service awaits.
After a good night's sleep, your adventure begins.
You're on a golden stag safari for big game.
But it's not Africa.
It's Argentina.
One-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo, huger, bighorn rams, wild boar, and the biggest
stag deer in South America, all gold medal quality, all the action you can handle.
Land rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages, hunting guides, ground
transportation included, and more, all more affordable than you can imagine.
The adventure of a lifetime starts at goldenstagsafaris.com.
The big game hunting ranch, goldenstagsafaris.com.
Balance, harmony, mental alertness, physical wellbeing.
If once you possess these qualities, but stress now weighs you down, you can get your mental
edge back in a holistic approach with Nutropic Mind Power from mindregard.com.
Not a drug.
Nutropic Mind Power is a lasting proven natural supplement with 12 powerful ingredients in
nutraceutical compounds and are non-GMO, plus it's gluten-free, wheat-free, and formulated
by Americans for Americans by an NSF certified laboratory.
Nutropic Mind Power is available at mindregard.com, spelled M-I-N-D-R-E-G-A-R-D.com, and comes
with a 100% money back guarantee.
Free your mind with Nutropic Mind Power cognitive supplement from mindregard.com.
Mind Regard, clearly see tomorrow and yesterday, today.
My name is Stephen Heuer.
After 22 years of nutritional counseling, I've observed that most brain malfunctions
have at their roots some form of toxicity and brain damage.
So whether it is poor memory, poor focus, lack of creative thinking, or more serious
matters like inability to focus, speak normally, or remember things, the emphasis to getting
one's brain working optimally needs to be on detoxification.
One World Way supports your body's number one means of detoxification, which is glutathione
production.
My name is Angie, and my son has suffered from borderline autism and constipation.
I got him on One World Way, and in two months, his constipation is gone.
He's become friendlier, he can carry on a normal conversation with me, and he has made
his first friend.
He's doing great, and he looks forward to taking One World Way every day.
You could offer him a present or a cake, and he would prefer the One World Way.
Go to OneWorldWay.com, that's OneWorldW-H-E-Y.com, or call 888-988-3325, that's 888-988-3325.
She was their old Obama phone lady self.
Michelle Dowry is here with us in the studio, a whole other hour coming up, and we will
also open the phones up as well.
But continuing here, I sent the guys over to McDonald's to get a Happy Meal, because,
and I don't do this to be condescending, I do this to get it all out in the open.
Wow, that's where I've never seen a Happy Meal where it's torn open.
My son must have been in this, seeing it's designed to get kids to go after it.
But it's the same thing with adults.
A free phone, it's like Indians selling Manhattan for a box full of glass beads that didn't
even cost half a pound, or British sterling.
It's selling your birthright for baubles.
The government shouldn't be the place we're getting phones from.
The government, guys, I don't think that door is completely shut.
Can we shut that door completely, thank you.
This is the type of issue that we're dealing with here.
And it is an artificial system.
Not only is this meant to lure kids in, bunch of GMO crud with Monsanto on the board of
this organization.
And it's a Happy Meal, but really what it is, is a spider's web.
So here's my issue, that's the same thing with the Obama phone, it's like a Happy Meal.
In fact, you've got the Obama phone right there, don't you?
Yes, sir.
It's like Excalibur, hold it up for the camera, people can see that.
There it is, ladies and gentlemen.
And again, just to be clear about this, the Republicans out there, half of them work for
defense contractors, they're getting government money too.
I'm not here judging you because you want an Obama phone.
What about all the corporate welfare?
What about the trillions in banker bailouts?
Did you know for every dollar that went to banker bailouts, they had like $1 in welfare?
Again, if we are gonna have a socialist system, the people are sure selling out cheap.
Why didn't you like Romney?
Romney was gonna take the food stamps.
He was gonna take the stamps, he was gonna make us work for the food stamps.
What else he said he was gonna do?
He was gonna cut our hours back.
In Ohio, they got the cameras, he was up on the camera with the speeding and Romney was
really on it.
I mean, Obama is continuing and expanding NSA spying.
Obama has signed a law where they can secretly disappear American citizens and even kill
us called the NDAA.
He's got drone attacks going on all over the world.
Again, I'm not saying Romney's good either.
My point is they're all really bad and Obama isn't your friend.
What do you think of Obama continuing torture?
What do I think he's continuing to torture?
Is that what you said?
Yes, I mean, are you aware of his foreign policy?
A little bit.
My point is that, I mean, do you think torture is okay?
No.
What about drone attacks?
Where they're just bombing.
And by the way, the countries where they're bombing, it's illegal.
There's no declaration of war.
They're just flying around killing wherever they want.
Do you think Obama really cried on TV for the dead kids at Sandy Hook?
No.
Do you think it was fake?
A little bit, I mean, he got to play his part.
He's the president.
I mean, if he goes out and cry to every little situation, hell, he wouldn't have no tears
left.
He got to play his part too.
The whole world is a stage, each of his players upon it?
No.
I'm not going to agree on that one.
But you're saying, here's the deal, I don't play my part.
I mean, if I cry, I really am crying.
My point is they'll kill hundreds of innocent people at a wedding to get one bad guy they
claim.
And Obama doesn't cry for all those little kids.
Have you seen the video of little kids in Libya and Syria with their lower jaws blown
off and stuff, screaming for mommy?
Right.
Why is Obama crying for them?
Well, he probably felt sad and moved on.
But I think he could have did more.
Well, he is doing more.
He's bombing more countries.
You are listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from cold.
Go plastic.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with SuperNatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
SuperNatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as stress, strep, pneumonia, coals, flus and
other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
Visit supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCM radio network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
I thought it would be fun to get the Obama phone lady in studio.
No one knew who she was, there was that one video, then she disappeared off the radar
screen.
Well, she's now down here with us in Austin, Texas.
We had a great time last night.
I don't want to say you're nervous, but you're real serious now.
During the breaks, you've been having a little bit more fun.
I want to go to some phone calls.
I want to go to a bunch of Twitter questions, a big stack of them that have also come in
here.
And I've got a bunch of other points I want to go over with you here today.
But you were talking about the hope that Obama will do things that will make your life, other
people's lives, better.
There's certainly nothing wrong with wanting a better life.
What do you think Obama can do?
He can do anything he want to do.
He's the president.
It might take a little time, but he can do anything.
The president, he wanted to build me a house from the ground, he could do that.
He's the president.
But he would have to take it from somebody else to do it.
Right?
That's like anybody else.
And then he would have to choose who got to build it, and of course, that'll be his friends.
But that's okay, he's the president, he got that pool to do whatever he can do to go that
Obama file.
Go ahead and take it.
All right there, hello?
I'm on the air, I can't talk to you guys.
My minutes are up my Obama phone.
Continue, so but don't you get that kings and presidents and others would say just do
it before, and it's called tyranny.
I mean, there's got to be rules that the president just can't do whatever he wants.
That's true.
He's the president, can't do everything he wants to do, but you know.
Did you see all the people?
Well, we'll talk about it later.
Let's take some phone calls right now.
Ryan in Texas, you were on the phone with the real live Obama phone lady, go ahead.
I was wanting to really know what deep down made you support Obama.
Deep down, why does she support Obama?
Yes, like the core reason why that makes her support Obama.
I mean, is it reflected, Glory?
Is it that you feel like you're part of something?
No, I didn't feel like I was part of anything.
I had a job to do.
Now I got a job, I'm making a little money, and when I did the campaign for Obama, I made
the big money.
But as I was out there campaigning to get voters to vote for Obama, one thing I pressed
was what kind of phone you got?
And it was like Obama phone, how you get it?
They didn't know like I didn't know.
So that was wrong led me to get them out there for the vote.
But if you really look at it, if you got a quarter, you ain't saying where the quarter
come from, it's just a quarter.
Just like the phones, they were free.
No, I understand, it's Pavlovian, I mean, the government is giving you something, therefore
it must be good.
But take your job you've got now, did you know the payroll taxes just went way up?
The amount of money they're taking out of your check?
Remember Obama said he wouldn't raise your taxes.
No, I didn't, I haven't got a check yet.
Well listen, we're gonna have to try to work this out cuz I'd like you to do some auxiliary
reporting for us.
But I first have to get you to the point where you understand, I mean, everybody's heard
about government doing medical experiments on people.
Caller, did you have anything else you wanted to add?
Yeah, I was also wanting to know her views on the gun control bill they're trying to
pass.
I'm gonna ask her that when we come back from break because that's a big one and I wanna
I want everybody to be able to respond to that.
When we come back from break, we'll get into the gun situation, I asked her about that
last night.
And we'll get to some of these Twitter questions as well.
Thank you for the call, Ryan.
We're gonna go to Jerry and others also on the other side of this quick break and she's
with us.
Michelle Dowry is in studio with us and she is the Obama phone lady.
And if you wanna see the quintessential Obama voter, I think she represents it.
She's a nice lady and I understand that this country's in a depression.
When you get to a point where the government is there providing for you, you start having
allegiance for it.
So pretty soon the government takes from one group, gives to another, they've got them
in a subsistence level, there's no real economy left.
Everybody's on the government plantation and game over, the globalists win.
We'll come right back with the one, the only, the Obama phone lady is very, very somber
in here.
And we've got a lot of video of her behind the scenes.
She's a crackerjack.
Sick of the globalist, eugenicist, control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing
as you get sick and die?
Start purifying your water with ProPure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none
is ProPure and it's available discounted at infowars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified.
Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%, easy to set up and use, doesn't
require electricity, purify water from lakes, streams, ponds, and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
ProPure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on ProPure, but if you add the promo code
WATER at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal-Bend
Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action.
Tyranny is here.
The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality.
It really says that the state is God.
The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most oppressive police states
on earth.
This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being
expanded nationwide.
This documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all
powerful shadow state.
Police state four chronicles the sickening depth to which our republic has fallen.
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship, body scammers, sound cannons,
citizen spies, stage terror and cameras on every street corner.
It's only the beginning of the new world order's hellish plan.
The police state isn't coming.
It's here.
Secure your copy today at infowars.com or see it online in the highest quality at prisonplanet.tv.
Crashing through the lies and disinformation.
That's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network.
Yes, everybody in Cleveland, low minority got Obama phoned, keep Obama in president,
you know?
He gave us a phone.
He gave you a phone.
He's going to do more.
How did he give you a phone?
You sign up and you're on full stamps, you're on social security, you got low income, you
got disability.
Okay, what's wrong with Romney again?
Let's talk about it.
Okay, we're here with the real live Obama phone lady and now her name is revealed.
She's that mystery person.
I'm like, I want that lady on.
What's her name?
Let's find her and our listeners found her.
Now she's since been called by The View.
She's reportedly going to go on that soon and a bunch of other stations, but she's here
first with us and she's a little subdued today.
I think we had a few too many beers last night, I'm joking.
I'm joking.
We didn't know actually we did.
Anyways, but she's going to be on the nightly news with us tonight as well.
And I want to go back to your calls.
I want to go over a whole bunch of issues.
I want to take your Twitter questions here today.
But you heard the last caller, but we were going to break.
Where do you stand on the right to keep and bear arms?
You're not on a Perry Mason up on the courtroom.
We just want to know where you come from.
Where do you stand on the Second Amendment?
Where do you stand on the right to own guns?
I'm against that.
There you go.
So you want the government to have guns, but not the people?
No guns at all.
Have faith in God.
Well, God has faith in those that have faith in themselves.
See, I mean- I'm not into the guns, you know, and to me it's a lot of nonsense with that.
I'm not into guns with the government having them.
No.
I mean, the government has bought 1.6 billion bullets, armored vehicles, helicopters, SWAT
teams.
A SWAT team busted in and shot an innocent guy 16 times.
And they said it was justified because he was reaching to turn the light on.
And they lied and said he had four guns, which he didn't.
Even though they got caught lying, because it's about officer safety.
So I got an idea.
How about everyone on Earth but police commits suicide?
Six billion, 300 million people commit suicide, but the 15 million police are so worldwide
for their safety.
Because if they say, if they think it's their safety, they kill you?
How about everyone on Earth commits suicide so they're safe?
That's what the New World Order wants.
They want to have world government to set up a medical tyranny to force cancer virus
injections into us via vaccines, and GMO they force fetus.
And these globalists think we're so dumb, Michelle, they've written books how they're
doing it to us.
Do you know about, I mean, you know about Tuskegee?
Why do you trust a government that you know nerve gas for our own troops, that you know?
Did you hear about in New York City, how they were giving little kids, mainly black kids?
Cuz the government loves black kids so much, wants to give you free stuff.
No, they're not your friends.
I'm trying to really reach out to you here, and I understand they've shut the economy
down.
I understand things are desperate, I get all that.
I understand that.
And what I'm saying is, the New York Daily News six years ago reported they were testing
pesticides on little kids till they killed them.
Now, see, I happen to care about those kids no matter what color they are.
They happen to be mainly black, because for some reason in the liberal intelligentsia
it's okay.
But some of the CPS workers blew the whistle and said, you know, these kids are dying.
Is this okay?
Should we be killing them?
Cuz we're the government.
I mean, is it okay for the government to chain little black kids down and feed pesticides
to them?
Bug poison.
Now, I mean, I can show you all these articles.
Now, does that sound like a nice group of people there?
No.
Okay, you told me, you and Harvey told me why you want the guns taken last night, and
I understand it.
Why don't you repeat what you said?
Well, I don't want the guns for the president to get them.
The people out here, you could buy guns on the street, you could buy them from police
officers.
Yeah, I know, that's where you got to get drugs and everything, the police, yeah.
Right, right, right.
And just by me being on your talk show and thinking about it, them are the biggest cruel
people there is, you know?
Just by you saying about the guns, the president got all these guns and protected, but what
about the people that help you protect us?
Well, I mean, here's the deal.
I've talked to people at MTV, multiple people, who said in the mid 90s, they said, we're
gonna promote this gangster rap to take over the culture.
That's a time bomb, and the rappers are killing each other.
They'll have $50 million in the bank, but to be a man, they'll shoot somebody.
I get, cuz that's what Harvey, your husband, was saying, he goes, look, I've had nephews
killed.
I get that that's terrible and horrible.
And there's a lot of rappers like KRS1, who's one of my listeners, and others, and Professor
Griff, who are saying that's wrong.
And you know what, it is a program for blacks to kill each other.
So I'm against that inner city violence, believe me, but that isn't a reason for everybody
else to lose their guns.
Take Chicago, you know they have the highest crime rate in the world?
We're on the radio in Chicago.
That's not for them, you're right.
But they've taken the guns there.
Only law abiding citizens then gave their guns up.
So see, if I could walk through with Obama supporters, and it doesn't mean you go vote
for Romney.
They all were in so much trouble.
Did you know the very same interest fund, both men?
Yeah, I knew that.
But then Obama, he is charming, he's like, hey, I'm gonna take care of you.
You know what I'm gonna, did you see in the first campaign people going, thank you, Mr.
President.
I'm gonna get a free house.
I'm gonna get a free car.
Right.
And those people did not get free houses and free cars.
He didn't do nothing for Lee and Harvard.
He promised them people he was gonna get a big office if he win this time.
You heard him on the news say how he come back to Cleveland and Detroit and get us low
black minorities to vote.
But look how we living, Lee and Harvard and Cleveland, Ohio still where his office at
is still the same.
Well, I mean, and again, Obama said, I will not sign the NDAA, don't worry about beating
it.
Because there was opposition, it was gonna get beaten, but he said, but I'm gonna veto
So people said, well, just let it pass.
Right.
Then he signed it.
So he went against our word and signed it anyway.
But the point is, it turned out he wrote it.
Right.
I mean, this guy makes, it's devilish lying.
Okay, and Romney's a devilish liar too.
The point is, is that it's how far gone we are, Michelle, is why things are getting worse
and worse.
Let me play you a clip here.
This is Obama saying your payroll tax, nothing's going up.
But you know, more than 14 taxes are going up.
And there's a 3.8% tax on investments.
There's another tax on payroll.
There's taxes across the board that have gone up on almost every American, every American
that works.
77% of Americans got a tax increase, you can just type that into a search engine.
Now when you get your next paycheck, I guess when you get back, I want you to notice in
there all the little things that are taken out, okay?
Now are you rich?
Heck no.
Did you know that Kennedy cut taxes by 50%?
Do you know what happened a year later?
Gave it back?
Tax receipts doubled.
Did you know the government knows if they cut taxes, there's a boom and that more money
comes in?
Michelle, why would they want to raise taxes?
Why would they want to chain kids down and dump pesticide down their throat?
See, did you see that news article about the top BBC presenter being a Satanist with kids?
Why would he want to do that to little kids?
He's a Satanist, that's why.
And see, the devil comes as an angel of light.
It's true, that's in the Bible.
And will speak scripture, okay?
This government is the most evil government the world's ever seen.
Our government funded Hitler and then destroyed him.
Our government created Lenin and Stalin.
Did you know that's declassified?
Do you know our government put Mao Tse Tung in?
Declassified.
Mao Tse Tung conservatively killed 66 million people.
The Chinese government says 80 plus million.
Do you know how many people that is?
A sports stadium is 100,000.
That's almost, moreover, 140, you got.
Yeah, 100,000 people.
How many sports stadiums is 80 million people?
Two, three.
Starved to death, lined up and shot.
Do you know our government shipped in shiploads of bullets so he could just mow them down?
It's not our government.
They're called eugenicists, eugenicists, they're scientific dictators.
Obama is reading off a teleprompter.
And we've got to realize that the entire system is evil.
And I don't wanna sit here and preach at you.
Let's play this first clip.
This is Obama four years ago saying, I will never raise your taxes, not $1, here it is.
And I can make a firm pledge under my plan, no family making less than $250,000 a year
will see any form of tax increase, not your income tax, not your payroll tax, not your
capital gains taxes, not any of your taxes.
That's a firm pledge.
Now, guys, just cuz he's here, I know I've only got two guys who are in the job, eight
people.
Five pins, 77% of Americans got payroll tax increase.
People making $30,000 or up, now is 30,000, 250,000?
Is that a lie right there?
That's a lie.
George Herbert Walker Bush got thrown out of office for reading my lips, no new taxes.
People tell me now, well, they just lie, it's what they do.
Well, I know they're liars, so I'm not gonna turn my guns in.
Let's go to the next clip here for you.
Let's play this clip.
This is him four years ago saying, I'm not coming after your handgun or your rifle or
your shotgun.
Here's that clip.
When y'all go home and you're talking to your buddies and they say, he wants to take my
gun away.
You've heard it here, I'm on television, so everybody knows it.
I believe in the Second Amendment.
I believe in people's lawful right to bear arms.
I will not take your shotgun away.
I will not take your rifle away.
I won't take your handgun away.
Now, what does the devil do?
What does the devil do?
The devil lies.
Lies, cheats.
What's the devil's number one name in the Bible?
The deceiver.
The enemy.
I know a deceiver and an enemy when I see one.
Now, if he just pledged to me, he wouldn't come after my guns.
Now they got bills he supports that will make me hand in all my semi-autos, my handguns.
Yep, he lied.
And here's what's even worse, Michelle.
They've all written papers in our public saying they want all our guns taken.
And then Piers Morgan sits there and says, nobody wants your guns.
That makes me mad.
He's lying to my face.
Right.
Okay.
Michelle, I'm going to give you some films covering eugenics and what they're really
doing, and then we're going to have you back on.
But when we come back, we're going to take more calls, get to more questions and more
lies.
For the Obama Phone Lady, I'm Alex Jones.
All right.
Hello, I'm Alex Jones.
Myself, my family, the Infowars.com team want to relay to you and your families that we
are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front.
Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats.
But we can't do that without your help.
By getting the films, bumper stickers and T-shirts at Infowars.com, you will wake up
people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before.
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here.
It's an info war.
The spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
Don't throw away leftovers.
Instead, throw all your leftovers, vegetable peels, eggshells, coffee grounds, pizza crusts
and more into the Bokashi.
If you love to garden and compost but don't like the hassle of turning a compost bin or
the smell, then check out the E.M.
Bokashi Food Waste Recycling System from Tereganics.
Finally, a way to recycle all your food and plant waste safely and effectively and stop
using fertilizers.
The E.M. Bokashi Food Waste Recycling System.
Rather than decomposition, the Bokashi system uses fermentation to break down waste so it
takes less time to create nutrient-dense humus for crops or gardens with no turning and no
obnoxious odors.
To learn more and order your Bokashi online, visit tereganics.com and click on the orange
button.
That's tereganics.com, spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X dot com or call 866-369-3678.
That's 866-369-3678.
Recycle all your food waste in about six weeks with the Bokashi Food Waste Recycling System
from tereganics.com.
Tereganics.
Life's getting better.
On the average, Americans work between 45 to 50 years hoping to build up enough wealth
to retire and live out their golden years.
Unfortunately, with taxation, the rising cost of food, energy, housing and medical, many
retirees are forced to live below the poverty line.
Is this a flaw of free enterprise or is our monetary unit we call the Federal Reserve
Note forcing us into perpetual debt, ensuring inflation and higher taxes?
These questions and more can be answered by reading G. Edward Griffin's book, The Creature
from Jekyll Island.
Congressman Ron Paul states it's what every American needs to know about central bank
power, a gripping adventure into the secret world of international banking cartel.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson.
I will give a silver dollar from the early 1900s to anyone who purchases this book.
Call 1-800-686-2237 and order a copy today.
It's critical that the public be made aware of the system.
Call and order your copy today at 1-800-686-2237.
That's 1-800-686-2237.
Hi there.
My name is Frank Bates.
What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble.
I just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are, incompetent, lying crooks
that are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high.
Some have called this a conspiracy, others have called it a coverup and you will be shocked
to find out how deep the conspiracy goes.
My video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them
and how you can beat them too.
Watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patriots have already seen
in the last three months.
Go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect
your home.
Go watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down.
But again, that's 123coverup.com.
She's here.
She's the Obama lady.
I promise we're going to your calls here in just a moment and a bunch of your tweet questions.
But look, we're getting right down to the bottom of it here.
You know the government's corrupt and bad, and so you're like, there's all this emotion
about the poor kids.
Yeah, let's turn our guns in, but you start thinking about, hey, who's really running
things?
Is it good to have only the government with guns?
And then it sounds like you're starting to agree with me.
Well, then I learned and found out and you showed me in paperwork and on TV what he said.
You know, I don't put nothing past anybody.
I've been a mother of five kids, single mother, and they told me if I sign my name, they're
going to give me so much of food stamps, so much of cash.
But then they put me on a budget and say, this is it.
If the rent's 600, then you're only giving me 300, how am I going to make it with five
kids?
But see, that's the end of humanity where they break up our families and the state pays
for things and they control everything.
Well, you got a point there because I'm a living example right now.
When I lost that job-
You're a peace fellow, that's okay.
Hey, guys, come help her, please, cuz if she had it off, then I put it back in and I don't
really know how to do it.
Okay, well, here I go, that's- He's going to help you, go ahead.
It's good radio.
By the way, you're wound up during the breaks, just be yourself, go ahead.
I'm not telling you to be wound up, but you're wound up normally.
It's not like you're in a courtroom or something, go ahead.
Well, see, like I was saying, I don't hear anything.
That's cuz we're not taking calls right now, go ahead.
Well, see, like I was saying, listening to Alex Jones and he's telling me and I've seen
it on the news, that's true.
Because those people wired me up to work for $11 an hour and for a couple months, and then
they threw me out the door.
They got what they wanted from me and you're off.
And that's true because even when I got a paycheck, I went to the boss and I said, you
mean I worked and you didn't take out any taxes?
Now, how could you do that?
Cuz I'm working for Obama, he should get the same privileges I'm working for.
Well, you're a contractor is why it happened.
But I've noticed with the Obama folks, they won't even give people the tax forms cuz they're
above the law.
Well, we didn't get a tax form, they didn't take out any taxes, it didn't go, now I got
a job that hit right to the government with the welfare.
My stamps got cut, everything.
When I was working for Obama, I got everything off the trip.
That right there tell you that it's not right.
Well, look, all I can say is they're doing everything they can to make it not pay to
actually work.
Or if you do work, you can't live on it.
I can't, and that's true, sir.
I just got a job and I'm glad I met you, Alex Jones, I just got a job.
And I'm making a little bit, but it's not what I was making with Obama.
When I was with Obama, I was making a nice dollar to pay my rent here after November
was over, I'm out of a job.
I couldn't even apply for unemployment or any of that.
So like he was saying, like you say, Alex Jones, I believe that.
Because when I got out of work-
We'll fix your piece after the break, I'm sorry.
I'll get it plugged in properly and get you audio stuff, okay?
Keep talking?
No, it's okay, just don't worry about it, okay?
You just got up, got unplugged, never got plugged back in, right?
We're gonna get you audio during the next thing, or we can just do this whole segment
on it right now.
Again, this is a program of domination, a program of total control.
This is a program of domestication.
That's what's happening.
Let's jam a phone call in here.
Jerry in Connecticut, you're on the air, go ahead.
Hi there, Michelle.
You should check out Dick Gregory's interview with Alex Jones.
It'll clue you in a lot to what's really going on in the world and give you a better perspective.
Because you know Dick Gregory, he's been around for the civil rights movement, he's been part
of everything, he's seen everything, he's a man who knows the real world.
He knows 9-11 is an inside job.
He knows they killed JFK, RFK, and Martin Luther King.
And they're the people who want all the guns because they want to put us in the damn camps.
And that's the end of the story.
They want to make us dependent so we can't live on our own, we can't make our own money
and stuff like that.
And you got to realize, this is a sucker game.
And I'll give you one good example.
Guys who basically funded Romney and also funded Obama, Goldman Sachs, they played derivatives
on foods around the world.
And everybody's been screaming, every civil rights group, because they've been killing
millions of kids.
Because every time they push the prices of food up through their manipulation of the
food prices, they're killing millions of kids in Africa, in Asia, and Obama says nothing.
Yeah, exactly.
When food goes up like, this is a great call, I'm going to hold you over, sir.
Stay right there, I'm going to come back to you, Jerry.
He's exactly right.
The increased food price is 30, 40% here, people just might not get as much food.
Most people are living in a subsistence survival level, they starve to death.
And then the answer is, oh well, there's too many people who let them die anyways.
Okay, let's just say that's true, I don't agree with it.
The globalists see us exactly the same as well, they want us dead.
Stay there.
We're on the march.
The empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver-based products.
Our most popular silver-based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two
ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well as our all-natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and
leave the silver at the surface, but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the
natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the
skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver-based products
are best for you.
That's www.silverlungs.com.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to www.supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting
chance.
That's www.supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Alex Jones here with a very important announcement for Truth Seekers.
We've carried a lot of amazing films and books over the years on the online video bookstore
at infowars.com and out of all the titles we've carried, one stands out because it is
just so chillingly convincing and that's Dreams from My Real Father by Joel Gilbert, available
at infowars.com.
This film exposes the fraud that Obama is like nothing I've seen.
If you want to know who Obama's real daddy is, this is the film for you.
Don't forget your purchase supports our broadcast and our growing media network.
You'll also find at infowarshop.com None Dare Call a Conspiracy by Gary Allen, the book
that woke me up.
We're also carrying Behind the Green Mask, UN Agenda 21 by Rosa Corey.
This book is coffin nails to the globalist takeover.
The Greater Good, the most professional and up-to-date film I've ever seen exposing the
scourge that is vaccines.
These titles and a lot more are all available at infowarshop.com.
Go up to infowars.com, you can see some of the great Photoshop artwork by the Info Wars
graphics team.
It's Piers Morgan machine gunning the Bill of Rights and Constitution with an AR-15.
Rahm Emanuel, take American people out of Second Amendment debate.
And he is now announcing that they want to use executive orders.
Again, they're expanding that.
Chicago mayor limit access to guns, Chicago mayor and former Obama Chief of Staff Rahm
Emanuel has proposed restricting the discussion over firearms ownership in America to law
enforcement.
I mean, what a dictator.
Guys, will you get that audio for me?
It's just unbelievable.
It's up at infowars.com.
This is just off the chart.
And again, I covered this at the start of the show.
Ladies and gentlemen, they are saying they're gonna use executive orders, rule making.
But Schumer came out and said, we'll just order gun shops, do what we want.
And by the way, you're like, well, they can't do that outside law.
The ATF's already been doing that.
So Michelle, Obama phone lady, we're gonna go back to the caller, Jerry, and then hurry
through some others and get to some Twitter questions.
They're gonna be on the news with us tonight for a more lively discussion.
I know we're just a little more calm here except during the breaks.
Why are you so restrained right now?
Which is fine.
I mean, I guess we're having a serious discussion.
Well, I'm phenomenal about what's going on and I thank God that I came here because I
seen it with my own eyes.
I guess, I mean, you were saying you've never seen the footage of yourself except on smartphones.
You have a computer at home?
No.
So all you've got mainstream television.
Mainstream television and my Obama phone.
Which isn't a smartphone, right?
It's just a regular phone.
Regular phone.
So yeah, cuz we couldn't send you text messages.
So literally, what's the number?
I saw a number like 65 million Americans only have access to a television.
Oh, it's a lot of them.
How many people in your community did just only have a television?
A lot, a lot of people because- And so you didn't know he told all those lies?
No.
I've got a bunch of others.
But I knew that he lied because about four years ago when I worked for the Obama campaign,
he said he was gonna re-renovate Harvard and the Lee area.
And that's where he started when I started campaigning for him.
Here it is four years went on and now I'm at another four years.
And that place still looks the same.
Now they've only put a few hundred billion into infrastructure, which is if you are gonna
have government funding, that actually gets the economy going and gives people real people
jobs.
Right.
If it's not given to your select buddies only.
But they've spent, last time I saw something like 47 trillion has been, 47 trillion, you
have to understand the whole country's GDP is like 15, excuse me, 47 trillion.
I think I said billion, those numbers are so big.
He only spent a few hundred billion on infrastructure total in the last four years.
And then 47 trillion to offshore mega banks, you're like, well, where'd that money go?
Right.
It went into derivatives.
So it didn't even really go anywhere, it was propping up garbage.
And then you're like, well, okay, well, then why are they doing it?
Just suck real money out of the economy and get us into debt.
See, we've been signed on, it'd be like if I put a chain on your leg, okay, that was
impossible to get off, tied to, let's say a bowling ball that weighed 500 tons.
Are you gonna ever be able to pull out of that?
No.
Okay, what if I threw you over the edge of a dock with that on your leg?
So now you're gonna be on the bottom of the lake.
Right, right.
It's impossible and it's not our debt.
So what I'm saying is, Michelle, they're predators, they're bad, they do everything they can to
bankrupt you so that you've got to go to them because they want control.
And that's true because, so for instance, how you say of control, I had a friend that
was a school teacher and when she lost her job, she went to apply for unemployment, they
turned her down.
When she went to the welfare, they gave her the money.
But by her not being, have you worked as a school teacher, now you're not working and
you're on government assistance, do you know how low that is?
So she dropped down that low, she started drinking beer.
They sell beer in the store, but she would get so drinking, I guess her mind went crazy,
but she would drink so much beer, then it got into what the system got in her life.
And I was like, well, how could they take that quick?
And just by her applying, losing her job, applying for the government, they contacted
her, took her kids, put them in foster care and all that.
And I'm like, here it is, a working woman, been a teacher for all these years, and it
wasn't enough money after she lost the job or laid off her-
And they took her kids.
And they took her kids, but if you go down the lane of how she got corrupted like that,
when she got corrupted, she started drinking.
When she got drinking, I'm like, it gotta be helped, let's see about putting her in
a place.
When we tried to put her in one of those detox place, by her being on welfare, she couldn't
get in.
Here it is, a woman need help just cuz of her welfare, she can't get in, but it really
hindered a friend of mine.
And I couldn't feel that she works 12, 13 years as a school teacher.
She bought the Samoogas house for these seven kids.
And today, right now, all seven of her kids, they went through that stage with that, but
they're doctors, social workers.
They really-
So the average foster child is on seven psychotropic drugs, about 67, 68%.
And those drugs are designed to fry their brains.
Right.
Did they put the kids on drugs?
They tried to get me.
I got a son that was tested of HHD.
Totally made up.
Totally, I got a doctor.
The gas get cut off by me, my family, and everybody going to Aknotaway, and I'm putting
her on there.
Aknotaway is a good doctor in Ohio.
She knew me, my parents, my parents' parents, it's like a generation went down.
And-
See, that's family.
Family is power.
Right.
The system wants to get rid of that.
And they want federalized healthcare so that doctor can't do what they want, the state
wants to be the doctor.
See, they're gonna take-
I believe that because the day right now, my doctor is getting old.
Her and her husband used to take care of me, now my kids go to her.
The husband has got a lot of arthritis going on.
He ain't in there no more, it's just her.
But people are smart, they're from China.
You know what they're doing?
They're sending a whole family to take up for what she's doing.
The mother, first it was the husband and wife, Aknotaway.
Now it's the kids, the husband and the wife being doctors.
Like I told you about Alex Jones show, that little kid of yours, he's gonna be the next
Alex Jones.
Believe that.
We get old, we can't keep going on and on.
That's the plan.
That's the plan, but I'm quite sure something happened to you.
This little kid gonna be here if this what he like doing.
That's all, you can't drag him away from it.
No.
He's a lot smarter than I am.
And just like they say is what we teach them.
I have kids now and they told me, you can't send that son.
I got a son that I grew up on welfare and a low black minority, single parent with five
kids.
That's, Satan the devil is a liar.
My son is Tyrone Mixon, he graduated from Hiram College.
He's a social worker, a VA social worker.
But-
But see how he survived the system, but now he works for the system.
Right, but only way that he got through was that for me being a low black minority with
my low income, cuz we couldn't use the dad income cuz he worked at Chevy Boulevard.
We had to use my income with my five kids.
I couldn't understand that, but as we kept going and he went to Hiram for four years,
we were eligible.
All right, let's go back to the calls.
This is amazing.
You're getting wound up now.
And we got a lot of great footage too, you're awesome.
Let's go ahead and again, Obama phone lady is here.
And some people online thought I was gonna get her here just to be mean to her.
Ladies and gentlemen, I don't need to be mean to people to feel powerful about myself.
It is upsetting.
You're saying I vote for Obama, I'm gonna get a free phone, he's gonna do more.
But there was that humanity and you knew it was funny when you were saying it.
And so yes, we're laughing, but we're not really laughing at you, we're laughing with
you.
What did you think I was gonna do when you got down here?
Well, one thing about it and two for show, can't nobody make you look funny if you don't
allow them to make you look funny?
I knew whatever thing I did on YouTube with Obama, the people were not happy.
And I don't know why, but I was happy.
Because I was out there campaigning and when it came time for that cameraman to run up
on me, I said, if he run up on me again, I'm talking.
And our bosses had already told us.
Hey, your bosses have told you?
Sorry.
Yeah, already told us, them cameraman's run up on you, you leave them alone.
I said, not me, walk two miles and the man keep brushing me with a camera, he pushed
me.
And the next time he pushed me, I got to talking, it was more than just me talking.
Wait a minute, that guy pushed you to get you mad.
He pushed me, and when he pushed me, he started talking, what are you going to do?
And Aranymi was just getting out of the truck.
Now you call him Aranymi.
Aranymi, Aranymo, Aranymi fool.
Tell us about, you saw him at Aranymi, tell the story.
Well, while I was campaigning, as you've seen on YouTube, we were walking in the circles.
But Aranymi was standing there and just got out of a truck entering the building.
And they told us to holler and hold our signs up and say more and more to him.
And if I can holler at Aranymi, what about this little man with this camera behind me?
So they kept on saying, don't talk, don't talk, keep it moving, keep it moving.
It's raining, we're walking, I done walked about two miles, and then he pushed up on
me again, and that's when I got to talking.
But when I got to the office, the next day, they was like, we need you in the office.
So I knew I had did something.
That's why they called me the Obama phone lady.
Uh-oh, now you're starting to wake up.
Look out.
What would you say to that camera guy if you could see him again?
Man, where the heck you at, and why you do me like that?
Cuz he ran off.
Now, that cameraman who got me on YouTube, he got whatever he got, he didn't give me
a name, number, card, anything.
But I thank you for getting me where you got me today.
In fact, when you got off the plane, you were thanking Obama.
I mean, I guess Obama is our great provider.
I don't know about all that right now.
Tell me about Obama.
You like him, don't you?
Well, I like Obama.
You think he's pretty handsome, don't you?
No, I think Harvey's handsome.
I wish Harvey, Harvey is pretty slick, actually.
I like him.
I love Harvey.
He looks like he could be in movies.
Okay.
Kind of a cool cat.
He is a cool cat.
I love Harvey.
But anyway, Obama, what I liked about Obama, and it's just for me.
When I campaigned this year, I was out in canvassing in the world of Cleveland, and
a lot of people didn't know a lot.
And one thing about it, I would be like, can I take your number?
And they'd be like, you can call me, but I can't talk back.
I'll call you at another phone.
I'm like, what?
This Obama phone.
And I was like, well, if a man gave you Obama phone, is you gonna vote for him?
Heck yeah.
I was like, plenty of people telling me, yeah, I'm gonna vote for Obama, but I don't even
got a state ID.
I had to show people how in Cleveland, you can get your birth certificate and stuff free
to get a state ID so you can vote for Obama.
Did you see any illegals vote?
Illegal?
People that aren't citizens.
Yeah, I even got them to vote.
No, hold on.
Seriously, I was just joking.
I did.
People that wasn't in our country.
No, no.
I had some people, foreign people, that had a paper stating that they were here.
They turned over from, they call them Arabs, Arabs.
In Cleveland, we call them Arabs.
And the Arabs on the store, they've been here two years or whatever, but they don't have
a state driver's license or a state ID.
You're saying in Ohio, they let people vote from other countries.
No, they had to get a state ID.
No, I understand, but getting the ID allowed them to vote.
Right.
Cuz they've been here.
And that dude told me he'd been here three, four years and he never voted cuz he foreign
or not from here.
And I said, how long you been here?
And he said two years.
And I said- And you're sure they weren't citizens?
No, they weren't citizens.
Not if you ain't from America.
They had IDs from Wyoming, W-Y-O-M-I-N-G, Wyoming or-
Yemen?
Something like that.
I knew they weren't cuz they talk like we talk, but they're not from here.
All right, Michelle, I just wanna be clear.
I like you.
I think you're a good person.
And I wanted to make sure earlier, just to be clear, you didn't know that people that
are foreigners aren't allowed to vote, right?
You didn't know that.
No.
But when they've been here in America so long, they could go get a state ID and vote.
I know, so they told you that was okay at the Democratic Party.
Yeah.
They said, go get them a driver's license.
They've been here for so amount of ups town cuz I had to check back with the office and
see how they can vote.
They're illegal American now, they've been here so long.
So they were citizens.
They were citizen, but they didn't know that they were citizen.
Well, I guess they did know because they still have foreign identification, but they've been
here a long time.
And then you would help them go get a driver's license that allowed them to vote.
Right.
State ID.
And they were able to vote.
They've been here for up some years.
He said he owned a store like four years, he never voted.
And I said, well, why?
He said he never even applied for a state ID.
Have you heard about the problem of illegal aliens voting?
No.
All right, well, let's just be clear.
You're not sure if they were citizens or not.
I believe they were citizens because I took them to get an ID and they were able to vote.
So they had to live here for a long time, a period of time, and just didn't know that.
Well, you know in California, they're giving illegals IDs.
I mean, they give them to them everywhere.
They give them to them in Texas.
Well, see, I didn't know that.
In Cleveland, I know, if you ain't got a state ID, that was my job title.
If you didn't have a state ID, you couldn't go vote.
But if I can go and get you, you can go with your birth certificate in Social Security
and get a state ID, you can vote.
So they had birth certificates and state IDs?
No, they didn't have state IDs.
They had them out of town IDs.
So they didn't have birth certificates?
They had birth certificates, but they had been here.
They're legal.
They're legal to be in Ohio.
But they didn't ever- They were legal immigrants.
Right.
They've been here a while.
They were citizens.
Yeah, they're citizens.
If they're legal, they're citizens.
They were citizens, but they didn't know nothing about getting a state ID.
All right, that makes sense.
Okay, they were citizens.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
They were citizens.
They've been here, what, three, four years?
Yeah.
And then they didn't ever- I've had a couple of them like that.
I had people, girls 21.
I had a lot of young girls.
You know, they talking on Obama, living in the projects.
If that phone stop your minutes, what you going to do?
Go to a payphone.
She had no other choice.
But by him giving you that phone, this what I preached to him when I was in the field service.
By him giving you that phone, do you want to give him a vote?
She tell me, I don't know what Obama do, but you talking on his phone.
Open your phone and tell me what it say as soon as you open it.
She open and say, Obama, you know he's running for president right now?
That's how I got it.
And then you didn't even have to give me anything.
Do you got your state ID on you?
And they will say, yeah, all I need is the numbers.
I can take the numbers off that state ID and give her a blue form where you can mail it
in.
You don't even got to go to here.
I got warrants.
I'm not going to the Board of Elections.
You don't need to.
Let me fill this paper out and the ballot going to come to your house.
When the ballot come in, you fill it out and mail it right back.
Wow.
Amazing.
Stacks of people like that in Cleveland, you know?
Let's talk to Jerry.
This is long folks, Obama phone lady here in studio with us.
Jerry in Connecticut, finish up your point, my friend.
Yeah.
Michelle, you seem like you're a believing woman.
You realize we're in the latter days, I'm sure you do, from all the signs and things
like that, right?
Right.
Well, why don't you look up Obama and November 5th, Illinois State Lottery winning.
If God was going to give us an indication that this man is on the wrong side of this
battle for our souls, then look up November 5th, Illinois Lottery.
The number that came up for the pick three, three, and this is not a, I checked this out
myself on one of those, you know, check the numbers, you know, type of thing came up six,
six, six.
No, I remember.
And then some others came up six, six, six.
Right.
I remember that too.
Yeah.
Anyway, the other thing I wanted to mention is the Tuskegee situation kept talking about
now that guy that did that experiment and the Tuskegee, he's an equal opportunity guy.
They didn't put him in jail.
You know what they did?
They took him off to one of the nuclear plants out in, I think it was in Ohio.
And then he decided to do an experiment by releasing all those nice nuclear particles
in the air to see how they would affect other people in the entire region.
Isn't that nice?
Our government is really working for us.
Yeah, they're really good people.
I think we should turn our guns into more calls coming up.
Hello, I'm Alex Jones, myself, my family, the Infowars.com team want to relay to you
and your families that we are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every
front.
Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats, but we can't do that without
your help.
By getting the films, bumper stickers and T-shirts at Infowars.com, you will wake up
people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before.
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here.
It's an Infowar, the spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
Hey there, Frank Bates here.
Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out 280 million Americans?
This is really scary stuff.
Defense experts warn that this odd device poses the greatest threat we've ever known.
In fact, just a few weeks ago, former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed
piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat.
I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up.
That's why my friend just created a free video at weirddevice.com that exposes this threat
and blows the doors off a conspiracy.
Go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover exactly what it is plus
discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack.
I'm not sure how long this video will be online, so go to weirddevice.com before it's gone
forever.
Again, that's weirddevice.com.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the best-selling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that carnivora be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the president could obtain its world-class healer.
Now, 27 years later, carnivore capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally
occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune
cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VenusFly or order from carnivora.com.
That's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A dot com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VenusFly or visit carnivora.com.
Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
Obviously we're going to have to go into 20 minutes, 30 minutes of overdrive to get to
all your phone calls and get to all these Twitter questions.
There are so many.
I mean, I've got hundreds here and they're all so good.
I'm going to try to go through a bunch of quick questions for you and not dominate.
Obviously on the nightly news tonight, I think David Ortiz is doing the first part, but I'm
going to do the interview part.
She's warmed up now, folks.
We're going to air some excerpts to it when she got here yesterday on the nightly news,
seven o'clock central.
But I'm also going to cover, man, this is bad.
I covered some of it today, but I didn't get into all of it.
The announcement is they're just going to go with executive authority.
Executive orders, ordering gun shops to shut down, not to sell semi-autos.
And now Rahm Emanuel has said, citizens aren't even in the discussion about guns, the police
are.
Well, that's judge dread.
I mean, it might as well just become the Soviet Union.
And this is where big governments and big police forces always go, while we obsess over
the police.
There are a lot of good police and either a department's good or it's bad.
There's hardly ever an in between, but the feds want bad departments like the Chicago
mob run Rahm Emanuel system and Rahm Emanuel is a despicable person.
Here is the mayor of Chicago, very dangerous person, saying that he wants the American
people to not be able to have any input on their guns.
Hey, punk, it's called the Second Amendment, here it is.
One, it's all about criminal access, it's not about gun control, it's about criminal
access to guns.
That changes the debate.
Two, put the police chief in the law enforcement community front and center, everybody else
from politician to whatever, take a back seat, because the police chiefs have a credibility
and authority and a voice on this, which is why they're all there.
I do believe as it relates to both the type of weapon being an assault weapon in this
case or the assault magazine, as Mike has, I think, strenuously focused us on message
on that, because the difference between a magazine that holds 10 and a magazine that
holds 20 or 30 is a lot of different type of damage that's done.
And those are the three things I do think you can change this debate.
I also think the country's in a different place like it was when we did Brady.
Man, the older he gets, he looks like a twin brother of Bloomberg.
I was just sitting there looking at him.
Ladies and gentlemen, you just heard him say, now by the way, in major polls, 98% you can
pull this up of police are pro-Second Amendment.
Most of the police chiefs are anti-Second Amendment because they're getting federal
money.
And there is a guy up there who's an Israeli officer, by the way, it's just unbelievable,
saying, by the way, our tax money pays to get Israel guns, which I'm all for citizens
having guns wherever, Switzerland, Israel, wherever.
And then he doesn't want us to have guns, he wants us to be like Chicago where the citizens
don't have guns.
What do you think of that?
I think that sucks.
Well, there you go, you're becoming an info warrior.
He gets to have guns and bodyguards, but we don't?
We need the same thing.
And you say we need a Second Amendment bad.
We need a Second Amendment bad.
That's true.
How about an Obama gun?
He gave me an M4, he gonna do more.
That would be constitutional if the government issued us all weapons.
I'm serious, that's what taxes are for.
The state should be taking taxes out to issue everybody that wants to be in the state militia,
we should have grenade launchers, everything.
You know Switzerland has that, they don't have any crime, almost none.
That makes sense though.
Absolutely, we're the people, we're the government.
That's right, we got you in there, right, give us some, keep us safe, you feel me?
You think anybody's gonna be messing around, everybody's armed?
No.
No, they're not.
And of course, then all the tough guys will leave their guns at home, Bill, don't take
your guns to town.
Right.
You know that song Johnny Cash?
Don't take your guns to town, Bill, leave your guns at home, son.
It's Obama lady.
The Obama lady in town, Austin, Texas right here.
Can you say I got me an Obama M4?
What's that?
That's an M16.
I got me an Obama M4, and he's gonna do more, he's gonna get me a grenade launcher under
it.
Say hello to my little friend, Overdrive, your calls, tweet questions and more, stay
with us.
Thank you for listening to GCN, visit GCNlive.com today.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e Foods Direct.
Coast to coast, direct from Austin, you're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
All right, Michelle, you're getting wound up.
There's callers want to talk to you.
We're going to them right now.
And who is that first caller?
Abdel in Arizona, you're on the air.
Welcome.
You're on the phone with Obama lady.
How are you doing, Alex?
Good, man.
What's on your mind?
Nothing much.
I just wanted to say hello to you and to Obama lady.
Here in Tucson, everybody calls it the same thing like we've been calling it since they
came out.
So it's kind of a spontaneous thing, I would believe to call the phone from the phone.
Yeah.
So yeah, I'm now everybody I know is calling their phone, the Obama phone.
It seems like anything that comes, socialist will go ahead and call it the Obama and whatever
it is.
And on that note, you know, I'm a long time listener.
I've been following you for about nine, 10 years.
I've had my own MK ultra experience here in Tucson that, you know, I would be for a different
call or whatnot, but yeah, you know, that's the thing is that even with me knowing the
whole situation with the new world order and everything, I still voted for him twice.
And I consider myself a libertarian.
I follow Ron Paul.
So that's how powerful and how dangerous he is.
Even me knowing better.
I still go ahead and vote for him.
That does sound like mind control.
My thing is you've got to call the whole thing as a fraud.
It's like when I got in, here's Morgan's face and said, look, the scams over, man, you want
my guns.
Shut up and stop saying, you know, they're like, well, you just want your guns.
We want something reasonable.
We just want some reasonable.
Here's the bill.
Gonna turn your guns in.
I'm like, shut up.
Stop lying to my face.
You punk.
Good job on that.
So that was awesome.
I got really excited.
I got it.
You know, the electric Liberty, you like to say kind of, you know, transcends through
the television.
And a lot of people saw that.
God bless you.
I appreciate you holding to say that.
What would you say to Piers Morgan?
Red coat.
What would you say to him coming over our country and saying, turn your guns in?
I'm like, shut up.
Shut up.
We got to keep it simple.
All of us are still in the country and say.
And turn your guns in.
Stop lying.
Take that stuff back to where you come from.
If you could be saved with a gun, we need to be saved with ours.
That's right.
So now you're being converted.
The Obama phone lady is now Obama M4 lady.
Protect me with Obama gun, Obama grenade.
Protection just like him.
There you go.
Common Sense.
That's right.
What do you think of Rahm Emanuel saying, let's take the gun laws out of the hands of
the people and just let the paramilitary take our guns?
No.
Doesn't Rahm Emanuel look like a bad guy out of a cartoon, like out of a-
He look like he drunk.
He look like he drinks, he's a little buzzin'.
Well he is a crazed maniac.
You know, he's a ballet dancer.
Is he?
Well, I wouldn't listen to nothing he say, any man step on they tiptoes a fool and don't
walk on tiptoes and get sewer and plumbing.
You like real men, don't you?
Yeah.
I want to punk Obama, you punk.
I think Obama's doing the punking of us.
He already did.
Look how those kids got killed in that school and he wasn't, I mean the tears look like,
you know, just dripping, but if I was a president and the man killed them kids like that, do
you know what I would have did?
Huh?
What?
I would have punked his ass by the balls, right in front of America.
I would have hung them straight up, see what you did?
Now look here, and all the boys there with the fruit rolls in their babies.
Could you imagine coming home, and I got five kids, I sent my kid thinking he's safe in
school.
Well hey, it's the government that advertises the place to go kill people is at a school
and then they take all the guns out and don't let the principals or anybody have guns.
The answer is they have instant access pistol safes that are biometric, you lay your hand
on it and it pops open.
I got them at home.
And I've also got a type of code into it, bam, bam, bam, boom, drawer pops open.
But you know what?
I'm really getting on you now.
I'm on the Alex Jones show now, because what you're saying is true.
Now I'm in Ohio, and I'm born and raised in the Heights, Cleveland Heights.
In Cleveland Heights, you got metal detectors and all that.
Hold on, I want to hear this when we get a break.
All the breaks are at the end of the hour, start of the hour.
She's like, what's going on with all these ads during the break?
It's commercial radio.
Most radio has 16 minutes of ads.
We only have 14.
I'm letting the audience know.
We'll be right back with Obama phone.
Hello, I'm Alex Jones.
Myself, my family, the Infowars.com team want to relay to you and your families that we
are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front.
Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats, but we can't do that without
your help.
By getting the films, bumper stickers, and t-shirts at Infowars.com, you will wake up
people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before.
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here.
It's an Infowar, the spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
You've come to expect winter specials from Herbal Healer Academy, and we're not going
to let you down.
Battle through cold and flu season with powerful natural and safe flu fighters, antivirals
like olive leaf extract capsules and elderberry power, vitamin D3, 180 caps, only $9, beta
glucans and an incredible immune system booster.
Our own four herb tea capsules and Respa-8, all specially priced during the winter sale
at herbalhealer.com.
Also exclusive homeopathic detoxes for lungs, kidneys, liver, whole body and lymph are on
sale.
Herbal Healer Academy offers correspondence courses to teach you how to handle your health
naturally.
And as always, new customers get a free 128-page catalog with your order.
Log on and save big now when you hit the winter specials at herbalhealer.com, healing the
world with nature one person at a time since 1988, celebrating 25 years in service to the
natural healthcare industry.
It's time for a home security quiz.
Answer this.
What effective home security device is smaller than a coffee cup fakes out burglars into
thinking someone is home at your house while you're away, plugs into any wall outlet, is
recommended by many police departments and sells for less than $35?
Yes, it's fake TV.
This year, about one in every 50 U.S. homes will have a break-in, with burglars usually
picking the easy target, a dark house that looks like no one is home.
Fake TV is a small electronic security device that makes it look like someone is home watching
TV by simulating the light from a real TV.
It's like a lamp on a timer, but far more convincing.
And for only $34.95, fake TV could be the difference between coming home to a secure
house or one that's been ransacked.
Go to faketv.com or call 1-877-5FAKETV.
That's 877-532-5388.
Or go to faketv.com.
Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
Ladies and gentlemen, directly from Cleveland, Ohio.
All right, we had a good time last night.
A lot of folks will ask, hey, we've had all this hardcore news.
All this stuff's going on.
Why is the Obama phone lady here?
And some thought, oh, he's gonna get her there and be mean to her.
No, I said, I bet she's a really interesting lady.
I could just tell from that video.
And I wanna try to say, listen, I get that Romney's not good either.
But let's just admit Obama doesn't care about us.
Let's just admit he's bought and paid for by a corrupt special interest.
Let's just admit they're trying to divide and conquer us.
And while we've been sitting here, I've been convincing you on the Second Amendment.
I've been convincing you on a bunch of other stuff.
And you were saying before the break, and we're going back to calls and Twitter questions
here.
And again, if you don't know who she is, folks, you know the thing about Obama.
I'm an Obama phone lady.
He gave us, well, repeat yourself there so they know who you are.
He gave us a phone and he's gonna do more.
And now you're saying the government should actually only tax us to give us M-16s.
Oh, he should give me a gun and some grenades.
You know, you taking it away, but we need our force here too.
There you go, ladies and gentlemen.
No, but seriously, you wanted to say something about the Second Amendment.
I was pointing out that they've made the schools victim disarmament zones, then they advertise
for crazy people.
Hey, don't just kill yourself.
The option is going down to a school and do it.
That's what the real tough guys do.
I think that sucks because here we is, I got kids.
I put my kids in school and the first thing I think they're safe.
They're at school.
When I was growing up, they didn't have all this going on.
And I'm really believing you, the government, you gotta have control of it.
You know, that guy killed those kids in that school just recently.
If I was the president, I would put him on a bus and put his whole body up there, hung
him upside down, straight out.
And they're gonna do it.
He's gonna do it in jail and they're gonna take 15 years to give them time and just sit
and rot.
I'm gonna rot all right.
Killed those innocent kids.
But see, they use that and dangle them out in front of us.
And meanwhile, the president signs weekly the death orders where they'll blow up a whole
apartment building or a whole village or a whole wedding to get one guy who hadn't even
been convicted, illegally bombing another country and they blow those little kids arms
and legs off.
And Obama didn't cry about that.
My point is that they're cold blooded.
Did you know our government runs Al Qaeda in Libya and Syria now publicly?
And Obama went in and murdered Gaddafi.
And again, he wasn't a perfect guy, but compared to Al Qaeda, he'd been friends with the West
for about a decade.
You know, Gaddafi was-
I believe that, I believe he just did that to get where he got, where he's at.
He did that to talk to the people just like when I did.
I didn't know what Alex Jones teaching me about what's on TV.
But I seen it with my own eyes.
You pulled it up on YouTube or the TV thing.
Obama line?
Right, and it came up.
That was Obama saying what he won't do with the taxes.
Here I am just got a job as a maid and my first check is eating me to taxes, eating
the hell out of me.
First check.
It's going up.
But-
He said he wouldn't do that.
I seen it right here on your show, Alex Jones' show.
He said he wouldn't take the taxes.
But exactly, but just 20 years ago, if a president did that, they got run out on a rail.
Right.
There's some, you want to cover some code for you, honey?
You bet.
And let's go to calls.
I'm going to quit hogging her here.
This is-
Yeah, let's call some calls.
Let's go to Mike in Tennessee.
You're on the air listing on 1600 WMQM.
Go ahead, sir.
Good afternoon, Alex and Michelle.
First, I just real quickly want to say, Michelle, if you haven't seen the Obama deception documentary,
I highly recommend that Alex gets you a copy of that as well as all of his other documentaries,
a year subscription to his magazine, as well as access to InfoWars TV that she can view
from any computer anywhere, including the public libraries.
Absolutely.
In fact, you see that magazine there, that was the December issue that we finished the
last week of November.
It says this man wants your guns and it says he's going to use executive orders to come
after our guns.
How do you think I knew that?
Because I'm not smart.
They told us they would do all this.
They said that.
I've just seen them said it on the TV and Alex Jones show that he wouldn't raise our
taxes.
Exactly, but back then it was only in policy reports.
See, they're in policy reports like we don't even exist because they know the paid off
media will never go show their real plans.
So see, that's why I get so mad.
I know their whole plan because they wrote it down.
This is not rocket science.
I know what I'm talking about because they told me.
It's like a confession letter.
It's like a killer who videotapes themselves chopping up some kid and I've got the video
and I'm like, look, he did it.
Here's the video.
Oh, shut up, conspiracy theorist.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
Anything else, Mike?
Michelle, I'm 51 and I grew up in Memphis, Tennessee and I grew up in a neighborhood
that had black fathers and white fathers that went to work.
Some were carpenters, some were dentists, some were trash men.
They came home every night to a house with a wife who'd beat the fool out of the young
boys if they got out of line and if they were at the neighbor's home, the neighbor's mom
would get a hold of you, call your mother.
When you got home, she would get you and when dad got home, it was all over.
The way they stole your birthright was they took the fathers out of the home, replaced
them with a welfare check and they- Hallelujah, hallelujah.
You're exactly right.
And by the way, Margaret Sanger said, we're going to get these black weeds.
This is a quote.
We're going to pay off black leaders and we're going to break up their families and we're
going to get them dependent and we're going to chop them up, okay?
And that's what goes on.
And what they've done, like Tony Brown says in Tony Brown's journal on PBS, what they've
done to the black community is the model for everybody.
They just went after you because people would say, well, they don't have rights because
they use prejudice to hit you from both sides.
The open prejudice, but then the fake liberals, that's their plan.
And so my whole point is, is that they've gone from 10% illegitimacy to 90 plus percent
illegitimacy.
And Dr. Spock in those books, they said, don't spank your kids.
They said, let your kids do what they want.
So they'll be out of control.
So now they get tasered and shot by the cops.
Now their father figure is a big fat fake gangster, like Freeway Ricky Ross, not the
real Freeway Ricky.
Rick Ross, the fake guy, not even a real gangster.
By the way, he runs and hides from real gangsters.
He's up there saying the tough thing to do, kill, steal, do all this.
People think that's what we're supposed to do.
You basically put on a gangster uniform for the cops now to alert who are trained on you.
They're like attack dogs trained to get a rabbit.
You put on a rabbit's uniform to be sent to a prison where they then put everybody racially
in their gangs to create a race system of divide and conquer.
The real colleges in America are the prisons designed, what this guy's saying right here,
to destroy the birthright, to destroy the father.
And they've now done it, and they're doing it to everybody.
And that's what Obama's there to do.
You know Obama got all the money increased to make sure they abort more people.
And folks say, well, look how bad the communities are.
Let's abort these people.
See how they've sold us on that?
He says, hey, let's kill people.
Because if we kill an old lady and don't give her healthcare, we can hire teachers.
Now we've got the idea of killing people to get a job, when all we ever needed was liberty
and freedom and self-sufficiency.
But now we've had the self-sufficiency destroyed.
Now they've got us right where they want us, Michelle.
They think they do.
Anything else, caller?
You're laying out the genius here.
Mike.
Their biggest fear is independence and people taking individual responsibility.
And once you give up the Obama phone bobble, you take back your rightful place as a sovereign
human being, a child of God, they lose.
Right, they lose.
That's right.
Remember, the slicker devil, I mean Mitt Romney's trying to talk to mainline, middle class people,
whatever color they are.
He's like, I don't care about 47%.
They're gonna do whatever.
He goes, I'll keep your taxes low.
But his plan was to raise them too.
He's there to con the middle class and the white people and the wealthy black folks and
all the people that have made some money, okay, that get the government in their friend.
But just he'll tell them what they wanna hear, and then they can put Obama in and say it's
a defeat for the ideas Mitt Romney put out that weren't his real plans.
Right.
You see, it wasn't just rigged in getting Obama in, okay?
It was rigged in that they ran somebody who was a phony up against him to begin with.
Because they want you to believe in the system.
Cuz it's not enough for them to distill your future.
They want you to beg for it.
You understand that?
Right, right, right.
I do believe that.
Cuz it's free will universe.
Right.
And I'm not trying to preach at you, but I wanted to get you here because I could tell
you were an interesting lady.
Right.
And I really wanted to communicate with you at point blank range.
And I'm glad you did.
Sir, good points.
Let's get another caller here in overdrive.
We're gonna skip this network break coming up.
Key in New York, you're on the air.
Go ahead.
Hey, how are you doing, Michelle?
Hey, how are you?
Doing good.
What's going on, Alex?
Worldwide broadcast, my friend.
What's on your mind?
Yo, you know something, Michelle?
The only reason why you're there is to be clowned.
That's the only reason why you're there.
Before you got there, they played that soundbite of yours over and over and over again to clown
you.
And the reason why he's trying to get you to say things is because he needs audio so
that he can play that back and clown you again when you leave.
Now, hold on just a second, Key.
Ain't nobody gonna-
No, no, but hold on.
When we called her, and when she got off the plane, I said, I think it's funny.
And we did make jokes about it because it's funny, but it's also sad.
And I said that at the time we aired it, if you go back to the first times we aired it,
and I said I thought she was an interesting lady and was talented and funny.
And I've said, I bet that lady's a character.
So we've got her here, and I clown around some too.
So all I'm saying is don't misrepresent what I actually stand for and what I believe in.
I mean, it is horrible that they're trying to domesticate us, and I'm here actually trying
to reach out to her to try to explain to her why we need a Second Amendment and things
like that, okay?
And obviously, I said I want that lady on the show months ago, and then I made kind
of a joke about it saying, okay, a bounty to get her on if somebody can find her.
And we got her on.
Is this not interesting radio, sir?
No, he's a chronic clown, and I can prove it to you that he isn't what he purports to
be.
You call him Obama, punk.
Well, check this out.
Alex said that you had 1776 all in Piers Morgan's space.
Oh, you're not going to take our guns because this is going to happen.
All of a sudden, Alex said if the ATF shows up at his house, he's not going to shoot back.
But the Ruby Ritz cats, they went for this.
Now they died, but they did what they said they were going to do.
But Alex said no, he's just driving to his knees.
You know what?
You're wrong, and I appreciate your call, and I am here on the front lines trying to
peacefully cause a cultural revolution 1776 worldwide.
And I know that they want to come set me up, and so I've always said the same thing.
If you come for the guns, it's going to cause a revolution.
But I'm not going to give them an excuse before that happens.
A, I want to stop it, and I've been clear about that.
B, I am trying to fix things peacefully, and I'm not going to give them the excuse.
I have said I'm not turning my guns in, period.
I don't care what phony executive orders they do.
But I've also said that I'm not going to open the door for them, that if they do come to
my house and kill me, to sit there and have me shooting my mouth off, that I'm going to
do this and that to the cops.
If they do come and kill me, it'll be in cold blood, and I'll be a martyr.
That's the opposite.
I mean, I'm Alex Jones.
On the air, I don't have bodyguards.
I go out and do all this.
I deal with this, and you're calling up saying that basically I'm a coward.
And anyone listening knows that that's not the case.
I mean, I march into the lion's den and get in people's face.
And I mean, it's just amazing, instead of just making fun of this lady from afar, I
got her.
Did I not tell you last night?
What did I tell you when you got off the plane?
Well, it's not about what you said.
I've been did it before I got to the Alex Jones show.
I even had my TV show in Cleveland, Ohio, Channel 19, and I turned them down.
But one thing about it, and two for show, if you see it with your own eyes and then
you know what you did, you know it's a game.
He did that probably to get me out there to get the voters to vote for him.
No, I know, but I mean, obviously, it's hilarious.
I mean, I'm-
I mean, I think it's funny because it's-
But I mean, I said on air, I said you could do voiceovers.
I mean, that's like a-
I could be a comedian.
That's like a Muppet character.
I mean, I'm gonna be honest with you, right?
I'm telling you where your talents are.
When you get upset and talk, I mean, it sounds like a Muppet.
I mean, you could go make money as a Muppet.
Okay.
You could play with that.
Well, but listen, the point is I do, the thing is I do Marvin the Martian voices.
Right.
I can do Muppet voices.
I mean, I'm saying, I said at the time, that's an interesting lady.
There's plenty of people on the news saying I want Obama in cuz I want free stuff.
We played like 10 clips of that.
None of those got 20 million views because they didn't have that spark.
That's the spark.
And everybody told me, even when I got on YouTube, first thing they said, wow, you were
so funny.
The way you said it.
Tell me your phone and you can do more.
You know, that was- But didn't I tell you that I thought it was
funny and that I disagreed with it?
Oh, yeah.
And I told John to tell you that on the phone.
Well, see, when I- What did we tell you about getting the, I mean, we were honest about
it.
Right.
The point is my attacker is always obsessed on saying, I'm not bona fide.
I'm not real.
I'm disingenuous.
When it's the opposite- It's real as an Alex Jones show.
You're real?
Well, that's what I like is things that are real.
Then if you don't know a man like you showed me sitting in his office-
Well, exactly.
And I mean- They wasn't going to raise and cut my tax.
You know why you're here?
Because when I'm at literally having Thanksgiving or Christmas, we're sitting around talking
about you.
Uh-huh.
And everybody- I'm the only one.
Everybody's talking about the bomber phone lady.
That's why I'm- I know.
So the guy's trying to make it some evil thing to get you here.
A lot of people is.
A lot of people saying, I showed my butt doing this.
Well, the point is, is that so what?
You were in the arena.
Wait a minute.
You were on the field.
If I die tomorrow, my grandkids can go on YouTube and say, my granny did something on
YouTube, Obama phone lady.
Well, let me be clear too.
I don't- The family I come from, my family's all like, you better be nice to that lady.
And I'm like, how dare you?
You heard me on the phone with my wife last night.
Right.
Don't say I'm on purpose trying to be mean to her.
I mean, I said, obviously, obviously, I don't agree with what they've done.
I don't agree with getting free Obama phones.
It's selling our souls so cheaply.
I'm here telling you honestly, I think this is horrible.
And you're here understanding what I'm saying.
And we're trying to figure out ways for- But you just said it-
I fight as hard as I can to try to keep jobs in this country.
I've napped in- Well, just now you showed that clipping of- and that's so true.
Looks like he just showed us how we get a, what you call it, Happy Meal, a cheeseburger
and a fry.
I'm black, low clap, low po.
Obama lady.
Instead of buying a Happy Meal, a cheeseburger and a fry for two bucks, that toy that probably
get a million of them, pay one price, throw it in the bag, and the kid is happy.
That's example.
Same thing for me.
They threw me a Obama phone, and more than us, there's so many minorities that I helped
sign up to vote for Obama about that Obama phone, that they didn't even come from Obama.
So I made myself look stupid because when I was canvassing, they didn't tell me about
the Obama phone.
If I never went to a canvas for Obama, first thing everybody I know say, they call him
Obama phone.
Exactly.
What they want is they want to get everybody on the dole so these big mega banks can skim
and decide where the contracts go.
It's all mafia.
Let me go over some of these questions and people are gonna kill me.
I've got a whole, where do they go?
Here they are.
These are Twitter questions from real Alex Jones.
Why and what made you go on the Alex Jones show?
Why did you say no to the other shows, but you said yes to ours?
Well for one, I said yes to Alex Jones show because when you called me and talked to me,
there was a man that approached, excuse me, approached me.
So you had already been looking for me and here I am in Cleveland and you're in Texas.
They was right there in Cleveland looking for me and no one came to me like you did
Alex Jones.
And I don't care how stupid the video look or whatever they said about the video.
You was the first one made me feel welcome and to learn more about what's going on.
Well the thing is you're a real person.
You're funny, you're talented.
You have that pizazz.
But yeah, it's horrible what's happening, how they're buying us off with this stuff
and trying to make us dependent where there are no jobs, so you got to go on welfare.
This is all we talk about.
I mean, here I am talking about let's not let the eugenicists target black people.
And this guy calls up and says, you're clowning this lady.
And obviously we're all-
But I wanted to say what I really wanted to tell him and you wouldn't let me tell him.
What was that?
Go ahead.
Well if he wanted to clown me, but you got to also look at it is same thing they did
it to get his votes and like you did about the bag they threw the toy in.
We're all getting clowned.
I'm the Obama phone lady and if I got clowned by that, guess what?
I'm going to get what I need to get through.
That's the main thing.
And to know the right from the wrong-
Only people that don't get clowned are folks that don't ever do anything.
Right.
And see, I do a lot.
I'm right now.
Like I said, I'm a single parent with five kids.
I do a lot and I need to get through a lot.
I'm 47 years old, how long we last?
We don't last long.
And I don't care what you said about that call because whatever it took on you two,
you seen it.
And if I look like that much of a fool, where you at?
You're a fool with me.
But again, there's lots of people begging for, you know, saying I got this free thing.
Those didn't get popular.
It's because it's funny.
Here, here, and it's funny because the way you deliver it.
Now there's another one.
Why do you think he's paying for that phone?
Do you think it's fair that they take money from somebody else?
No, I don't.
They could have used that money to give me a gun and a grenade to help save my soul.
If it wasn't for me, it'd blow me down.
The Obama phone, lady.
Here's something else.
Oh my gosh.
You got to be like that.
You see how that caller just did us?
Here's that same question.
Do you want a free firearm?
I hadn't even read these yet.
How do you feel about the tax increases on more than 77 percent of Americans?
We already talked about that.
Why are you, who are you going to vote for in 2016?
It darn sure won't be Obama.
I don't know.
They're talking about a third term for him.
Well, I don't think he's going to last that long.
I mean, Rahm Emanuel says we don't even need voters anymore.
Right.
We just, the police will now run things.
And I do believe that because where I live at and where I was at, the police is running
it.
And I've seen it with my own eyes.
And I'm glad you brought a lot to my attention about that because I've just moved from Cleveland
Heights to Cleveland.
Cleveland, you can walk outside butt naked.
You go to Cleveland Heights, they're going to arrest you, say you raped somebody because
you're butt naked.
The police is running it all.
You know, years ago, my father dead and gone.
He told me it was going to people, it was going to be people on the devices on the TV
that they can look through you and see where you at.
I believe that because now they got them things they put on kids' leg and they look through
the TV.
No, no, no.
Your Obama phone tracks everywhere you go.
I believe that.
They dial in and listen to you.
No, it's horrible.
They control you because they give you so many minutes a month.
Do something.
Here's another caller, the most incredible voice.
Are you getting job offers for TV, radio, voiceovers, et cetera?
It says you way better than Piers Morgan.
Thanks for the comment.
By the way, folks, I'm telling you, she needs her agent.
She needs to do voiceovers.
I guess I'm able because I'm trying to help her.
Send me an agent out.
Have you heard about FEMA camps?
Yes, I did.
I used FEMA before.
FEMA is the one to help you if you say your flood is in the basement.
But they're also the shadow government.
They're with the government.
Do you take the flu shot?
No.
Why?
I got faith in God.
Oh, yeah.
Well, it never even protects you anyways.
Right.
Take it.
We're going to do more of these questions tonight on the TV show.
All right now.
Let you get some late lunch.
All right.
And we're going to go back to retransmission covering news from the earlier broadcast here
and I'll be back tomorrow.
Live 11 a.m. Central.
A lot more tonight.
7 o'clock central, prisonplanet.tv with Obama Phone Lady.
All right.
Obama Phone Lady is here.
We're on the march.
The empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.