Big Brother, Mainstream Media, Government Cover-Ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
It is 2013.
We are here, at least on the Gregorian calendar.
The Chinese New Year, I guess, starts in about a month.
It'll be the fitting year of the snake.
Year of the New World Order.
And I guess the Age of Aquarius has kicked off as well.
The Illuminati believes that they are about to ascend to power.
Whether you believe in that or not, they believe in it.
And that is why they are moving on every single front.
Again, ladies and gentlemen, we are live here.
And we are going to be here for the next three hours on this New Year's Day.
The globalists are not just gonna try to strangle the Second Amendment.
Using the deaths of the poor children at Sandy Hook.
They are going to annihilate publicly the entire Bill of Rights and Constitution.
And basically have a political orgy in the blood.
And here is one of the headlines.
Democrats crank up death panel talk following Obama win.
That's a curtain, MOMfallwars.com headline.
Here's the actual slate headline by a George Soros operative.
The case for death panels.
Remember the headline in, what was it, Newsweek?
The case for killing Granny.
While they, but that was after Obamacare passed.
Before they said, conspiracy theory, we would never.
That is preposterous.
Wayne LaPierre comes out and says, we need to arm the school teachers like Israel.
That stopped their mass shootings in schools.
That's ridiculous.
Israel doesn't have any guns.
Guns are outlawed there.
Talking to you like you've got a 55 IQ.
And you know what, it works on people.
Because the average person isn't even so much stupid as they're incredibly coddling and
lazy.
And just get into, the hype, the soap opera, the cover of People Magazine, the dead children,
tuning in and lighting candles.
But if you go, hey, they're killing kids with drones.
Hey, thousands die a year from the inoculations in the US alone.
Tens of thousands of kids per Asian country get paralyzed with a polio shot.
Shut up, extremist.
It doesn't exist.
See if there's any inkling of responsibility for jellyfish people, they say it doesn't
exist.
But if it's like the big mainstream media, time to get sad, time to get upset, time to
do something, let's do something right now.
And so you've got the domesticated mass literally sucking their Prozac thumbs, sitting on their
Prozac thumbs, looking at us.
The people that at least know that we're in deep trouble and the society's in a very decadent
downward spiral.
And they're looking at us going, men with guns, go get their guns, they shouldn't have
them.
I'm scared of them with guns, but I like your black uniform.
I like it, I like checkpoints, it makes me feel safe.
Hey, did you know government killed 260 plus million people?
Measuring university studies like University of Hawaii?
Whatever conspiracy there is, there's no death panels, but there are.
So here it is, the case for death panels.
There's a bunch of articles outgoing, you wanna fix the economy, kill old people.
And so I wanna after a special guest, remember Susanna Hupp, who was one of the Luby's Massacre
Survivors, former state rep after that.
Old talk show host on our local affiliate 590 AM, and she's gonna be popping in later
in the second hour of about 15, 20 minutes.
Remember she testified to Congress, she said, we have our guns to protect us from you, they're
not for duck hunting.
So yeah, that's the lady, she's gonna be joining us, a fellow Texan.
But other than that, we're gonna have open phones today and I'm going to wait till later
in the broadcast to get into agenda 21 and what it really means, how it means eugenics,
how it means death panels.
So that is all coming up today.
And they're also declaring war on the Constitution, calling it evil.
The Obama noise are so like a case of hemorrhoids, the Obama noise will be right back or worse
than hemorrhoids, I actually.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health.
With silver lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver based products.
Our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two
ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well as our all natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and
leave the silver at the surface.
But rather, we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry
of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more
effectively.
Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver based products
are best for you.
That's www.silverlungs.com.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east, but we are still in the eye of the perfect
storm.
The most devastating economic conditions since the Great Depression, America's worst drought
in agricultural history, and now the economic results of the presidential election.
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply.
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from E Foods Direct, and I recommend you do
the same.
It's time to get your own supply from E Foods Direct.
I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food.
I'm taking control of my future, and you're nuts if you don't do the same.
Go to efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex to find the specials, and you can start with
a holiday gift pack that's normally $80, now under $50.
Remember, I can warn you, but I can't feed you, call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com
forward slash Alex.
Would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late?
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex.
E Foods can reduce fluoride up to 95%, easy to set up and use, doesn't require electricity,
purify water from lakes, streams, ponds, and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
Propure is the best gravity-fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on Propure, but if you add the promo code
water at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance.
You are listening to the Alex Jones Show.
Here we are, ladies and gentlemen.
We are live.
It is the first day of January, 2013.
In the Chinese zodiac, the year of the snake kicks off on the 23rd, a fitting title.
And for the globalist, it is to tyranny and beyond.
You know, Buzz Lightyear says to infinity and beyond.
For the globalist, tyranny is just the beginning of their absolute takeover and re-engineering
of what's left of humanity in an ultimate act of complete domination.
And the globalist in all their publications brag how they have generationally worked to
take over much of the planet so that they can fully, irrevocably, savage humanity and
reduce the population down to almost nothing.
Show that they can take full control of human development and basically use those of us
that are left as playthings or as test subjects for life extension technologies and other
systems.
And that is what we face in 2013 is the velvet glove being taken off of the iron fist.
I had a caller yesterday who asked me, why do you sound so irritated sometimes when you
are taking phone calls?
And it's because of a lot of things, because sometimes I hear the rebroadcast and I sound
friendly and nice and answer the questions and I'm congenial.
Other times I hear rebroadcast occasionally when I can stomach listening to myself.
And I sound pained, I sound rude.
And it's really because I am exhausted at many core levels, but also energized at core
levels.
So I've got a big heart for the fight against the globalist, but physically, especially
I don't get enough sleep or don't eat enough, or I get overly angry at the globalist.
I tend to kind of overheat like a race car engine and well, explode.
And so that's the answer to the fellow's question as I thought about that last night.
And I've had this as a resolution many times because back when I was first on talk radio
17 years ago, I was pretty much a call driven show.
I would do a two, three hour radio show every day and 80% of it was phone calls because
I enjoyed the phone calls.
Now I've always got so many things on my mind and so much news that I'm frustrated that
I'm not getting to all the news that I've researched and wanna cover.
I'm frustrated because of the spoken words limitations to describe fully what an article
or a piece of news signifies.
And I'm frustrated that I wanna take a lot of your calls, but that I then tend to not
go to your calls.
And when I do, they're complex questions or complex issues.
And I basically throw little mini temper tantrums because it's almost like an interrogation.
I love going out and meeting listeners.
I love going out and doing events, but at the same time, I hate it because it's very
exhausting.
If I go out and talk to a couple thousand people after an event and shake hands for
three hours and listen to their questions and listen to their comments, it's draining.
Because I actually listen to you, I actually gauge you, I actually read you as a person.
And that's very tiring.
And it's the same thing with all this news.
I mean, I researched news last night, I researched it this morning.
I have stacks over 100 articles here I wanna get into, huge piles of video clips I wanna
analyze.
But each article, when I pick up one of these articles or I pick up one of these quotes,
I have to summon the data in my mind associated with that information.
And so that itself is a frustrating event.
And I mean, just thinking about it right now is making me nauseated.
I'm not like running on the air, happy I've got a clip of Dianne Feinstein saying her
goal is to disarm the general population, quote, Mr. And Mrs. America.
I already knew that was her goal and read her quotes over the years, but it's painful
to look at, it's painful.
And then it's painful to try to put all the evidence on display for you.
But enough about that, I'm gonna give the number out here and I don't want people to
call in and go, we appreciate you, you're great.
That's not why I'm whining about this on air.
I'm telling you about this so you'll understand where I come from, so you can put up with
me.
Some of you that get irritated by hearing the irritation of my voice, it's not with
you.
It's with that I know I'm right, I know that I understand the enemy.
The enemy is so arrogant, they brag about their plans everywhere.
And I am fundamentally upset.
I'm upset with the globalist, I'm upset with the general public being weak minded.
I'm upset with myself not being able to fully articulate what I know and understand.
Because if you knew what I knew, if you could see what I see, our troubles would be over
very, very quickly.
But then I realized the general public is literally being swallowed by fraud.
The alternative media, as bad as it is, because at least it's real and it's human.
When the globalists try to inject cognitive infiltration that Cass Sunstein talked about
at the White House in to create infighting and kind of a background noise to nullify
us.
But it still isn't working because there's an over driving human survival instinct that
still beats in the most unconscious of people.
But my goal is to really try to awaken humanity and to try to reverse our course.
Because the course we're headed on is oblivion.
It is anathema to everything good and wholesome.
People say, why does evil always get in control throughout time?
Because it has the desire for the power.
And I study the scientific crafting of the system where they roll out certain technologies
and certain systems.
And then we beg and clamor and pay for them as status symbols when they are tools of control.
But then to even reach in to the matrix, proto-matrix system that the general public has already
fallen to, you must use the tools of the enemy.
I am not against technology, but again to use a Lord of the Rings analogy because that
seems to get through to people.
Rings are made for all the races in Middle Earth, for the elves, for the dwarves, for
the men.
The rings are made by the older creations of the entity, the god that created the universe.
So it basically has kind of a Christian timeline in Tolkien's writings.
If you get deeper into it, it's an analogy, an allegory.
And the rings are forged, and the nine rings are given to men, and a certain amount are
given to the elves and the dwarves.
And they have incredible power in them inherently, and it's given to them by an angelic creature.
But the angelic creature has decided to become destructive, Lucifer, Morgoth against Mordor.
And Morgoth falls and is reincarnated as Sauron, but the point is that the rings are given
and you take the rings, you take the cell phone, you take the smart meter.
You go into the gym and they go, discount if you thumbprint to sign up.
And you do it all Pavlovianly set up like a chicken pecking a tic-tac-toe machine to
get grain.
And it is a system of total control designed to get you into an electronic straitjacket
to cut off self-sufficiency, to shut down the family farms, to make you dependent, to
bring you into model compact 2021 cities that are advertised again as cool and fun.
To then have a controlled bioweapon attacks that are released as people go into more authoritarian
control in the name of avoiding the biological warfare attacks that they claim terrorists
are going to launch.
As we sit there huddled in our compact cities, watching the general third world population
wiped out in the future, you need to understand that it is the globalist orchestrating all
of this.
And anything they give you, anything we use, anything in our culture that has been rolled
out and promoted by the system is a ring of power.
You guys print me the intro to the Lord of the Rings book.
It's one ring to bind them in the darkness, bind them.
I want that full quote when we come back if we can.
One ring to rule them all, because that's really what it is.
And in the darkness bind them.
We are fighting adherence of death and destruction and ugliness.
It is what they resonate with, it is what they will create.
And it's in their globalist literature, it's in everything they say, everything they do.
And so later I'm gonna get into that, I'm gonna get into top professors demonizing the
Constitution and calling it evil and saying get rid of it.
They're openly saying yes, kill the old people now, all over the news.
You see, they're not just gonna go after the guns.
The fact that they're going after them and saying openly we want you to turn them in
is the signal that the real third act has begun.
And if you look at the arrogance and the fire in the enemy's eyes right now, they're on
the march.
They have decided to drop the hammer and I can tell you, along with that will be false
flag stage terror attacks blamed on us.
So you're thinking they'll never get away with this.
They're going to attack themselves and blame it on us.
A great time of evil is upon us, ladies and gentlemen.
And you better decide which side you're on.
My New Year's resolution is when I give the number out, I'm gonna take the calls.
And if I don't get to them, we're gonna wipe the phones out till I do go to calls.
We're gonna take your calls on any issue you wanna discuss straight ahead, 800-259-9231.
It is January 1st, 2013, that'll take some getting used to, 800-259-9231.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east, but we are still in the eye of the perfect
storm.
The most devastating economic conditions since the Great Depression, America's worst drought
in agricultural history, and now the economic results of the presidential election.
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply.
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from eFoods Direct, and I recommend you do
the same.
It's time to get your own supply from eFoods Direct.
I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food.
I'm taking control of my future, and you're nuts if you don't do the same.
Go to eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex to find the specials, and you can start with
a holiday gift pack that's normally $80, now under $50.
Remember, I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex.
Would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late?
Or 09-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex.
We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration.
As an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years and serving thousands of satisfied customers,
the Berkey Guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration systems.
The Berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable black purification
elements that purify water by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria, cysts and parasites to
non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides.
Order the Berkey light system today, complete with two black Berkey elements for only $231,
and the Berkey Guy will ship your order free of charge.
With the purchase of a Berkey light, the Berkey Guy is also offering a set of fluoride and
arsenic filters for only $39.99.
That's over 30% off the retail price.
Call the Berkey Guy at 1-877-886-3653.
That's 1-877-886-3653.
Or order online at GoBerkey.com.
That's GoBerkey.com today.
HempUSA.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine and probiotics,
and we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder absolutely free.
Micro plant powder only at HempUSA.org.
Call 908-691-2608.
That's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder, seeds and oil can do for you only at HempUSA.org.
See this offer ends January 31st.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson.
Have you ever wondered why banks, stockbrokers, investment advisors won't talk about gold
IRAs?
They've been available since 1986, yet the financial industry won't recognize the value
of gold for your retirement.
Gold is outperformed paper investments, yet no word about IRAs.
If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns, call 800-686-2237.
Take care of your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
Hi there.
My name is Frank Bates.
What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble.
I just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are, incompetent line crooks that
are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high.
Some have called this a conspiracy.
Others have called it a cover-up, and you will be shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy
goes.
My video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them
and how you can beat them too.
Watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patriots have already seen
in the last three months.
Go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect
your home.
Go watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down.
Again, that's 123coverup.com.
It began with the forging of the great rings.
Three were given to the elves, immortal, wisest and fairest of all beings.
Seven to the dwarf lords, great miners and craftsmen of the mountain halls.
And nine, nine rings were gifted to the race of men who above all else desire power.
For within these rings was bound the strength and will to govern each race.
But they were all of them deceived, for another ring was made.
In the land of Mordor, in the fires of Mount Doom, the Dark Lord Sauron forged in secret
a master ring to control all others, and into this ring he poured his cruelty, his malice
and his will to dominate all life.
One ring to rule them all.
Crashing through the lies and disinformation, it's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
It is the first day of 2013, I've been a lot of soul searching and I want to commit to
you in this year that I'm going to put out the greatest output of information and of
the highest quality that we have ever produced.
I am going to make a new official film this year, I've not announced that yet, I will
on Friday.
I meant to do it a few weeks ago but got behind, announced the biggest contest we've ever done.
It'll be $100,000 contest and it is key to our Paul Revere operation, that's what I intend
to call it, Operation Paul Revere.
We are going to launch the TV show onto the satellites and I am going to create informational
videos on certain key subjects explaining how things work.
Only keys to unlocking the secrets of the New World Order and how to defeat them.
Because I do understand their operations, I understand all of their operations.
It does not mean that I could consciously at one time grasp the entire compendium of
their system.
But if I focus on particular sub sectors of it, I can see right down to the bone on what
they're doing.
Because they've published their operational manuals and only thinly veil and compartmentalize
their true goals.
In fact, in many cases they openly brag.
Also many of the servants of total evil are very twisted and weak people.
And they almost reflexively in the control systems are used to dealing with the zombified
public that is in a trance state.
So those of us that are in different degrees of awakening, it's like watching people in
slow motion.
And so don't ever forget how much power you've really got if by the grace of God, your consciousness
has not been shuttered.
Again, my friends, it is Tuesday, the first day of January 2013.
We come back from break, I will go to your phone calls at 800-25-99231.
And just be ready.
I've said this over and over again, but it's my New Year's resolution.
To make your point, I'm gonna try to go to the next person.
It's just sometimes the calls are so incredible or they're breaking such amazing news.
Like the caller yesterday going, yeah, they've got hidden cameras in the VA in the smoke
detectors in Tampa.
And we search engine it, and there it is in the Tampa newspaper.
And they're like, we're allowed to secretly watch you.
Well, yeah, I mean, they got cameras in the bathrooms at public schools for 15 years.
Government issued laptops, watch you at home.
I mean, it's just all over the top.
And that's just what you know about.
I mean, I don't just get up here and say almost every vaccine they look at has cancer viruses
in it on purpose.
I've got the top scientist bragging.
I've played the video clips of the polio developer going, yeah, we knew we gave 100 million Americans
the first round cancer viruses and it's killed tens of millions and they laugh about it on
PBS.
On the PBS station in Boston, I mean, when you get these globalists together like on
TED TV, Bill Gates gets up there and goes, we're gonna reduce the carbon output.
That means reduce this down to zero and he puts an image of stick figures of a family
up there and the TED TV conference elitist all laugh.
They're not liberals, they're killers.
You don't get in the club unless you go, yeah, I see the public as animals.
I wanna kill them.
They go, good, you're part of the team, you have the will to be cold blooded and understand
survival of the fittest.
Know what you are is going to be used and destroyed.
I will assure you, I will assure all of you that you will be destroyed.
You will not get a seat at this table, you understand that?
One ring to rule them all, one ring to find them, one ring to bring them all and in the
darkness bind them.
Is that not the technocratic surveillance smart grid tracking everything we do?
One ring to rule them all, one ring to find them, one ring to bring them all and in the
darkness bind them for taxation and control.
They also kill you with the wireless systems as well.
Stay with us, we'll be back.
We're on the march.
The empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other
harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
All natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east but we are still in the eye of the perfect
storm.
The most devastating economic conditions since the Great Depression, America's worst drought
in agricultural history and now the economic results of the presidential election.
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply.
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from eFoods Direct and I recommend you do
the same.
It's time to get your own supply from eFoods Direct.
I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food.
I'm taking control of my future and you're nuts if you don't do the same.
Go to efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex to find the specials and you can start with
a holiday gift pack that's normally $80, now under $50.
Remember, I can warn you but I can't feed you, call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com
forward slash Alex.
Would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late, 409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com
You've got a business, you didn't build that, somebody else made that happen.
Coming up, defending the republic from enemies foreign and domestic, it's Alex Jones.
That's right, coming up, the defense of the republic.
Okay, I'm gonna go directly to your calls.
And then Rick Perry has signed an order that's got no attention to bring in the Trans Texas
Napa Superhighway even though our state representatives have voted it down twice.
What Mordor wants, Mordor gets until the public awakens.
And we have top Georgetown professors, advisors to Obama, saying the Constitution is just
a criminal document.
Those are some of the quotes.
We're gonna be going over all that.
They're openly announcing all over the place that we need to kill all people, get rid of
them.
I'm gonna explain to you how the collectivist model works, and there is no doubt that collectivism
is a nightmare.
It sounds good, it'll make you feel good up front at the beginning like the first time
you inject heroin, but it leads to absolute ruination and domestication and dehumanization.
But it's like the ring of power, people believe because they're good, they could have a big
government that would redistribute wealth.
My friends, the globalists that have set up collectivism and that run the world economy
are absolutely cold-blooded, exterminist, ultra-Hitlerian eugenicist.
And anything they do with taxes will be turned towards bad in the end.
And we told you that once they got health care in, they would start the death panels
because they've done it in dozens of other countries.
They follow a program.
We can look at scores of nations further down the line than we are.
It's a blueprint.
It's like a movie we've already seen over and over again, and that's what's so frustrating.
They teach the general public that everything is your opinion.
No, this is not my opinion.
This is not my opinion.
If you walk out on the top of a 50-story building without a parachute, and you jump off that
thing and swan dive towards the concrete below, you are going to die.
That is not my opinion.
And if you let the globalists execute their plan, it's like steps downwards into hell.
We know where each step goes, just like a detailed road map.
There is no debate.
I'm going to go to your phone calls.
Justin in Missouri, you're on the air.
Welcome.
Hey, thanks for taking my call.
I just wanted to ask you what you think they're going to sneak into that fiscal negotiation
regarding the Second Amendment.
Oh, that's a good point.
They can have the government shut down, the welfare checks, or credits not be put on the
cards.
And then Feinstein, who is key on the committee to be able to control what bills can go in
and out or what agreements, they're saying that her bill, she's the one that wrote it
and got it rammed through with Biden in 1993, they're saying it's her bill.
I mean, she's the person that Obama's going to hand the ball to, she's the running back.
And they're running the play to try to engage in 100-yard drive against us, and they intend
to do it.
And again, the fiscal clip has been done in Iceland, everywhere else, we said this was
coming.
They say, my gosh, we're holding up the budget, everything will collapse, the street lights
won't be on, the police won't get paid.
It's all over, we'll lose our credit rating if we don't raise taxes and increase the national
debt.
And this is all maneuvering us into abject collapse, which is what a group of loan-sharking
foreign banks who are loaning us our own money back would do.
So it is rack and ruin, it is a direct course, and that's why I got so angry on the hike
and bike trail.
I had to start wearing earplugs or something last Friday because I'm sitting there, or
was it Saturday, and I've run to the top of a hill and I'm stretching.
And I hear these three guys who were obviously in state government cuz I could hear how they
were talking, and they were manager level.
They all thought they were really smart, their whole bearing, and they were just bragging
that, don't worry, Obama knows how to deal with them.
Boehner's on the team, once the third comes, he'll be elected to leadership and then he
can do whatever he wants, Boehner can, and the economy isn't gonna go down.
They actually believe Obama's their buddy, and they're supporting it, and they're trying
to fix things, I mean, the government puts cancer viruses in shots and tries to get you
to take them, you dumb idiot, they wanna kill you.
And I just looked at the guys, and I turned on the charisma, not on purpose, a much more
charismatic in person.
And I just literally said, well, I mean, I already talked about it on air, I broke it
down and at the end, those guys were shaking, and they should be cuz they just heard truth.
And they went, yeah, like Greece, yeah, yeah, you're right, I was like, well, do something
about it.
I told them, I said, you know the truth, see, you just knew the truth, but you were up here
having what you thought was a politically correct discussion, like children in dress
up pretending they're the lone ranger in Tonto.
You're a real human alive in 2013, this was 2012, there's a real war going on, wake up
and get involved in it now, stop living a fantasy land.
I'm sorry, sir, go ahead.
Yeah, I thought it was gonna be another, gotta read it to see what's in it, like the health
care bill.
And it wouldn't shock me at all if they try to completely go after the Second Amendment
in little sneaky ways in there.
No, God bless you, sir, I appreciate your call.
First caller of 2013, my friend, Chet in New York, Chet, you're on the air, welcome.
Happy New Year's, Alex and Bunch.
Hey, yeah, I'm up here in the new Rome, actually, now it was New York, but now that we have
Emperor Cuomo involved with his new degree of gun confiscation, which he's right in line
with Diane Frankenstein there.
Yeah, he said he may issue a gubernatorial executive order and just have you hand them
in.
How's that sound?
Shocking, the thing is, I think the rest of the country, they look at New York like that
liberal part, New York City, Manhattan, you've been around there.
A lot of nice people, but it's the politics.
New York's got a lot of rural areas, hunters, etc., and people have been massing arms all
over the country.
No, I know, listen, upstate New York and rural areas of New York, I've been there many times,
I know the culture absolutely is about as country boy can survive as Alabama or East
Texas or same thing with Northern California.
Anywhere where people actually live in the countryside, in the real world and actually
work, they understand that you need guns to protect yourself.
And we've got all the people in the city who are domesticated, who are delusional and really
think the government's their friend.
I agree 100%, like you said, I think you guys hit the point before where nobody's calling
for violence on our end, but it looks like they're really pushing their little, I think
their explosion button on themselves because there's a lot of people that are just not
going to give their guns up because I've spoke with them.
So I just figured I'd throw it at you, my friend, and hey, great work you're doing.
A lot of other people get in on this New Year's, but I'm staying optimistic because there's
so many of us now.
I appreciate your call, my friend, look, I'll just say this, everybody needs to be involved
in a maximum effort now to engage government and collaborator globalist occupation medium.
And let them know, hey, we know you're authoritarian criminals that want to disarm us.
You don't call up and say, hey, you know, guns actually protect people 80 plus times
more often than they're using the commission of a crime.
Hey, areas that have more guns have lower crime, hey, England's crime rate tripled,
I kept saying doubled, it tripled, and is the highest in Europe since they took the
guns 15, 16 years ago.
Same thing with Australia and New Zealand, they know that, they're predators.
All those media people getting paid millions of dollars a year have bodyguards, they lived
in armed areas, their kids go to schools with armed guards.
They know, they sit around and talk about how you're dumb and how you're scum.
They can't even contain it on MSNBC, anyone that lives in the Southwest, anyone that lives
in the South, Midwest, that's like 80% of the country, you are scum, you are filth.
If you're a white person, they say you're dumb, you're ugly, you're scum, you're stupid.
And that if you don't accept socialism, you're a racist.
It is a total delusional elitist attitude.
I've been behind the scenes at CNN, you name it, over the years, and these are cold blooded
mercenaries, these are mercs.
And their uniform is a camouflage of non-threatening hippieism, folks, they're not hippies, they
are shock troops, stormtroopers, the army of death, okay?
And they learned, as Margaret Sanger under the advisement of Eber Bernays and the Rockefeller
Foundation, go read their quotes, to pose as non-threatening egalitarian philanthropist.
They have the moral high ground, they care, well, there's no death panels, really the
bill has it.
The books written by Daschle that wrote it says it, wrote those provisions, no, no, no,
that's not in the book.
Don't listen to him knowing no one's gonna go read it and find out we're telling the
truth.
That the Israelis don't own guns, don't listen to him.
There's no world government.
Well, I have hundreds of announcements out of the Bilderberg and Davos of world government,
world taxes, those don't exist, children, children, they talk, and they go, we talk
with a soft NPR voice.
You ever tune into NPR and every person on there?
I was one time being interviewed by NPR and they said, can you talk softer?
Can you settle down?
During the interview, they taped it down at UT, that's down there where their local studios
are, this is like 13 years ago or something.
And they're coming over the ISDN line going, sir, can you try to talk in a softer voice?
I wasn't even yelling.
I go, well, this is what my voice sounds like.
They're like, well, can you just sound softer?
And the woman was on the line going, can you relax, relax?
You know, I grew up around rural folks, many months out of the year being sent down to
work on the ranch from the time I was about 11 on.
And I've talked to people that deal with horses and what you deal when a horse gets old is
you do have a trailer come pick it up to take it to the Elmer's Glue factory.
And I was never there when they sold horses or got rid of them.
But you sit there and the trailer pulls up and you walk over and you, because horses
are real smart.
They're just real instinctive, that's when people think they're stupid.
No, they're real smart, but their instincts are really strong.
So it's like they have a mind, but they can't use it.
And they know, you may have loaded that horse in a trailer 10 times in that year, but you're
loading them in a trailer to go butcher them.
You're not gonna wanna get in the trailer.
And you just come over and you shh, shh, shh, here's some range cubes, here's some apple.
Come on, come on, let's get in the trailer, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, hi, this is NPR.
Just get in the trailer, hey, little girl, hey, little boy, come get in the van, I got
candy.
Hi, little, I got a puppy, I got candy, I got some free healthcare for you.
I'm gonna give you some more welfare, I got an Obama phone, get in the car, we got some
shots for you, it's something you don't get sick.
Come on, come on, get in the car, get in the van, yeah, but my mommy says don't, it's all
right.
Mommy's in the van, mommy's in the van, your government, it's nice, come on.
We wouldn't stage Sandy Hook, no, no, get on in the van.
Get on in, get on in, sweetie.
Van door slams, eat the candy, well, I want my mommy, it's okay, eat the candy.
And then the tape comes out around the head, and then they tie you up, tie the three year
old up, yes, that's how it works.
Let's go ahead and talk to Alice in Kansas, Alice, you're on the air, should I talk in
an NPR voice, hi, Alice, good to have you on with us on All Things Considered, welcome.
Hi, Alex, I've been listening to you for 15 years and I feel your exhaustion and your
pain, I understand where you're coming from, and I just felt a leading of the Holy Spirit
to give you something that might comfort you, it should take less than two minutes.
There are five points, I just want you to maybe listen and consider in your prayer time.
I wanted to tell you that you are a warrior of the Lord, He has chosen you, and in the
end, you answer only to the Lord, it doesn't matter what any man thinks of you.
Number two, you are the teacher, listeners are the students, it is a privilege for the
student to come to your class, you give it out, and the wind blows where it will.
They either get it or they don't, you have fulfilled your vow and responsibility to God,
and that's who you answer to, period.
Number three, you don't just justify yourself to any man anymore, if they don't like your
class, they can leave it and turn it off, they can address the issues, but they cannot
attack your character as soon as they attempt to assault you, that ends the call, no exceptions,
and do not address it further, just go to the next call like you would if someone was
using foul language, I'm nervous.
Let me just add this, ma'am, your kind words, I think we're all teaching each other, life
is a great college, and I have asked God, my prayer is, God, I'm weak, I'm evil, I'm
a sinner, please help me be a good person, and in these desperate times, please use me
to be a vessel to stand against people that wanna hurt innocents, I'm weak, will you please
give me the strength to do what has to be done?
That's my prayer, and that's what I stand for, and that's basically all I can do, and
I think that's all anybody else can do, but my great calling, God's letter on my heart,
is to get other people to stand up and be leaders as well, and I know there are people
out there listening who feel the calling to stand against evil, but you're so humble,
you're like, well, I'm not a leader, and I think what you're saying to me is I am a leader,
I need to stop being not so much humble, humble's good, but not let that get in the way of standing
up and really resisting, and I say that to others, we have a job to do, and it doesn't
mean we're gonna do it perfect, we just gotta ask God, help us do the right thing, and then
let God sort it out, we've gotta give it to God, but that doesn't mean just give it to
God and then do nothing, it means God, lead me, and I'm telling you, folks, if you ask
God for discernment, and if you ask God to open the universe up to you, it will happen.
Now, I wanna warn people, though, when the universe really opens up, it is mind-blowing,
and it only intensifies, do you see my point?
Yes, I see your point, I have two more things to say.
Go ahead.
Okay, the fourth one is be aware of the wiles of the devil, Satan comes but to rob, kill,
and destroy, and every time you allow a caller to assault your character, you waste the next
20 minutes of valuable air time that God gave you, explaining your righteousness, it gets
you all upset, it makes you physically ill, and it hurts your body, it exhausts you, what
a great weapon he uses against you, and he uses it frequently, so draw your sword, put
up your shield, and allow it no further, and then your peace will come back to you.
Number five, don't allow the pressures, I mean, don't allow the praises of men, men
betray but God will never betray, it too is a weapon of warfare and used against you,
if you will let it, it can alter your ego, ego may the praise of God be with you.
I agree, Allison, I'm out of time, great call, God bless you, and this new year's resolution
to take more calls and to work harder is the way to go, what's the saying, duty is a mountain,
death is a feather, we'll be back with more of your calls, stay with us.
This is Alex Jones with five good reasons you should consider buying a solar power generator.
Number one, new climate legislation could easily double or triple your electric bill.
Number two, our new energy czar wants to control how much power your electric company allows
you to have, it's true, total government control of electricity in the name of smart grid technology
is coming.
Number three, in some areas of the country, the power grid is dangerously overloaded,
and now new socialist legislation is only compounding the problem.
Number four, dangerous weather is always a threat to local grids, every year thousands
of families lose their power from weather-related outages.
Number five, a solar power generator provides powerful backup insurance and peace of mind.
Folks, I really believe in the solar power generators offered by Solutions from Science,
one of my oldest sponsors.
You can get more information at www.mysolarbackup.com, that's mysolarbackup.com.
Remember, the government doesn't own the sun, so go to mysolarbackup.com or call 1-877-327-0365.
Would it save you time to get the best quality water filters and the best quality storable
foods from one company?
You bet it would, and now you can, at BigBurkeyWaterFilters.com.
Big Burkey Water Filter products and great tasting, long lasting, storable, wise foods
are both now available on one website, BigBurkeyWaterFilters.com.
Wise foods, ready to eat meals, are packed in airtight nitrogen pouches and come with
a 25-year shelf life.
Big Burkey Water Filters are powerful enough to purify treated, untreated, or even stagnant
pond water.
Combine Big Burkey Water Filters with wise foods for an unbeatable preparedness combination.
Get free shipping on every order over $50, and GCN listeners receive 5% off all ceramic
filter systems.
Visit BigBurkeyWaterFilters.com or call 877-99-Burkey.
Or go to BigBurkeyWaterFilters.com.
You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa, where a nicely furnished cabin
with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine, and laundry service awaits.
After a good night's sleep, your adventure begins.
You're on a golden stag safari for big game.
But it's not Africa.
It's Argentina.
One-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo, huger, bighorn rams, wild boar, and the biggest
stag deer in South America.
All gold metal quality.
All the action you can handle.
Land rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages, hunting guides, ground
transportation included, and more.
All more affordable than you can imagine.
The adventure of a lifetime starts at GoldenStagSafaris.com.
The big game hunting ranch.
GoldenStagSafaris.com.
Yeah, I've been watching.
I've been waiting.
Welcome back.
Monday through Friday, 12 noon to 3 p.m. Eastern.
What is that, 9 to noon Pacific?
We are here live, ladies and gentlemen.
I am Alex Jones, your host.
This segment and the next, then Representative Susanna Hupp is scheduled to pop in with us.
She's the one of the survivors of the Luby Massacre, who spoke out in Congress eloquently.
Always good to have her pop in.
She's been on a few times over the years.
And then at the bottom of the next hour, we'll continue with calls and news.
After I get into a breakdown, where I need to be calm and try to go over what is 21 really
is, not just they're gonna make you live in a 250 square foot thing and double your taxes.
It's more than that.
It's designed to destroy civilization.
It was Oliver Wendell Holmes that, to paraphrase, basically said that taxes are the cost of
civilization.
Well, what about when your taxes are used to create a Malthusian destructive civilization?
So we're gonna be breaking that down here today.
The exact quote is taxes are the price we pay for civilization.
Briefly here, ladies and gentlemen, the new Infowars magazine is out.
It's available to buy in bulk at cost in groups of 10 up to 100.
Big color, the size of the old Rolling Stone, full of graphics, documents, articles.
2013, the year America dies, you can buy them in bulk.
So I give them something like a color book, basically.
And as print goes out, we go into print.
Because we should be balanced.
We shouldn't just be Internet only.
We should have hard copies of things.
And so I've committed that we're going to always put out hard copies of whatever we
produce, whether it's films or you name it.
Very important.
And so you can get the January issue, 2013, the year America dies, question mark.
Very powerful issue.
And you can, again, order at infowarsstore.com or call 888-253-3139.
We have the high quality, propure water filters that I use, the gravity-fed stainless steel
systems, the best out there, with 10% off of the promo code water at the already lowest
prices at infowarsstore.com.
You can also call 888-253-3139.
And your purchase of books, videos, all of it, supports this broadcast.
The amazing healthcare products that we've researched and used, the best out there at
infowarshealth.com as well.
You can also sign up to be a distributor with us and get discounts at infowarshealth.com.
Okay, let's go back to the calls.
Al in Delaware.
Al, you're on the air.
Thanks for holding.
Hey, Alex, congratulations on making it to 2013.
You're a trooper, my man.
You're the son I never had.
You are the light at the end of the tunnel, haven't talked to you in a couple of years.
I got to tell you, you're the reason I was able to take my home from the bank.
You're the reason that I've been able to survive this long, preparing and getting ready.
These people are bad-eared warlocks, rabid dogs off the leash.
No such thing as a politician, as a politician, they're plotiticians.
Alex, you've taken me places I could have never gone elsewhere.
I've lost all my friends, but I've got you and three little dogs and I couldn't be happier.
Thank you.
Well, your friends are in the matrix and wearing an Infowars t-shirt, you'll find like-minded
people in your area.
But yeah, folks that bought gold when we said buy it at 300 have done well.
We've taught folks how the banks run scams.
I've had countless people show up at events where we just told them about mineral supplementation,
where they're literally healthy now from death's doorstep.
And none of it is a secret.
The globalists know all this.
That's what's so frustrating about it all.
But you know what?
Liberty is the light at the end of the tunnel.
We are just a window into liberty and freedom, my friend.
Anything else you'd like to add here?
Yeah, the truth is driving people crazy.
They just can't take it.
Well, I'll tell you something.
They called me a drug dealer at settlement and I said, oh, no, you don't after 30 years
of a builder.
I got a woman and a half an hour they gave me my house right after starting the Patriot
Act.
And I served in the military.
These are corrupt, dangerous, hell on wheels, nightmarish people there.
I tell you what, stay there.
I want to come back to you.
You're on fire.
You're right.
They are rabid dog warlocks in giant hordes like locusts.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
Alex Jones here with a very important announcement for truth seekers.
We've carried a lot of amazing films and books over the years on the online video bookstore
at Infowars.com and out of all the titles we've carried, one stands out because it is
just so chillingly convincing.
And that's Dreams from My Real Father by Joel Gilbert, available at Infowars.com.
This film exposes the fraud that Obama is like nothing I've seen.
If you want to know who Obama's real daddy is, this is the film for you.
Don't forget your purchase supports our broadcast and our growing media network.
You'll also find it in infowarshop.com.
None Dare Call a Conspiracy by Gary Allen, the book that woke me up.
We're also carrying Behind the Green Mask, you in Agenda 21 by Rosa Corey.
This book is coffin nails to the globalist takeover.
The Greater Good, the most professional and up-to-date film I've ever seen, exposing the
scourge that is vaccines.
These titles and a lot more are all available at infowarshop.com.
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are now into hour number two.
We have former state rep and Blue Beast Massacre survivor, Susanna Hough, joining us.
And then we're gonna continue with your phone calls, but right now we're talking to Allen,
Delaware.
He was talking about how they use the Patriot Act.
Yeah, they'll just come in and foreclose on a house that's even paid for, where they don't
even have a note in some cases.
And they'll just say, you're a drug dealer.
I mean, the cops pull you over now and just say, we're gonna search you.
We think you're a drug dealer.
The government ships it all in, they play all sorts of crazy games.
This whole Patriot Act, the whole Homeland Security system, it was always set up and
designed and aimed at the American people.
That's always been the case.
And now they're just gonna let you know in the next four years, it's official.
They're announcing death panels to kill old people.
They're saying the Constitution is evil and must be overthrown.
I've got articles, that's coming up.
Add any other points, Al, you needed to make.
Well, the points I want to make is that every time we turn around, the government is hijacking
industry.
They're hijacking every last one of us now.
They have literally shanghaied the Constitution.
They're coming at us in such an evil, evil and just utterly egregious, I call them fleas,
Alex.
These are felonious litigators, egregiously attacking society.
And let me tell you something, you work your whole life to build up your wealth and you
think for one minute they're not coming to get it?
You think for one minute they're not gonna addict you to some bogus financial product
and then you're gonna build your wealth, you're gonna renovate your homes, you're gonna put
your children through college for what?
Let me tell you what it's for, it's the shackles of debt and lies and this is where we're at.
They've not just done this country, Alex, they've done the whole world, the entire world.
No, they follow the blueprint.
That's what I'm telling the domesticated people that are in this delusion that the overall
controllers of the system are their friends.
They are totally ruthless and just like Susanna Hupp said, 15, 16 years ago to Congress that
she owns firearms to protect herself from government.
That's what the founding fathers said, and that's what it's all about.
And everywhere they've taken the guns, the crime rate explodes, they love it.
This is a criminal energy, a criminal force that, I mean, look at Congress involved in
insider trading.
When they got caught, they said, well, we'll pass a law to outlaw it, which actually legalized
it where they can just get a waiver.
I mean, it is insane what we're dealing with.
The laws they create are lies, we know our documents.
Look, we're naked, we don't have a Justice Department, Alex.
We don't have, 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue is nothing but a crow's nest.
These people are so far gone plotting their next move on you.
And everybody's walking around like, everything's gonna be fine, the economy will turn around.
And socialism's not so bad.
I just about can't take another minute.
No, no, they sell them, they throw America in the water and then throw the life raft
out of socialism when it's actually a bowling ball to take you to the bottom.
When you get to the bottom, they go, here's another bowling ball.
And again, the truth is that people are in two camps, they're either waking up or they're
asleep.
And God help us because they are demonizing gun owners, calling them Nazis, Klan members,
baby killers, scum of the earth.
They demonize a group before they come after you and they want a purge of gun owners.
We have former representative Susanna Hupp on the line with us.
We're gonna come back from break and talk to her and play that short clip of her from
her longer testimony that's so famous before Congress telling Chuck Schumer and others,
hey, we don't have these guns, I'm sick of hearing about how it's for duck hunting.
It's to protect us from you guys up there, aka Waco and events like that and the full
testimony we've posted up at infowars.com.
But I wanted to get her take on the other side about this unprecedented Diane Feinstein,
our video, still posted at drugsreport.com on the right hand side.
This video of Diane Feinstein saying, Mr. and Mrs. America, turn in your guns.
That's a quote.
Let's get that clip ready.
I want to play that for her.
She's also a talk show host on 590, one of my affiliates, one of our 140 plus.
We'll be right back, ladies and gentlemen, stay with us.
We'll be back.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver based products.
Our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two
ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well as our all natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and
leave the silver at the surface, but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the
natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the
skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver based products
are best for you.
That's www.silverlungs.com.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die?
Start purifying your water with ProPure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none
is ProPure and it's available discounted at infowars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified.
Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%.
Easy to set up and use.
It doesn't require electricity.
Purify water from lakes, streams, ponds, and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
ProPure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on ProPure, but if you add the promo code
water at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the East, but we are still in the eye of the perfect
storm.
The most devastating economic conditions since the Great Depression, America's worst drought
in agricultural history, and now the economic results of the presidential election.
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply.
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from E Foods Direct and I recommend you do
the same.
It's time to get your own supply from E Foods Direct.
I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food.
I'm taking control of my future and you're nuts if you don't do the same.
Go to efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex to find the specials and you can start with
a holiday gift pack that's normally $80, now under 50 bucks.
Remember, I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex.
Would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late?
400-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network and now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Representative Susanna Grasha Hupp, former representative.
She's a survivor of the Luby's massacre, some of her family was killed.
She famously testified before Congress to Chuck Schumer that, hey, our guns aren't for
duck hunting.
The full testimony's up at infoawards.com right now.
We just reposted it up there.
She said it's to protect us from you guys up there.
And I wanted to get her on the air because she was instrumental nationwide testifying
before legislatures everywhere.
Not just the Texas legislature that she later chaired committees on to get concealed carry-in.
And we've seen 25, 30% or more reductions in every state that's done it.
So she'll be joining us to the bottom of the hour here in just a moment.
Here is just a short excerpt of her testimony before Congress.
The Second Amendment is not about duck hunting.
And I know I'm not gonna make very many friends saying this.
But it's about all right, all of our right to be able to protect ourselves from all of
you guys up there.
Man, and boy, that was what back in the mid 1990s.
And here we are in 2013.
Great way to kick off the new year with a champion of liberty, who I've gotta say if
any one person got concealed carry-in, you can say what you want about it turning a right
into a privilege.
The point is, is that it put guns on the street in law abiding citizens' hands and the criminals
are keeping their heads down.
Violent crime down over 20% nationwide on average since then.
We've shown the new FBI statistics, except in areas where they've taken the guns, crime
is up.
Former representative, talk show host on 590 AM, you name it, best-selling author.
Mrs. Hupp, good to have you on with us.
Hey, happy new year to you, Alex.
Wow, I am excited.
What's your take on everything that's happening and the open calls now and the Feinstein bill
to physically make you turn guns in?
It's a scary thing, isn't it?
I've talked to a lot of friends of mine who, we all trying to talk big.
You hear the, from my cold dead fingers comments, but the truth of the matter is, if a bunch
of jack-looted thugs show up at my door and put a gun to my child's head and says, turn
over all your guns or else, I'm probably going to turn over my guns.
So I think it's really important and I think this is why so often revolutions are mostly
about young people and young people without extended families.
You know what I mean?
It's a scary world right now.
It certainly is, but there's 160 plus million gun owners.
If 1% fight back, that's 1.5 million soldiers.
I agree, most people are going to turn them in, at least in the first wave, but the tyranny
that follows is going to result in a civil war.
And if you notice all the branding of Obama as the new Lincoln and how he's going to kick
the butt of the states, it's pretty creepy.
It is, it's very frightening.
And when I talk about people turning in their guns, I think there are an awful lot of people
that are going out of their way to purchase guns that don't have a track record, that
can't be traced to them.
And those guns are going to be hidden and buried all over the place.
And we might be some of those people, Alex.
You and I are going to be the first doors that they knock on.
You're right.
We're going to make examples of people.
Why do you think, for listeners that just joined us, we have the club, Diane Feinstein
and others are saying, Mr. and Mrs. America, get ready to turn your guns in.
Why do I think she's doing that?
I think because she's absolutely clear that she has the backing of the president.
And she now has, I would say, 70% of the media firmly behind her.
I was actually sitting, getting a manicure a few days ago, and there was a lady kind
of across from me, somebody I didn't know at all.
And she got to talking about the guns and the shooting in Connecticut.
And she turned to me and said, well, I just think we should get rid of all the guns.
What do you think?
Of course, that was a mistake, right?
No, I took it very easy on her and I didn't tell her any of my background or anything.
And I simply said, well, you know, I've thought about it.
But it seems to me that not one single one of these mass shootings has ever occurred
where guns were allowed.
And she stopped and she kind of blinked.
And she got up and she went and washed her hands and then came back and sat down and
looked at me and she said, you know, I never thought about that, but you're right.
So I think there are an awful lot of people out there that you can't grab with statistics.
You can't grab with logic.
I think there are a lot of people out there that you have to put them in the position
of being, you know, as close as you can, put them mentally in the position of being completely
helpless and then ask them if they would rather have somebody with them, even if they choose
not to have a gun, if they would rather have somebody with them that knows how to use one
or not.
You know, even if they won't defend themselves, most people are willing to defend their child.
So I do my best to talk about that sort of thing.
I know it's hard for you to talk about it, but you do to save other lives.
And I've got to commend you again, as you know, people can pull up the uniform crime
statistics.
Since concealed carry became ubiquitous in most states, crime rates on average around
24 to 25%.
National, it's only about 20 because of some of the gun-free zones like Chicago and New
York.
But the Luby's massacre was a mass murder that took place October 16, 1991 in Killeen,
Texas, United States.
When George Hennard crashed his pickup truck through the front window, got to ban pickup
trucks, on a Luby's cafeteria and shot 50 people, killing 23, exchanged shots with responding
officers and then hid in a bathroom and fatally shot himself.
You were there, you lost your parents.
I know it's tough to talk about, but we've now seen fathers that lost children in the
last few shootings come out and say, don't use this to take people's guns.
But the media tries to ignore them.
You as a survivor, I mean, you more than anybody have a right to lay out the record.
Can you, for people that don't know, describe what happened and what would have happened
if you would have had a firearm?
Well, to try to keep it brief for you folks, my parents and I, I was about 31 I think at
the time, where I just dated myself.
My parents and I had gone to a local cafeteria and we were actually eating with the manager
of the cafeteria, the place was packed, it was bosses day, it was the day after payday,
middle of the day, beautiful day, and this guy drove his truck through the window, it
was a floor-to-ceiling window, and crashed into a number of tables and came to a jerking
halt, pretty much in the middle of the restaurant.
And of course you think it's an accident.
And we began to rise up to go help people they had knocked over and we heard gunshots.
I was on the passenger side of the vehicle and it was maybe 15 feet away from me.
My father and I immediately got down on the floor and put the table, turned the table
up on its side in front of us, my mom was down behind us, and the shooting continued.
I realized this was 1991 and these mass shootings weren't occurring back then, so it wasn't
the first thing that comes to your mind.
We were waiting for him to say something like, alright, everybody put your wallets up on
the table, or something like that.
But that didn't happen, he just kept shooting, and when he worked his way around the front
of the truck and he was working toward us, a full, I'm gonna say 45 seconds had passed,
and I realized he was just executing people.
And it just, 45 seconds, Alex, 45 seconds is an eternity.
And I did realize that I reached for my purse that had fallen on the floor next to me.
I thought, I've got it, I've got this guy.
I used to carry a gun in my purse illegally because an assistant VA out of Houston that
was a patient of mine convinced me to carry it illegally.
But I did like most people, you know, you think, eh, what are the odds, if I need a
gun it's gonna be if I break down on a back road somewhere.
It sure as heck not gonna be in a crowded restaurant in the middle of the day.
But my gun was 100 yards away in my car where I had begun dutifully leaving it.
So long story short, at that point, my dad started to break free from my grip and said,
I've gotta do something, I've gotta do something, he's gonna kill everybody in here.
And he made a run at the guy, and the guy just turned and shot my father in the chest,
again, I apologize, I'm trying to make it a short story.
No, it's important, thank you for sharing it.
The good news with that, my dad was mortally wounded, I mean, he had covered maybe half
the distance, he was seven, eight feet from me, but he was still alive.
The good thing about that was it made the gunman change directions and he had to go
off to my left instead of continuing directly toward me.
Somebody way at the back of the restaurant broke out on one of the windows back there
and began to escape through that window.
People were able to escape that way.
We were kind of up in the front corner and couldn't get out.
When I saw what I thought was the chance, the gunman had his back turned toward me,
I stood up, I grabbed my mother by the shirt collar, I said, come on, come on, we gotta
run, we gotta get out of here, and my feet grew wings.
And to circle it back around, my mom did not follow me out, and I didn't know that until
after, literally, I was outside of the restaurant.
She was staying with your dad, wasn't she?
The police officers later told me what happened to her, they said that, and a number of them
were patients of mine, and they took me and my family to lunch about a week later and
told us.
They said that when they got into the front, they saw a woman on her knees cradling a mortally
wounded man, and they didn't know who the gunman was.
And they saw this 30-something-year-old man walk up to her, they said, he put a gun to
her head, she looked up at him, put her head down, and he pulled the trigger.
And they said all they had to do was fire a shot into the ceiling, and this guy rabbited
to a back bathroom alcove area, as he said, exchanged a little gunfire with him, and then
put a bullet in his own head.
My parents had just had their 47th wedding anniversary a couple of weeks prior to this,
and it just didn't occur to me while I was running, mom, mom wasn't going anywhere
without dad.
So I was really angry, Alex, I was really, I was really angry, I felt very guilty.
I was very angry, and I know people think I made this up later, but you can check that
the newspapers from the second day, I said I was angry at my legislators, because they
had legislated me out of the right to protect myself and my family.
And you can say, well, Susanna, you could have missed.
Yeah, I could have.
Your gun could have jammed.
Well, okay, it's possible, it was a revolver, not likely, but it's possible.
But the one thing you can't argue with is it would have changed the odds.
I can't begin to tell you how frustrating it is to sit there and wait for it to be your
turn, and having no way, no means of defending yourself.
I can't imagine being in that position again and having my children or my grandchildren
with me and having no way of defending them makes me physically ill.
Well, we now have countless cases since you went public back in 91, 92, 93, where people
have at churches and everywhere else stopped gunmen.
Just happened down in San Antonio, it's just happened other places just since the Sandy
Hook shooting, and the media will not cover it nationally.
And we see these countless local news videos of gunmen coming in trying to shoot people
for no reason at shops and concealed carry folks that know how to use them, take them
out.
And I see the gun grabbers rushing in to try to ban guns right now, because they know the
gun culture and the self-defense culture is taking over society, all the top rated TV
shows.
Women out buying guns, liberal women's magazines show women with guns now, not because they
want guns, the liberal owners, but because they realize women have woken up.
They're losing, that's why they're launching this offensive against the Second Amendment.
Would you like to elaborate on that statement, do you agree or disagree?
I agree with you, but I do think that they see an opportunity here because of the Connecticut
shooting.
It's so hard for any of us to imagine that all those little children being just executed
like that, it's just, you want a way-
And they put the guilt onto us.
Have you ever seen such demonization of gun owners where they say, we're Klan, we're Nazis,
we helped kill those children when it was a gun free zone and the media advertising
crazies go to schools and kill people.
If anybody has blood on their hands, it's them.
Isn't that the truth?
That's something that I've advocated for for years is for teachers to be able to carry.
And of course, here in Texas, individual schools can make that decision.
My school does not allow the teachers to carry, but I can tell you that I know a few that
carry anyway.
They just keep their mouth shut and do it, thank God.
The bad guys, I don't know why people don't get this, bad guys like that want a high body
bag count.
They're gonna go where they think they can shoot as many people as possible without anybody
shooting back at them.
Nobody knows these cowards like you, no doubt your father saved your life.
Nobody knows these evil people like you, Susanna Hupp, a survivor of the Luby's Massacre, are
with us.
And really, the grandmother of the concealed carry movement, no doubt, not to use the term
grandmother like she's old, but she's the person that really started it.
Thank God and saved countless lives.
Why do these cowards always commit suicide as soon as the cops show up?
I mean, it just shows they really are ghoulish demons that they all act exactly the same.
You know, I'm trying to teach my children, I have two boys, 16 and 14, and I think society
in general tries to teach people that these bad guys are just misunderstood, or they've
had a hard life, or all the various of thundery excuses that you can come up with for them.
I mean, I've actually literally had people asking me, why didn't you try to talk the
guy down?
Like, really?
I mean, I can't even argue with that, it's such a stupid statement.
Yeah, just shot your dad in the chest, and then you're gonna go talk to him.
Let me go talk to this guy about his childhood.
What I'm trying to teach my children is that there certainly are criminals, I would say
the vast majority of criminals in the world that were created, they did have bad childhoods
and whatnot.
But there's also evil.
I honestly believe there is absolute evil that exists in the world.
That's my next point.
Have you noticed that with Son of Sam, Ramirez, the Night Stalker, Harrison Kleibold, Lanza,
and the guy that just shot the firefighters, they were all admitted devil worshipers.
Shouldn't we be profiling them?
I did not know that, but I'm not even slightly surprised.
Okay, maybe mildly surprised, but not shocked, have I passed?
It's incredible.
Evil exists, and I believe that you must do your best to stand between evil and innocent
evil.
And it doesn't mean, again, I want to make this clear, because I'll tell you what one
of my biggest fears is, Alex.
One of my biggest fears is that I'm gonna be in some position that I get shot and killed
by a bad guy, and I'm not able to get a round off for some reason.
And I'm so afraid that the other side is gonna say, see, her gun didn't help her.
And I've said it a million times, it's not a guarantee, it changes the odds.
It means you're not a helpless prey animal to be fed upon by devil worshipers and psychopaths.
At least I'm not gonna be an easy target, I'm gonna do my best.
I'm gonna do my best to bloody them.
They might take me out, but I'm gonna do my best to put them in the hospital, at the very
least.
Everybody's gonna know who the bad guy is.
Here's the headline, Daily Mail, it's also in AP.
I am the devil, former classmate reveals school gunman had online devil worshiping page as
childhood barber recounts how he never spoke and just stared at floors.
And that's the shooter of the firefighters with Lanza, it's the same story.
So this just goes on and on.
So all of them, devil worshipers, here it is, Satan worship, the Sandy Hook, on and
on and on.
Son of Sam, Night Stalker, list goes on and on, it's amazing.
In the time we have here, cuz I know you've gotta go, maybe you can do five more minutes
after the break to talk about your book, which I need to carry at the Infowars online bookstore
because I know it's so important.
We all need to reach out to the dumbed down people that really think turning their guns
in is gonna protect them.
But looking at Dianne Feinstein, have you seen the testimony in Congress where she admits
she has a concealed carry but doesn't want you to be able?
I have seen written quotes from it, but I have not actually seen it, no.
It's amazing, though.
I mean, how can they all have bodyguards and she can be worth 100 billion bucks, but then
we're not supposed to have guns?
I remember being on CNN or one of those shows when Rosie O'Donnell, there had been some
incident with one of her adopted children and a bodyguard protected the child.
And I went on the air and said, she must be horribly, horribly, feel awfully silly at
the moment because she's telling all of us to disarm and most of us don't have her kind
of money that we can hire personal bodyguards for our kids and she must be terribly embarrassed.
But I feel that way pretty much about Feinstein and most of them, it's just an elitist attitude.
It's okay for me, but it's not for you because I don't trust you.
Well if you notice, I've even got Christian Science Monitor admitting, I have an article
that our government's trying to restrict free speech online and going the way of China.
I've got an article after you leave us, we're gonna go over where top Georgetown professors
saying yeah, go ahead and kill old people, death panels.
I mean, they're not just going after the Second Amendment, do you see it as a big canary in
the coal mine that they are this open and brazen right now?
Here's what I really think, Alex.
I don't think Obama is the problem.
I don't think Feinstein is the problem.
I honestly believe that our public education system is the problem because those are the
people that are growing up to run for office that think socialism and Marxism is a good
thing.
They're the ones that grow up and vote for the Obamas and the Feinstein's.
So I truly believe, you know, you and I tend to attack this and a lot of partisans tend
to attack this at the top, you know, when we have to get so and so out of office or
into office.
And I really hope that the problem is down in the school system.
Have we crossed the Rubicon of becoming a collectivist society where they've got so
many people domesticated?
You know, they're like squirrels you feed in your backyard after a while, they don't
know how to go out and get their own food.
Yes, yes, and I was talking about this last night on the radio show, in fact, on the one
that I was filling in on in Austin.
Yes, I, unfortunately, I, I think we have hit the tipping point.
I and I think that's evidenced in this last presidential run.
I just think there are now more, you know, we were a little bit sheltered here in Texas,
because Texas is still a pretty Republican conservative.
I'll tell you what, I know you got to go, but we're gonna go to break, come back and
do five more minutes with us, and then we'll let you get back to work because I want to
finish up with the tipping point solutions and your book because there are ways to beat
this.
But it's just like in Poland, it's called non-compliance, we've got to do everything
we can before this becomes a shooting war.
We'll be right back with Susanna Hupp.
We're on the march, the empire's on the run, Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at Infowarsshop.com.
These are items that I did research on, that I personally use.
You've got the life straw, so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor hand-crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out
in the field.
Strategic relocation, third edition by Joel Skousen.
When disaster strikes by Matthew Stein.
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Hand-crank shortwave AM-FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at Infowarshop.com
and your purchase makes our Infowarshop possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you?
Infowarsshop.com.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other
harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
Get SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die?
Start purifying your water with Pro-Pure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none
is Pro-Pure and it's available discounted at Infowars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified, optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%, easy to set
up and use, doesn't require electricity, purify water from lakes, streams, ponds and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
Pro-Pure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on Pro-Pure but if you add the promo code
WATER at checkout you get an additional 10% off at Infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
Defending the republic from enemies foreign and domestic.
It's Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are back live and we're finishing up with an interview we're
doing with Representative Susanna Hupp, former representative survivor of the Luby's Massacre.
Our book is from Luby's, the legislature, very highly rated at Amazon in the reviews
and is really good for people out there who don't understand what's going on.
We either reach out to the domesticated Obama-noids or it's over.
And the collectivist are very arrogant.
She just said people in Texas or other more constitutional areas, where the economy by
the way is still operating cuz we're not socialists completely, are in a bubble.
We think, they'll never have government run healthcare, they'll never make us pay for
abortions.
They'll never take over the Catholic Church and make them pay for abortions.
It's all happening.
They'll never do this, they'll never do that.
Really they've done this in every other country.
They're following a model.
And they're powerful corporate interests that want monopolies.
They want a quasi-socialist system with a fascist system on top of it.
And there's also some hoaxing going on where they say this is a mandate for socialism cuz
Obama won again.
No, they ran a neo-con socialist Obamacare writing Mitt Romney.
So the fix is in is the problem.
Representative, I wanted to talk about your book some, but first, solutions.
If we have reached the tipping point of domestication, we know the solution is wait till it rots
and collapses like the Soviet Union.
Well that's gonna be authoritarianism.
I don't wanna be sent to the Gulag Archipelago.
How do we short circuit it before it gets really, really bad?
Well, you're not gonna like my answer.
I guess my answer is two-fold.
Number one, we truly, truly need to get into the school system and begin to re-teach what
made America great because they're not teaching it now.
They're teaching that socialism and Marxism is good.
What do you mean I don't like your answer?
I mean, I love, I mean, absolutely.
And look, the government's taken over.
It's time for us to do what the socialists did.
I think people should infiltrate government and do whatever you have to to get in there
to report on these people and sabotage these people.
Yes, yes, that's very well put.
Well, I said that you wouldn't like it because unfortunately, it's not a glamorous answer
and it's a slow task to make changes in the school system.
The second thing that you do brilliantly is teach people to be prepared.
And it used to be only us crazies that would stockpile food or stockpile water or ammunition
or whatever.
But now they actually have television shows about it.
It's not just crazies, it's not just people that are living for their front teeth.
But our grandparents all did that.
It's normal.
All mammals store some food.
I mean, even grasshoppers do it and they're insects.
I mean, you're crazy to just live day to day in some supermax prison-style grid.
Let me ask you this, then we'll talk about the book and let you go and hopefully get
you back soon.
I have a clip in my film In Game Blueprint for Global Enslavement.
And in it, it's you talking to the head of the psychiatry association.
And you say, why are 67% at that time of foster kids on psychotropics?
And you were heading up the committee and it was a big investigation.
And he says, they come from bad gene pools.
Well, A, that's what Hitler said.
B, they don't even do blood tests, quote, gene pools.
I mean, no, they grab kids from their parents and then drug them, as doctors have said.
What do you make of that?
That's not liberal drugging kids.
That's evil.
Yes, and in many, many, many cases, those children were on more than three psychotropic
drugs.
And many of them weren't even okay for children of the age that they were giving them to.
I'm deeply concerned with the drug culture.
And I don't want to, look, I don't want a bad mouthful of drugs.
Look, I just got off a run of antibiotics for a sinus infection, but there are good
drugs out there.
The problem is, this is one of the things that can be tricky in a free society.
We do have these enormous drug companies that push this stuff and actually get it wrapped
into the government system, where the doctors that are working on the foster kids, for instance,
have to follow a particular protocol in what drugs they use.
They can't deviate from that protocol.
So it's very interconnected and very difficult to unravel, quite frankly.
Well, that's right, in the public schools, it turns out, get more federal funding, the
more kids are, quote, special need on the drugs.
In fact, the WOAI investigation that spurred the state investigation, if you remember,
found that the national average was 67% of foster children are on psychotropics, and
the average child was on seven drugs.
Seven drugs.
Yeah, which is crazy.
I mean, that in and of itself is crazy.
And there is absolutely, my husband is a neuropsychologist, so I would go to him and use him for information
on a regular basis.
And you're right, unfortunately, there is a financial benefit to not only the school
system, but the parents.
There was a kind of a negative, basically, they would go in and a lot of them, not all
of them, but a lot of them would go in and say, well, this kid's creating a lot of problems
for me, he really needs to be on medication.
Somebody would put him on medication, and the foster family would get more money per
day because of it.
And then the medication makes them worse, so the answer is not get them off drugs, get
them on more.
They're eating Twinkies, they're drinking Cokes with caffeine, they're eating, I mean,
my children, if they get red dye or something in a candy on vacation, we let them eat it
or something.
They go nuts, don't they?
They go crazy.
And then it turns out those dyes have a drug effect.
The kids are bouncing off the walls cuz they should be eating steak and potatoes and broccoli
and exercising all day.
Instead, I mean, if I drank Cokes and ate Twinkies, when I come down off of it, I've
done it a few times, I wanna beat the hell out of people.
I mean, no wonder the-
Particularly young boys.
I mean, it used to amaze me to watch the teachers, they were taught to give the little boys time
out.
Instead of what they should be doing is telling them to go outside and run around with schools
five times.
Well, you know public schools first got rid of dodge ball, now most of them have banned
running.
So I mean, of course, young mammals, I mean, that'd be like drugging a puppy because it
runs around and chews on the other puppy.
Yes.
I mean, baby mammals all act the same.
Ma'am, you're amazing.
Thank you for your time and thank you for getting your testimony out there that the
answer is more guns, less crime.
Tell us briefly about your book.
I wrote that book for the average person to read and be able to make the arguments with
their neighbors and friends.
It's also a great book to pass on- You know who I really wrote that book for?
I wrote that book for a housewife that just aren't sure how they feel about guns.
You know, they're not into going out and blasting Bambi and they're just uncomfortable
with things that go make a loud bang.
And I understand that, I completely understand that.
And I'm a mother and I've been there, I understand, I'm not into going out and blasting Bambi
either.
But it's a quick, easy read and it's for those people.
Absolutely.
Well, you know, you've got two sons, I've got two daughters and a son and I love them
like life itself or more.
But it is really a good feeling now that my eight year old is shooting and hitting bull's
eye at 50 yards.
We haven't trained the four year old yet.
And it's such a good feeling that my girls are tough.
Because they punch me when we're playing and it really hurts.
And that they're not putting up with anybody trying to rape them or attack them.
And then I'm gonna defend the Second Amendment so when they go off to college or when they
get married and they live, some guy bust into their apartment or into their house to try
to beat them up or rape them, they're dead.
And that's real empowerment.
And it's not feminism, it's survival, it's basic common sense.
And as I said, our culture of liberty, the women's magazines, the Austin Chronicle's
been having articles about women's shooting.
Not because the Socialist Anti-American Chronicle, run by a horrible guy who I know, wants to
do that.
They're being forced to do that if people are gonna pick up their magazines.
And our culture of liberty and self empowerment is growing.
And so that's why the empire is striking back.
And your book breaks that down and I hope everybody gets it and gives it to women who
are anti-gun in their family or who are on the fence.
Thank you very much.
All right, we'll have a great week coming up and I always enjoy getting to hear you
on 590 AM when you're filling in.
God bless.
Thank you very much.
Happy New Year.
You too.
There it goes.
Our representative, Susanna Hupp, survivor of the Luby's massacre.
We're gonna get her back on in a few months.
Maybe even sometime have her come in and fill in.
She lives on there, Austin.
She does that for our local affiliate, just an amazing lady.
Boy, I tell you.
Ladies and gentlemen, I said that I would get into agenda 21 because I was really brainstorming
on it last night and this morning.
And how it ties into things, what the Obamacare means, what the death panels mean, what life
is really gonna be like.
Cuz I always mention this or that or say I'm gonna break it down and I've done some special
reports.
But then I get an hour and 43 minutes into this and I'm not so much exhausted as that
it's a feeling of I can't do this justice.
I can't do this justice.
So what I wanna do is I'm gonna go to your calls until eight after next hour, seven after.
And then I'll cover this for a segment and continue with your calls, pardon my New Year's
resolution.
And I want the crew in there cuz I don't have a quote producer that tells me what to do.
I kind of have radio bookers and a great crew that runs the TV and does research.
But I need you guys to make me that when I say I'm taking calls, get to them, get to
them quick, cycle through them.
Cuz it brings up a lot of really important angles and issues.
And I like taking calls.
Whenever I'm listening to rebroadcast, I'm like, I wish you'd take calls, Alex.
But again, it's just that I've got so much information I wanna get to you.
Agenda 21 is taking civilization and militarizing it against the people.
And it is the strangulation of humanity.
It is the scientific exterminism, an ultra-Hitlerian, incremental, scientifically controlled kill
grid.
And I'm gonna attempt to really talk about it and give you some examples and tell you
where it's going.
And remember, I told you 15 years ago the printer ink was tracking everything you do.
And putting where you bought the printer, what you did, a whole record of it on there.
I told you that 10 years ago smart meters were going in that would control your temperature
and track everything you do and be later used to charge you more.
And interface with all your appliances that all have spy tech being built into them.
Now it's mainstream news because it's ubiquitous.
See, they always say, that's crazy counting on you being ignorant when it's first going
in cuz they don't want you to resist it at that point.
But once it's ubiquitous, they go, yeah, we are listening to you with the NSA, all of
you.
Yeah, the NSA is tracking everything you do.
Yeah, we are reading what you say.
You know what, the post office is opening some of your letters.
You know what, yeah, okay, well, government apologizes for shooting kids up in Guatemala
with live syphilis.
We're sorry, but we're gonna keep doing it.
I mean, I sit here looking at all the admissions, these are not my opinions.
And then I go study, let me see who that bank chairman is.
Let's go see if he gives money to eugenics organizations.
You go look it up, population reduction funds, and Nature Conservancy, and Sierra Club, and
all these anti-human groups that claim they care about the Earth.
It's always the same.
There's only a few thousand of them, and they're all, all into the same thing.
All of them.
I can randomly pick some globalist calling for gun control and go find out they're calling
for the end of the First Amendment authoritarianism.
I mean, these are monsters who have a mesmerized population watching television all day.
The television and the false culture is like a black hole destroying the real world.
It's sucking it in and wrecking minds.
And there are people that really think television's their friends.
They're imaginary friends on their favorite show.
And they sit there and basically talk to the television, and they get sad when they give
them the cue to about the dead kids.
It's Sandy Hook, but not sad when somebody protests and jumps up during a meeting about
thousands of dead kids from military strikes.
And they're just programmable biological androids.
That's what the globalists call you.
They call you human resources programmable, and I'm not a programmable.
Let me tell you something, you psychopaths are the most programmable.
You sit there and look at a regular folks who are weak minded and childlike because
you got them when they were babies in front of the television.
And you think you're powerful because you're socially engineering people with subliminals
and all the rest of it.
I've studied psychopaths and their servant sociopaths and their mercenaries and the different
classes that serve them, different criminal classes that serve darkness because they get
to engage in their particular poison.
You guys are totally obsessive compulsive, if you wanna use that limited term.
It doesn't fully describe it, but it's a term people can get.
It's similar to that.
You guys are ritualistic.
You guys aren't alive.
You're not really creating, you're twisting.
You are not creating literature, music.
You are not creating art.
You are not creating beauty.
You are not.
You guys are missing out.
And a lot of you, it is from inbreeding and things.
There is such a thing as genetic psychopaths.
Most of them are genetic.
Royalty takes really aggressive, generally psychopaths are very manipulative dominance
and breeds them into psychopaths.
That's why you get these robotic classes that are just ready to do anything.
And they always like the same thing, black uniforms, burning cities, torturing children.
They all do it through, I mean, you studied history?
Any of you?
Every culture, black uniforms, burning children on fires, mass death.
Because good people don't have the sheepdog instinct to get in there and deal with these
people.
And by the way, we're a lot stronger and more inventive and powerful.
And by the way, we have levers that we don't enjoy crushing, we don't enjoy killing, but
we can do it a lot better than they can.
That's the thing, a lot of people get into evil because they feel weak.
They're not really psychopaths or sociopaths.
They get into evil believing it will give them power.
And then by example and modeling, they're able to do outrageous things, which is kinda
like building their self-confidence.
Honestly, just go take a Toastmasters, and I've never taken one of those, but I've read
about them, course for something if you wanna be confident, instead of going out and doing
evil things.
And those of us, see, evil people only have what they call evil.
And they do bad things and hurtful things for the power and the enjoyment.
The Bible says thou shalt not murder, and it's mistranslated as kill, cuz the whole
Bible's about go out and defend yourself, go out and kill the enemy that's attacking
you.
It's murder, premeditated, an innocent, knocking somebody on the head who's walking through
the path who's got a bag of food you want 3,000 years ago.
That's murder.
But to kill, to defend yourself is what God demands.
Because if you don't, the wolves take over when you act like a sheep.
So I'll come back, take a few calls in the next two segments, then get into agenda 21.
But you need to understand, folks, that you have innate power.
You have an entire electrochemical software system and all the instincts, and it's been
proven scientifically, the racial memories that are more just like essence data.
It's not like an actual exact memory.
You have all of this, you only have to access it.
You're not accessing your programming.
I mean, you ask God, the universe, whatever you believe it is, to help you be someone
who stands up for good.
You're also asking your subconscious to activate.
And then once you open the door, God can spiritually energize you, because you are a biological
android with a spirit.
This is an Earth suit, but you've got to open the door and say, okay, programming activated,
and then ask the creator of the universe, because God's for free will.
You've got to say, I'm ready.
You understand?
Give me the knowledge.
Please, for good.
I'm ready.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the president could obtain this world class healer.
Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally
occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune
cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VenusFly or order from Carnivora.com, that's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VenusFly or visit Carnivora.com.
Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
Hey there, Frank Bates here.
Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out 280 million Americans?
This is really scary stuff.
Bates experts warn that this odd device poses the gravest threat we've ever known.
In fact, just a few weeks ago, former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed
piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat.
I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up.
That's why my friend just created a free video at weirddevice.com that exposes this threat
and blows the doors off the conspiracy.
Go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover exactly what it is plus
discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack.
I'm not sure how long this video will be online, so go to weirddevice.com before it's gone
forever.
Again, that's weirddevice.com.
Hi, my name is Annette and due to menopause symptoms for nearly two years, I suffered
severe heart clashes which prevented me from sleeping all night.
It was so hard to work because I continued all day to have the hot flashes from hell.
I was exhausted and depleted.
After only three weeks on one world weight, I have no hot flashes and I'm sleeping normally
again.
I feel energized and strong.
This is an amazing product.
It is a little known fact that every single cell of your body is supposed to produce ten
percent of its protein content as glutathione, but due to toxicity and aging, it does not.
Could glutathione be a missing factor in optimal cell function for your entire body?
If you restore the optimal glutathione levels in your cells, especially your glands and
organs, then as a result, your glands and organs work better.
Imagine the quality of life improvement you might have.
To order One World Way, call 888-988-3325.
That's 888-988-3325.
Or visit oneworldway.com.
That's one world W-H-E-Y dot com.
The Genesis Communications Radio Network proudly presents the Alex Jones Show, because there's
a war on for your mind.
By the way, the petition to deport Piers Morgan has reached 114,000 right now.
I bet we can probably punch that up on screen for viewers.
It's also linked up at the drugsreport.com, or at least it was.
So now it's 100,139, since we printed this off a few minutes ago, another 100 or so signatures.
By the way, just to be clear, cuz my own crew thought this, they're all like, we didn't
see you on Piers Morgan last night.
I told the crew, I said, when Piers Morgan comes back from vacation, I'm supposedly on
his show the 7th, but I said, don't hold your breath.
I said that on air as well, so people may not have heard that right on air.
It's the 7th on there, and I bet they check it out.
I really could care less, it's not that big of an audience, but it would be an Internet
hit to go in there and obscure him.
And you'll hear him call me a pathetic person and stuff, that's just ridiculous.
Let's go ahead and go to John in New Hampshire, welcome, sir, thanks for holding.
Okay, Alex, Temple Warrior from New Hampshire.
I listened to you from the start when you started, and I know you made a lot of good
points with me, how I'm a former law enforcement official and now I'm a selectman in New Hampshire.
And the thing that got to me was we have to take back all these local town and city positions
and get back, take back our government.
So I ran for selectman, I was elected, and they stuck in, tried to sneak in that UN Agenda
21 into our town with a grant and all these promises, and I had been enlightened from
your show, and then when it came up, I questioned it, and naturally when I brought up anything
with the word UN Agenda 21, they thought I was crazy, but when it came down to the vote,
it was a split vote and my vote was a deciding vote and-
And by the way, you know that's all an act, they now say we're insane, Israeli citizens
can't own guns and teachers aren't armed.
It's a known fact they are, they just go, no, because we'd win the debate that Israel
ended its school shootings by arming the teachers.
So they go, instead of debating us on that, they go, no, Israel doesn't have guns.
So it's the same thing, they put out talking point manuals, it's even come out in the New
York Times on how to deal with you, to act like it doesn't exist.
That laughing at you and all that is part of the mind game, but again, you kept getting
the word out and all these masters owning things are authoritarian, they're designed
for any town, China and India and Mexico don't have these rules, the globalist all run those
countries, it's forcing all our industry out, it's a takeover.
I'm sorry, go ahead and finish your point.
So I came down to a split vote and I was the deciding vote and I shut it down, and you
would have thought I was Jack the Ripper, but I felt great that day and I told them
they're not gonna get it back as long as I'm on the selectman's board.
So did I hear you right that you were a police officer, now you've run and gotten into the
selectmen or city council, what a beautiful story.
And patriots, now I'm never a person for deception, I think you should be honest that you're a
libertarian or constitutionalist or whatever you call yourself, a liberty lover.
But I think it's good to get in, see they infiltrated us by acting like they were just
liberals when they're really authoritarians.
I think it's important to get our people in acting like we're not that threatening to
get in and then it's a lot easier to stay in, what's your take on that?
That's exactly what I did when I was first in town, some of the leftist organizations
invited me to state who I was and what I had in mind.
And I just yest them to death and let them believe I was a good person, which I am.
And then when the key votes came in town, we get a constitutional chief of police and
we just put in a great town administrator and I'm sure they're-
That's it, exactly, exactly.
And again, most of the mainline liberals are well-meaning, they're just helpless fools,
but again, exactly.
And then once you get in, you can educate them, we've got to use the enemy's tactics.
You are listening to GCN, visit GCNlive.com today.
You prepare by purchasing gold, food, and firearms, but if you don't have a home security
system, then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection.
When you're sleeping, who's watching out for intruders and spooks?
Check out SimpliSafe, it's a new do it yourself home security system that is completely wireless.
Go to GetSimplySafe.com.
SimpliSafe is independent and off the grid.
It runs on battery power, so even if the grid goes down, you're protected.
It's completely customizable, so you can use it in your home, business, boat, trailer,
storage unit, or shed.
SimpliSafe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes, so there's no
need to let a stranger into your home.
If you move or need to relocate, you can take this system with you wherever you go.
SimpliSafe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day, seven days a week.
Go to GetSimplySafe.com, that's GetSimplySafe.com.
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
And to quantify what I was just saying, I don't mean to use all their tactics, but you
got to know when to hold them, know when to fold them, know when to walk away, know when
to run.
I would have never gotten into Bohemian Grove if when I was questioned by the feds and others,
I didn't say, I'm with hillbillies.
And technically, that's the name of one of the clubs inside the Grove, and I guess I
am kind of a hillbilly, I'm from a bunch of East Texas blood, I mean, that's pretty hillbilly.
But the point is, it's all semantical, because this is a foreign occupying globalist force.
I think running for office and being open about the New World Order is a great way to
do it as well, just to educate people.
But knowing when to hold them, knowing when to fold them, when you're really trying to
get in and defeat the enemy, it's a complex issue.
Let's go to Brian in New Mexico, you're on the air, go ahead.
Thank you, Alex, for taking my call, and first of all, I want to wish you a Happy New Year
for your family.
You too, brother, God bless you.
My biggest concern, I think, is with the media.
There's a lot of evil and crookedness, people, you know, with their backroom deals and such.
But the media who knows it and perpetuates it and misguides people, I think is the key
problem that we're facing, not even the technical brainwave changing patterns of TV and such.
All the advertisements are there to make you feel fragmented, broken, weak, and if we don't
use the right toothpaste, we're not going to be able to do whatever, you know, we want
to do.
We are incredibly powerful beings, and yes, we are being drugged and manipulated in order
that we don't tap into our greatness and our power.
But even in the most drug-down, mentally deficient person, there is a spark that the globalists,
I think that's what they're ultimately afraid of, is a few thousand people have taken control
over the whole population of this planet, and they do it subconsciously.
They can't physically control us, at least not yet, so they do everything they can to
make us feel, you know, like we're worthless, but we are incredible beings.
Just last year, I've been producing a television show, a public access TV show here in Albuquerque,
and through backroom deals with the corrupt mayor and the city council, basically they
gave control to a for-profit group that is now censoring all live things, and they're
not allowing any controversial topics, so I'm basically out of a viewpoint, or an outlet
to express my viewpoint, but still just talking to people day-to-day, you never know how just
the simplest conversation will have huge ripples.
Going back to the gun thing, I was at the dog park, and some guy was saying, well, we
don't need guns, and he's going, brrr, you don't need that to hunt deer.
I said, first of all, you don't have a gun, or you would know that you can't hunt deer
with it, you can't get an automatic weapon, but they're in this mindset of what they see
on television, and really, I think the biggest thing that people need to do is get rid of
their television, or if they do watch it for research or whatever, know how they're being
manipulated, and really spend more time with your kids, talk radio, just more real life
things is what I think this population really needs.
Yeah, that's why they ain't talk radio, is that it's not scripted, especially shows like
this, but even mainline talk radio is not scripted compared to mainline globalist type
propaganda.
But all over the country, they're trying to shut down access TV, people should use it
while it's still there, people should defend it.
They tried hard to keep me off of it, it's a great way to reach locals and organize things,
but there's other ways, most AM and FM stations are begging for people that wanna come in
into an hour or two on the weekend.
So do a YouTube channel first to show that you can talk, and then use that to say, hey,
here's my local internet show, I do local news, and volunteer to come in and say, and
I'll try to get sponsors, and then you can be a salesman as well, just on spec.
And most stations, if you're well-spoken at all, will give you a weekend show, and then
you're reaching a lot of people, then you start telling folks about your show, you get
them tuning in, then there's a buzz, pretty soon you're filling in for the weekday show,
pretty soon you got your own weekday show, pretty soon you're syndicated, pretty soon.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth-friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com, or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package, and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now, or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars, and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com, or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarshop.com.
These are items that I did research on, that I personally use.
We've got the LifeStraw, so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor Hand Crank Generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out
in the field.
Strategic Relocation, third edition by Joel Skousen.
When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein.
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Hand Crank Shortwave AM-FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com,
and your purchase makes our Infowars possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you?
Infowarsshop.com.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu, and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold, and food poisoning, and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day, while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases, such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus, and
other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
The councils of government, we must guard against the accusation of unwarranted influence,
whether sought or unsought, by the military industrial complex.
In Dallas, Texas, three shots were fired at President Kennedy's motorcade in downtown
Dallas.
The first reports say that President Kennedy has been seriously wounded by this shooting.
It is a big idea, a new world order.
It was almost as if it were a planned implosion, it just pancakes.
Either you were with us or you were with the terrorists.
I also believe that a lot of gun owners would agree that AK-47s belong in the hands of soldiers
not in the hands of criminals.
Guns will be caked and no one will be able to be armed, we're going to take all of them.
For many of the police and guard troops, it is an uncomfortable job to do this in an American
city.
Global governance at last, is it one world the central bank is in charge, but aren't
we all just living and dying for what the central banks do?
And for me, give me liberty or give me death!
Ladies and gentlemen, I want to break down just a snapshot of the premeditated evil that
is Agenda 21 implemented.
And then we'll go to your phone calls continuing on this live first day of January 2013 transmission.
But I want to read a quote here of Oliver Wendell Holmes, a Supreme Court Justice, taxes
of the price we pay for civilization.
And that is what the collectivist will always put in your face when you come out and point
out that we are having our basic liberties and freedoms eradicated.
Here is another headline, Georgetown Law Professor, scrap, archaic, idiosyncratic and downright
evil, those are quotes, Constitution.
And that is a top Georgetown Law Professor in the New York Times saying that, Louis Michael
Seidman, and of course, a big Obama supporter.
We have other articles up at infullwars.com that are just snapshots into how all of this
works.
Here's one by Kurt Nemo, Democratic operatives crank up death panel talk following Obama
win and put out their twisted graphs showing how much US healthcare costs versus other
countries.
And when you go read the article by George Soros operative at Slate, their headline is
the case for death panels.
You hear the same talking point, the case for killing Granny.
And of course, we have the clip as well from people out there like the host of the HBO
show Bill Maher, where he says more death is what we need, get rid of more people.
But then he says turn your guns in for the poor 20 dead children.
They can selectively turn it on and selectively turn it off.
This is all agenda 21.
Let me explain how collectivism has worked in every country and why the true robber baron
elites in the last 150 years or so have put their full weight behind it.
A, it makes people dependent, B, the globalist always exempt themselves internationally from
the laws they put on people in subsectors.
What national sovereignty they allow to continue, they play off against the other nation states.
And in the White House Science Czar's book, Ecoscience, you can read it online, it's free,
close to 1,000 pages long.
And in all of their other publications, they openly talk about how they're going to set
up a government control system to make you dependent on government.
And to quote, have a police state like China, that's Dr. Bianca at UT who calls for 90%
of us to be exterminated by an airborne release of weaponized airborne Ebola.
They all say the same thing.
In fact, guys, I don't see it over there on the bookshelf, Ecoscience is a big giant white
book.
It's always been over there.
You guys go see what's there.
I think Aaron's here today, if not, go back and get it, cuz the reason I'm staring is
I'm wondering where's my book?
It's always been over there.
You guys can walk in front of the cameras, I don't care, I just don't see it.
Very hard to get a physical copy of that nowadays.
The point is, ladies and gentlemen, is this is a fact we're talking about.
And Agenda 21 has to be dealt with because it is a system of turning off the society.
What do you do when the civilization and the government is a purely predatory group?
And that's the norm throughout history, who have taken tyranny and codified it into a
political system where they, with scientific expertise through insurance models and other
systems, go after you and even actuary out the implosion of the society in orchestrated
systems.
Thank you, they found it, it was under my desk.
We did a video breakdown on this with Webster Tarpley, where he called the views in this
book ultra-Hitlerian, titled what the elites master plan for global extermination.
It's free online, it's an emergency SOS to everyone.
And here's the problem, we have over 100 books, we ought to do a review of these books sometime
over an hour just reading quotes, where it's all the same thing basically plagiarized and
repeated over and over again.
I don't know who plagiarized too, but sometimes it's word for word.
It's kind of like the Bible, there's a hundred different versions, but a lot of it's pretty
much the same.
I mean, it's amazing.
And they set themselves up as the saviors of the world in the name of tyranny.
They're the saviors of the world, and now they're gonna kill you, they're gonna dumb
you down, they're gonna cut off your resources.
When really it's the parasitic establishment saying, France will now go without lights
at night because everything's collapsing.
They're gonna turn the lights off in Australia at night.
Major cities in the US aren't gonna have lights and your smart meters are gonna charge you
more during the day for electricity.
And then you go read their own books, they say, we use too much energy, we need to make
people more frugal.
It's altruistic to be poor, it's beautiful to live under austerity, you go to Whole Foods
and half the magazines say it, how sexy it is to be poor.
And it's not being sold to make you get back to the earth and actually be self-sufficient,
that's one thing.
No, it's the opposite.
They put everything in to make you where you can't be self-sufficient, but then come and
cut your resources off.
And then say you're gonna work even harder in a 250 square foot apartment with your whole
family to where you can't take care of yourself even though you have two jobs, so you get
a supplemental government card with big robotic farming and manufacturing operations with
robots giving you goods you need to survive.
This is the plan, show that you're forced to take inoculations, I mean, they say in
all their publications that they're going to put all of us that don't take the shots
and don't do this in ghettos.
And then just like Malthus wrote 200 and something years ago, they're going to pump pathogens
in to kill us in the ghettos.
They say we're gonna put you in ghettos if you won't go along with all this and then
there's gonna be some outbreaks and then you actually read deeper they go we're gonna release
it on you.
I mean, this is a nightmare where they're hunting us and that's what happens in corrupt
psychopathic civilizations is that corrupt elites get into control who are ruthless and
they make a sport and a game out of incrementally shutting down the society.
But they take their time cuz they enjoy their work, but also so that you never struggle
out of the net.
And they're openly now saying if the IRS run by foreign banks says you haven't paid your
taxes, no judge, no jury, no due process, your car is not gonna start.
All the new cars with kill switches built into them electronically is basically a cell
phone component, all the new cars.
Not just the black boxes in them, but other kill switches that's on record.
All printers, they have a record of when you bought it, who you were, they just turned
them off.
Your printer will turn off, your computer will stop working, you're gonna be face scanned
off the cameras.
The computer won't turn on unless the camera is uncovered and unless the face scan authenticates
when you turn it on.
If you try to go to the store to buy food, even with cash, cash will still be there.
It's just the face scan instant, this is already going in everywhere, by the way, told you
this 15 years ago because MIT said it was the Pentagon plan for total control.
Now it's in, remember all that'll never happen, that's fair mongering.
Face scanning to go to college, forced inoculations to go to college, no law, they just make you
do it.
They say it's policy.
Total control and then lots of mindless entertainment and peer pressure dumbing people down while
your neighbors are dying of cancer and your kids brain damage from shots.
And you've got all these health problems even though you supposedly eat healthy and exercise
all the time and everybody's got asthma and allergies.
And the cancer rates gone up almost 3,000% for adults, it goes up 10,000% like it already
is for kids and nobody asked why it's happening.
And they all talk about how they're going to kill us with the cancer and how they put
the stuff in the water.
And you sit here and read stuff they wrote in the 70s and it's happening now.
And you're like, hey, you go up to the cops and say, hey, don't you want to fight the
new war?
They're like, I got a uniform, I feel powerful.
I'm like, do you have any kids at home that are retarded?
Well, yeah, actually I do.
Do you know they did that to you, chances are, I really don't care.
See, it's learning how to love your own destruction, Saul.
You know what happens to your digestive health around the holidays?
Right.
Unusual schedules and foods you don't normally eat can cause upset stomach and indigestion.
But you can prepare your digestive tract with ProEM1 Probiotic Cleanse from Terriganix.com.
ProEM1 is all natural and made with certified organic ingredients.
It contains no genetically modified ingredients or preservatives and has no animal products,
wheat, soy, dairy or gluten.
ProEM1 does not require refrigeration, so you can take it with you over the river and
through the woods to grandma's house.
ProEM1 supports a healthy, regular digestive system, supports weight loss and improves
absorption of food nutrients.
Improve your digestion and keep off those extra pounds with ProEM1 Probiotic Cleanse.
Call or click Terriganix.com, spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X.com.
Toll free, 866-369-3678, that's 866-369-3678.
Terriganix, life's getting better.
Hi there.
My name is Frank Bates.
What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble.
I just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are, incompetent line crooks that
are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high.
Some have called this a conspiracy.
Others have called it a cover-up and you will be shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy
goes.
My video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them
and how you can beat them too.
Watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patrons have already seen in
the last three months.
Go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect
your home.
Go watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down.
Again, that's 123coverup.com.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the president could obtain this world-class healer.
Now 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally
occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune
cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VENUSFLY or order from Carnivora.com, that's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VENUSFLY or visit Carnivora.com.
Protect your immune system, it's the only one you've got.
Quantitative easing, unemployment at depression levels, Europe financial system falling apart,
China getting out of U.S. Treasuries.
At the end of 2008, the time of TARP, the national debt was at 11 trillion gold trading
around $850 per ounce.
Close to 2012, the national debt exceeded 16.4 trillion, gold doubled to $1600 per ounce.
The 20 trillion threshold for the national debt is inevitable.
Politicians in Washington have a ferocious appetite for spending and stimulus.
What's worse, a printing press to finance.
100 years ago, we had a gold standard to limit this madness, but now you have to adopt your
own gold standard.
Don't be fooled with paper promises.
Get Midas Resources 10 Reasons to Buy Gold free by calling 800-686-2237.
Understanding the gold and silver market may be the only insurance you could have to avoiding
the next economic crisis.
Call 1-800-686-2237 and order your free copy.
Again that's 800-686-2237.
You know a lot of people see videos produced in partnership with the British government,
the UK government, for plannedopolis and it's where everybody lives in the ghettos that
won't accept total control.
Everybody else is controlled by central computers.
Nobody's allowed to have cars but the elites.
And people would see these videos and think it was a joke.
But this is what they really plan.
And when you've got over 100 books written by top globalist, talking about how they're
soft killing us, and talking about how once they get us in the compact cities, they can
then wipe out the third world, the people in the compact cities will then beg the government
to give them even more control.
And then they're planning to wipe out the people in the mega cities.
And they sit there and they brag about all this and you're sitting there reading psychopaths
telling you what they're gonna do, in many cases not even veiled.
And then you go out to the public and you go, hey, Europe's got death panels.
And people go, that doesn't exist.
I heard you're a liar.
You're like, no, let me show you a video clip or let me show you their own book.
No, I don't believe that crazy.
Now that they get healthcare in, government healthcare, they're like, yeah, of course
there's death panels.
And here's how the trap of collectivism works to get you into this system, okay?
I was just looking at plannedopolis where the government decides the route of where
you're gonna go to allow you to leave your house.
You have to get the computer to authorize it, that it's been approved.
I mean, this is how totally sick these people are.
And again, they think you're so rudderless now that they put out classic authoritarianism
with a high-tech icing as if it's a good thing.
But here's how collectivism works.
They say, okay, everybody pays for everybody else's healthcare now.
So healthcare costs are too high, cuz when you put government money into something it
drives up the price.
And so we're gonna say what you can eat and how much you've gotta exercise and that you
can only eat meat once a year, which they're openly announcing under the UN World Food
Council.
I'm showing their UN video right now on screen for TV viewers.
I mean, you cannot make this up.
It's just unbelievable, folks, to see how dumbed down the public is.
They have no idea how much trouble they're in.
They're already jacking the food, the water, everything, and bragging about it.
And the trap works that once they say, well, things are collectivized, well, I'm paying
for it, so I say how much you're gonna weigh.
And they use an example of a 700-pound woman on welfare and say there ought to be rules.
But then you find the rules, say 860 calories for breakfast and lunch, and then another
500 for dinner, which is basically starvation level.
And if you're 1% above their fat index, the state takes your kids.
I mean, you read what they're gonna push, it's unbelievable.
And parents can't pack school lunches, and that's already rolling out.
I mean, just three years ago, I was reporting on them not letting people pack their own
lunches in Chicago and other areas.
People didn't believe me, and now it's going in everywhere.
I remember 15 years ago reporting on them banning dodgeball, people didn't believe it.
Now schools everywhere don't even let you run at recess.
It's total prison control.
And so now, and I've got articles breaking this down, they come out in all these George
Soros-connected outfits like Slate and have their operatives, in this one case, say the
case for death panels in one chart.
You guys punch this up on screen.
And it shows a skewed and manipulated chart to begin with, because they're showing end-of-life
care, specifically not overall healthcare, percentage of GDP.
And they don't have family in healthcare, they haven't researched it.
They're here deceiving people.
And it's the same line Bill Gates puts out that will play after the break where he says,
kill granny, hire ten teachers.
They don't explain to you that the insurance companies owned by foreign banks have set
this up, that when you've got insurance, it's three to four to five times more than if you
didn't have insurance, depending on the hospital.
Sometimes if you don't, it's three or four or five times more.
You see, it's all a scam.
I had a friend's mom get bit by a rattlesnake on Town Lake here in Austin, on the edge of
Town Lake.
And because they had top of the line insurance, and because they knew that they were wealthy,
they charged them $300,000.
They negotiated it down, I think they said $170,000.
And she went to the hospital, didn't have a problem, gave them antivenom that costs
like $50.
But because they didn't negotiate it, they tried to charge them $300,000 because they
had top of the line insurance and were worth just buku money.
That's how this stuff operates.
I have insurance, my fingers cut off, I go to the hospital, illegal aliens are going
in front of me for an hour.
No insurance, no nothing, not even checking their names, your God, your God, your God,
you're here to bankrupt the system.
You want to come and have a free baby, boom, it's paid for.
But citizens, you can't get healthcare even when you have the insurance, and that's how
it is in England.
I've watched the C-SPAN debates in British Parliament, where you wait 18 months for an
operable brain tumor that isn't operable in one year, stay with us.
We're on the march, the empire's on the run, Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
It's me.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die?
Start purifying your water with ProPure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research, and the best gravity filter out there bar none
is ProPure, and it's available discounted at infowars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified, optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%, easy to set
up and use, doesn't require electricity, purify water from lakes, streams, ponds, and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
ProPure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on ProPure, but if you add the promo code
water at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Prepare to enter the secret of world of emergency dictatorship, body scammers, sound cameras,
citizen spies, stage terror and cameras on every street corner.
It's only the beginning of the new world order's hellish plan.
The police state isn't coming.
It's here.
Secure your copy today at infowars.com or see it online in the highest quality at prisonplanet.tv.
There's a need for a new world order, but it has different characteristics in different
parts of the world.
Live from Austin, Texas, broadcasting worldwide, it's Alex Jones.
So you've got these poor people out there, US citizens, they can be Hispanic, black,
white, you name it.
They don't know under the Hippocratic Oath and the entire history of Western medicine
that a third of the healthcare a doctor provides as an honorable profession was to be free.
Free.
And then the wealthy were supposed to give endowment and money to tax-free hospitals.
This is just a window into agenda 21.
The Rockefellers by the 20s start taking over medicine.
They are the biggest owners and controllers in their tax-free foundations of the charity
hospitals.
They don't tell you it's charity hospital when you go in it.
So they're tax-exempt, but they run a money-making operation.
And we had a crew member, he was a contractor for me six, seven years ago, probably gonna
die of Crohn's disease.
He'd been kicked off insurance, couldn't even get it.
And I had to argue with him.
I said, I know you've been to 10 hospitals, 15 doctors.
You're losing weight, basically go home and maybe die.
I said, listen, I know that you have to go in and explain and show them your financials
that you can't get insurance.
And there's charity care.
He said, I don't believe you that I've gone in and told them this and they tell me it
doesn't exist.
And I said, listen, you gotta keep doing it.
And I was just talking to CJ out there about years ago.
He looked into this to help somebody he knew for charity care with dental stuff.
And by the way, my dad manages 18 dental offices, okay, I happen to know about this.
And now these big conglomerates will tell the dentists, don't tell people about this.
They don't do the Hippocratic oath anymore for about 20 years, do no harm, Hippocrates.
So under Obamacare, they're getting rid of charity care.
And they're making everybody go buy insurance even if we can't afford it.
And now it's gonna double the premiums this year, that's Bloomberg and AP reporting that.
And then it lets the government control what health care you get through the death panels.
And they use an example of an old lady who's gonna get a million dollars of care, and that's
all jacked up in a bad example, a cherry picked example, to say you're gonna lose your job
as a teacher now cuz she's gonna get health care.
Well, see next, you're gonna lose your job if we give this 65-year-old person an eye
surgery.
And it's all this idea of the pie is one size, cuz the globalists say within just ten years,
they already have this, they'll have robot machines that for $100 can sit there and give
you an eye surgery to correct your vision.
Life extension is gonna be totally cheap.
They've gotta bring us back into a dark age for the general population, except for what
they call megacity or city-state reservations, high-tech reservations.
This is now being announced.
People are like, how did you know this 15 years ago?
They wrote books about it, non-fiction.
It's all planned.
I don't know how else to explain this to you.
And you've got these fools waddling around going, I want my old on the phone, I want
my free health care.
And I was just talking to CJ about how, yeah, he found in Austin, the only places that advertise
charity care were in Spanish.
And they're getting endowment money, they're getting government grants, taxpayer money.
It's not supposed to run like that.
You got a hospital that has regular care, regular prices.
They look at how much you make, and it goes on a scale.
And then the doctors, like Ron Paul did for a decade, he would go two nights a week and
work at the poor hospital for $2 a night.
And that was customary, cuz that would pay for your food and gas, because he was a real
servant.
He got into it under the Hippocratic oath that you were taught as a physician, you're
doing this to serve people the highest calling, to wash people's feet.
It was Christian, ladies and gentlemen.
It was Christian, the first hospitals were the hospitallers, Christian sect.
Before, just go die, or go to the local medicine woman.
And so that's the issue, is that you are meant to provide the care.
You are meant to, let's say if you're having to get people crowns and stuff, you're supposed
to call up companies and go, we'll give you all our business for crowns.
But are you gonna provide us a certain percentage of free stuff so we can give it to the poor?
She used to, everybody just did that, understanding it's what you had to do.
Now that's all gone, churches are gone.
They're now 501c3, it's all gone.
So again, they come out and say, taxes are what you pay to have a civilization.
That's actually not true.
Local taxes are what you do, you locally agree on some taxes if there's a big problem, a
special problem.
Or hey, we wanna build dikes to expand our shipping area, like the Dutch, and then locally
you vote and you pay to do it.
And then those jobs get paid locally to merchants and for people to expand the building of it.
But globalism is everything to these development zones.
I mean, they all wrote books about it, Rollerball, James Caan in the 70s, there's a fiction movie
about this where you've got Energy City, Manufacturing City, Computer City, Military City, all corporate
cities run by the same guys where the corporate super elite land in these jet copters and
they want the top Rollerball world champion's wife.
And why?
Because they're jealous of him and it's an exercise of power.
This actually happened in Rome and other cultures, they would come to the top, sports heroes,
you name it, say, I want your wife, and you had to give it to them.
Folks, this stuff happens over and over and over again.
What Prema Noctu, where they would in the Middle Ages come and demand your wife on the
wedding night.
This stuff has happened, that's what the TSA down your pants, all of it is an exact historical
blueprint with a high tech overlay.
And so they get you into the cities, they do all this, and look at this commenter in
our article, Democrats crank up death panel talk following Obama win.
And I'm gonna play this clip here in a minute, but look at this commenter, he was commenter
number 30, printed this this morning, it's a lot more comments now.
I have to agree with Bill Gates on this one, the American people cannot afford to spend
1 million to keep a terminally ill patient alive in their later years.
Someone who is 80 years old has lived a long life, and they also say kill babies up to
age three now.
We cannot print money forever, and music will stop sometimes.
The analogy of laying off teachers is a good one, because we need to focus on the children
which are the only hope that we have for the future.
Man, that is a classic eugenic statement, that is carousel Logan's run, my mother's
in that movie, by the way.
The point is, is that she never tried to be in a movie, one of her friends was going to
be in Logan's run and she's in it a couple times, find those clips and play, it's pretty
interesting.
The point is, is that when you hit 30, they kill you, they send you up in a gladiatorial
event, a laser beam blows you to bits.
All these things are in your face, Zardosh, where there's an elite that lives forever
with high technology.
And they have compact megacities where they then send out hunter killer drones to go out
and kill the wild humans so their populations don't go up too high.
I think you heard that, it's called Hunger Games.
They're throwing it in your face over and over again, and it all has been written about
200 years ago by Malthus, picked up 160 years ago by Galton, put out 100 years ago by HG
Wells, who wrote scores of nonfiction books, I happen to have read them.
In the movie Things to Come that came out what in the 30s, we guys find Things to Come,
they've got B2 bombers, bat wing bombers of the world government flying around blowing
up the holdout nation states and attacking gun owners.
And it's clearly American gun owners being killed in the book and the movie.
When do you write Things to Come in the 30s?
Like in 1901, he wrote a book where they had atomic weapons.
They already had the equations to build atomic weapons in the 1830s, ladies and gentlemen.
They are suppressing all of this stuff and they think they're God.
And agenda 21 is not to help you.
They take model cities, take the building restrictions off, take the taxes off to build
all a bunch of high rises and make them beautiful and make them sexy.
Austin is the world model of agenda 21.
You already take a great first class city, great people, low taxes, everything, build
it all fancy and say this is agenda 21 like a piece of cheese on a rat trap to bring the
rat in so it claps on his head.
Cheese smells good, cheese looks good.
And by the way, sometimes rats get really smart.
An old trick, an old wives tale trick, and I've had to do it, drop a few other pieces
of cheese on the ground lining up when they start seeing other rats get hit or mice get
hit by the trap and get clapped.
They stopped going and taking the cheese with the peanut butter.
Well, you know what you do?
You start putting other foods out because they associate the smell of that food with
getting killed.
Try this, does this, like the devil's always got this different sin.
That didn't work?
How about this?
Is this the lever I find to move you?
Well, if they stopped doing that, if you've killed 10 of the rats, you got to, they're
crapping in your attic, make stinking your house up.
What do you do next?
It happens to anybody who lives in the country.
You dribble a few pieces of cheese out on the floor knowing they're gonna eat a couple
pieces and think this is good.
This is good.
I'm gonna get that last big piece, bam, you're dead.
Boom, you're dead.
Kill you and your rat family.
You don't buy his DVD.
It's an inside joke, one of my favorite videos out there.
All right, continuing here, ladies and gentlemen, I said I'd go to your phone calls and I need
to.
See, I could talk for 10 hours about Gen 21.
I haven't even gotten into all the evidence.
It's diabolical.
And I mean, here's an example of the system and how evil it is.
Did you know they're announcing in the United States if you are a sperm donor, they're going
to give your information over and make you pay child support?
That's a Gen 21, everything's a con game.
Sperm donor forced to pay child support to lesbian couple despite giving up parental
rights to the baby before she was born.
It turns out the women broke up and the woman went into the state.
And guess what?
The woman don't have to pay.
You gonna pay, Jack.
See, it's all about injustice.
All about injustice.
See, cuz he's a family man and produces and has some money.
You gonna pay.
And that's why they're racing to shut everything down because once they shut it down, they've
got you.
And, my gosh, we're going bankrupt.
We need to kill old people.
And yeah, are there doctors that greedily know they've got a brain dead woman or man,
79 years old, and they'll do double hip replacements and put 12 stints in their heart and do a
brain surgery?
Yep, and it's up to the state board to prosecute those people, not the feds who are ten times
more corrupt.
See, they can always point at little local corruption.
There are million dollar cases where they go and take somebody who can't be saved and
sit there and do this.
But that's why you can't have a free country that's not moral.
Rob Jacobson was talking to me during the last break.
And he said, why can't we arm teachers, but we're gonna arm cops and trust them?
And my example was, well, what about not arming pilots?
You trust them to fly this giant, multi-ton, giant, 100-ton aircraft, giant missile, tens
of thousands of times the power of a handgun or rifle, but you don't trust them to have
a gun in the cockpit.
Cuz the message is you can't protect yourself and you can't take care of anything.
And that's what a Gen 21 is, is the electronic kill grid, an attack on all civilization in
the name of a new civilization.
Because the globalists can't let us chart the course of technology in a good direction
because it will empower us to a level that will transcend the ancient psychopath guilds
that set up predatory subunits and prey on their own species.
We have decadent, degenerate, cancerous subspecies, homo sapiens psychopathicus, I don't know
what you wanna call it.
We must transcend them by knowledge and teaching and understanding.
Instead, we're letting these people play God because we don't crave being in charge, we
give the world to them.
You must first get over your fear and then you must move against the enemy or there's
no future.
You think it's fun to get up on the nightly news last night and have Stuart Rhodes say
the things he said on air?
It's very serious.
He's a serious person and so am I.
Now this isn't a game, this isn't a drill, this isn't a joke, this is the real deal.
You're being targeted.
They learned with Hitler, he moved too quick.
They know how to kill you quietly and softly now and they've got all these little subsets
of criminals.
They even rate in computer systems, mid-level minions and what type they are and their psychological
breakdown.
It's all there in the giant globalist NSA data banks and they place the different psychology
types in different formations, all because they have the fruits of our labor.
And soon they won't need the fruits of our labor because of robotics.
But they're gonna use the robotics in farming and manufacturing to first make us purely
dependent where we'll do anything to get those bobbles and trinkets of rank and social standing
but also survival.
And then all the trinkets we're given will have a backdoor control to dehumanize us and
track us and in the darkness bind us.
And so we must understand that they're gonna go, you're right, we can't trust pilots to
fly planes.
That's why they're robotic, who programs the robot.
We're entering a psycho world run by technocrats, you're in a science fiction movie.
And let me tell you, Gangnam style, I mean, all that stuff is rhythmically designed to
distract you, to divert you, all the little goofy programmed world where everything's
fun.
Everything's funny, don't worry, it's all fun, it's all good, government loves me.
It's a fraud.
They're not gonna stop just killing the old people.
They're gonna kill you and they're already killing you.
And they're already introducing the idea of, all of Africa just died from that airborne
Ebola or that mouse box.
We've gotta lock down our cities, thank God we're safe.
And yeah, yeah, well, you've retired now and we don't need you anymore, you're obsolete
so we're gonna get rid of you.
That's actually the plan.
Let's go to Bill Gates talking about it, here it is.
Bill Gates breaking it down, ladies and gentlemen.
We had a tricaster heart attack, all day we've been prepared to play this.
This is a trade-off society is making because of very, very high medical costs and a lack
of willingness to say, is spending a million dollars on that last three months of life
for that patient, would it be better not to lay off those 10 teachers and to make that
trade-off in medical costs?
But that's called the death panel and you're not supposed to have that discussion.
So you...
Of course...
Is it more interesting than you just said, would you just, the last three months in life
for one person or something, because we haven't had a discussion of how to allocate that money,
it means we lay off three teachers to do so.
I mean, in other words, we haven't had this type of allocation.
We're making that trade-off because of huge medical costs that are not examined to see
what...
That's enough.
And then you let a guy whose dad, it was the head of Planned Parenthood, an open eugenicist,
so is Bill and his wife, you let a guy run your healthcare.
The mistake we made was letting government and foreign corporations take over the healthcare
and now they can totally engineer us.
And I was talking to CJ during the last break, he'll come back and talk about it, about the
illegal aliens are the only one that get charity care now because they're a client group meant
to drive down the wages here domestically, just like prison labor.
Hi, this is Alex Jones.
Did you know that the global elite are now storing non-hybrid seeds in secret storage
vaults near the Arctic Circle?
Did you know that in a real meltdown, non-hybrid seeds can become more valuable than silver
or gold?
It's true, seeds have outperformed even gold and silver before in this country, and it's
possible that could even happen again.
So our friends at Solutions from Science have put together the perfect mix of non-hybrid
seeds.
They call it a survival seed bank, and it can produce an endless supply of nutrient-dense
food for you and your family.
And here's the best part, these seeds have not been genetically modified in any way,
and you actually get enough seeds to plant a full acre crisis garden.
So visit them today at survivalseedbank.com, that's survivalseedbank.com, or give them
a call at 877-327-0365, that's 877-327-0365.
Remember in a real crisis, non-hybrid seeds are the ultimate barter item.
This is Alex Jones for survivalseedbank.com.
Are you still a traditional smoker?
Now experience a new lifestyle and try vaping with e-cigarettes by LASIG.
Imagine no ashes, stains, nasty smell, or coughing and hacking.
With LASIG e-cigarettes revolutionary micro-electronic technology, rechargeable battery, and unique
replaceable cartridge, you'll get all the benefits and satisfaction of smoking without
the hazards.
Use your taste from a wide variety of our new American-made vape-free e-liquids at LASIG.com.
And LASIG smokes the competition by serving thousands of worldwide customers with real
people customer service, fast, free, same-day shipping, and a 30-day warranty and satisfaction
guarantee.
So are you ready for a new vaping lifestyle?
Then call 870-518-4307, that's 870-518-4307.
Or visit LASIG.com, spelled L-E-C-I-G.com, LASIG e-cigarettes for today's modern smoker.
Weakened by GMOs, stressed out about money, and blasted by the electric environment.
Hi, I'm Pastor Ginny, and that was the state I was in back in 2010.
Then I learned about RNA drops.
I learned that 97% of my DNA that scientists have called junk is actually packed with millions
of gene switches that play a critical role in controlling how my cells, organs, and other
tissues behave.
I learned I don't have to put up with disease decay or decline like I'd been conditioned
to believe.
I began taking RNA drops, a 100% natural formula designed to turn on those switches and provide
me with amazing health and joy.
Learn more about RNA drops and order a free sample today.
Visit RNAfreesample.com, that's RNAfreesample.com, or call toll-free, 888-577-3703.
Pay only shipping and handling for a free 30-day supply of RNA drops.
Get the information you need and the health you want at RNAfreesample.com.
Ease the T-Rex of political talk.
Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Today there's an article in the New York Times, no, not the one calling for us to turn all
our guns in, literally, Georgetown law professor scrap archaic, idiosyncratic, and downright
evil constitution.
That's a quote.
Well, of course, a tyrant would call something that keeps separation of powers and checks
and balances evil.
As the nation teeters on the edge of fiscal chaos, observers are reaching the conclusion
that the American system of government is broken.
Cuz globalists have infiltrated it and maneuvered us towards being bankrupt, and the Republicans
and Democrats are arguing over how much to increase taxes and how much to gut the country.
Yeah, it's broken cuz you can't fully bankrupt us ten times over like you've done Greece.
They wanna wreck us, folks, as the nation teeters on the edge of fiscal chaos.
Yeah, by you people, observers are reaching the conclusion.
And then the weak-minded go, yeah, I am, I'm mad about the Constitution.
Darn it with property rights and juries and freedom and everything that made the country
so wealthy.
I want what they've got in North Korea.
I want instant access with one hereditary dictator with big fat cheeks running everything.
Hey, Hans, how you doing, Hans Blix?
Come on in, Hans.
We wanna resurrect Kim Jong-il, put him in charge.
Yeah, he'll get things done.
And this guy, it's not a dumb liberal.
It's not a liberal saying get rid of our Constitution.
They're pig tyrants.
But they walk around with the NPR voice.
Hi, I'm real friendly.
Get in the car, little kid.
It's the same thing.
Shh, kid, no, get in the glue truck, little Orsi.
I talk real soft and act non-threatening.
Though we got the government arming against you, we want your guns.
Yeah, we're real friendly.
We're real liberal.
Yeah.
You know, I get around these people and behind the scenes they're like, when we get you in
the feet of the cabs, we're gonna stomp your guts out and rape your wife.
But in public, I'm liberal.
I mean, just look at these people as the nation teeters.
Let me do it in the Ted Knight voice, as the nation teeters on the edge of financial chaos.
Observers are reaching the conclusion that the American system of government is broken.
Seidman wrote, but almost no one blames the culprit.
Our insistence on obedience to the Constitution with all its archaic, idiosyncratic, and downright
evil provisions.
Time to scrap it.
Time to scrap you, parasite.
Some nobody professor perched in there with Obama at Georgetown, perched in there like
an elitist, seeing all of us like salami sandwiches in the coal case to be eaten off of and figuring
out ways in the government empire that if we could just increase taxes and increase
productivity, we would be able to have a higher standard of living for us, the governing class.
All I know how to do is sit around and act powerful and official all day.
I mean, these people that run this government promote torture, murder, death, and then you
see the lazy eyed Obama supporter, the average idiot, literally stumbling around half dead
from vaccines and GMO.
When they're 30 years old, they look like they're 50, they're killing us all.
Just look at the kids look like dead slobs everywhere, rich neighborhoods, poor neighborhoods.
They're just killing all of us, just zombies.
And that's what I tell us were zombies always movies because we're turning into zombies
and it can be a simulation of there's always video games where you torture zombies now
and the zombies are getting more and more human.
And again, it's all stimulants to dehumanize us.
They're telling us you're garbage, you're undead.
We don't need you because see, they don't need biological androids anymore.
They've got machines now.
Doesn't mean they won't take their time and have fun cutting off your resources and having
your daughters, you know, get in the backs of their limousines to service them.
All the elite literally defecate on them in many cases, you know, you know, see your daughter
can get some money.
It won't matter.
Oh, they're going to take their time psychopathically America and the world is one giant basement
where a psychopath has all of us just having their way with us and they really want to
have their way with us now.
But the second amendment stands on their way of gang raping and pulling our teeth out with
pliers.
Thank you for listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver based products.
Our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions.
Our two ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well as our all natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and
leave the silver at the surface, but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the
natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the
skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver based products
are best for you.
That's www.silverlungs.com.
Coast to Coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
By the way, I'm not joking and I've been in DC and other areas and I watched the cream.
These women are more beautiful than Miss America.
Loading in to all the UN vehicles and ambassador vehicles to go to the different globalist
facilities and literally, because you can read about statistically what the globalist
are into, their art, everything, to absolutely desecrate beauty.
That's what they live for.
And because it's an act of domination because these are nasty demons and I for one am done
with them.
And I just wanna make sure that when the globalists implode our country, everybody knows who did
it.
Cuz what matters is who wins in the end.
All's well that ends well, hmm?
That's right.
Did you think the universe would not organically generate things to resist you?
You think your stupid computers that you can't even read are gonna be able to predict what
humans are gonna do?
You will destroy yourselves.
Let me consciously tell you the truth.
Your body is already ordering you dead.
Because even though you're consciously a psychopath and inhabited by dark evil, your body, your
flesh even cries out against you.
Because it was made by the creator and that's why you're so miserable and why you're so
sick all you evil people.
That's why you wanna make us sick cuz you're inherently spiritually sick.
Well, let me tell you, the pit you've dug, you will fall into it.
We will not.
Feinstein and the militia, Jay, you're on the air, go ahead.
Hey, Alex, thanks for taking my call.
Thank you, sir, for holding my call.
I wanted to mention a video on YouTube I saw a while back about the militia, the American
militia movement in 1995 confronting the Senate subcommittee on terrorism with Dianne Feinstein.
And they basically go up there a couple months after the Oklahoma City bombings-
No, and they blame gun owners as terrorists.
In fact, I saw those hearings live.
What was the name of them?
It was the Senate subcommittee on what?
It was the United States Senate Judiciary Subcommittee on Terrorism.
And I think it might have changed names a couple times or something.
But anyway, it's just a perfect example of Mrs. Feinstein using race and demonizing the
militia movement after this bombing happened.
It's a really good video.
You can see her, she asked them, each one to answer the question, do you think in any
circumstance it is okay to bomb a building?
And they get mad, and it's such a dumb question.
I've seen those famous militia hearings.
We ought to re-air some of those tomorrow.
It's Senate militia hearings, and there was a couple of them, but they're pretty powerful.
And then there's a black militia guy, and they're asking if he hates black people, talking
about that one?
It's so stupid.
Well, absolutely, no, no, no, I've seen the hearings, I will get to it.
Thank you so much, God bless you, I'm glad you brought that up.
Heck, that's the hearing where she's talking about concealed carry.
Sabra in Washington, last person we have time to get to, thanks for holding her on the air.
Oh, Alex, Alex, this is Klingon from Washington State, Alex, I love you, Alex, you're Elijah,
Alex.
Alex, Alex, you're Elijah, you got the saints backing you up.
Now listen to me, last night on George Norridge, 1247, Pacific time, he said his granddaughter,
Rhianna, 18 years old, was run off the road yesterday, twirled around down an embankment.
He was very upset.
December 15th, Alex, are you listening, darling?
Do you hear me?
Yes.
They wait for me, Alex.
They tried to rendition me, Alex.
Do you remember me?
I'm Klingon from Yahoo!
Chat.
I'm Sabra.
I raise and train Rottweilers.
Yeah, yeah, what happened to you?
What happened to you?
Oh, Alex, this was their technique, this was their technique.
I only get off the property two or three times a year, we live on 30 acres, we're always
working against the Satanists, always, trust me, we're really busy.
Two or three years I get off the property, I went out for the first time in four months,
they're on me, I'm coming back home, I'm at a stop sign, out of town, we live south of
Bellingham, Washington.
And what happened?
Yes, I'm at the light, it didn't turn red, I got a big one-ton van, sucks in behind me,
an E-350 Mercedes is in front of me, I noticed right away, something was different.
What'd they do?
What'd they do to you?
We're almost out of time.
Oh, Alex, they tried to kill me, when they couldn't rendition me and stop me, they tried
to run me into a pile of 20 cars.
No, they got their black ops everywhere, everybody better be ready.