We've got it
Waging war on corruption
It's Alex Jones coming to you live from the front lines of the info war
We only value liberty and freedom when it's under assault when we're losing it that's the old cliche
you don't know what you've got until it's gone and so the good news is there are many different
tracks in human history the good the bad the ugly and many others there are different competing
forces in this world the problem is evil so often is very highly organized but over the weekend and
it's been a process we talked about this some on Friday I I had more epiphanies and more deep
understanding of how the entire system works to the point of almost not even being able to come
into this radio show my point is is that I can't just get up here and rattle off facts and
statistics and tell you my point of view on this or that we need to have a fundamental discussion
about the fact that the real world is verifiable and what's really going on is hiding in the living
room like a 10 trillion pound elephant and that so many people that hear about corruption and
evil they're prideful they don't want to believe they've been enslaved or they're prideful and say
so what there's nothing you can do about it and and think that gives them control over it and I
guess it's part of the decadence of the society because we've had it so good for so long but it
really hit me this morning and this afternoon harder than anything's ever hit me because the
shadows are getting long night is falling over our society and so undoubtedly myself and many of you
are gonna get more focused more serious reality and danger has a way of doing that but I had a
realization this morning and when I had the realization I knew that I'd always known this
and then all of you know this and that when I say this you're gonna say that's no revelation at all
but it is a revelation because it's not figurative and it's not a term I would just use to describe
something like calling an extremely fat man an elephant or a hippo this is not like calling
something something it's not because it describes it this is the thing this thing I will call out
is the elephant not the fat man not the freak show it is the elephant it is the bona fide
with the tusk and the ears and the big trunk a little tail and it can step on you and it's a
very psychotic elephant and what I'm speaking of is royalty royalty and the real discrimination
that's going on in our world and the system consciously knows this and is building this
and as soon as I had this realization I began to search engine statements and treaties and globalist
and I knew what I was going to be able to find before I entered it even though I had never read
them saying it and they admit they are consciously building a world government where the ruling class
is royal and is exempt from the laws they put us under and they themselves call it the new royalty
and that's why they divide and conquer black white old young northern southerner Christian
Muslim Jew this that gay straight on and on and on they do that because they are scientifically
dividing and conquering and again I know you know that but the point is they are building a world
where they are the royalty and I'm gonna break it down coming up with all the latest news stay with
us we're live you prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms but if you don't have a home security
system then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when you're
sleeping or away from home who's watching out for intruders check out simply safe it's a new
do-it-yourself home security system that is completely wireless go to get simply safe comm
simply safe is independent and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if the grid goes
down you're protected it's completely customizable so you can use it in your home business boat
trailer storage unit or shed get simply safe comm simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install
yourself in under 20 minutes so there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you move or
need to relocate you can take the system with you wherever you go you aren't always at home
but simply safe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days a week again
that's get simply safe comm we now take you live to the Central Texas command center and the heart
of the resistance rallying Patriots worldwide you're listening to the Alex Jones ladies and
gentlemen thank you for joining us live it is Sunday the 27th day of January
2013 and we will be here for the next two hours roughly Lord willing I of course will
also return weekdays weekdays live noon to 3 p.m. Eastern and carry by over 140 stations
live or tape delayed also XM 166 again thank you so much for joining us for this important broadcast
okay here is what is coming up I'm gonna go over some of the headlines here and then I'm gonna get
to the biggest realization and epiphany that I have ever had and again when I go over this
awakening this realization wife is a is a roadmap of awakenings or people who live in delusion it is
a bottomless pit of ignorance and when I cover this awakening I've had many of you are gonna say
tell me something I didn't know and that is in itself the awakening that is in itself the
awakening that I already knew this but it hit me and and I can see the social engineers I've
read their writings at nauseum read them here on air but I understand the globalist and the social
engineers to such a level because I've been intimately studying them for 20 years on air
for 17 that I know more I can clearly say than that even most of their top technocrats because
most of their technocrats are worldly they're sold out they've used their knowledge to basically just
gain power so they are lazy in their research in fact in a way I realized my broadcast is almost a
college for people who want to go out and do bad things and be evil that was another a huge
awakening I had this weekend because I learned more all the time I learned more in a month now
that I learned previously in a year 15 16 years ago my mind has just been burning with understanding
the last few months and it is exhausting at a certain level but it's also a great exaltation
to be dedicated to something and to and to begin to become a master and as you become a master you
realize you're nothing but a first-grade pupil but the universe is just opening up and it is
my goal it is my goal to try to really articulate what I know and then to go show you the research
I've done and again much of it you're gonna say I already knew that that is really the biggest
sector of this constellation of great understandings epiphanies whatever you want to call them
widening horizons that I've been having as of late I will tell you that I'll get to this by
the bottom of the hour and it's like jumping off a 200-foot cliff and a beautiful Mediterranean
Sea it's beautiful but it's also chilling to even try to describe it and I'm not embellishing here
building up what I'm saying I I can envision things they're doing now just because I know
their mind and then search engine it which is an incredible power it's like a modern crystal ball
and find the exact words I was envisioning the enemy engaged in and find them speaking at
themselves it's just it's unbelievable and to know who the globalist are and to know what they're
into they are really pathetic people to have this knowledge and to not want to give it to people and
empower people and instead know that so many smart people have discovered what I've discovered
and they just go join the Legion of Evil the Legion of Doom that is a very dark understanding
but again they're missing spiritually on some things and they're they're missing out on a
loving upbringing and they get a lot of them also were were were sweet people who were abused by a
generally barbarous and petty and shallow world and so they then go out and to say well I'll just
be dark and corrupt and I'll build a wall around myself that's what Pink Floyd's the wall is all
about and then the worms the worms they enter your brain because when you give up your love and your
passion your love of creativity and your empathy your soul begins to be shuttered and the prison
you build around other people that you believe is protecting you is really a fortress prison
you're building around yourself and again I know when I say all this you're gonna say I already
knew that but did you know it because that is only one piece in a larger mosaic or just stalled
that I will attempt because you know thoughts at the speed of light your thought is at the speed
of light you're an incredible creature living on a gorgeous planet hurtling through deep space I
mean everything around you is magic consciousness is incredible everything is unspeakably wonderful
when you realize the good in the world and then you see the ugly and the ugly is like a malformed
malfunctioning injured animal in a ditch flopping around it it no longer is even an enemy until you
realize you've been so weak and listen to its siren song so long that you have given yourself
over to a subordinate position of this evil so that is what I will attempt to break down at the
bottom of the hour as I just promised to do but I will tell you at the core understanding is that
royalty is the goal royalty and again we talk about the city-state nations exempt from law the
UN exempt from law the diplomatic immunity Congress exempt from insider trading congressman
caught raping children it's back in the news they don't get in trouble they're a bunch of
Jerry Sandusky's you don't get in the club now at the high levels unless you are all of that is well
how do they get away with that they are royal and they consciously are building a royal system Kim
Jung ill his father put him in power in North Korea now his son third generation they're now
calling him royalty in North Korea they're now saying the Sun comes out and the birds sing
because of him another generation or two they will be wearing gold crowns and Americans will
pay money to go drive around on yachts with them and pose when they wear red robes and crowns you
see the British royalty is 50 or 60 lines of North Korean dictatorship so so we bow down to
People magazine and and worship Kate Middleton you see how sick that is and that's what National
Security Act is that's what the New World Order is that's what that now they're trying to get
countries to sign onto treaties where the six mega banks have diplomatic community I mean
diplomatic community ladies and gentlemen you can walk off a plane with a five-year-old child with
a chain around their neck and no one can stop them and this is in the back of the news all
the time to the point of it even put it the news that often now when the UN gets caught flying US
foster children out or flying other kids in it's just a footnote if you're a new listener going
that's incredible well you just just go search engine UN caught in sex trafficking UN caught
using diplomatic community and no one gets in trouble when the police you know catch some guy
in Houston you know running over people diplomatic immunity can't get in trouble you can now purchase
from the UN and multiple governments diplomatic immunity you see they're a group of pirates who
get so much power through fraud they tell you they're royal they tell you they're exempt they
tell you because of their signet ring or their UN seal they're allowed to have a woman chained in
their closet as a sex slave in New York and they don't get in trouble they're allowed to kill her
chop her up and put her in the trash can when the trash men find the chopped up woman the police say
we can't do anything and then used to they would recall people that did that they don't even recall
them now you see that's beyond royalty could a king in England 600 years ago killed children
just because they wanted to like Jimmy Savelle and all the news with him and the royal family
coming out no they had to do it in dungeons quietly now they do it out in the open so that's
the big epiphany I'm gonna give you all the documentation on that and more just like they're
exempt from the gun laws the Senate Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers
the prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse the globalist model
is to shut down societies and starve Patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover that's
why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at info wars shop calm these
are items that I did research on that I personally use you've got the life straw so you can turn
fetid water into safe water anywhere you go the cage or hand crank generator to charge up key
equipment during power outages are out in the field strategic relocation third edition by Joel
Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein thorough safe used by Homeland Security to protect
yourself during any radiological event and crank shortwave AM FM radios everything that we've
researched and found to be the best is available at info war shop calm and your purchase makes our
info war possible we're getting prepared are you in full wars shop calm looking back on 2012 we
ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy in the devastating
summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those
that have lost everything at e foods direct we hear from customers every day that are fortunate
enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from
New York City wrote almost all of the grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods
just in time to be able to help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too
early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what Alex
has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or go to e foods direct
comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food
on the planet call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash
Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct now that we have moved into the winter season there
is an increased need to support our immunity and health at silver lungs we are committed to meeting
your needs by providing a full selection of silver based products our most popular silver
based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our 2 ounce nano silver nasal applicators
as well as our all-natural silver soaps just released is our 100% natural silver gel our new
silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the
silver at the surface but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more
effectively visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver based products
are best for you that's www.silverlungs.com the new year is a great time to take charge of your
health and wellness get serious and make a stand with supernatural silver this is a breakthrough
in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic
silver supernatural silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections
yeast and molds supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective
for water purification it is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support
and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness go to www.supernaturalsilver.com today
and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance that's www.supernaturalsilver.com check
out our new low prices and like us on facebook coast to coast direct from austin you're listening
to the alex jones broadcasting network network we now take you live to the central texas command
center in the heart of the resistance you're listening to the alex jones show we will have
open phones in the second hour i'm also going to play a message from anonymous which has been
hacking into the federal government court websites and has reportedly retrieved a bunch of data
including confidential informant information and more it'll be all the different narcotics
traffickers the government's got that it protects because that's come out in court before before we
go any further here let me just go over some of the headlines that we have up at info wars.com
and prison planet.com sheriff's radio ad says 911 not best option urges residents to take firearms
training we're going to play that clip coming up in a little while federal government declares
itself royal uh 12-minute video report i shot this morning it's got a lot of exhibits and documents
what i'm saying a special report why people think sandy hoax is sandy hook is a hoax almost called
it sandy hoax i'm going to be getting into that obama admits he's a gun enthusiast at least he
says that on the surface to pacify people so that they won't think that he's coming after their guns
i'm going to explain that in a moment again i already mentioned the sheriff radio ads his
911 not best option urges residents to take firearms lessons you know what there are now
hundreds of sheriffs coming out saying they won't enforce things that are unconstitutional
a bunch of congress people are saying it state reps are saying it governors are saying it that's
the spirit that's the lawful rebellion against this government that's been occupied by foreign
powers on record trying to take us back to serfdom and slavery because liberty and freedom is checks
and balances on their tyrannical usurpation but i'm noticing a lot of police chiefs a lot of
sheriffs a lot of people are saying hey i'm on the people's side i know the government is out
of control and hijacked and corrupt in fact congressman brown came out federal congressman
and said obama's only loyal to the soviet constitution and is basically part of a foreign
takeover newsweek came out and said you bet it's good the communist chinese say we should turn our
guns in we're going under globalism they own our debt and alex jones needs to be dealt with that
was in an article called piers pressure problem about piers morgan i mean this is this is going
on and and the operatives for the system know what they're doing still other police in areas like
chicago new york and other places aren't just arresting people that videotape them in public
they're now savagely beating them and here's an article at info awards.com photographers viciously
attacked a police officer for taking pictures of historical building now federal and state courts
have thrown out where they arrest people filming them in public because that's totally legal and
lawful there's no perception of privacy 12 states are still arresting people but because the courts
are throwing it out they now just beat you savagely uh and that's because the higher ups
in the mafia areas that control major sectors of the nation want our will broken i saw an
incredible video a million dollar homes nice area very well-dressed women saying you don't have a
right to put a smart meter on our house it surveils everything we're doing wirelessly
with all the new appliances we have a federal lawsuit this came out in the chicago tribune
it's outside chicago and you're not allowed to go over my gate they they climb over the gate the
police with the locals the local power company they put the smart meter on the house and then
they arrest the woman saying that's eavesdropping to videotape us in your own yard i mean that's
north korean style tyranny in fact on that subject here's an article out of the washington post
former cia officer john caracal is sentenced to 30 months in prison for leaks you're good at
reading names uh in there cj how do you pronounce that caracal caracal i'm pronouncing it right
i've seen him in interviews before he went to prison and he exposed cia torture that people
went to prison for now now under all common law all u.s law you expose criminal activity
to the press anybody you're protected national security doesn't protect that but they still
got a kangaroo court sent him to jail now that is royalty right there the government could order
torture in some cases of children as young as four years of age in front of their parents
with battery acid and large objects i'm not going to go any further but it's joseph mingola did
stuff to little kids sexually with large objects that was the nazi known as angel of death
and this went on at camps all over the world black sites as they're known
the whistle got blown on this and a lot of good people
talked about it and exposed it and this fella gave it to well-known press trying to get it stopped
and and he did get it stopped well obama got caught running a torture camp in mangazi
of course that came out just a few months ago but they had to publicly
stop promoting it see they tried to normalize something that's illegal just by saying they
were doing it remember rumsfeld bragging about torture and stuff and then when it came out what
they were doing they sent their underlings to prison but a whole bunch of people had exposed
lies about wmds lies about iraq nukes lies about torture lies about they go to jail now 30 months
in jail for exposing something that's illegal that's never happened in our country not with
the pentagon papers any of it that is unprecedented you expose children that's how they got khalid
sheikh muhammad to confess to bombing things that weren't built until after he was in prison in one
case a building built four years after he was in prison he'd been in prison about eight years till
he confessed three or four years ago he confessed to everything but crucifying christ and killing
lincoln i mean it was incredible and they they threatened to torture his small children in some
cases people didn't didn't do what they were told and needless to say they like to rape the kids
because that's why they got into this see there's only one place you can rape kids and have the
government protect you and that's in these black sites those sites and um it's it's it's unspeakably
evil and and america we can't sign on to this okay in the name of fighting terrorists speaking
of that i have an incredible uh headline here uh israel let me show tv viewers we're also
streaming video and info wars news.com and presentplanet.tv israel threatens serious
strike if rebels get chemical arms now the russians are there guarding serious chemical
arms asad's not an angel but compared to al-qaeda he is the west nato the us and france and others
have put al-qaeda in in the last 22 months that's now declassified to attack and try to overthrow
the the asad regime now they're saying the u.s is saying this as well they may attack
they may attack
this is so amazing i can't believe this is reuters they may attack damascus because they don't want
the rebels to get the chemical arms first we had to say that damascus would use the chemical arms
so the u.s and others had to invade physically not just use proxy al-qaeda not a saudi arabia
and other areas same folks they use in libya same folks that were running security in bengazi that
killed the ambassador our government runs al-qaeda i had jerome corsey new york times bestseller big
mega conservative swift voted john carrey and he said our government runs the drugs and runs
al-qaeda and he said basically you do you know that i need to be apologized to by everybody
that i'm right it's not our government though it's criminal foreign globalist elements that need
the terror threat to take our rights look at the homeland security documents
where they say it's gun owners veterans conservatives libertarians returning veterans
people like that are who they're targeting it was never about al-qaeda this is a foreign takeover
of america by criminal interest who wrapped themselves in the flag and i'm risking my life
to bring you this information this isn't a joke or a game now obama's engaged in a psyop now saying
he doesn't want our guns but his bills say they'll take most our guns we're going to break that down
and get to the royalty factor sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison
to your water and laughing as you get sick and die start purifying your water with pro pure
my friends i've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is pro
pure and it's available discounted at infowars.com its filters are silver impregnated to prevent
bacterial growth there's no priming required it's nsf 42 certified optional fluoride filters
can reduce fluoride up to 95 easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity purify water from
lake streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial minerals which is key save
money by not buying bottled water and avoid bpa that leaches from the plastic propure is the best
gravity fed filter out there it's what my family uses infowars.com already has the lowest price
on propure but if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10 off and
infowars.com you can also call to order 888-253-3139 millions of people are going to get
sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself
with supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial solution recent advances in
silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent
bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing supernatural silver
is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious
diseases such as strep staph pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology
has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the
effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions the science digest journal says
silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder
of modern medicine go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20%
off that's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on facebook
if you want an american company with american products made by americans here is the cow ben
soap company alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years these all natural
soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and safe
see them on the web at fivestarsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog
buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using
now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs this is an
amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
see them on the web at fivestarsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog
the new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness get serious and make a
stand with supernatural silver this is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several
hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver can be taken
orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds supernatural silver is
also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water purification it is the number
one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect choice
for your emergency preparedness go to supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a
chance that's supernaturalsilver.com check out our new low prices and like us on facebook
coast to coast direct from austin you're listening to the alex jones broadcasting network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does he
live from austin texas broadcasting worldwide it's alex jones
yeah i've been watching i've been waiting thank you for joining us monday through friday
12 noon to 3 pm eastern that's 11 am to 2 pm central back sundays 4 to 6 pm central
and here we are and i'm very thankful to the i don't know close to 100 stations now
picking up the sunday show alone uh it's great to have you all on board and almost every station
that ends up picking us up on sunday ends up within just uh two to six months carrying us
weekdays and that is that is very very exciting okay uh and again i know this news is painful to
hear on the broadcast and i want to get into how government is exempting itself from the law
and actually making themselves uh into the new royalty and how this is the way of governments
and then we'll tie it in to the unprecedented attack on the second amendment and new deception
from obama and we've got him caught uh red-handed on this but but first off for radio listeners
uh it's in the international business times it's in the associated press it's in
the weekly standard here's the international business times government officials they're
not servants government officials authorities masters see royalty government officials can
still own assault weapons under feinstein bill that's the main bill they're trying to get past
that doesn't just ban 158 specifically firearms because it says and anything similar anything like
it's it's thousands of different firearms it's it's it's most pumped shotguns if they've got
what they call military features like a handle or a hole in the stock it's it's thousands of
firearms let me just give you that uh little news tip there now dion feinstein we played the clubs
you can just type in dion feinstein admit she has a concealed carry she admits she's worth 100
million dollars that she magically made since she hit the senate in 93 didn't have that when she
got there uh you know pelosi's worth 300 400 million dollars didn't have it when she went
but so what you own a couple hundred thousand dollars a year was 176 000 as a senator you know
she's had some good investments everything's gone well now she got caught inside her trading but
they just passed a law legalizing it because they're the new royalty and you know they they
caught more senators with underage kids but they you know they're saying you know what
they're senators i mean that's okay all right you know and if you whistle blow on it you'll
go to jail like the like the uh scia guy the fbi came and grabbed him because the government's the
royalty and what they're noticing is the police don't want to confiscate the guns because they're
going to have their guns confiscated in fact retired new york police are having an downturn
in their guns under the new law and you know what i've got an article here where they're refusing
in mass that's coming up but so are the citizens so now cuomo is talking about well we'll retro
actively do a writer bill through so you can have your guns oh good because because you're royal see
if you ever work for the government which is about a third of the population you're now exempt from
all the laws you put on us just like congress is exempt from last time i checked over 400
laws they've passed since 1975 you can look this up i mean you know they're exempt from obamacare
they're exempt from insider trading because they say so they're exempt from reporting
incomes that citizens don't have to i've seen numbers of upwards of half of congress
doesn't pay taxes remember geithner hadn't paid in decades the treasury secretary because
i've seen so many famous ultra-rich robber baron say taxes that's for common people you know you
read about general electric and google paying zero tax or two point three percent tax because they
write the laws suckers you understand how this works they're pirates with slick pr groups out
there big money wants higher taxes because they get it in government contracts and bailouts now
let's continue here with the new royalty and i shot a video again up at info wars.com that
actually shows for radio listeners everything i'm going to be talking about here it's called
federal government declares itself royal right up at the top of info wars.com in the featured news
area very very important to go to the site and to get that video and send it out to your friends
and family so they understand something see our country was founded in 1776 that's when it kicked
off with force saying we're not going to bow to any man we only bow to god and it was the preachers
that led the fight they were called the black brigade because preachers regardless of their
catholic or protestant wore black no no king but king jesus because all the royalty the giant
swelling royalty from sir which there were thousands of in the in the colonies up to lords
patronage uh get free houses free everything from the government it's like a welfare system
and and you couldn't and be involved in manufacturing you couldn't own or sell
large pieces of land you couldn't be in business manufacturing anything
unless you were royal or got a license from royalty
and george washington uh was unable to get pieces of land that he had actually fought
for in the militia because he wasn't royal and you know they wrote books and papers about how
the royals are a bunch of lazy arrogant scum they could rape your wife if they wanted to they could
beat you up they had fake courts they didn't follow the laws and the englishmen had fought
in england for hundreds of years to get basic rights you know they they cut king's heads off
and so there was freedom in england to a great extent in 1775 1776 but not here and people said
hey we have the same rights magna carta parliament act stop it and it didn't stop and government
would exempt itself from the law english military officers would uh beat somebody's son up and kill
him in front of witnesses and not get in trouble they bayonet someone for no reason in front of
witnesses so citizens started taking the law into their own hands and killing redcoats the civil war
had already started for about a decade before so they started quartering troops and beating
up more people and killing more people and confiscating guns and you know the rest of the
story fema teaches it's called terrorism fema teaches i have video of it in my film road to
tyranny but the founding fathers are terrorists scum they actually desecrate george washington
they have four shows on tv bad mouthing the founding fathers and anybody that supports
them now shows like i hate paul revere on amc this is an occupational government british
intelligence that's why you're taught to love british you hear me talk about british don't
talk about brits you've been taught movies and tv james bond all of it it's not the british people
it's the corrupt system if you want to call anything a real british system and not a sax
coburg continental royal german family propaganda that's the british empire real british or
scottish or irish people fighting for liberty that would be america okay but they in 1922
they established the pratt house under british intelligence churchill wrote three books on this
bragging about it the history of the english-speaking peoples i read it like
15 years ago only volume was it two or three points you can go look it up guys type in a
history of british-speaking peoples by uh church all that i want to give the exact name to folks
i haven't read that by 15 years there's three volumes i read the last volume about modern times
and this is all public what you're about to hear the treaty of rome 1959 to set up the euro
admits it's run by the royal families of saxco berg gotha and the british empire the dutch
royal family their cousins the biggest one of the biggest empires in history next to the british
and the spanish empire now run by juan carlos king of spain this is who's at bilderberg this
is who runs things this is who gets your highways handed over to them to put toll roads on them
and notice the un is above the law the un has diplomatic community to do whatever they want
and all this pr about how they love the children while they're busy running dozens of wars at any
one time literally probably 30 wars right now more than two dozen look it up all this murder
incorporated modern colonialism against the nation-state against the middle class they've
already sucked out all the poor people in africa and asia and latin america now the globalist brag
they're colonizing america they're colonizing europe they're bankrupting us to make us poor
yes the four volumes of the history of the british speaking peoples nobel prize in literature
so i guess i read the uh i guess i read the fourth volume the birth of britain the new world the age
of revolution the great democracies there you go i guess i thought there were three there's four
volumes this is all laid out okay a system of control the british royal family is tax exempt
and gets two billion dollars a year converted from pounds of taxpayer money
and now now the government here is making itself royal looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves how
did we ever survive from natural disasters like hurricane sandy and the devastating summer drought
to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost
everything at e foods direct we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand after hurricane sandy danny from new york city
wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed but i managed to get my e foods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared 10 years too early than
one day too late i can warn you but i can't feed you heed the warnings and do what alex has done
call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash alex and build your food supply it's the
best tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com
slash alex you can bet your life on efoods direct now that we have moved into the winter season
there is an increased need to support our immunity and health at silver lungs we are committed to
meeting your needs by providing a full selection of silver based products our most popular silver
based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our two ounce nano silver nasal
applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps just released is our 100 percent natural
silver gel our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate
and leave the silver at the surface but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural
skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering
the silver more effectively visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver
based products are best for you that's www.silverlungs.com sick of the globalist eugenicist
control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as you get sick and die start purifying
your water with pro pure my friends i've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out
there bar none is pro pure and it's available discounted at infowars.com its filters are
silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth there's no priming required it's nsf 42 certified
optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95 easy to set up and use doesn't require
electricity purify water from lake streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial
minerals which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid bpa that leaches from
the plastic probe here is the best gravity fed filter out there it's what my family uses
info wars.com already has the lowest price on propior but if you add the promo code water at
checkout you get an additional 10 off at info wars.com you can also call to order 888-253-3139
the new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness get serious and make
a stand with supernatural silver this is a breakthrough in silver technology that is
several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds
supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification it is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support
and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness go to supernatural silver.com today
and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance that's supernatural silver.com
check out our new low prices and like us on facebook coast to coast direct from austin
you're listening to the alex jones broadcasting network network from the front lines of the
information war it's alex jones
again this is such a wide subject and the last hundred years or so every american president has
had royal background on both sides of their family obama on his mother's side is related
to bush and cheney if you don't believe me just search engine and it's it's mainstream news but
you have to understand royalty is just criminal groups that were able to take over because they
were the most vicious and normally they're just whoever's in charge at first and then within two
or three generations they declare themselves gods they declare themselves of the stars and that you
are slaves and then only they have rights and if you study this that's why obama always kneels to
the british royalty to the saudi royalty well there's dozens of photos i mean what is there
like 15 or more groups he's bowed to you've seen that i have something i want to show some of the
viewers out there on tv but anybody can just type in obama bowing to see him bowing to every royal
house major and minor out there now if you expand on that let's put up the history of the red carpet
the greeks and babylonians used it to symbolize uh royalty and that and that he who walked on
a red carpet was a god not mortal and that the mortals blood was the path on which they walked
it is a giant ocean a river of blood on which conquering god kings walk by the way i'm reading
from major university uh websites agamemnon known that only gods walk on such luxury responds with
trepidation i am immortal man i cannot trample upon those uh tinted splendors without fear thrown
in my path and it just goes on from there so there is the times of times of old our presidents
did not walk on red carpets until the time of edward bernays the father of the word modern
propaganda who worked for the department of war and others he's the reason you eat bacon and eggs
they couldn't sell the pork bellies they put out advertisements in the newspaper saying everybody's
got to have bacon with their eggs he's the guy that said have feminists walk with cigarettes and
tell women it's cool you can get the other half of women smoking he said we can break up the family
by telling women it's cool to work all day and then we'll get double taxes whether you support
women working or not the point is and bernays wrote three books go read them three that i've
read i think he must have written more the point is he wrote propaganda and others and he sits
there calling you dumb animals when you read the book and how there's a giant mind control system
and how they would treat this is in the 20s politicians like royalty and have red carpets
and have hollywood that had just started together with them at dinners to to to blur the the the
people that have become the new royalty artists and people which is actually in the old times
more healthy than royalty at least they did something you liked with the politicians and
now our politicians fly around what is it 10 million dollars per trip with air force one
and whoever the speaker of the house is gets an identical air force one it's called what air force
two there's an air force three and then even minor officers generals get their own private jets and
their own private little female assistant hookers to follow them around this is the decadence and
and and again if you read article one section nine clause eight of the constitution several
other clauses that we have posted up at infowars.com and prison planet.com in the federal
government declares itself royal video and under it i have links to these areas it is a felony and
an impeachable offense when the president or anyone in the federal government or with the
federal commission takes a title of nobility but we've had sitting presidents become knighted
by the way that a lot of stuff comes with that if they that's a huge payoff no title of nobility
shall be granted by the united states and no person holding any office of profit or trust
under them shall with the consent of the congress accept any present ammonium of office or title or
of any kind whatsoever from any king prince or foreign state they all take giant speaking gifts
million dollar speaking gifts by the saudis by the emperor of japan that's why they bow that's
why they sell us out and and now they can order torture even though it's illegal and if the cia
blows the whistle they go to jail that's in the news today 30 months they can order all sorts of
other criminal nsa wiretapping without warrants and they claim the government's secret and above
the law and now they're going to give all federal employees and police period and the house and the
senate can have any firearm they want that government bans the bill just says we can have
whatever we want we're above the law why not the un set up by the rockefellers 1945 presidio san
francisco and they gave them the land to build it in new york that they have diplomatic immunity
that's why you never hear about un war crimes even though it was even the new york times last year
they're in multiple african countries and multiple south american countries just type into a search
engine uh un uh back groups engaged in genocide under un and you'll get it you know four thousand
people in burma kill them for their land whatever all over the world and it's in the new york times
yeah the un group went in and uh you know killed everybody in this african village take their land
but it's for the earth you know every miss america says i love the un it must be nice i heard it over
and over again this is the mind control and and again my big epiphany was oh my gosh i mean i
already knew this but you know this whether you love the vatican or hate the vatican whatever
the vatican has its own city outside of italian law and can do whatever it wants
and declares itself sovereign and has diplomatic immunity worldwide
it has its own swiss military to back them up see the swiss are smart they learn from the vatican
they have their own country and say we're outside of your national laws israel does the same thing
it's basically a city-state the city of london within london listen this is key is a tiny area
i've been there most expensive real estate in the world and it's above the law pays no taxes
it's its own country and that's where the rothschild banks and rockefeller banks are
the un in the u.s above the law nafta and gat these organizations the organization of american
states and others they're above the law eu bureaucrats just type in eu bureaucrats pay no
tax guys show them that i want people to see that watching on tv just type in eu bureaucrats pay no
tax no wonder the head of the imf said 77 tax isn't enough for the average greek to pay you
need to work six seven days a week and pay more tax she's exempt from tax see and now they've
introduced bills where the where if you work for the government you're exempt from the laws you're
enforcing it is the essence of royalty that's all royalty means notice how the police wear four
stars on their lapels like their generals now on their emulates they they wear bigger and bigger
hats more and more salad dressing on their shirts you know the generals that's royalty the generals
walk around with little gold canes under their arms black boots the police they're the authorities
they're the officials you're the servant in america they we were the first country other
than a short period in a few city states of greece to say government isn't god the people are number
one and there's a bill of rights and constitution to protect these enshrined rights that even at 51
say let's enslave the other 49 two wolves in a sheet voting on what's for dinner no one can take
that away obama is in the news i'm going to read it when we come back in the next hour and then go
to your calls saying hey i've got the majority in polls wanting to take guns and the house
republicans won't let me because they speak for their you know for their minority constituents no
they speak for the bill of rights and constitution he says i'll just do an executive order
too grand to pay taxes too arrogant to care about democracy no wonder the euro elite sneer
at the idea of referendum daily mail and it goes on about how she pays no taxes they pay no taxes
again ladies and gentlemen and the globalist always create luxembourgs and switzerland's
and israel's and vatican's and cities of london within london where if you get entrance into the
city of london they let you into the group you pay no taxes you're above the law you're god
if you can become a un diplomat or one of their legates one of their minions you now are are
literally above the law this is royalty in north korea three generations of dictators
right around in these huge displays where people worship them at sports stadiums as god and that's
supposedly communism for the little guy all communism is is a tiny elite ruling everyone
as their slaves saying oh look you're free you all share equally in the work that's all any of
this is fascism socialism communism it's always tiny groups ruling over you before the communist
revolution of 150 years ago roughly there was no left and right left was feminine male was seen as
right the devil left god right whatever you think of that that's what left and right was there was
only is there more freedom or less the globalists seek to overthrow the renaissance to overthrow
the enlightenment of the last 500 years that our republic's founding was the greatest expression
of there is a systematic revolution by special interests backed by royals at the head of it
the Rothschilds are now lords with the Saxe-Coburg-Goethe transylvanian german royalty that runs
england the dutch royalty the saudi royalty the spanish royalty look at who owns our toll roads
the spanish royalty literally juan carlos they are in a revolution against our forebearers gains
in the revolutions of 1776 and others we are in the ultimate battle against royalty and criminality
you prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms but if you don't have a home security system
then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when you're sleeping
or away from home who's watching out for intruders check out simply safe it's a new do-it-yourself
home security system that is completely wireless go to getsimplysafe.com simply safe is independent
and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if the grid goes down you're protected it's
completely customizable so you can use it in your home business boat trailer storage unit or shed
getsimplysafe.com simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes
so there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you move or need to relocate you can take
the system to the next level you can use it in your home you can use it in your house you can
you can take the system with you wherever you go you aren't always at home but simply safe
will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days a week again that's
getsimplysafe.com millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other
illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a revolutionary new
broad spectrum antibacterial solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted
in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning
and help improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep staph
pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology has the ability to terminate
entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal
or ionic silver solutions the science digest journal says silver is our mightiest germ
fighter it is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine
go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20%
off that's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on facebook coast to coast direct from austin
you're listening to the alex jones broadcasting network from his central texas command center
deep behind enemy lines the information war continues it's alex jones and the gcn radio
network all right i'm gonna get the number on the next segment and take calls after i get into
some of the other news but the government declaring itself above the law and that it's
doing it for your own good and so arrogant that the government runs al-qaeda publicly and runs
the drugs publicly and then gets caught and doesn't get in trouble and now senators are
getting caught with little kids they're not getting in trouble and that was in the news
this week that's when you know you're in deep trouble because royalty will give to their friends
and themselves everything even if stuff starts collapsing it's like you know the friends are
about to storm the bastille and they say they're starving to death they're saying bread bread they
must have bread they're starving to death and you know even our generals were like we've got to you
got giant stables in stores full of food you've got to feed them or they're going to kill us and
she says just let them eat cake just just just give them some cake just something most people
never get cake in their whole life in france it was so so tyrannical and they just stormed the
whole place and killed everybody and then and then its own evil came out of that the french
revolution and uh ladies and gentlemen this is the type of stuff that's going on this is the
type of stuff that's happening and so so i'm not just saying they're becoming royalty figuratively
they are royalty the new world order is run by royalty and the roth child's married into it and
it uses the royalty system government officials not servants see when the media does that you've
got to call them email them and say stop calling them officials if you can just make them call
themselves servants that's half the battle and and alex de tocqueville and others historians
wrote about the united states after our revolutionary war had been successful that we
were different because people didn't bow down to classes here it was about how hard working you
were and what you stood for that's what all this was about and how we were so different in that
and that's what made us so great royalty stagnates things why did half the wealth in the world
belong to five percent of the world the u.s population until the 70s because ladies and
gentlemen we had more liberty and you're like well we had all sorts of bad stuff we had slavery
we had everything else the idea of human liberty not just being for royals where they're sovereign
and have rights well now it was going to be not just white guys who were wealthy like had been
in england now it was going to be all white guys and not just if you were catholic or if you were
protestant because there was a battle over who would have rights and who was in control now it
was catholic or protestant or quaker and then pretty soon other people said you know what
black people shouldn't be slaves white people said that we should they should be free and that
debate happened for 50 60 years and then you saw what happened and then women said oh we want to
be more free but see that was then co-opted as a control mechanism anything's going to be co-opted
just like the french revolution by the illuminati the jackabins people like illuminati that's a
tom hanks movie no that's encyclopedia britannica you see knowledge will open the world up to you
and you'll realize it's the very same elements our forebears 235 36 years ago are fighting the
exact same bloodlines we're fighting the rothschilds then folks and the gothas then
okay and and we're under the same system right now and i don't care whether it's the big monolithic
catholic church or israel or the city of london in london the banking city or the un they all act
just the same because it's the same trick they dress up they have a red carpet they wear a crown
men in black suits stand around intimidate the villagers we are your god if a giant alien
spacecraft landed and a red carpet rolled off and you know a guy walked off 18 foot tall green alien
with a gold crown on and broadcast in english i am your king i guarantee you obama the queen of
england and all the rest of them if gorp you know the the alien from ploop tart showed up and said
i'm going to annihilate your planet if you don't bow to me and he had other blurps from the planet
bloop tart standing there with earpieces and laser guns i guarantee you our leaders would go and kneel
to them and bow and say we now you know rename this blerp too i'm not joking because if you
wear a crown and have a red carpet it's over well let me tell you something i've been on the red
carpets i've been around the biggest people in hollywood they're empty on average there's nothing
going on there stop thinking you're you're low down you're superior to the inbred elite they
want to poison your water and your food because they're threatened by your superiority your hybrid
vigor they know that they're that's why they discovered genetics was trying to help themselves
sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as you
get sick and die start purifying your water with pro pure my friends i've done a lot of research
and the best gravity filter out there bar none is pro pure and it's available discounted at info
wars dot com its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth there's no priming
required it's nsf 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95 easy to set
up and use doesn't require electricity purify water from lake streams ponds and wells this
filter system leaves in beneficial minerals which is key save money by not buying bottled water and
avoid bpa that leaches from the plastic probe here is the best gravity fed filter out there it's what
my family uses infowars.com already has the lowest price on propure but if you add the promo code
water at checkout you get an additional 10 off at infowars.com you can also call to order 888-253-3139
i have sworn upon the altar of god eternal hostility against every form of tyranny over
the mind of man thomas jefferson it's alex jones on the gcn radio network
it's our number two the total free number to join us is eight seven seven seven eight nine alex
eight seven seven seven eight nine two five three nine on any subject you wish to discuss
eight seven seven seven eight nine two five three nine the websites are prison planet.tv prison
planet.com and infowars.com we are using the infowar to fight the globalists who are trying
to construct a prison planet now if you just joined us last hour i broke down the fact that
the un is exempt from their own laws and world law because they say so and they have weapons the
british royalty is exempt from their own taxes and own laws and are the richest people in the world
the rothchild's after them and it's the same thing with juan carlos of spain one of the biggest owner
of eu properties he's given the major roads able to put toll roads on them he puts toll roads on
our roads oh you you heard me right this is the royalty the cia officers blow the whistle on
torture that matter if it's illegal they go to jail for whistleblowing congress has exempted
itself from hundreds and hundreds of laws in the last 30 years they didn't do it before because it
was illegal they've bum rushed us just had a revolution of tyranny where they exempt themselves
from capital gains taxes they exempt themselves from obamacare taxes and now dianne feinstein's
bill exempts all federal employees and police period from ever being under any of the gun
restrictions so for life you're given a title of nobility meaning you're above the laws that are
on the general public article one section nine clause a to the constitution and several others
it is illegal and i show the constitution and break it all down in a video tutorial i shot
today up at infowars.com federal government declares itself royale think about it and the un
so many other globalist organizations set up these city states that are exempt from taxes
exempt from laws exempt from everything with diplomatic immunity and we just accept okay
you're allowed to run drugs and get caught not get in trouble you in oh the military u.s military now
admits they grow the opium and ship it out on c130s but let's not talk about that national
security i've got fox news abc bbc all saying that and you know what's important about this
broadcast and why i i'm so blessed what i talk about this year you'll hear in two or three years
on the big neo-con radio shows i tune into those sometimes now and literally stuff i was pioneering
a decade ago or five years ago or six months ago now it's quicker and quicker is on their shows
i make it safe to talk about this but i'm going to ask you something how can congress last year
get caught some some congress people making 30 40 50 million a year on insider trading
nancy pelosi goes to congress with nothing last time i saw something like 400 million dollars
million dollars the mayor of san francisco worth less than a million dollars go look at her
financials they're public she's worth over 100 mil right now the latest numbers just came out
some estimates are 150 mil how do you make 150 mil on 175 000 176 000 a year the answer is you don't
in san francisco you live in a doghouse for that these people know what they're doing and they got
caught and they think you're dumb because you act like you're dumb you don't do the research you
don't put the time in you got all the fantasy football numbers figured out to show off to your
buddies women have all the fashion stuff figured out but you don't know how the world works see if
you're really cool if you're really successful the information i know in business i can go out
and make a mint right now the information and i'm not gonna even start bragging the point is is that
i want you to have that knowledge the globalists don't want you to have the knowledge i want to
empower humanity i want to move the whole species forward not dumb everybody down so a group of
insiders can control everything i'm fundamentally offended that our founding fathers fought against
laws where british nobility could own guns and their servants and minions and their militia
but the rest of the citizens had to turn their guns in 234 years ago
i'm fundamentally offended that when they got caught insider trading that was big news cnn
abc helped cover it up they went don't worry they're gonna pass a law outlawing it there
are already a bunch of laws outlawing it i mean literally more than a hundred they've had
congressional studies on it over the last 200 plus years hundreds of laws on this hundreds of laws on
this they passed a new law saying it made it illegal it made it legal but you can't pass a law
saying you can kill little kids because you feel like it you can't pass a law saying blacks are
slaves again because moral authority says it's wrong it's moral authority that gets things done
it's recognizing we're being told we're slaves they passed a law saying of the house for senate
ethics committee look this up just happened last year 2012 says they can have an investment on
something i mean there's examples of feinstein giving 25 million dollars to a brand new startup
genetic engineering company in san francisco that has no company no nothing like cylindra
energy no no business no nothing half a million bucks 25 million in a bill she writes and gets
passed and then she's the biggest stock owner she's the biggest stock owner of a brand new
mailbox that's the business a mailbox and a scientist and then she gives it 25 million of
taxpayer money and then she gets three million of it the next month i mean you know and go look this
up look her saying she's above the law and she's going to still be able to own any guns she wants
and she is a big gun owner and bloomberg's a big gun owner but you can't own guns in new york what
dirt bags it makes me sick you know going back about six seven years i got to know charlie sheen
because he's a listener a lot of other hollywood folks but they you know they're they're they're
private friends and charlie's had some wild times i know he's a smart guy he was on piers morgan
friday i happen to see it today he's like well i don't have guns anymore because of a domestic
problem but i that's okay because i've got great security team hey charlie we don't all make three
million dollars a week bro and i know you know better than that i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna
call him you know this this just blows me away your piers morgan has a private security detail
nancy pelosi has a private security detail and our taxpayer money to pay for it she got an insider
trading on record but she but she said she's royal you know the un gets caught drug dealing
or running white slavery well you know they're the un they're immune i mean the un sex slavery
trafficking is legendary oh but they're immune it's all funny to them and folks they are now
passing laws have passed laws to take your private and public pension funds they've already done it
in europe we're next they're they're buying armored vehicles and 1.6 million bullets and arming to the
teeth and building bunkers because they know everything's going to collapse by design to
consolidate it and they hope you're too stupid to understand that and so the un the globalist all of
them they're not i'm not saying their royalties a figure of speech to you know hey you know your
husband's acting too good or your wife's acting royal hey honey stop acting like the queen of
england no no they set it up according to letters of mark and and and global regulations backed by
nato force where they are royal they're on red carpets they're up there with the paparazzi they
land in the you know billion dollar jets uh 10 million dollars per flight they are royal they
are royal we are under a royal national security global governance corporate dictatorship where
they carve up the planet and go okay the dutch royalty gets all the water plants literally almost
all of them uh the spanish royalty worldwide gets all the existing roads to put toll roads on it how's
that sound uh the british royalty gets bp and uh dutch royal shell they're the biggest owners look
it up and tax exempt you you hear about the major corporations don't pay taxes the the the dutch
royalty it's on record and the british royalty and others it's national security state secrets that
that what their money is but but their holdings have come out but but it's public that they're
tax exempt and that's not enough to own the two biggest oil companies that's not enough for them
that's not enough to own half the land in canada and the rare earth minerals in africa for the for
the sax coburg witch the the transylvanian witch queen did you know they're really transylvanian
can't make that up folks if you don't believe me prince charles has moved back to transylvania
they're they're not even german royalty nothing against transylvanians i had a romanian on once
and he was like well don't knock that i'm romanian nothing against romanians these are the guys up on
the hill the romanians didn't go out at night because of them it's like jimmy savelle best
friends with the royal family caught with all these little kids of course you don't let your
kids out at night near the castle i mean yeah that's all the royals are into that's where
all these legends come from they're not they're not real vampires they're spiritual vampires and
they want to dumb you down so that you're not inbred like them here's the big secret the royals
are all inbred the rothschilds are inbred they hate you they have genetic disorders they're
inbred psychopaths that's why they chemtrail and poison the food and water they want to hurt you
they're jealous of you looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural
disasters like hurricane sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at e foods direct we
hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply
of food on hand after hurricane sandy danny from new york city wrote almost all the grocery stores
are closed but i managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece
it is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late i can warn you but i can't
feed you heed the warnings and do what alex has done call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoods
direct dot com slash alex and build your food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term
storeable food on the planet call 800-409-5633 or efoods direct dot com slash alex you can bet your
life on e foods direct if you want an american company with american products made by americans
here is the cal ben soap company alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years
these all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth
friendly and safe see them on the web at five star soap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog
buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs
this is an amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap
makes you feel see them on the web at five star soap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog
alex jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers the prognosis for the
entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse the globalist model is to shut
down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover that's
why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at info wars shop.com these
are items that i did research on that i personally use you've got the life straw so you can turn
fetid water into safe water anywhere you go the ktor hand crank generator to charge up key
equipment during power outages are out in the field strategic relocation third edition by
joel scousum when disaster strikes by matthew stein therosafe used by homeland security to
protect yourself during any radiological event hand crank shortwave amfm radios everything that
we've researched and found to be the best is available at info war shop.com and your purchase
makes our info war possible we're getting prepared are you info wars shop.com millions of people are
going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect
yourself with supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial solution recent
advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent
bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe
enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases
such as stress staff pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology
has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the
effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions the science digest journal says
silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder
of modern medicine go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for
20% off that's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on facebook
coast to coast direct from austin you're listening to the alex jones broadcasting network
live from austin texas broadcasting worldwide it's alex jones
by the way i want to apologize the listeners we've been burning the phone lines up we have
a computerized phone system and it was closed and i guess they didn't hear me say the number
the phones were open so here's the number one more time for everybody it is eight seven seven
seven eight nine alex eight seven seven seven eight nine a-l-e-x eight seven seven seven eight
nine two five three nine on all these issues i've been raising so they're gonna pass a law
where thousands of guns not 158 it's 158 types and anything similar wide open you ban your guns
come after you not let you sell them transfer them shut down gun shows turn homeland security
loose on gun owners the list goes on and on and on and they're telling you though that
everything's okay because they're going to still be able to own guns again here's the
international business times government officials can still own assault weapons under feinstein
bill and that's that royalty here's weekly standard feinstein gun control bill to exempt
government officials when government passes law saying they're exempt or they can arbitrarily
do whatever they want that's royalty and our ancestors all over the world fought against
royalty so they couldn't just say take him to the dungeon take her away where i want your wife and
many a king was killed over this many a queen so in ancient times the last 600 years or so most
royalty couldn't order you killed because they felt like it courts were created some kangaroo
some not now they're back to ndaa disappear torture him unbelievable so again i'm done
talking about the royalty uh cuomo says new gun law does not exempt new york cops could prevent
police from responding to school shootings and will make the cops turn this is active
cops turn in semi-auto and of course the retired are now having to turn theirs in and i've got
articles here where tens of thousands including police current police in new york are saying we're
not doing this new york state there over a hundred sheriffs have come out we're going to play a clip
of that in a few minutes saying they're not turning their guns in and they're not going to
take the citizens guns but we've had some of these sheriffs on all over the country black white old
young northerner southerner westerner people are waking up and that's the good news because the
fbi crime statistics are violent crimes drop 59 49 excuse me we have the statistics up at info
wars.com old video presentation off fbi.gov 49 drop in in violent crime in the last 20 years
and that drop is accelerating 21 of that is just since 2007 we've done whole tutorials
up at prisonplanet.tv and info wars.com off fbi.gov showing you their stats okay so the
system's panicking the police know that where they don't have gun ownership the criminals
are busting in raping people and killing them and the criminals have guns so we've got that news now
let's look at this incredible deception by obama obama up at camp david we do skeet shooting all
the time so he's coming out again saying hey we gotta be nice uh to gun owners he's saying that
uh you know what we just want to restrict some of your guns it's about hunting but it's no big deal
so again the second amendment is not about hunting so he says i agree you have the second
amendment just everything semi-auto is going to be taken now in australia they took all the
semi-autos over a decade ago now they're banning bolt action and single shot they've done this in
over 100 countries in the last century let me go to the other article that's the weekly standard
fox news obama suggests republicans unwilling to compromise and gun control debate
this is a quote from obama the house republican majority is made up of mostly of members
who are in sharply gerrymandered districts you mean areas you don't control the electronic
wedding machines that are very safely republican and may not feel compelled to pay attention to
broad-based public opinion you don't pay attention to opinion you've manufactured with fake polls
the bill of rights says i keep my private property and that i can have whatever religion i want even
if you get 99 to say they disagree you understand punk we're a republic not a democracy a pure
democracy is hell because what they really concerned about is opinions of their specific
republican constituents no obama you globalist traitor they're concerned with the constitution
and bill of rights he said it's understandable that people are protective of their family
traditions when it comes to hunting so gun control advocates also need to do
a little more listening than they do sometimes more patronizing folks i've shown these quotes
as state senator he said ban all guns the un treaty says ban all guns that civilian ownership
should be completely abolished the civilian ownership of firearms should be ended because
it threatens the legitimate power monopoly of the state they say there should be an abolition
of civilian ownership of firearms that's a quote go read it that is in the interpretation addendum
july 7 2001 unit deer rockefeller facility new york city look it up it's in there okay so so so
this is the garbage this is how they're playing possum with us let's go to a clip of obama four
years ago four years and change you're in the 08 campaign saying i won't take any of your guns by
the way in these thousands of guns that are banned thousands of different types because
it's this type or anything like it it says pump shotguns ladies and gentlemen it says a shotgun
with a handle on it a stock that has any groove on it i mean and remember oh we never want your
guns we would never come for them no no no no no that's a conspiracy theory now they're all out
coming for them ammo bands you name it they've they're taking they're saying cops can't have
guns in new york semi-auto oh but they're now saying we'll pass a federal law to nullify that
as if that can nullify state law if you cops just trust us you'll get your guns back they'll just
pass another law later they don't want retired cops having guns they say the military the number
one enemy retired military because they know you know how to fight in the myak and homeland
security documents that are public that we were given by law enforcement big national news three
and a half years ago you think they're going to let you have guns you know this is a criminal
takeover the russians in 1917 told the retired military to turn their guns in and when they did
they killed them all 30,000 in one day in moscow alone if you're dumb enough to help the new world
order you get what you deserve collaborators let's go to this obama clip here it is when y'all go
home and you're talking to your buddies and they say oh he wants to take my gun away
they say he wants to take my gun away you've heard it here i'm on television so everybody knows it
i believe in the second amendment i believe in people's lawful right to bear arms
i will not take your shotgun away i will not take your rifle away any semi-auto i won't take
your handgun away okay all semi-autos are banned under this okay and once they get the list it's
got to be it's got a forced buyback provision in there it's a confiscation bill let's go out to
break with one more here's biden in the same month of 08 saying nobody's getting my handgun or
shotgun now this is a guy who wrote an assault weapons bill in 92 that made all semi-autos be
turned in this is a known liar hoping you're stupid remember he's going to keep his guns
he's royal you're you're his property here it is i guarantee you barack obama ain't taking my
shotguns so don't buy that malarkey don't buy that malarkey they're gonna they're gonna start
peddling that to you i got two if he tries to fool michael ready he's got a problem and uh
and uh bill clinton didn't have sex with that woman monica lewinsky and it didn't matter there
was 15 witnesses and doctors that lance armstrong was doping he looked at you on espn and said i
didn't do that i mean give me a break i can see a roid head a mile away look this is the type of
guard and and then people defend lance armstrong because he said hi to him in the street it's
pathetic we've made the football people royal now except they're not really royal because they're
not above the law totally and completely disgusting and now obama's back going hey i don't
want your guns i just confiscated almost all of them hey you got a right to hunt of course trying
to ban that as well this is a group of criminals securing their property i got news for you so
called royalty with red carpet you're not my owner i'm not your slave sick of the globalist
eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as you get sick and die start
purifying your water with pro pure my friends i've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter
out there bar none is pro pure and it's available discounted at info wars.com its filters are silver
impregnated to prevent bacterial growth there's no priming required it's nsf 42 certified optional
fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95 easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity
purify water from lake streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial minerals
which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid bpa that leeches from the plastic
propure is the best gravity fed filter out there it's what my family uses infowars.com already has
the lowest price on propure but if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional
10 percent off at infowars.com you can also call to order 888-253-3139
if you want an american company with american products made by americans here is the cal
ben soap company alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years these all
natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly
and safe see them on the web at five star soap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog
buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using
now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs this is an
amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
see them on the web at five star soap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog
you may be arrested and or subject to other police action
tyranny is here the grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality it really says that the state
is god the united states is now recognized globally as one of the most oppressive police
states on earth this film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of fema camps
now being expanded nationwide this documentary exposes how the continuity of government program
has established an all-powerful shadow state police state four chronicles the sickening depth
to which our republic has fallen prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship
body scanners sound cameras citizen spies stage terror and cameras on every street corner it's
only the beginning of the new world order's hellish plan the police state isn't coming
it's here secure your copy today at info wars.com or see it online in the highest quality at prison
planet.tv now that we have moved into the winter season there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health at silver lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver based products our most popular silver based products are the 32
ounce nano silver solutions our two ounce nano silver nasal applicators as well as our all
natural silver soaps just released is our 100 percent natural silver gel our new silver gel
is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the
surface but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry
of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively
visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver
based products are best for you that's www.silverlungs.com
coast to coast direct from austin you're listening to the alex jones broadcasting network
he aligns himself with the truth and it's time for you to choose a side you're listening to alex
jones by the way i'm going to go to your phone calls now we have a short message part of a
message that anonymous the real anonymous was put out concerning the murder uh via persecution of
aaron swartz that's coming up in the next segment but if you go up to infolwars.com
we have a special report why people think sandy hook is a hoax rob do stay up here all weekend
i shot this on friday evening to get this done and folks have criticized me for not saying it's
a conspiracy and a staged event i have said aurora clearly has all the hallmarks 90 plus
percent chance it is i'm not going to go over all the reasons for that the guy was under a
mind control darpa contract that's one point of hundreds literally hundreds multiple shooters
reported the guy drugged up in jail saying he was under mind control top air force psychiatrist over
him national security declared on his notebook where he was supposedly gonna do all this with
his air force psychiatrist has the report you want me to keep going no i'm gonna go to your calls
this one they got crazy prozac serotonin reuptake inhibitor heads it's in the inserts it can make
you do this goth young white kid fits the mo they're real attacks that guy a few months ago
shot an innocent police officer here in austin at walmart for no reason they said he was walking
around drooling with a gun in his hand at walmart cop comes up that was his mistake guy walking
around with a gun but whatever if i was a cop somebody called me a guy's walking around walmart
with a gun i'd wait till backup got there but the guy had courage he went in there and the guy just
shot him and i said that guy's on psychotropics turned out he was on xanax and alcohol his
roommate said he didn't even know who he was i mean it's just when a woman chops her baby's arms
and legs off with a meat cleaver for no reason and she was a bible study teacher with no criminal
record something's wrong i said she's on serotonin reuptake inhibitors she was woman drives her kids
off on a lake for no reason all five of them serotonin reuptake inhibitors i mean it's the
same story i've just i read the news every day it's what i do harris and kleibold on the drugs
turns out the aurora shooter was on five psychotropics to be whacked out of his brain
and not know who he was to be set up that had multiple shooters i know that's an inside job
if they'll stage fast and furious as larry pratt has said they'll stage anything i'm gonna go to
your calls the point is i have not gone there that there's actors and blue screen and it's all fake
until i actually confirmed we caught them cnn and blue screen it's got the i got the video it's
their original video and a bunch of the stuff it looks really bad and this even shakes me up i mean
i say in the video is everything got to be a conspiracy i mean you think i'm the one who
thinks everything's a conspiracy no i cannot believe how bold these people are and when i
saw this blue screen thing i said that can't be real and i went and looked it up and it was the
it was the cnn video and i show you the rest of stuff it's it's it's pretty damning i don't know
what's going on but it looks bad that's all i'm going to say and i have real federal sources who
said look into it they think it's fake too so there's a lot of good people in the system let's
play the sheriff and then go to the calls can we queue up that sheriff we have that ready i didn't
tell you yeah here is the sheriff's ad sheriff david clark's radio ad says 911 not best option
urges residents to take firearms licenses this is the guy with the city of the largest city of
their milwaukee this is the sheriff that that the city of milwaukee resides in and the city council
is attacking him well he just got his funding cut they had to cut sheriff's deputies we've
had a lot of sheriffs and police chiefs say buy guns they know law-abiding citizens buying guns
lowers crime we have the clip oh it's ready good uh here is that clip i'm sheriff david clark and
i want to talk to you about something personal your safety it's no longer a spectator sport i
need you in the game but are you ready with officers laid off and furloughed simply calling
911 and waiting is no longer your best option you can beg for mercy from a violent criminal hide
under the bed or you can fight back but are you prepared consider taking a certified safety course
and handling a firearm so you can defend yourself until we get there you have a duty to protect
yourself and your family we're partners now can i count on you this safety message brought to you
by the milwaukee county sheriff's office now again ladies and gentlemen that's what a real government
servant does and it's honorable to be a real servant that's what a real servant does that's
what a real servant does not oh my gosh let's get a bunch of people up here in fancy outfits with
all these epaulets and stars and in dc and say take the guns from the american people so we can
be like chicago and new york the crime capitals of the world chicago is the crime capital of the
world mexico took all the guns their country is the crime capital of the world the only thing
beating them is city-wise chicago 537 murders last year the citizens are under siege because
they don't own guns because they follow the law i mean come on it's time to wake up and the good
news is i think this is going to backfire my instinct tells me this gun grab the corrupt
the corrupt establishment the royalty knows slaves aren't armed they've stolen your bank accounts
your future your jobs they've de-industrialized you to make you poor so they can buy you cheap
you've still got guns and your bible you've still got your beliefs as he calls you bitter clingers
remember obama and you've still got your guns folks you have the belief which they don't control
they want to be god okay no god before them and they want your guns they want your guns and they
want your soul okay let's go to carolyn in washington you're on the air oh hello yes go ahead
hi um i'm a first-time caller um thanks for taking my call um i uh yeah this all this going
on right now it's just really boggling my mind no kidding it's a lot to take in what do you think
about the royalty points i've been making uh it's dead on we got a bunch of north korean dictator
wannabe royalties up there walking around on red carpets it's a stinking joke you punks the
servants learn we're the boss to stop stealing from us and saying we're terrorists and we don't
want to pay eighty percent of our money in taxes no love is the old man in intimidation to them
they uh don't know any different they never experience love it's a threat to them that's
right what did you originally call in for i'm ranting and raving oh um i was uh calling about
uh well it's kind of related to this uh it's the uh since community colleges around here well the
one i used to go to openly preaching socialism well see they tell you communism doesn't exist
and now this is communism we're going under and even when they call for communism people go you
can't criticize that it doesn't exist the devil's greatest trick was he doesn't exist so what do
they teach you at your college well um i didn't see it in the classrooms but i saw um like outside
the community colleges uh these um you know like a little stand they set up um like with flyers and
things like that sandwich board set up yeah they have this um stand there uh saying uh come join
uh the socialist alternative they call it a democrat no no no listen they're all open and
again the mega banks they're monopoly guys they want the general public socialized getting a hand
out and then 90 of the money going offshore to them thank you for the call david in north
carolina great points ma'am david you're on the air okay david hung up let's go to josh in florida
josh in florida you're on the air welcome welcome alex thanks for taking my call i'm a first-time
caller and i wanted to make a point about a gun show i went to this weekend just south of pampa
the small town it's not very big and uh the line was completely out the door around the building
and the police presence was out of control i mean you you wouldn't believe the police state of our
gun shows now like you can't oh yeah they're acting like it's a it's a senator's meeting with
little kids in there or something that they should be at when they're running around like flies we're
getting info from gun dealers that the atf is leaning on them saying look you're not going to
sell semi-autos or we're going to shut you down and they've done this before they're just lawless
did you see rama manual say have the banks kick out all the gun shows and gun shops banks need
to refuse gun owners i mean they're publishing our names they're attacking us like we're jews
in nazi germany absolutely and that that comes as no surprise to me from a chicago mobster but
what another point i wanted to make was that once i got inside the gun show it was so blatantly
obvious the florida department of law enforcement and the atf undercover agents in there watching
people surveilling everyone i mean i i got followed around just for buying high capacity
magazines so i mean it's it's no no they're there now the whole homeland security anti-terror grid
was always set up for gun owners in the takeover globalists run al-qaeda and they're now announcing
we are the al-qaeda thank you for the call yeah i know it's just hellish look the entire homeland
security apparatus what is it 100 billion a year is now after your guns you're the enemy
the new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness get serious and make a
stand with supernatural silver this is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several
hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver can be taken
orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds supernatural silver
is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water purification it is the number
one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect choice
for your emergency preparedness go to supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones
a fighting chance that's supernaturalsilver.com check out our new low prices and like us on
facebook you prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms but if you don't have a home security
system then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when you're
sleeping or away from home who's watching out for intruders check out simply safe it's a new
do-it-yourself home security system that is completely wireless go to getsimplysafe.com
simply safe is independent and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if the grid goes
down you're protected it's completely customizable so you can use it in your home business boat
trailer storage unit or shed getsimplysafe.com simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install
yourself in under 20 minutes so there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you move or
need to relocate you can take the system with you wherever you go you aren't always at home
but simply safe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days a week again
that's getsimplysafe.com looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves how did we ever survive from
natural disasters like hurricane sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships
brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at efoods
direct we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having
a supply of food on hand after hurricane sandy danny from new york city wrote almost all the
grocery stores are closed but i managed to get my efoods just in time to be able to help my
sister and niece it is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late i can warn
you but i can't feed you heed the warnings and do what alex has done call 800-409-5633 today or go
to efoodsdirect.com slash alex and build your food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term
storeable food on the planet call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash alex you can bet your life
on efoods direct millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other
illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a revolutionary new
broad spectrum antibacterial solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted in
a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning
and help improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep staph
pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology has the ability to terminate
entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal
or ionic silver solutions the science digest journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter
it is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to supernatural
silver.com today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20 off that's supernatural silver.com
and like us on facebook coast to coast direct from austin you're listening to the alex jones
broadcasting network network leading a frontal assault on the lies of the new world order
it's alex jones on the gcn radio network jersey peten new jersey tim in connecticut tj in minnesota
kurt north carolina jack in texas mike and idaho many others we're going to you right now have your
comment i'll move the next person jersey peten new jersey thanks for holding her on the air
well thanks alex i want to thank you for the opportunity to speak with you today alex i'm
a licensed and registered professional engineer with nearly 30 years of experience my pathway
to you and the great work that you and your teamwork doing was driven by my desire to
understand the physics of 9 11 that led me to architects and engineers for 9 11 truth
where nearly 2 000 my colleague colleagues representing over 25 000 years of professional
engineering and architectural experience have shown beyond a reasonable doubt that all three
towers are brought down by controlled it's worse than that i've got the police and locals saying
get back the government's gonna blow up building seven and i interviewed the deputy head of
emergency management he said they blew it up and they killed him two weeks after i interviewed him
they killed him barry jennings i mean i've got him on did i heard him on the news that day so
they blew up building seven absolutely folks alex and all of the highly credentialed experts he has
brought to you are right now is the time to act the founders were children of the enlightenment
the constitution and the bill of rights they created are the most significant political
documents ever produced in human history and they said we're not bowing down to royalty anymore i'd
rather die than lick the boots of some punk on a red carpet who sucks my tax money out of me and
tells me he's better than i am and those men defeated an empire nobody had ever beaten and
that's why our stinking criminal government badmouth the founders and hollywood does is
because they're unamerican foreign usurpers god bless you gotta jump jersey mike great point
mike and idaho uh go ahead mike you're on the air first time caller thank you i just a couple of
quick things um jump off here jump off here jump off your speakerphone brother oh sorry what do you
think the timeline is before we really uh people start scooping up people such as yourself and
stewart roads and others who's standing up for what's right they're going to start going after
selective gun owners they'll pick quirky groups like waco burn them down kill them when you resist
you'll be called terrorist and they plan on large numbers of police and military getting killed
that's why cops and military say they're not going to be part of it plus a lot of them are patriots
and then they'll they'll nuke a city or something and say the patriots did it with al-qaeda
we've got three different west point papers now claiming conservatives are going to work with
al-qaeda which is you know is ridiculous but they don't care you know again the globalists run
al-qaeda but they're going to say we're al-qaeda so that's the kind of they're going to do school
shootings mall shootings tsa shootings i mean i know who they are and and just be ready videotape
it expose it when it happens be careful uh they're getting ready to drop the hammer on us this is the
takeover well i just want to also give you an open invitation if you ever come to poquito idaho you
could come on my show it's a local tv show and i know you're i'm not a pierce morgan but it's
called voices of the republic and i sure like to do it keep going call me tomorrow on the radio
uh jack in texas you're on the air moving quick here go ahead alex um this is very important i
have absolute proof of an imminent false flag attack in syria well i mean israel says they've
got to invade because i'm not talking i'm talking about documents i have absolute proof i can send
it to you right now i'm in tarel texas i'm not going to be here very long i can meet with your
people this is imminent this is happening right now i have absolute proof i can't meet with every
person that says it's imminent i mean everything everything i can send it to you right now so
you're in the army uh no sir um i am calling on behalf of 4chan.org the uh the politically
incorrect board um recently a hacker hacked the website of brit am defense and uncovered plans
operations orders emails um the qatari government is hiring these uh british mercenaries to use
ukrainian nationals to sneak russian chemical weapons into homes and detonate them and create
a video they're going to blame it on the russians they're trying to start world war three i probably
signed my own death warrant calling you with this alex it's real it's happening no no no the israelis
say they're in reuters they're about to go in because al-qaeda is going to get chemical weapons
when the west openly put al-qaeda in that's how dumb the royals think the american people are
and it is katar that's involved behind all of this uh unbelievable uh i mean that's actually
in the news and they've been saying go ahead i mean i have everything alex i can send it to you
right now i can meet with your people yeah i don't have time to listen i don't here's the deal we
get people every five minutes wanting to meet with us i mean but but but the issue is you should
shoot a youtube video showing the documents and put it out in public so people can scrutinize them
because you know all documents that are put on the internet aren't accurate but they're clearly
been publicly getting everybody ready for a false flag where they claim syria uses chemical weapons
now they know that won't fly so they're going to say al-qaeda is going to use them so they have to
invade we have to invade because our own al-qaeda has them i mean this is how dumb they think the
public is so jack listen uh why don't you scan those in put them up to youtube uh and uh again
4chan is just it's just you understand anonymous can be good it can be bad but a lot of times it's
it's government sock puppets you understand that i understand that alex look i'm sending it to you
at showtips.info at showtips.info.com um you look at it you be the judge i'm telling you this is
damning this is what are you sending are you sending it right now i'm sending it right now god
help me i'm probably signing my own death no you're not listen listen listen listen i just
sent it to show tips at info wars.com all right well just i mean who knows if it's even real so
quit thinking they're going to get you they don't have real power listen god bless you my friend i
appreciate your call mark in georgia all i know is the government runs al-qaeda publicly even
jerome coursey who would have burned me at the stake five years ago for saying that agrees with
me mark in georgia you're on the air go ahead hey alex uh great show you're right on hey listen i
want to know where can i go to uh get uh get it with a group like the minutemen to uh get ready
to start uh try to take our government back because it is going down like you're saying
it's going down fast well mark we gotta be cool here we gotta be cool here the glub obama's out
saying i don't want your guns i don't want the nda don't fight the bill i'm gonna veto it then
he signs it and he wrote it he's like i don't want your guns don't listen to conspiracy theorists
when we have the bills we need to stay cool they're going to stage stuff and blame it on us
we just do yeah everybody talks about you know taking our government back take it back person
by person wake up police and military they had tsa running illegal checkpoints searching people's
bags and they walk up with guns and say these are armed ones we're going to search you on lamar and
austin there's a newscast kxan and go well it was voluntary you know it was color of law file
lawsuits we kicked them out of houston they're going around city by city city seeing where they
can abuse people all austinites where i live should be up in arms politically about this
saying no to that fight them on every front the answer is not have a big shooting war with the
globalist uh and i appreciate your call but i mean you know that's what it comes down to kurt
in north carolina you're on the air go ahead alex first of all i'd like to say thank you i appreciate
your show and uh i totally agree with what you brought up recently uh about the royalist uh
that you're talking about fight the same people exactly i think it's just another step because
right now they're worried um there's so many people standing up uh in yeah they see everybody
buying guns congress has a nine percent approval rating they're panicking their offense attack is a
defense move we need to go on the double offense on these people exactly and you know you were
talking about how they were going to make it to where the people in the military police were going
to be exempt from this feinstein bill that's just the carrot in front of the car to get the
mule to move where it wants to because the police and military in mass are joining us because we
warned them before it happened exactly and they're trying to draw as many people away from the truth
as they can well just pray for me folks because i can tell you i got good sense and i know how
dangerous this is but we're going to defeat these people together they will do horrible atrocities
sandy hook is so they can say gun owners you're not turning your guns in you're going to cause
the next attack and they can have their own mercenaries do a mass shooting with a hundred
dead kids blame a patsy then they're going to say see we told you you can see it all scripted
fully wake up because folks you can't just turn your semi-autos in and have them leave you alone
this purge is about demonizing all constitutionalist conservatives and libertarians you're the enemy
of the takeover even if you've been co-opted by republicans you're still the enemy the only way
out of this is by standing against them look at what he's done in the past people you obama
supporters need to wake up well i mean most of them are actually halfway awake but they're on
government payment they don't know how to live without the money god bless you kurt
benjamin in texas you're on the air go
okay he's gone now let's talk to chris and kentucky you're on the air
hey alex hey buddy i tell you this is a great time this is exactly what you were saying
start taking it by your counties like sheriff piman in jackson county we're gonna win i tell
you the awakening is even bigger than i thought it'd be people are waking up out here i just
because we've been we've we've been attacking for 20 years before they launched their operation
we're not in the dark no we're not and i like what sheriff piman says i'd rather have a bunch of i
want the feds to stay out of my county there are no provision because they're not taking the guns
away from the citizenry or my deputies he's an outstanding man in that county it's all happening
right now it was all foretold and the founding fathers from 235 years ago are fighting with us
right now their quotes their words the republic they fought for we have been given it as an
heirloom we stand with george washington think of it think of it