Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, get ready, strap yourselves in. It is Friday, the first day of February
2013. We're gonna be here for the next three hours, and then we'll return, Lord willing,
this Sunday, as I always do, 4 to 6 PM Central Standard Time, 5 to 7 PM Eastern for the Sunday
transmission.
She hadn't been on in about four or five months. Rosa Corey, who's one of the best researched,
well-spoken firebrands hailing from, where, San Francisco, and the author of Behind the
Green Mask, U.N. Agenda 21. She will be joining us coming up in the second hour to talk all
things Agenda 21.
Because that is the global treaty to bring in deindustrialization in a system designed,
economies designed to implode in concentric rings down to a feudal system where we are
under total social engineer control. And again, everything is Agenda 21, everything is eugenics.
And as I do more and more research, it just slams me like a ton of bricks how accurate
we are.
And I'm not saying we're accurate, we're good people. I'm saying we know what we're talking
about. We've got them, we have them. This morning, I was almost late to work, because
in amongst my other duties in the morning, I ended up watching about 45 minutes of the
video that is academic and very dry, but bone-shilling.
And the article is up at infowars.com. Population control propagandist, this is at Yale. We
get very little opposition from the public through the sitcoms, drama, and TV. We get
very little opposition of the public because of the very gradual evolution of the characters.
And here they are admitting what we already know, that the dramas, the sitcoms, the soap
operas, not just here, but worldwide, are globalist-financed. ABC, NBC, CBS all get
Melba Melinda Gates money that ends up going to these shows.
And it's the same thing in Africa, Asia, you name it, to demonize the family, to demonize
private property, to demonize liberty. And it's the ultra mega rich on record doing this.
And what's sick is, yes, you can argue there are areas that are overpopulated, like some
areas of India are absolutely hellish, areas of China absolutely hellish. That's not debatable.
It's that they use the pretext of dealing with population to bring in a total control
grid and actually target the middle class and the nouveau riche and the real intelligentsia
that are threats to the old robber barons.
And they're using this whole population thing as a cover to bring in a new dark age that
they're exempt from in their technological reservations. I mean, this is earth shattering
key, key, key, key, key, key information. I mean, this is the real way the world works.
This is why everything's happening. We have a socially engineered system where the general
population is obsolete. They don't just plan to try to have clean industries put in where
people end up only having two children on average or less. And population goes into
a negative push, whether it's Japan, the US, Italy, Germany, every country is the same.
You see, I've actually read the population reports. I've actually read Ehrlich's books.
I've actually read Paul Ehrlich's books and the rest of them. And the Henry Kissinger
documents memorandum 200, State Department memorandum 200, 7277, all of them. I mean,
I see all of them, thousands. I mean, that's all I do.
So much I can't even, I don't even remember 10% of what I've read. I mean, it's so mountainous.
It's so congruent. It's so mechanized. It's so clear cut. It's so diagrammed. And I can
walk out and see it in the billboards, the culture, the TV. I don't even need to, I can
see what they're doing.
Let me go type in and look for a white paper saying this. And I go type it in. I know their
language. I find the exact white paper with the exact words I just envisioned of them
talking about how they planned five years ago, what I'm looking at now.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just
in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct. Introducing
Pro Wine. All of your filtration in one system, portable, on the go. No more do you have two
or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride. You have a system that cuts out the sodium
fluoride and up to 95% of hydrofluorosolic acid. Advanced manufacturing technology combines
silver impregnated white ceramic with new aqua medics advanced media for removal of
fluoride and other heavy metals, all in one filter element. It is the only one that does
it and out of the gates, we have it discounted at 10% off with promo code water. This is
the only system that in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides, herbicides, chloramines,
ammonia, and chlorine. Hydrofluorosolic acid, the most common form of fluoride not covered
by other fluoride filter brands and sodium hexafluorosilicate. Get your Pro Pure with
the new Pro 1 filters today at Infowarsstore.com or by calling 888-253-3139. Millions of people
are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu, and other illnesses. Don't be one of
them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution. Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can
be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold, and food poisoning and help improve
wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful
enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia,
colds, flus, and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the ability to terminate
entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal
or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ
fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go
to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off. That's
SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
You have the power. Humanity has the power. We have the power. Do you want to fight? You
better believe you got one.
Rallying patriots worldwide in defense of human liberty, it's Alex Jones.
Thank you for joining us, listening across the United States, whether it's on our 150
plus AM and FM affiliates, Global Shortwave, the internet at Infowars.com or prisonplanet.com
or watching us at Infowarsnews.com, the TV version of the radio transmission, or of course
listening by the internet or shortwave all across the world.
Thank you so much for tuning in on this Friday, the first day of February, 2013. Probably
one of the most well-spoken, focused fighters against the eugenics, new dark age, global
government system of Agenda 21. Rosa Corey will be joining us, hadn't been on in about
four months.
She was on the nightly news a few months ago, but hadn't been on with me in about four or
five months. She's going to be joining us in the second hour and in studio. Pastor Steve
Anderson is one of the people in an amazing new film that we're carrying. He's the preacher
who lives in Arizona and has to drive through a border patrol checkpoint 100 miles in.
They all know who he is and always want to search his vehicle. And he says, why don't
you do something about the illegals? So they beat him up. That's not why he's joining us,
but that video has been seen millions of times online. A lot of folks know him because of
that.
Also, he has prayed for the downfall of President Obama before, which is biblical, and he's
been demonized nationally for that. That's probably how some of you will know him. But
after the tribulation, Let No Man Deceive You, powerful new Christian film. And even if you're
not a Christian, what are there? A billion, 200 million Catholics and another billion
or so other sects of Christians.
So that's two billion plus Christians out there. People who claim they're Christians,
some estimates are 80% of Americans identify themselves as Christians, though not really
practicing, but still believe in God and identify with Christ. Christians from the lion's den,
and of course that was Jews, but that's what Christianity came out of right through to
all the prophets, right through to 50, 60, 70, 100 years after Christ in Rome.
The Christians said slavery was wrong, and it was mainly white slaves that were slaves
from all over. You weren't Roman, you could be a slave. It was the Christians that helped
phase out slavery 2000 years ago. It was Christians who wouldn't worship other gods and were thrown
to the lions. And this is all on record. Why do Christians submit to tyranny today? Why
did Christians found America by saying no king but King Jesus, King George is a tyrant,
and led that rebellion, but today why do they submit?
And the biggest issue is they teach a pre-tribulation rapture. So we're gonna examine that. And
again, even if you're not a Christian, this is important anthropology, important sociology,
important psychology. The globalists study all the groups out there, and then they manipulate
us against each other.
So I study Islam, I study Christianity, I study it all. I study Satanism, the occult.
I am a Christian. I studied it all, animism, atheism, agnostics, Rosicrucianism, Aleister
Crowley, baloney stuff, all of it. And I'm telling you, the globalists believe in God,
and they believe in spiritual forces. I mean, how do you know when somebody's looking at
you?
You can be walking through the woods on your own property on 1,000 acres. I know I've been
doing that before on my family's property in East Texas. And repeatedly, I know when
somebody's looking at me, and I'm always right. You always know in the restaurant, you feel
somebody staring at you, turn around and somebody's looking at you. And it's somebody you knew
years before, they're like, I thought that was you, Bob, thought that was you, Carol.
They've proven, that's how a monarch butterfly, four generations can fly to northern Canada,
and then one flies all the way back using the sun and magnetic systems, windage, everything,
flying at 10,000 feet all the way to Mexico. That's the incredible cells they found in
fish, they found in birds, and they're in humans as well, that are electromagnetic,
and that are picking up on all sorts of not just magnetic systems, but cells they don't
know exactly what they do, but that are antennas.
I mean, you're picking things up, the globalists know this, they're obsessed with it. And they
want you to be dumbed down and unaware of it. Most of the major atheist movements, the
low level atheist, think they know it all and are real intellectual, and they never
believe it, even in government corruption, that couldn't exist. Things that are admitted
can't exist, it's a very one dimensional, dried, stale perspective, I don't blame people
wanting to be atheist.
You look at establishment religion, boy, that would make me an atheist any day, or at least
an agnostic. But the spiritual, it's definitely real, and humans for our entire history have
known this, so there's always priest, a priesthood who tries to get between you and the universe,
you and God. You and God's creation, the universe, there's always that priesthood that wants
to get between you and your creator, you and the power that is God's creation.
Because that's where the proof of the civilization, the proof of the intelligence is the civilization,
is the creation, is the master builder. People say, that's Illuminati, master builder, great
architect. God is called the great architect and the master builder in the Bible, the Luciferians
take everything and they take it onto themselves, every symbol, every name, they take it and
then there's no symbols left, there's no names left, they've taken them all, they've stolen
them.
Oh, you're talking about something that's the devil, no, you are looking at the counterfeit.
Now, I'm not gonna preach cuz I got a bunch of news to cover, we'll get to that coming
up with the pastor in studio with us today. He's also gonna be on the Nightly News with
Darren McBrain for an in-depth commercial free, commercial free during the interview,
as commercials, as bookends on the TV show of 7 o'clock central every night, Infowarsnews.com.
But the new film is available, Let No Man Deceive You after the tribulation and it goes
well with Romans 13, The True Meaning of Submission by Chuck Baldwin and his constitutional lawyer
son Timothy Baldwin.
Great to give to every preacher, filled with the, I don't know, it's gotta be a hundred
Bible verses about it's your job to stand up against evil and corruption and bullies
and thugs. And that if you don't, God will absolutely hate you more than anybody else,
that you knew innocents were being hurt and you weren't evil but you were a coward.
God hates a coward, you need to get that straight. Justice hates a coward, common sense hate
a coward, women hate a coward, children hate a coward, and cowards hate themselves. A man
who has courage only dies a single death. Cowards die thousands of deaths. Every day
is fear, fear of people think, fear of what's gonna happen.
I absolutely hate fear. I absolutely despise it, because it does kill your intellect. It
is the mind killer, to quote a great writer and I'd say philosopher, Frank Herbert. Fear
is the mind killer, fear is the little death. You let it pass through you, over you, around
you, past you, behind you. Get behind me Satan, get behind me. People say, what does that
mean get behind me?
Get out of my way, get out of the road, get out of my way, stop it, get out, get out.
The devil accuses, tells us all day how we're bad, we're evil, we're guilty. And we all
are guilty one way or another, but are our hearts guilty? Are we doing it on purpose?
Do we love evil? No, and that's why, that's why the system tells you you're bad so that
you feel guilty, so you step aside. When you run into the devil on the road, there is no
turning back, there is no turning back on the road. There is no turning back on the
run.
But we're not running from the devil, we're trying to run to God. Because it's a race,
and the devil, whatever you wanna call it, doesn't want us to achieve that level of awakening
and understanding. Consciousness, the system wants to keep you within this control box
feeling small, feeling ugly, feeling powerless, feeling scared so that you don't break out.
Climb to the surface, come out of the cave, Plato's cave, THX 1138, Robert Duvall climbs
to the top, allegory of the cave and sees the world. Logan's run, climbs out from the
subterranean system of control, the technocracy, and sees the open earth.
An artificial system to control us. And again, there's an hour and a half video, excuse me,
an hour and 50 minute video up at infowars.com right now. Population control propaganda,
we get very little opposition from the public. And they go on to say, we get very little
opposition from the public because of our television programs.
They are a very gradual evolution of the characters. And what do they say, to end the family, to
end fealty, to end any type of honor, where you're just a nobody that's programmed by
the television, by the culture. And they say, by increment, we do it. And it's everything
I've talked about, it's everything Alan Watts talked about, because it's all in Eber Bernays'
three books.
The father of modern propaganda, Sigmund Freud's nephew. When you go watch it, they're sitting
around giggling and getting off on the fact that they're manipulating you because you're
trusting. And you look at these men, these are weak, power grasping, shaking men who
have a look of egomania in their eyes, that they are world controllers, that they are
engineering you, that they have taken control.
And they are world saviors, and they're there to all these PhD students doing their dissertation
in this Yale hour 50 minute thing. It's a nightmare, I haven't even watched the whole
thing yet. I watched about half of it, it was very painful. Cuz I already knew it 100
times over, but just to see them smacking the lips and doddering around. These people
are all cold and intelligent to one level, but they miss any depth or variety or versatility.
Or they would absolutely run the other direction. And they talk about the Rockefellers, everybody
funding them, and Maurice Strong, and Paul Ehrlich, and John P. Holdren, and all of it.
And how I was just here 40 years ago like you, and I've led the worldwide program for
the engineering program in television to break down the family, to help the family. And you
will soon be in this force. I mean, it's all there, and you're just like watching soldiers,
armies built, and they're not even actually trying to reduce population.
I'll tell you about that when we come back and then get into all the other big news.
Looking back on 2012, I know personally I'm thanking God that my family and I made it
through the year from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer
drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out
to those that have lost everything. My friends at eFoods Direct hear from customers every
day that are fortunate to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand. Danny
from New York City wrote in following Hurricane Sandy and said, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister
and my niece. Bottom line, it's better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day
too late.
Feed common senses warning and do what I've done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com
forward slash Alex. They have the best tasting long term storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 and ask about the Alex Jones special or go to eFoodsDirect.com forward
slash Alex. Get self-sufficient today. Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com forward slash
Alex.
Is 2013 your year to achieve more? More vitality, more health, more well-being? Hi, this is
Pastor Jenny. For 25 years, I spent my life's work teaching others how to achieve more.
But in 2010, I got a lesson of my own about RNA drops. I learned that there are millions
of gene switches latent in every single cell of my body that are waiting for an activator.
I learned by taking RNA drops, I could begin to activate that power in my cells and achieve
the more that I desire. I'd like to share what I discovered with you and send you a
free 30-day supply of RNA drops valued at $50 for just the cost of shipping and handling.
Go to RNAFreeSample.com. That's RNAFreeSample.com or call me toll free at 888-577-3703. That's
888-577-3703. RNAFreeSample.com. Discover the more that's waiting for you.
HempUSA.org has a revolutionary wonder food for detoxing the body and rebuilding the immune
system. Microplant powder can help unclog arteries and soften heart valves while removing
heavy metals, virus, fungus, bacteria, and parasites. Plus, it cleans and purifies the
blood, lungs, stomach, and colon. Keep your body clean with microplant powder. Visit us
at HempUSA.org or call 908-691-2608 today. Hi, this is Ted Anderson. Have you ever wondered
why banks, stockbrokers, investment advisors won't talk about gold IRAs? They've been available
since 1986, yet the financial industry won't recognize the value of gold for your retirement.
Gold is outperformed paper investments, yet no word about IRAs. If you would like to have
gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237. Don't get left behind by rising inflation
and low returns. Call 800-686-2237. Secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237. Is this
the year you finally get serious about your family's drinking water? If so, keep listening
for a special offer from Big Berkey Water Filters. Did you know that over 60% of municipal
water is fluoridated? Berkey Water Filters distinguish themselves from many other filtration
systems with the capability to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine, fluoride, arsenic,
and disinfection byproducts from municipal water via the black Berkey and PF line of
filters. Then there's affordability. At only 1.7 cents per gallon, Berkey Water Filters
purify treated and untreated water, even stagnant pond water. Stop and think how much money
you could save by simply reducing buying bottled water and using water filtered by your Berkey
Water Filter. No need to be constantly replacing expensive filters with a Berkey. A single
set of filters can last for 5 to 10 years. Choose the best size Berkey for your needs
at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com. And right now, all GCN listeners get 5% off all ceramic filter
systems. Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY. That's 877-99-BER-KEY or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
Free shipping on every order over $50. Big Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean
water.
You have found it, the tip of the spear in the fight to awaken free humanity, not just
in the US or North America, but worldwide. I am your host, Alex Jones. And remember if
you're a new listener tuning into us on AM and FM stations all across the country, those
are precious affiliates.
And the fact that this broadcast is exploding, even though we come from a smaller independent
radio network, not one of the big three giants, is unprecedented in the history of modern
radio. And it's because station managers, owners, and sponsors in your area understand
that a lot of what I've talked about unfortunately is now coming true. They realize we're in
trouble and they want to get this information out to you as a service.
So be sure and spread the word about all the stations you're listening to. And be sure
and sponsor the local station if you're a business owner. And be sure and support the
sponsors and let them know you appreciate it. That is so important. That is so important.
Because people at Yale, Yale's come out recently and said, let's kill babies, some of the professors
up to age three, even if they're healthy. It's been in the Journal of Bioethics. That's
the new death panel groups where they get their walking orders.
They say, well, the death panel, the bioethics board, says it's okay, so now we can kill
you. And then the police go, well, they're wearing a white lab coat, it must be okay.
That's how Hitler did it. He got his first tyranny into the medical system. And I'll
get more into this with Rosa Corey coming up on June 21. I want to get into all the
other economic news that is incredibly important. Huge purges of gun owners have begun, legal
gun owners.
This is moving faster than I thought. More giant military drills on a stage. We've never
seen anything. This is an order of magnitudes bigger. There's huge drills every day in major
cities terrorizing people to acclimate the public for military occupation. It's all coming
up.
But here's what I want to explain to you. And we covered a lot in my film, it's been
out six years, in game blueprint for global enslavement. Available on DVD at info wars.com
but in higher quality or in prisonplanet.tv, but it's free on YouTube, folks. But don't
have it be pearls before swine, okay?
Go watch it. It has an online bibliography. What is the endgame.com? What is the endgame.com
so you can double check every 30 seconds. We have it marked on the time code with a
bibliography. Where the UN says they want to exterminate at least 80% of the public,
where they state it's US government policy, the British Royal Commission on population.
Anything we quote in the film, it's right there. Even if it's George Herbert Walker
Bush calling for world government, new world order, everybody knows he did that.
And we show the State of the Union, we still give the date, where they said it and where
we got it. The date in Congress of the United States, State of the Union. I mean everything
documented, it's like an online film book. Here's my basic indictment. We've had the
different population associations on that have broken down the numbers. These numbers
are fact, you can look them up.
The eugenicist 150 years ago, well actually about 163 years ago now, by 1850, the robber
baron British royalty and others, even the other financial elite were interbreeding.
So they were having a lot of deformed children, mentally ill children. The reason they started
marrying commoners by the 1930s or so was because Queen Elizabeth has a bunch of siblings
and all of them had to get locked up, just completely insane and deformed and it's a
very sad story.
But that's why they've now been forced to marry commoners. See, they're so elite they
can't even have kids because of the psychos inbreeding together. And I mean psychos, they've
inbred psychopathic traits to create, certain breeds of dogs are overbred and completely
insane and everybody knows that. It's many times worse with humans. I mean most Egyptians,
that's why they would have a dynasties collapse over and over again.
Because the oldest live would live to be about 20. And imagine these would be completely
mentally retarded, king, sterile, unable to talk, totally deformed, and they would prop
them up and worship them as God. And then whatever utterances came from their mouth,
they would then follow immediately.
And this is what we go through. So they were obsessed with, why are we dying? Why are we
deformed? And so all their scientists said, we're gonna discover it. So they discovered
genetics out of it, came eugenics, well, first eugenics, then genetics, then bioethics, biometrics
is over 100 years old.
Everything you know, the first computers, IBM was commissioned by the Rothschilds and
Rockefellers to create computers to try to track why the elites were having, most of
their kids were dying at stillbirth. And this is all on record, race studies, the Hollerith
machines, it was IBM machines, the Nazis had to put the tattoos on people.
I'm gonna come back and finish this. I say I'll do it simply, but it's just incredible.
This is everything. This is why it's all like this. And they've made the decision to cut
off the resources incrementally over time, cuz they've learned you can't resist that.
I'm gonna explain it all when we come back and then get into why all this other stuff
is happening. Because if you don't know this basic foundation, you won't know anything.
We're on the march. The empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now. Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog. Millions of people are going to get sick this winter
from coals, flu and other illnesses. Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural
Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum anti-bacterial solution. Recent advances in
silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent
bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing. Supernatural
Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes
of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, coals, flus and other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest
Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is
emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the
promo code Silver2012 for 20% off. That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action.
Tyranny is here. The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality. It really says
that the state is God. The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most
impressive police states on earth. This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret
network of FEMA camps now being expanded nationwide. This documentary exposes how the continuity
of government program has established an all powerful shadow state. Police state four chronicles
the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen. Prepare to enter the secretive
world of emergency dictatorship, body scammers, sound cameras, citizen spies, stage terror
and cameras on every street corner. It's only the beginning of the new world order's hellish
plan. The police state isn't coming. It's here. Secure your copy today at Infowars.com
or see it online in the highest quality at prisonplanet.tv.
He's bounding down. Are we going to do what they say? Ladies and gentlemen, I have reverse
engineered this entire thing and it isn't hard. The global list of all written books
going back over 160 years describing the problems, why they've done what they've done, why they
made the decisions because they see the general public as absolute dumb animals.
Really the general public just isn't lusting after power. The general public is a mix of
good people, bad people, ugly people, evil people, sweet people, creative people, eccentric
people. It takes all kinds to make the world go round. But hereditary power always ends
up taking over whether it's North Korea, whether it's the kings of Europe, whether it's the
kings of Japan, the emperors, whether it's been the kings of the Chinese.
The communist always just end up turning the Politburo into an above the law hereditary
royalty. You go to places like North Korea, they're now in some cases four generations
into people who are given the seat on the government council or given the seat in the
local government job. And given the house that their grandfather had that was given
to them by the communist.
And this is what they set up. And so imagine you've got inbred groups already inbreeding
for being aggressive, being ruthless, being cunning, being smart. Let's say if your ancestor
is William the Conqueror, who was particularly powerful king, obviously out of France, was
France today, because he was from a commoner.
A king in that area mated with a particularly aggressive barbarian woman. And so then you
get William the Bastard, as he was known, and he then goes into England and takes over.
So they weren't all psychopaths, but they were cunning, smart, aggressive. Then you
inbreed psychopaths, control freaks, sadists, because they're willing to do the horrible
things to stay in power.
In fact, they enjoy it. So it's an attribute for their type of cancer to take control,
to see the general public as cattle, the prey animal, they the Morlocks, we the Eloi. They
use an H.G. Wells analogy, which he wrote nonfiction books admitting that was an analogy
of the ruling class and the general population. That we were pure, that we were beautiful,
that we were sweet, didn't matter.
You won't rule things from the subterranean keep like the Morlocks. You're going to be
fed on. And when one of you gets grabbed and drug away, the others will just run and hide
in the bushes but come back out. And so that's what they do, that they see us like animals.
They say we're animals. And the entire technological system, unlimited money, the unlimited stolen
money of countries and peoples and tribes and other empires has all been poured.
Imagine you're the elite. You say all my kids are dying. My royal line is dying. We've got
massive mental illness. That's why this whole government system, this train that's already
been built, that we've been put on, that's a self-oiling mechanized perpetual motion
system.
That's why it just continues forward because thousands of trillions in the aggregate and
that's conservative, has been pumped into it in the last 160 plus years. And a melding
of the ancient empires, a melding of the ancient royal systems, the corruptions, all the corrupt
minions that served and climbed into the ranks to become lords.
And then to add their genetics to the pool of the super shark, super aggressive cancer.
It's a cancer cell in a body system. They're right, we are a collective, but the individual's
what makes us strong. An individual operating correctly is the opposite of the collective
but is within the collective.
They create a false collective where a cancer program is overlaid. And they know it's a
cancer and know it will destroy the old system, which they live off of. So they decided to
fully re-engineer the entire old system where everything else is eradicated and it's only
cancer. And this is not going to work. It's never worked, but they believe technology
is going to allow them and they all talk about this.
Bertrand Russell and Ted Turner and Paul Ehrlich, they all write these papers. I've listed them
here, I've made films about them where they sit and talk about this. It just thinly, thinly
in many cases not even failed. And so that's why they've gone to a system now where they're
gonna shut off the resources incrementally to bankrupt you and make you go under their
control so they can then sterilize you, so they can then death panel you, so they can
then euthanize you.
And that's why they brag that they fund and run most of the big sitcoms, movies, dramas
with product placement, propaganda placement, that they're now, you hear it on the shock
radio. You see it in the movies, making fun of old people, making fun of babies, saying
children are gross, being married is stupid. Men are all dumb, women are in charge, not
to empower women to isolate them and to make them be under state control and only trust
the state as their husband.
And that's what they say, the state will be the husband. And so they're taking control
of the human system at a subconscious level. And they even write about this, they realize
it because they hate the strength of the unwashed masses. They hate the vigor, they hate the
hybrid power. They hate it to the ends of the earth, it is a glaring light to them.
And they want it blotted out. So really, this is why I indict them and I'll give the rest
of the news. The globalists know that once you industrialize a country and even bring
in clean industry, that the population, I said goes down to about, for every two adults
they have on average two children.
That's not actually accurate. In the entire industrialized world, it's about 1.5. The
US is right at two people for every two, but that's because of the 10 million or so immigrants
brought in every five years. We're actually imploding as well. I mean, it's different
numbers every year, but it's about 1.3 children for every two children in Italy, about 1.3
to 1.2 in Japan.
It's about 1.5 in Germany. It's about 1.3, 1.4 in Russia. It's about 1.3 in Britain,
if you cut out the immigrant influx. So the West is dying. And this was done through social
engineering, done through the 50s and 60s, social revolution sold as empowerment but
actually destroyed the family, to get both people working.
So now the state raises your children, very diabolical plan. Now, that's the plan they're
going with in the West. They have a surface plan in Africa, Asia, Latin America claiming
that through the sitcoms and dramas and conditioning. And they admit it's all conditioning and laugh.
Look at the little animals, they don't know we're doing this. And they stand around. I
mean, I got a video posted at info wars.com.
Top professors, top globalist, the head of the UN program, and they just sit there and
laugh at you that this is all public. And they talk about how they're gonna incrementally
do this. And they've got all the PhDs out there, all the people about to get their PhDs
in the graduate program, sitting there listening to this getting off on it.
And they go to TED TV events and they have the intelligentsia there, the technocrats
there, the mid-level technocrats. And they say, yeah, we're gonna reduce this number
and show an equation of humans with carbon dioxide and show it going to zero, which means
zero humans. Everybody laughs and Bill Gates laughs. See, it's all a laugh because that's
gang sign.
It's like they speak another language. It's an equation, very simple equation. But they
know people watching that, how are they even gonna know an equation? They don't know what
the three branches of government are. They show an equation that they're going to kill
us. And he actually says, we've gotta get this number down to zero, using vaccines to
lower their population.
He even says it, shows the equation, and then they all laugh. Yeah, it's funny to them,
cuz they're not really trying to save the planet. That's how they get the low-level
people into this. They're a bunch of inbred psychopath sadists up top. And you read the
1949 Royal Commission on Population, that's the blueprint of all the modern stuff we followed.
Ehrlich, the UN, agenda 21, UNESCO, all of it.
You read all of that, Biological Diversity Assessment 96, all of it. They say, well,
if we go in and do clean industry, or even give them basic horticulture, and drill wells
for them, water wells. They talk about how the Christian missionaries are going in and
actually helping people, and that's gonna be a problem.
They go, we've gotta come in claiming we're helping, but we've gotta block all this development,
even though it'll lower their population. And they'll start having less than two kids,
because they'll be informed, they'll wanna have some more wealth. They won't need ten
kids, cuz half of them are gonna die to take care of them in their old age.
Plus, the only wealth you have as being really poor is children. By the way, it is the real
wealth. But the point is, is that the globalists all know they've all got five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten kids, they all know that. Ted Turner's got five, biggest landowner and
15 jet airplanes, all the rest of it. You're a useless eater, he's not, according to his
mindset.
So you've got all this going on, they blocked, and they say this in the 1949 Commission on
Population. You can pull up the synopsis online, you've gotta go to a big library to find it.
We've done it, we've shown it in film, shown the screenshots. They admit, they just say,
we're just gonna keep them from industrializing.
That'll cause a population explosion, but we'll then just mitigate that. And of course,
that's the vaccines and programs at a certain point, but we wanna use that cheap labor pool
in select development zones with a mercantile model, that's globalism, 2.0 is globalism
of mercantile.
A selective system, a selective insider crony system where they pick the winners to leverage
out the West so we can then social engineer them. So they wanna social engineer the West
cuz we're the real target. Highest education, highest IQ, genetically in the studies, whatever
issue you wanna look at, that's the main target.
Of course, these are all averages. And they're also targeting the Chinese, again, they're
also targeting the Japanese, but they're targeting every other country, ladies and gentlemen.
And countries like Africa are just slated for extermination. That's why some countries
have lost half their population in the last 30 years. I mean, this is so diabolical.
To grow a giant people bomb, point out the problem, offer your solution, globalism, which
is really blocking clean energies that are developed while claiming you're promoting
them.
And then only using that as wealth transfers in boondoggles that aren't even supposed to
work on record. Solyndra and others where they don't even build anything and fake electric
cars while blocking carburetors in the 70s that got 100 miles to the gallon on record.
I mean, this is so evil, ladies and gentlemen, because they're cheating. They're not smarter
than us that they're in control. These royals in almost every dynasty, no matter which group
they were, African royals, and there were plenty of those.
There was a King of Africa that ruled the Middle East for a while, probably richest
man in history. So you can look that up and show that richest man in world history was
African. The Asians had their kings, all of it, it's the same system that they are willing
to then always kill whoever became the king or the queen would then kill or lock up their
family members.
Meet Manza Musa, the first of Mali, the richest human being in all of history. And there's
an example and a painting of him. Okay, so this is the type of stuff that goes on and
they all operate the same. So just like a grizzly bear will go and smell, a male grizzly
bear will go and smell a male baby and try to kill it.
Because he sees it as a threat later in territory and food and mates, just like lions and tigers
do that. The system is doing that, but to all of us in a power grab, they see us as,
and we can show the article out of the UN just last week, as locust, as a horde of locust.
Grasshoppers coming and eating all the plants down to the roots. They see us as a disease
because this is their world they've conquered.
But then the sick thing is they actually increased populations, kept them from stabilizing as
a people bomb to leverage out the West and sell the West on eugenics ideas. Cuz most
trendies will tell you, of course there's too many people, of course, yeah, of course
they're putting stuff in the water.
What do you think we've got to do this for the Earth? They're not even doing it for that.
They're doing it to just control everybody and their main target. It's come out a decade
ago or more. They have school study tests where they give them to sixth and seventh
graders and the boys that show the highest aptitude, black, white, doesn't matter, and
who show the leadership traits.
Those are the ones that get flagged. You get called into the principal's office or the
nurse's office and they say, you're a troublemaker, we wanna put you on Ritalin. Even when the
people aren't troublemakers, they try to put them on it because it's targeted to cause
neuron death, brain shrinkage, and also organ problems.
The heart gets larger and has ventricle issues. That's just a few of the side effects. This
is a scientific program laid out in grids like we're animals in a coyote extermination
program or something. They're trying to wipe people out, dumb down their opposition, neutralize,
put the public in a trance, and then carry out the orderly, gradual, ambient extermination
of the general population.
Now there's Margaret Sanger quote, the most merciful thing that a family does to one of
its infant members is to kill it. She was talking about kids period. This is a death
cult. And so these people stand around like they're saviors of the world. They're not
saviors of the world, they are stealing the world.
And by the way, it's the globalists doing open air genetic planting all over the planet.
They're the ones with thousands of laboratories, thousands firing gene guns into random plant
animal, bacterial, you name it, organisms to create mutations. They're the ones releasing
the ingredients to mousepox for humans that kills over 90% of those that come in contact
with it, and it's airborne.
They're the ones, these UT professor Pianca and Dr. Peter Singer, what at Princeton, go
look up any head of a biology department, type in eugenics population control. You're
not let in to the club unless you're for this. That's why Pianca, remember this famously
five years ago, gave a speech to the Texas Academy of Sciences. He got their highest
award.
It's been to Europe. And he said, I look forward to the airborne Ebola being released and 90%
of us dying, including my family. It's sad, but it's for the better. And there was a standing
three minute ovation. Photos were taken, newspapers reported with crying. Even my family's gonna
die. And everyone was so moved by it. Yes, all the top Texas Academy of Sciences people.
I talked to the reporters that were there. They were taking photos and covered it. And
they estimated 90% stood in the ovation and it went on for three minutes as he projected
on the PowerPoint a giant screen of pile of red skulls, red skulls.
He actually went and did a Google search later of that photo. It's a Rwandan pile of skulls.
You can actually do the image search. Giant red pile of skulls and they're in their church.
They're in their church standing ovation, standing ovation, standing ovation. It's their
church. It's their time to cry. It's their time to have a sacrament. It's their time
to take the blood of Satan, not the blood of Jesus.
It's their time to take communion. It's their time, it's their time, it's their time, their
time. And as your factory shut down, as your businesses shut down, as things bankrupt and
rot, they see it as a victory. As Detroit falls, they see it as a victory. And then
they all are building a Gen 21 compact subsystem districts that are openly known in the planned
Opelis documents in all their statements as the governing corporate stakeholder zone.
Those will be armored. Those will be lavished. The latest medical systems, the latest entertainment,
unlimited power. Those areas are exempt from the rolling blackouts already globally going
in. They turn our power off now on rolling blackouts in Austin to the point we have to
have generators.
They're talking about taxes on those, but the quote government district downtown and
the key agenda 21 new high rises, they are exempt and they're exempt from the increased
power prices. The city of Austin decides what you pay according to your needs. They decide
food storage, check survival tools, check weapons and water filters, check. But what
about a permanent source of cooking power that can run forever without buying fuel or
paying for maintenance? Introducing afterburner stoves, home of the original patented rocket
stove that Kelly kettle and the solo stove afterburner stoves has what you need and now
offers all GCN listeners are complete preparedness packaged with the means to cook meals and
sanitize water. Whether you dig in or bug out, cook almost any meal with just a handful
of sticks. We already have the lowest online prices guaranteed, but if you enter coupon
code GCN at checkout, we'll knock off an additional 15% and send you our amazing six
hours solar rechargeable light bulb absolutely free all for only $249 visit afterburnerstoves.com
or call 866-716-5214, 866-716-5214, afterburnerstoves.com. Cook hot meals with just a handful of sticks.
Feeling like there are too many pressures and demands on you? Losing sleep, worrying
about tests and schoolwork, either on the run because your schedule is just too busy?
You may be under too much stress and it may be affecting your mind. Get your mental edge
back with Neutropic Mind Power from mindregard.com. Neutropic Mind Power is not a drug, but a
natural supplement. Its 12 powerful ingredients are natural and non-GMO, plus it's gluten-free,
wheat-free and formulated by Americans for Americans by an NSF certified laboratory.
Neutropic Mind Power is available at mindregard.com, spelled M-I-N-D-R-E-G-A-R-D.com and comes
with a 100% money back guarantee. Free your mind with Neutropic Mind Power, a cognitive
supplement from mindregard.com. Mindregard, clearly see tomorrow and yesterday, today.
All in love. With food storage savings this February at beprepared.com. Starting today,
beprepared.com saves you over $300 with a premium 1600 one-year supply, including 126
cans of freeze-dried and dehydrated food. Or get the new gourmet 14-day food supply
with a full 2000 calories per day with pre-planned menu. Stroganoff and noodles are 20% off with
purchase of six or more. Mountain House pork chops are back in stock at 34% off. Pack your
own low-moisture foods with our new do-it-yourself super pale combo on sale at 22% off. Add to
your preparedness with minor surgery kits at 15% off. And wool-blended blankets are
only $11.89. The February fall in love with savings sale starts today at beprepared.com.
For contents and details, visit beprepared.com or call 800-9
Folks, I know I'm ranting. You should be ranting, too. You should be really upset,
as well. I mean, this is all public. I mean, if you go to infowars.com or prisonplanet.com
in the featured news section, population control propaganda, we get very little opposition
from the public because we are very gradual evolving the characters on the TV shows.
This is going on all over the world. And it's got the quotes in there about how they're
basically breaking up society and the family to save the earth from population and how
it's all Paul Ehrlich's plan and how it's the UN plan. And this is at Yale. And there
are literally thousands of these videos where they sit around and the Yale put this on its
science section website. They're not hiding this, okay?
Cuz they know the average person that watches TV, you tell them, hey, there's messages in
there, there's messages in there. They're like, yeah, right, there's messages where
we live in the Soviet Union. That's why you've got all the anti-gun messages, all the anti-founding
father messages. I was last night up here working and I saw a clip of that Milwaukee
sheriff on Piers Morgan, I guess on Monday, I'd missed it, or Tuesday.
It'd been a few days ago and Piers Morgan was sitting there talking to him about, why
aren't you for any background checks? Why don't you wanna close the loopholes? And the
sheriff's like, because it doesn't work. Criminals are still gonna get guns. And that's the whole
point. There's already background checks on law abiding citizens.
But they're using that to come after us. And I've got gun purge news where that's happening
of people with no criminal record, veterans and others, getting arrested and charged with
felonies in New York before the law even went into effect. Checkpoints where it's a routine
vehicle check. You have a 30 mag clip in a bag in your backseat and you're going to jail.
That's to a veteran who's involved running a program raising money for other veterans.
One big awards in the community and people are like, he's a veteran, he wins awards.
Why is the sheriff's department, why is the grand jury throwing the book at him? You're
the enemy. You're a robot that's now to be decommissioned. You've gone out and fought
for the New World Order and shot up with the deadly vaccines and they're not killing you
fast enough.
The DU isn't killing you fast enough. You're supposed to come back here and die or go to
prison. You're the number one enemy. You're what Homeland Security is targeting. I've
got all these articles where vets are getting targeted. It's like it's weird, they're pulling
vets over. The cops just say they're pulling me over for no reason.
They've got your license plate scanned. You're in a database. It's telling them in many of
these major cities to pull you over. See now it's not just warrants or priors with these
scanners. It's now vet. That's a vet, pull him over. And they know when they're vets,
they walk over.
So you're a vet, got back from Iraq last year. Get out of the car. I'm gonna search it. Look,
look, they're coming for everybody, okay? They're coming for us. They wanna start a
civil war. They've got a purge going. I've got a stack of articles on that front. This
is social engineering, where they hire cops now that'll follow orders and show they'll
follow orders.
And they put them on the street and a lot of them will do whatever they're told. You've
either got departments run by good people that are saying, get guns, protect yourself.
This is tyranny. You got 1,000 plus Green Berets signing a public letter saying they're
gonna resist this and it's tyranny. You've got people showing whose side they're on.
You're either gonna kneel to this or you're gonna resist it. And we better resist it in
the Infowars right now. By the way, we go to infowarsstore.com. We are giving away 150,000
bumper stickers free in groups of 50. Infowars.com bumper stickers, average sticker gets seen
about 20,000 times a year they estimate, depending on where you live, 10 to 30,000.
So I just say 20. Ladies and gentlemen, we're giving 150,000 away. How many tens of millions
is that? They'll see it. Infowars.com stickers, save the Constitution. Infowarsstore.com,
they're going really quick. I put it up last night. Go there, send us your email, free
shipping, free stickers, 100% free. Infowarsstore.com.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
Introducing Pro1, all of your filtration in one system, portable, on the go. No more do
you have two or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride. You have a system that cuts
out the sodium fluoride and up to 95% of hydrofluorosolic acid. Advanced manufacturing technology combines
silver impregnated white ceramic with new aqua medics advanced media for removal of
fluoride and other heavy metals, all in one filter element. It is the only one that does
it and out of the gates, we have it discounted at 10% off with promo code water. This is
the only system that in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides, herbicides, chloramines,
ammonia and chlorine, hydrofluorosolic acid, the most common form of fluoride not covered
by other fluoride filter brands and sodium hexafluorosilicate. Get your Pro Pure with
the new Pro1 filters today at Infowarsstore.com or by calling 888-253-3139.
Reaching war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, Rosa Corey, firebrand, great research author. He's going to be joining us in the
next segment. Give us an update on Gena 21, the latest info there. I haven't even gotten
into all the news. I'll intersperse it in this hour and the next. Pastor Steven Anderson
is going to be joining us in studio as well with a new film we're going to be talking
about.
I haven't even gotten into all the other news yet. I mean, just look at this financial news.
It's just amazing. Another Harvard study finally getting attention out of the Huffington Post.
I thought it's a conspiracy theory, Huffington Post. Harvard study confirms fluoride reduced
to children's IQ massively, reviewing more than 27 other studies by governments and major
universities.
Reduces IQ, increases cancer. And of course, that's just sodium fluoride when they put
in the hydrofluorosolic acid. Of course, Paul Ehrlich and the Lighthouse Science are John
V. Holder, and I mean, they talked about that. It's an adjuvant to accelerate all the other
soft kills. The bisphenol A's accelerates those, turbo charges them.
The aluminum dioxide they're spraying on us, all the other goody goods. And then of course,
the globalist all religiously like the plague. On record, the Chinese elite, the US elite,
you're appealing, they all literally obsess on purified water organics religiously. But
they want you to have it, cuz they care about you and your family.
They're good people. Now, I started plugging this, but ten seconds does not have to plug
it. If you go to infowarsstore.com, and you go to the bumper sticker area, you'll see
it says free stickers. You can also buy them at cost, at cost, like 4.99 for 50 stickers.
But if you wanna get them totally free, no shipping, no money, 0, 0, 0, 0. Might be one-tenth
of a cent the amount of computer energy you use, electricity, while you're on the website.
So I guess it may cost you about one-tenth of a penny. But that's your own money or electricity
bill. I guess I lied, it's not totally free. But I'm not charging you anything. If you
wanna start splitting hairs, how many angels can dance on the head of a possum?
All of this type of stuff, how many chimpanzees can dance on the head of a pin? I've made
that term famous now. You can go there and we've got, I don't know, like six or seven
new bumper stickers that are also available for sale. But you can get these for free,
50 of them. But you've got to copy the pledge and send it back to our email for our liability.
Cuz I already have homemade stickers where LA sends me a bill saying someone stuck a
homemade sticker up.
If somebody sticks an Obama sticker up in LA, do they send me $100 bill saying they'll
arrest me? Of course, obviously, I'm not gonna pay it, it's made up. It's not even one of
our stickers. Everybody gets to sell bumper stickers to put on people's cars. It's not
my fault if somebody buys a can of Coca-Cola and goes and throws it at somebody.
Are we gonna blame the Coca-Cola company? I mean, again, that's an example of what we're
talking about here. But you have to just be over the top, just wherever you want it sent,
you just send the email back with the attached PDF, pledging to put it on your own property
or to give it to others who wanna put it on their property.
And it's 50 stickers, that's easy to give out. It's a great conversation piece. It's
all available at infoawastore.com. Now, I put it on YouTube last night, we can give
out about 3,000 groups of 50. As of this morning, about 1,600 had already been given out. So
by the time I plug this, everyone's gonna rush in there.
So that doesn't mean everybody's gonna get them free. We'll probably pull the offer by
the end of the show. But youareindangerinfoawastore.com, that'll get people talking. It's a great conversation.
There are so many great new stickers. And again, we got 150,000 printed, another 30,000
of the same stickers for sale at cost, at cost, at cost. You pay the shipping and 4.99
or 4.95 for 50, and that is the cost.
I had them break it down. That is the cost. That is the cost. Bumper stickers at cost
for those that wanna help us do more. And if we get donations and we get financial support
and the money comes in, I'll start doing this every month. Cost is like $20,000, I think,
to get the stickers and ship them.
I think Weldon said 30,000, but the point is, it'll reach tens of millions conservatively.
It's part of Operation Paul Revere.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers. The prognosis for the entire planetary
economic system runs from bad to worse. The globalist model is to shut down societies
and starve patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover. That's why we've assembled
the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarshop.com.
These are items that I did research on, that I personally use. You've got the life straw
so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go. The Ktor hand-crank generator
to charge up key equipment during power outages or out in the field. Strategic Relocation
Third Edition by Joel Skousen. When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein. TheraSafe used by
Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event. Hand-crank shortwave
AM-FM radios. Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com
and your purchase makes our Infowars possible. We're getting prepared. Are you? Infowarsshop.com.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog. You prepare by purchasing gold, food and firearms,
but if you don't have a home security system, then you're missing a critical weapon in your
arsenal for home protection. When you're sleeping or away from home, who's watching out for
intruders? Check out SimpliSafe. It's a new do it yourself home security system that is
completely wireless. Go to getsimplisafe.com. SimpliSafe is independent and off the grid.
It runs on battery power, so even if the grid goes down, you're protected. It's completely
customizable so you can use it in your home, business, boat, trailer, storage unit or shed.
Getsimplisafe.com. SimpliSafe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself and under 20 minutes
so there's no need to let a stranger into your home. If you move or need to relocate,
you can take the system with you wherever you go. You aren't always at home, but SimpliSafe
will stand guard, protecting your property 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. Again, that's
getsimplisafe.com. Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers?
Well, so does he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin,
Texas, Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is Friday, the first day of February, 2013, and we're going to
be going to a very special guest, the author of Behind the Green Mask, U.N. Agenda 21,
Rosa Corey, a book we sell at the mfowarstore.com online book video slash patriot bookstore.
Very important to get that book and get that out to county commissioners, sheriffs, police,
city planners, cuz most people are following agenda 21. They just don't know because they're
compartmentalized.
This is basically the red pill with a green cover. Okay, the green red pill. Now, before
we go to her, this is the type of news that I have here in front of me. And this is all
up at prisonplanet.com and mfowars.com. This is now every day. I've never seen the magnitude
of huge invasions, practicing taking over government buildings, universities, facilities,
public schools. They're now saying the army will respond to, quote, domestic terrorism.
And they're calling terrorism, quote, gun crime. The whole homeland security system
officially to go after gun owners. This is a way to purge people. And speaking of that,
also up at mfowars.com, and this is in the local news, decorated combat veteran arrested
charged with five felonies for possession of an AR magazine.
Those are now illegal in New York State. And it turns out his family's just now speaking
out, this happened before it was even officially implemented. They don't care. And it said
a routine vehicle check. They have checkpoints all over New York now, folks. They now have
them in Texas. They're gun checkpoints. They call them gang checkpoints, vehicle checkpoints.
And they know you're a vet, it's in the computers, and they're going after you. And again, it's
not every jurisdiction, but some of these jurisdictions have really evil police.
They're now hunting the veterans, and that's on record. Department of Homeland Security
targets gun collector. And the KRQE piece I wanna play later, they're like, well, they
caught him by this. And then it goes on to say he hadn't done anything wrong, and then
he's a firearms importer of decades.
And they claim a serial number might not have been properly on one rifle. And it's a local
gun dealer. And they go, well, he might not have filled out all his forms right. And the
news acts like he's the, and they have a neighbor woman. You gotta see the video at mfowars.com
on the KRQE going, he's just so evil, I mean, my gosh, I saw the guns, I saw them bringing
the guns out.
I hope something's done about him. I mean, just amazing. So we've got that, Newtown calls
for armed school officers. Gun control officials set sights on ammunition and background checks
now to take those guns. Teams shot at Atlanta school, but they had an armed police officer
there, so it got stopped, so that's the answer.
Suspect suicide bombing kills two at US Embassy in Turkey. Well, that's really heating up
over there. That's some of the news on that front we're gonna be getting into. DHS revamping
immigrant welcome materials set to include Obamacare, how you don't just get your babies
paid for now, free Obamacare.
But citizens have to buy the insurance, and the official IRS website says they may make
families buy up to $20,000 a year as a new average within three years. This year, premiums
are set to double from average of 5,000 to 10,000 per person. Within three years, 20,000
per family, cuz it's mandated, written by the insurance companies, my gosh, unbelievable.
That's CNS news, Obamacare to soon cost average American family 20,000 a year, natural news
story up at infowars.com by Mike Adams. Stocks jolted by jobs data, Dow briefly test 14,000,
that's cuz of dollar devaluation, the real economy is going into free fall.
Excuse me, gas prices heading up again. Yep, now it's time for inflation, 8.5 million Americans
left labor force in the last four years. 169,000 Americans drop out of labor force in January
alone. Yeah, hey, listen, I was realizing I was about to hire some more crew members,
but I just realized they're gonna force me to get Obamacare.
I don't know if I can keep who I've got. Anyways, all part of the agenda 21 shutting down the
economy. You can have a coal power plant, but we're gonna bankrupt it. Again, this is
the admitted program to bankrupt us because only the insiders are exempt from everything.
Now joining us is a lady that more and more, other than maybe myself or somebody like Glenn
Beck is out there really exposing agenda 21, something I've been covering for 17 years.
And I'm proud of the fact that we forced this out in the open.
She wrote the best little book, cuz other books out there are like fiction and stuff
about this, so really weird. Hers is nonfiction, it's only 168 pages long, great bibliography
at the bottom of each page. Behind the green mask, you want agenda 21, all the information
you need to understand what is happening in your town, why it's happening, who's behind
it, and what you can do to stop it.
Awareness is the first step in resistance. She is a ASA forensic commercial real estate
developer and appraiser specializing in eminent domain valuation. Only 30 years of experience
analyzing land use and property, now it's over 30 years, enabled her to recognize the
planning revolution sweeping the nation while fighting to stop huge development project
in her city.
She researched the corporate, political, and financial interests behind it and found Unigine21.
Rosa speaks across the nation and is a regular blogger on her website, DemocratsAgainstUnigine21.com.
Now again, we sell her book at InfowarsStore.com. My point here is, and we're gonna go to her
and give her the floor for the first few segments, and I've got some questions and I wanna open
the phones up for your questions.
We've gone every town around Austin, Austin's a command base of this, every town's being
taken over by it. And what it means is, you can't build an office on your house you've
owned for 30 years and got two acres. Your property taxes are gonna go up, your power
prices are gonna double.
But the selective insiders who get waivers, their power bill gets cut. That's happening
in Austin, that's happening in San Francisco. Government has the lowest rate. Next is groups
that get certified by the local environmental council, but you can't get certified unless
some payoffs get made. This is open criminal mafia, but they act like trendy liberals,
so it's a cover.
But you go to their meetings, it's the Dallas Cowboys are there locally, retired ones, big
bank heads, Republicans. That's why all the Republicans leadership's behind this, Mitt
Romney, you name it. It is bipartisan, global screw job. Now, you can't cut a tree what
ten inches around in Austin, even if it's an invasive cedar, they'll come and find you.
I know one guy got to find something like $50,000 in a week for cutting invasive cedars
growing up under his fence at his wrecking yard.
So it's not even a plant from here, but they can cut down giant five foot around oaks if
they wanna build something. So that's just the tip of the iceberg. I'll take you now
to Rosa Corey joining us via phone cuz she's on the road. She's traveling the entire US,
battling them. And she's been very, very effective because on many other issues, she's what you
call a liberal.
But a real liberal, someone who's more like Thomas Jefferson, who wants everybody to have
equality and freedom. The system that calls itself liberal, they are the globalist operatives
using that as camouflage. And she joins us now, and we're gonna break in four minutes.
But roll through the basics of what it is, how they're adapting to our counter strike
against them, and some of the biggest criminal actions they're engaged in right now, Rosa
Corey.
Hey, Alex. You know, what we're talking about here is the erection of a totalitarian state
right in front of us. This is what globalization is. It's the standardization of all systems.
And so you're seeing it in every possible element, every possible aspect of your life
from healthcare to law enforcement to schools to land use, water use, restrictions. This
is the way that corporations take over. This is the corporatocracy. So what do corporations
want? They want low wage workers, global markets, standardized systems, and they want to destroy
competition. And this is what we're getting here. This is artificial scarcity all over
the world, whether you're in the UK or Australia, New Zealand, Canada, the United States, EU,
wherever you are, this is the globalization of all systems. And we're experiencing this
now because we have a long way to fall in the United States in order to bring us to
the same level as developing nations. So when you think about corporatocracy, it's about
developing new markets. There's no loyalty to existing markets. So if we collapsed into
poverty or slightly below the median for the entire world, that is of no concern to the
huge corporations. What they're looking for is to bring up the very low third world
nations so that they can buy their goods and work cheaply. This is what we're looking
at. This is what we're dealing with here. This is a totalitarian state being erected
because they need to control all system inventory and control. That's what this is about.
And the cover is it's for the earth. But I've been to the smart growth conferences as early
as 97. In fact, we have some bombshell video that Mike Hanson has that he needs to upload
to his YouTube channel, my camera guy at the time, where they were just admitting it's
a takeover. They'd laugh when my camera was off and just go, of course, it's a takeover.
And I had some really mean Dallas cowboy guy. I forget his name. He's famous, big white
guy with long, long gray hair. Just push me out of the way. Just like, yeah, you better
get out of my way. I mean, they know what they're doing. Yes, they do know what they're
doing. And that's, you know, this is really hard for people to believe. They think, well,
you know, this can't be possible. How can this be going on, for instance, in the United
States, the totalitarian, you know, dictatorship happening. But this is what it looks like.
People are not aware that this is what it looks like in your town. They're not going
to call it agenda 21. They'll call it sustainable development. They'll call it regional plans.
You'll see it as water and land use restrictions, smart growth, wild lands project, common core
in the schools, that standardization of your school. And they'll lie and say, we're going
to give you park land. We're going to take this farmer's land is 5000 acres and not pay
him anything. We're just going to take it. Then they turn around and build condos on
it that that the mayor who takes it his buddy builds the houses. I mean, it's it's just
unbelievable.
Yeah, this is about what they're doing is it's a completely unlevel playing field because
they're using your taxes to subsidize low income development and high density transit
oriented.
So they can raise the general public's taxes even more. That's what Bloomberg says. Let's
talk about that. You're going to live in a 250 square foot San Francisco is doing it
to apartment. They're going to raise your taxes in an actuary to force you into that.
We'll be right back with the incredible social engineering.
Injuries, slow healing, aches and pains, constipation, weakness, fatigue are all common. The older
one gets the progressive deterioration of the body that occurs almost universally. The
older one gets can partly to significantly be prevented with conscientious attention
to nutrition. If the Hanselman can play rugby in their 90s, then it is possible for everyone
in North America to experience a more youthful life as well. One key ingredient to warding
off aging and reversing some of it is the type and quality of protein consumed all protein
foods or supplements you currently consume are heat damage, destroying 50 to 75% of your
ability to utilize the bodybuilding amino acids. One world way is not heat damage and
allows your body to utilize 100% of the amino acids. This feat no one else has achieved.
The results to your health can be amazing. Call 888-988-3325. That's 888-988-3325. Or
visit Oneworldway.com. That's Oneworldway.com. Don't throw away leftovers. Instead, throw
all your leftovers, vegetable peels, eggshells, coffee grounds, pizza crusts and more into
the Bokashi. If you love to garden and compost but don't like the hassle of turning a compost
bin or the smell, then check out the EM Bokashi food waste recycling system from Terra Organics.
Finally, a way to recycle all your food and plant waste safely and effectively and stop
using fertilizers. The EM Bokashi food waste recycling system. Rather than decomposition,
the Bokashi system uses fermentation to break down waste so it takes less time to create
nutrient-dense humus for crops or gardens with no turning and no obnoxious odors. To
learn more and order your Bokashi online, visit tereganics.com and click on the orange
button. That's tereganics.com. Spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X.com. Or call 866-369-3678. That's 866-369-3678.
Recycle all your food wastes in about six weeks with the Bokashi food waste recycling
system from tereganics.com. Tereganics. Life's getting better.
On the average, Americans work between 45 to 50 years hoping to build up enough wealth
to retire and live out their golden years. Unfortunately, with taxation, the rising cost
of food, energy, housing, and medical, many retirees are forced to live below the poverty
line. Is this a flaw for the enterprise or is our monetary unit we call the Federal Reserve
Note forcing us into perpetual debt, ensuring inflation and higher taxes? These questions
and more can be answered by reading G. Edward Griffin's book, The Creature from Jekyll Island.
Congressman Ron Paul states it's what every American needs to know about central bank
power. A gripping adventure into the secret world of international banking cartel. Hi,
this is Ted Anderson. I will give a silver dollar from the early 1900s to anyone who
purchases this book. Call 1-800-686-2237 and order a copy today. It's critical that the
public be made aware of the system. Call and order your copy today at 1-800-686-2237. That's
1-800-686-2237. Hey there. Frank Bates here. Have you heard
about the weird device that could wipe out 280 million Americans? This is really scary
stuff. Defense experts warn that this odd device poses the gravest threat we've ever
known. In fact, just a few weeks ago, former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an
op-ed piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat. I can't believe
that more people aren't talking about this. It may be because the liberals and the government
are trying to cover it up. That's why my friend just created a free video at weirddevice.com
that exposes this threat and blows the doors off the conspiracy. Go watch the shocking
video at weirddevice.com right now to discover exactly what it is, plus discover the number
one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack. I'm not sure how long this
video will be online, so go to weirddevice.com before it's gone forever. Again, that's
all
All right, Rosa Corey is one of these guests where I just find it so hard to shut up because
everything she's saying is true.
Everything she talks about gives me flashbacks of 16 years, 17 on air.
But listeners were like, have you seen these UN documents?
Have you seen the Rio meeting four or five years ago?
This is in 1996 or so, 1997, cuz they just had the Rio meeting in 1992.
And so I've been on this forever, and then I know how criminal it is.
I'm not up here with rhetoric, okay, calling them criminals.
It's diabolical mafia takeover through zoning, through government, all selectively enforced.
Let's go back now to Rosa Corey.
Rosa, we were getting into these new compact coffin apartments.
Continue, this is a short segment breaking down what we're facing.
Great, well, this stuff sounds great.
If it didn't sound so good, we wouldn't be falling for it.
I mean, who doesn't want walkable, bikeable transit neighborhoods, you know?
Sounds so great, but smart growth is the hardscape for your future poverty.
It is for a failed economy and a loss of private property that they're designing these small
apartments stacked in the center of your town so that you supposedly don't need a vehicle.
But the fact is that you will only be able to go where that train line that may or may
not exist goes.
But the idea is that you will be restricted to city centers, mega-regions, mega-cities,
and you will not be able to get out into the rural and suburban areas.
This plan is about bringing people out of rural and suburban areas into city centers
where they can be more easily controlled, monitored, and surveilled.
That is what this is about, more eyes on the street.
Community-oriented policing is Department of Justice.
This is about creating more crime, calling it community crime, and then being able to
jail more people.
Those prisons are public-private partnership.
So this is what we're looking at, is a combination of non-profits, corporations, and government.
This is how government has taken over.
And again, right here where I live in Austin, they now have TSA checkpoints downtown and
at the train, and they admit, you're not going to have the money to have a car.
You're going to be on a bike or in these compact cities, and guess what they're doing out in
Elgin and other areas?
They're going to use federal taxpayer money to build 10-story high-rises in the country,
make everybody move into them, and they say they'll then be a factory off the back like
China.
Yes, it's the Chinese model.
That's exactly what it is.
With the suicide nets, I guess.
And you know, the Walton Family Foundation, the Ford Foundation, the Rockefeller Foundation,
many huge foundations are funding non-profits that then pressure your government and partner
with corporations to make this happen.
This is what it's about, but we have power.
The people have power, and we can stop it, but we need to work together.
And by the way, for those that don't know, the globalist Al Bragg, China is the model,
and it's an anti-human system, not meant to build up a civilization, meant to destroy
it, to reduce population.
It's not that, oh, there's horrible labor in China before they get built up, like our
industrial revolution 150 years ago, the globalist didn't get to fully take over.
The robber barons got beaten back in the 20s and 30s and 40s and 50s.
This is their massive counter-strike.
This is their move.
Mm-hmm, that's right.
You know, this is, if you look at who the large corporations are behind this, some of
them, like Siemens and IBM, are a continuation of the Nazi plan.
This is exactly what we're looking at, control, management of information, and restriction
on your use of land, water, and minerals, and every aspect of human life is going to
be controlled, and it is in the process right now.
And by the way, they talk about once all the robotics is fully in and they have robots
fixing the robots, which they're almost done with, a bunch of big tech companies see the
ads on CNN bragging, soon robots will fix the robots that fix the robots.
They won't put suicide nets up anymore.
They'll tell you, go right on up and jump off.
We have so little value.
And the pig demon, Al Gore, the fake liberal, he's the guy on the board of Apple who's made
sure they don't pay people a living wage in China.
I mean, what a monster.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you know, if you take a look at what the largest job growth, what the largest industry
growth is over the next 20 years projected, it's retinal scanning and imaging machines,
secure data storage, satellite imaging, and of course, social networking, so none of your
information is private.
It's just incredible.
And I think about the Foxconn workers for Apple and just the devastating things they've
gone through.
I've got an image up for TV viewers of these innocent young people, I mean, total slaves,
absolute total slaves, and look how skinny they are, but it shows how powerful humans
are.
They're pretty darn healthy despite the horrible, and they still have their human dignity.
They have pretty makeup on and stuff, the girls do, but they live in these facilities.
They have forced abortions inside.
That's on record.
They do a scan every month.
These people, these poor people, pray for them, folks.
We'll be right back with Rosa Corey.
We're on the march.
The empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Coming back on 2012, I know personally I'm thanking God that my family and I made it
through the year.
From natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the
family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy, our hearts go out to those that have
lost everything.
My friends at eFoods Direct hear from customers every day that are fortunate to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand.
Danny from New York City wrote in following Hurricane Sandy and said, almost all the grocery
stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my
sister and my niece.
Bottom line, it's better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
Heed common sense's warning and do what I've done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex.
They have the best tasting, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 and ask about the Alex Jones special or go to eFoodsDirect.com forward
slash Alex.
Get self-sufficient today.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex.
Alex Jones here with a very important announcement for Truth Speakers.
We've carried a lot of amazing films and books over the years on the online video bookstore
at Infowars.com.
And out of all the titles we've carried, one stands out because it is just so chillingly
convincing and that's Dreams From My Real Father by Joel Gilbert, available at Infowars.com.
This film exposes the fraud that Obama is like nothing I've seen.
If you want to know who Obama's real daddy is, this is the film for you.
Don't forget, your purchase supports our broadcast and our growing media network.
You'll also find it at Infowarshop.com.
None Dare Call a Conspiracy by Gary Allen, the book that woke me up.
We're also carrying Behind the Green Mask, UN Agenda 21 by Rosa Corey.
This book is coffin nails to the globalist takeover.
The Greater Good, the most professional and up-to-date film I've ever seen, exposing the
scourge that is vaccines.
These titles and a lot more are all available at Infowarshop.com.
Introducing Pro One, all of your filtration in one system, portable, on the go.
No more do you have two or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride.
You have a system that cuts out the sodium fluoride and up to 95% of hydrofluorosolicic
acid, advanced manufacturing technology combined silver impregnated white ceramic with new
aqua medics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals, all in one
filter element.
It is the only one that does it and out of the gates, we have it discounted at 10% off
with promo code water.
This is the only system that in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides, herbicides, chloramines,
ammonia, and chlorine, hydrofluorosolicic acid, the most common form of fluoride not
covered by other fluoride filter brands, and sodium hexafluorosilicate.
Get your Pro Pure with the new Pro One filters today at Infowarshop.com or by calling 888-253-3139.
You've got a business, you didn't build that.
Somebody else made that happen.
Defending the republic from enemies foreign and domestic, it's Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, we're going to go back to Rosa Corey here in just a moment.
I'm going to give the number out if you've got questions or comments for her, she'll
be with us till about five after next hour, then we've got our next guest in studio.
The toll free number to join us is 800-259-9231, first time callers on this Friday.
Your questions or your statements on agenda 21.
And this is global governance, it's all under UNESCO.
That's why it's global standardized training on every front, on every issue, social, cultural,
religious, economic, it's so diabolical.
Now again, the book behind the green mask, UN agenda 21 is available, the lowest price
you're going to find anywhere matching her price at Infowarsstore.com and your purchase
supports our work.
You ought to buy these by the cases and give them to city planners and others to identify
if they're a conscious operative or a lot of them read it and wake up and resist and
Rosa can talk about that.
So the good news is, this is so diabolical and so on record that if we just expose them
and resist them, we're beating them all over the place and that's why they are screaming
bloody murder.
A year ago they said this didn't exist, now they're going, of course it exists, it's good
and you people are stopping us, we're gonna be talking about that in a moment.
Now the new issue, the February issue of Infowars magazine is out, the hard copy, 60 page big
color glossy with an image of the 50 states forming a gun, why the tyrants want your guns.
And this is guaranteed to sell out, sometimes the magazine sells out in four or five days.
We put 70,000 on the streets in Texas and sell 30,000, we hold back some.
You can either buy them in bulk in groups of 10 up to 100 at cost or get a one year
subscription.
And when you get the one year subscription while supplies last, we are also able to then
generally put in the last issue, a few that we hold back.
So you can subscribe at infowarsstore.com or you can buy them in bulk while supplies
last at infowarsstore.com or you can call toll free 888-253-3139, again that's 888-253-3139.
An amazing magazine, people are blown away by it and it's a pamphlet, it's a 60 page
color pamphlet that you can buy at cost to give to people to wake them up, it is an info
war.
And finally, four years ago, we sold the Obama Joker socialism shirt.
Really it's fascism, so we had both variants, but we only sold it for about a year and then
I said I'm never gonna sell it again, we may sell a different design later.
Our great graphics designer Janee Meadows, she put together the Obama Tyrant shirt that
I'm holding here in my hands.
And it is Obama the Joker and it says Tyrant, infowars.com.
When people then ask you what it's about, it's a great conversation piece to wake them
up.
And on the back, we've taken our most popular t-shirt ever and put that on the back, infowars.com.
An AK-47 with the right to keep and bear arms shall not be infringed on the back and the
words come and take it.
So I think this is gonna end up being the best t-shirt most popular ever and that's
how we fund our news operation and everything here and fight these globalists.
Now, before I go back to Rosa, I wanna say this about guns.
The NRA, I saw a statement they put out yesterday and in the past they were like, yeah, we think
there should be background checks for everybody.
Get rid of private sales even to your neighbor of a gun.
And they were asked, why have you changed and said you're not against private sales
now?
Because the system doesn't work, criminals will still have guns.
Well, let me take that one further and then we're gonna go to our guest.
Let me take that one further.
We don't trust the system.
Yeah, it sounds reasonable to have a mental background check and a bunch of background
checks to get a gun.
And if angels were running things, the good angels, then I would be for it.
The globalists have taken the guns everywhere in the world while they arm against us, they
are taking our guns.
Australia took all the semi-autos, now they're taking the bolt action.
It's happened everywhere.
These globalists are on record saying they're going to have the abolition of our guns.
The UN is on record while they engage in atrocities worldwide.
It's the same thing.
I like bike lanes.
I like a city ordinance saying you get a tax discount if you put a garden on your roof.
I like things like that.
The problem is they take all this good stuff and make it global and selectively enforce
it.
And that's just the window dressing for all the bad stuff that goes on.
I wanna give her the floor for about ten minutes before we go to calls.
I'll have to stick a sock in my mouth cuz information is so important because I know
it's real.
I know it's a criminal takeover.
It's like if I saw a guy robbing my neighbors, I'd be like going, hey, Bob, somebody's in
your garage.
But this is our liberty, our freedom, our economy.
They wanna wreck it.
They're on record wanting to wreck it.
And it's not that environmental stuff isn't reasonable.
That's the sugar coating on the cyanide pill to make it taste good.
You can give somebody Kool-Aid, Jim Jones, but it had cyanide in it.
Tastes like grape Kool-Aid gonna kill you better than a hammer.
Tastes real good like antifreeze.
It tastes good.
It'll kill you.
And that's what's frustrating is that they all wanna sound reasonable and they want us
to sit back and be nice and debate with them in a false paradigm.
No, it's time to get aggressive to shake people out of their trance.
That's why they're now admitting Piers Morgan was a defeat when I blew up.
For him, they're now admitting, this is the way to get.
Being aggressive does work.
Of course it works.
They're aggressive.
Get aggressive or get overrun.
Now, Rosa, I'm gonna shut up for ten minutes, then we're gonna take a few calls for you.
But break down, again, the latest on what they're doing, our victories, how we beat
them, where you see this going.
Rosa Corey.
Well, you know, first of all, I wanna make sure that people know this is the hijacking
of the environmental movement.
That's why I called my book Behind the Green Mask, because if it didn't look good
and sound good, then we wouldn't be going for it.
So there is a political and social ideology that goes, you know, that's sort of overarching
on this, and it's communitarianism.
And Dan Jones just called Obama a communitarian.
He said that we've gone way too far in the individualistic direction, and we have to
pull it back to rebalance towards communitarianism.
And what that means is that your individual rights are balanced with the so-called community,
and the community can change at any time.
What this is about is about taking away your right to privacy, to your freedom, to live
where you wish, to move freely, and to instate instead the power of the community.
So this is why it's about consensus and the Delphi technique, where you get invited
to give your opinion on a new plan in the center of your town, but if you don't agree
with what the direction of that plan is, what the goal is, then you're considered to be
fringe, and you are ignored.
And that's what this is all about.
It's about artificial consensus and giving the illusion of community buy-in.
So that's why I say awareness is the first step in the resistance, because people need
to educate themselves about what this looks like in their town, because you're going
to see it called many different things.
Your smart meters, you might see it as the international codes, you'll see it as whatever
that plan is called, Vision 2025, or One Valley, One Vision, or whatever they're calling
it in your town.
It's the same plan all across the world, and Agenda 21 is the action plan to inventory
and control all land, water, minerals, plants, animals, means of construction, education,
energy, and information, and human beings in the world.
That's what this plan is about.
Now, we have a chance to fight this.
I believe that 2013 is the year of critical awareness all over the world, and we are really
breaking through.
This is the year where people are understanding that this is a global, regional neighborhood
plan.
It's global, designed to look like it's coming up from the grassroots, and it is not.
So it's up to us.
There's no heroes, nobody on the sidelines here.
You know, we've got to get out there and expose these public-private partnerships in
our local communities and our towns.
We want to educate our local officials and let them know that we will support them if
they refuse to take federal grants for partnership for sustainable community grants.
We will support them, but if they don't, if they don't listen to us, we will take
them out.
We need to recognize that we have power.
So what we're doing is we are getting active in the resistance.
We're understanding that you don't wait until it gets violent.
You want to call a halt to it while you can.
So you want to stop redevelopment projects.
This is so-called urban renewal, which actually directs you into city centers.
You want to stop them from pulverizing your rural roads to gravel.
You want to get out there and protect those farmers that are out there being restricted
and regulated to death.
They're putting monitoring on wells, private wells.
What is happening with your government is that you are looking at treason.
Treason is happening in every town all across the world.
There are people who think that they're doing the right thing.
It's up to us as the informed electorate to let our elected officials know that they
are committing treason, and treason has no statute of limitations.
There is no statute of limitations, so these people will be held to account.
And this is our job.
There are way more of us than there are of them.
And we need to expose collaborators, speak out, anti-Delphi these meetings, and work
together to break that left-right paradigm, because that terrifies those who are in power.
And we can do it.
We are doing it all over the world.
I'll actually be in Texas in March.
I'm traveling all across the country speaking out, and people are joining me.
This is tremendous.
We are really getting movement across the world.
And by the way, the globalists operate like we don't read their own websites and white
papers.
Talk about their panic button.
They're not just freaking out in the Washington Post, New York Times, admitting we're fighting
them globally.
They are panicking in their own white papers right now.
What's hurting them the worst?
I mean, I guess just exposure, people go to the meetings, no one's allowed to even talk.
They just tell you what to believe, or even if you do, they then certify it.
I mean, people understand what's happening here.
Well, you know, we have a series of videos online called Near Riot at Delphi meetings,
which are really great.
And the thing is that people now are beginning to recognize what it looks like, because they've
been told, you know, these controlled opposition people will tell you not to talk about Agenda
21.
And, you know, you're being directed by people who are infiltrating your...
Exactly.
They'll say it's discrediting to talk about Agenda 21 and the UN biological diversity
assessments.
It's just, don't do that.
That is how they're controlling people.
Yeah, that's what controlled opposition looks like.
So you need to show up and occupy those government meetings and talk about Agenda 21 sustainable
development.
Let them know that you know what it is.
Those three pillars of Agenda 21 are economy, ecology, and social equity.
And when you see that together, you want to break that down, and you want to advise your
elected officials that you are going to take them out if they don't drop this out.
You've got to remove yourself from this, what it is, is money coming from the federal government
that is funding these plants.
And then that money is coming from corporations and nonprofits.
So what you want to do is break that cycle and refuse to participate.
You want to be the resistance.
That's right.
All the big mega corporations, they put tiny seed money in to get the politicians.
They conduit federal HUD money and others just like Acorn, but in a hundred other groups
plus back to them to then let them take over the local government, take over the infrastructure,
and then have their buildings subsidized and go tax-free while not letting you fix your
roof.
You know, that's right.
And it's not only, hey, it's not only in land use, we're talking about education with a
common core standards where teachers no longer can teach, where students are being restricted.
I'm sure, Alex, you know about those little kids, the 60-year-olds who got suspended from
school for using their fingers like guns and saying, dang, dang.
It's total Soviet mind control.
Right.
So what we're talking about is actually social engineering and restricting human beings so
that they literally don't know what is right and what is wrong.
And this is how you break down a society.
We want to talk about a hostile takeover.
That's what this is.
The authoritarians, I've read countless books, Bernays and others, they say we tell them
ridiculous things are bad.
We tell them common sense things are bad.
We tell them good things are bad so they feel guilty and off balance and will do whatever
we say.
They're giving them a guilt complex.
And again, the teachers don't know.
They're just given the programming, the handbooks, it is meant to prepare children to believe
they're criminals.
It is pure evil.
That's right.
We need to refuse to participate.
Refuse to give your personal information, refuse to collaborate, refuse to pay nonprofits,
refuse to give donations and refuse to volunteer.
If you're a teacher, refuse.
We need to do this together.
There are so many of us who are becoming aware.
We need to stand tall, stand together and refuse this indoctrination that we're getting.
How freaked out is the enemy right now?
They are so freaked out.
It's incredible.
They were thinking they were going to pull this off and be able to, they're in the end
game.
But you know what?
We are giving them a run for their money and we will prevail because this is not going
to fly.
People are not willing to allow their entire culture to be destroyed in order to be moved
into these mega units and centers of cities.
You know, your town, whatever your little town is, that is a collector feeder town and
that will be closed down and you'll be moved into the huge city.
Take a look at mega regions on our website.
This is a project.
Oh, they've openly announced it.
I'm in this particular mega region and they admit that you're not going to live in these
little towns unless you have special permits.
It's all under the original UN maps where half the country's off limits.
I mean, this is so diabolical.
It's true, but you know what?
We do have them on the run.
When you start seeing this, you know, they're vilifying me in the press.
That's when I know I'm winning.
When they're actually out there talking about this and they're saying, oh, that agenda 21,
that's a good thing.
When they wouldn't even admit that it existed for 20 years, you know, then you know you're
winning.
We are out there.
We are bringing up the troops and nobody is going to be left behind.
Nobody on the sidelines, no heroes.
We all work together.
That's another reason.
You know what?
My book is a great opportunity for you to get up to speed on this quickly and we've
got 20 pages in the back on what you can do.
So you want to educate yourself and others as quickly as you can.
Absolutely.
I want to come back and take two short segments of calls and we have a pastor, Steven Anderson
in here talking about the police state in a new film and a lot more, but Rosa Corry
is our guest, author of Behind the Green Mask, available at Infowarsstore.com or by calling
888-253-3139.
We're about to go to break in about a minute.
Any other key points you want to relay to people right now?
Yeah.
You know, this plan is predicated on sharing information.
That's part of agenda 21.
It's all about sharing our info through technology.
This is a technocracy.
It is.
So every part of your life is being shared.
You have no personal privacy.
You need to break that paradigm and refuse to cooperate.
That's why they want you in the mega-opolises with the face-scanning cameras, the controls
where they can turn the taxes up to bankrupt anybody they want and literally render you
down to people living in jail cells.
That's their plan.
Turn the cities into giant, medium security prison grids.
I mean, it's while the elite live in the country and are exempt flying there by jet copter.
That's exactly right.
This is about controlling populations, restricting ability to move freely and to speak out.
But they're going to have model, and Austin is it, model megacities where the elite lives
that are quasi-exempt.
It's so incredible.
I mean, these people, it's a science fiction movie, folks.
You're living in a science fiction movie.
You've got to read her book.
You've got to see my film, End Game, Blueprint for Global Enslavement.
This is a stated on-the-record program.
These are criminal authoritarians.
You've got to realize they are your mortal enemies.
This is Alex Jones with five good reasons you should consider buying a solar power generator.
Number one, new climate legislation could easily double or triple your electric bill.
Number two, our new energy czar wants to control how much power your electric company allows
you to have.
It's true.
The government control of electricity in the name of smart grid technology is coming.
Number three, in some areas of the country, the power grid is dangerously overloaded.
And now, new socialist legislation is only compounding the problem.
Number four, dangerous weather is always a threat to local grids.
Every year, thousands of families lose their power from weather-related onages.
Number five, a solar power generator provides powerful backup insurance and peace of mind.
Folks, I really believe in the solar power generators offered by Solutions from Science,
one of my oldest sponsors.
You can get more information at www.mysolarbackup.com.
That's mysolarbackup.com.
Remember, the government doesn't own the sun, so go to mysolarbackup.com or call 1-877-327-0365.
Lunch is ready.
And it's an MRE Smorgasbord at longlifefood.com.
In 1983, Long Life Food Depot was one of the first to sell MRE pouches to the public.
And we're still selling them almost 30 years later.
Today, Long Life Food Depot has the world's most complete MRE online buffet.
Because MREs are all we do.
Tasty varieties of chicken, beef, salmon, and pasta entrees, plus sandwiches and our
easy-to-use pouches.
Full moisture, long shelf life, and ready-to-eat hot or cold.
We sell by the pouch or case, so the choices are endless.
And so are the graduated quantity discounts.
The more you buy, the more you save.
Call 800-601-2833 or go to longlifefood.com to join our email list for upcoming announcements.
Like the rollaway food pod, plus enjoy fast and free shipping.
Just call 800-601-2833 or visit longlifefood.com.
Emergency preparedness, emergency relief, longlifefood.com since 1983, sending real
food to your real future.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the President could obtain this world-class healer.
Now 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally
occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune
cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VenusFly or order from Carnivora.com, that's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VenusFly or visit Carnivora.com.
Protect your immune system, it's the only one you've got.
I read part of the Telecommunications Act in 96 and it said by October 1st, 2001, all
cell phones had to have a trackership in them to track you via satellite triangulation via
the cell towers and that the government would be able to dial in and listen to your phone
even when it's off.
It was all there and that they would start sending you messages onto your phone and it
described text messages and others, it described smartphones, they're like 30 years ahead of
us.
Here's Fox News, text on missing kids startle cell users and this is out of Los Angeles.
They first tested on the East Coast, now the West Coast, now it's happening in Austin,
my crew are getting these.
And they say now it's gonna be presidential announcements, your smartphone will break
in and it'll be Obama.
I mean, people of Earth, we are the Glaxian Empire, I mean, it's total control.
The police are being trained to set up checkpoints to take your guns, it's already happening
to veterans in New York, checkpoints.
They just randomly pull you over a checkpoint, search your car, 30 round mag, five felonies.
I mean, they're coming, this is how they're gonna purge us.
And you're like, well, I'll just turn my guns in, they're still coming.
These are authoritarians, we're in so much trouble, I just can't believe it's actually
happening.
And there are a lot of people that want power, here it is, FEMA implements special chip and
cell phones to send out alerts.
I've told people about this 16 years ago, and they looked at me like I was a space alien.
Ladies and gentlemen, they're running army checkpoints all over the country, they're
having hardcore army drills everywhere and saying the army's gonna respond to extremists
now in America.
They're getting ready for the organized collapse where they'll pose as the saviors and try
to then bring us under their control.
That's part of the plan, is a stepped process of collapses.
Rosa Corey, we're gonna take a few calls, but your comment on what I just covered.
Well, it goes worse than that because there's something called mandatory volunteering.
And if you haven't caught on to that, it's basically slavery.
This is the trend where you're going to be expected to do your mandatory volunteering
if you wanna get anything from the so-called community.
So we're talking about restrictions on every aspect of your life.
It's not enough to pay 70% on average if you actually work for the government one way or
another.
Well, Rahm Emanuel said you're gonna serve at least two months every year, up to age
65.
Yeah, that's right.
Lifelong learning and participation in your community.
Which means brainwashing.
Giving back.
That's it.
Yeah, we're not doing enough.
We're not doing enough.
Let's go ahead and take a call from a listener who's listening on KKGM up in Dallas-Fort
Worth, 1630.
Ryan, you're on the air.
Go.
Hi.
There is two ladies that recently got arrested for their smart meters.
I wanna know, Rosa, did you hear anything about that?
Cuz I have a similar story.
Yeah, sure.
That's in Naperville, and a very good friend of mine, Thelma Tarmena in Houston, actually
held a gun on the guy who was gonna put one on her house.
So people are resisting and fighting smart meters.
Smart meters are, of course, part of United Nations Agenda 21.
And for those that don't know, they admit that, and all the new appliances, and the
CIA director admitted, Petraeus said, we're spying on you through your, quote, washing
machine.
And all the new ones, it dials in and monitors you.
I mean, they're putting a giant eavesdropper on your house.
Check this out, Alex.
I don't know if you knew this, but you know how they crushed the old cars?
Well, they're going into, you know, like Goodwills and stuff and buying up old appliances and
crushing those so that you can't get, you won't be able to get an old appliance that
doesn't have a chip in it.
They know what they're doing, boy.
Mm-hm.
That's what the design is, so.
Think of the diabolical evil, folks.
I mean, this is a nightmare.
Yeah, but you know what?
We are going to win this.
We need to work together.
I agree.
Let's get the information out to people.
Ryan, what happened to you real fast?
I had a sign.
I listened to the lady from Democrats versus Agenda 21, the lady that you have on.
Anyways, I put a sign on.
I wrote a bunch of letters to the proper officials.
I even put a lock onto the smart meter.
They came through trespass, you know, with the sign said exclusively that you're allowed
on my property, but not to switch out the meter.
They ripped the sign down, took off the log, put in the smart meter.
I called the lady, actually talked to the PR people.
Stay there.
You are listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
Visit SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Oh, man, I want to go to more of your calls.
We're almost out of time.
We've got a powerful in-studio guest as well.
But she's coming to Texas.
We'll get her in here for two hours at that time.
Rosa Corey is our guest, author of Behind the Green Mask.
Ryan in Texas, yeah, no, it's illegal for them to come across your property and do this.
They could just turn your power off, I guess.
Then you've got to argue with them on that.
That's why they have laws trying to block real solar power you control, they want it
in their grid.
And that's really the answer here, is to get out of the system.
Real sustainability, their sustainability is the opposite of sustainability, it's slavery.
But what happened when you said you violated my rights?
They said, well, by law, that we can come in and do whatever we want, that's our property.
And I said, well, you know what, I want your property removed.
And I'm gonna take it out, and I'm gonna go on eBay and buy myself a little analog meter
and replace it.
And they say, well, if you even touch it, that's tampering and we'll have you arrested.
And I go, well, I want it out.
And they go, the only option is for you to go solar.
And anybody that refuses to have the smart meter installed in the beginning quarter of
this year, they're just gonna start turning people's powers off.
You know what, I say go dark, and then they're gonna send the health department saying you're
unsanitary and stuff, and say, hey, get a civil rights lawsuit, and then bring out that
they're dialing into everything you're doing, watching and listening to you, including jacking
your computers.
This is on record, folks, in the Google Patents and dialing into your camera and microphone.
God bless you, sir.
Let's go get a quick comment from Rosa Corey.
Yeah, this is what the smart grid is about, is about controlling everything that is related
to technology.
So your internet, your phone, your electricity, everything.
And also, it's about, as you said, Alex, it's about identifying people who are dissenters
and then shutting off their power.
It's about being able to control, but you do need to resist, I agree, go dark, and then
fight them.
We need to do this as a nation, stop it, refuse to collaborate.
It's time to get back to that anyways, get the candles out, go dark.
Yeah, I lived like that for a long time in Mexico, it's great.
It's like camping.
I mean, go dark, folks, go dark.
We either fight, and it's only gonna get worse, okay?
This is a scientific, in their words, technocracy.
They think they've got it all planned out, and they're counting on you to be lazy.
God bless you, sir.
Go dark, sue them, fight them.
This is the new civil rights movement.
While they're busy saying, if you don't wanna turn your guns in, you're a cracker, and that's
on MSNBC, Total Racism, to create racial division.
The real discrimination's going on against all of us by the globalist.
Mike in New Hampshire, you're on the air, welcome.
Hey, how are you, Alex?
Good, sir.
How you doing?
I got a quick question for you.
Geez.
You're almost out of time.
Almost out of time.
Yep, yep, yep.
You know, I'm 36 years old, and I have three children up here, I'm very invested in what's
going on.
I would like some sort of brochure that I would commit to knock on every door in my
town here in Epping, New Hampshire, and telling them about Agenda 21, which I find-
Okay, look, let me tell you, we have those flyers for you on our website.
Democrats against UNAgenda21.com, those flyers are called What's Wrong with Sustainable Development,
and Why Is Everyone Talking About Agenda 21?
Make those flyers, you can make 100 flyers for six bucks, walk them around, get that
info out to everyone.
Absolutely, it's time to hit them and hit them hard.
And you said you've got children, that's what this is about.
This is the Chinese communist slave model with a tiny elite on top that are free market
and get the money.
The globalist, the CFR admits, the deal they made with the Chinese communist is the plan
here.
They've done this in China.
Rosa?
Yeah, and that's it.
This is what we're fighting.
One great thing is that this year, I am being invited to speak to governors, to Congress
people, to senators, all across the country.
So people are getting through to their elected officials, we want to draw this down, we want
to block it.
This is an ideology and we will stop it.
Three people never submit to this kind of tyranny.
No they don't.
Rosa Corey, we're going to talk to you again soon.
Callers, I'll get to you.
I get to talk to Pastor Williams, we can talk agenda 21.
The book behind the green mask, UN agenda 21, Rosa Corey available at infoawars.com
right now.
But go to her site, print off the flyers in your printer and get them out to people.
Give the website out one more time.
Democrats against UN agenda 21.com.
Great job.
We'll talk to you soon in studio.
Thank you.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
You prepare by purchasing gold, food, and firearms.
But if you don't have a home security system, then you're missing a critical weapon in your
arsenal for home protection.
When you're sleeping or away from home, who's watching out for intruders?
Check out Simply Safe.
It's a new do-it-yourself home security system that is completely wireless.
Go to GetSimplySafe.com.
Simply Safe is independent and off the grid.
It runs on battery power, so even if the grid goes down, you're protected.
It's completely customizable, so you can use it in your home, business, boat, trailer,
storage unit, or shed.
GetSimplySafe.com.
Simply Safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes, so there's no
need to let a stranger into your home.
If you move or need to relocate, you can take the system with you wherever you go.
You aren't always at home, but Simply Safe will stand guard, protecting your property
24 hours a day, seven days a week.
Again, that's GetSimplySafe.com.
Looking back on 2012, I know personally I'm thanking God that my family and I made it
through the year.
From natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the
family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy.
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
My friends at eFoods Direct hear from customers every day that are fortunate to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand.
Danny from New York City wrote in following Hurricane Sandy and said, almost all the grocery
stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my
sister and my niece.
Bottom line, it's better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
Heed common sense's warning and do what I've done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex.
They have the best tasting long term storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 and ask about the Alex Jones special or go to eFoodsDirect.com forward
slash Alex.
Get self-sufficient today.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex.
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center and the heart of the resistance.
Thank you for joining us again on this Friday, February 1st, 2013 edition.
I am your host, Alex Jones, and wow, we just had Rosa Corey on with Unigena21, the book,
and everything she's saying is totally true.
I mean, we're calling them total eugenics, world government, population reduction, turning
the cities into total prisons, where everything surveilled beyond 1984, forced abortions,
suicide nets around the agenda 21 factories, all of it's true and then some.
And we've just had it so good because of liberty, they can point out the problems with America,
but compared to other countries, 5% of the population, half the world's wealth.
Now as the liberty is taken, now as the Constitution is ignored, now as the Bible is ignored, everything's
going to hell in a handbasket.
And you can't deny that, whether you believe in God or not, when you become decadent, when
you don't care about other people, when you don't make a stand, when you don't take action,
you are rudderless and a ship without a rudder just goes around wherever the wind blows it.
And that's why I have a article up at infowars.com, population control propagandist, this is at
Yale with top UN officials.
We get very little opposition from the public because via the television programs, we have
very gradual evolution of the characters, it's an hour and 50 something minute video,
you can go watch it.
Go do it, go watch them laugh about you, go watch them talk about how they're conditioning
you with the television.
I mean, you go see those messages that are anti-man, anti-family, anti-liberty, that
are savage.
That's because they want to screw you up, they wanna have you be alone.
And they say that if you go after other groups, you hate them, no, no, no, no.
What's happening is they want to make us all under the state's control.
They want to bankrupt us and the Democratic Party officially has adopted by the 60s, the
Cloward and Piven strategy that we've talked about for 15, 16 years that's become now widely
understood just like agenda 21.
Where the top sociologists for the Democratic Party said we're gonna bankrupt things in
the name of the poor, but it's meant to bankrupt things to bring in our socialist society,
which isn't even socialist.
When you hear socialism, that means get control of you so you can be under eugenics.
Now, I know we got loaded phones, we're gonna get to so many that are patiently holding
like Sean in Australia, I didn't even notice we had a caller from Australia, William, Eric,
and we'll probably go into overdrive next hour, cuz our guest is here all the way from
Arizona.
I shot a video talking about this last night, Weldon Henson, a few weeks ago, who does research
over what we carry.
Either I watch and read something and like it or have an idea or he's going over stuff
we're sent and brings it to me.
And he said, hey, I really like this after the tribulation, let no man be deceived.
Do you know who these guys are?
And yes, I know who all three of the men are that are featured in it.
And it's a very well done film, and it's after the tribulation, let no man be deceived.
Now, I wanna explain something here.
Let's say you don't believe in God, you don't believe in a sixth sense.
You don't know why you know when you're walking through an empty place, you feel somebody
looking at you and there's a guy behind you.
You don't know why all that happens, why a monarch butterfly can fly to Canada and back
or whatever.
You just think all that is here, the TV is the reality, whatever.
The elites are all very, very spiritual.
And let me tell you, they worship something that looks a lot like the devil of the Bible.
In fact, they say that's who they worship, they believe Lucifer is God.
And I was brought up a Christian and I have had spiritual experiences and we've got that
part of our brain connected to our spirit.
But you get a little bit older and you hear all this, but then when I went to Bohemian
Grove and saw 1,000 plus world leaders in religious rapture that I'd experienced in
Baptist and Evangelical churches I went to as a child.
But on a dark side, people really, in a religious experience, an average atheist goes, they're
just having fun worshiping the big owl and doing a mock sacrifice to it.
But you see, when you're there, you know it's not just a play.
Plays come from religious events thousands of years ago, the stage, the people watching.
The whole world's a stage, each of us, players upon it, you find out, man, there's something
going on here.
But I know this, it was Christians that said no to slavery in Rome 2,000 years ago, it
got thrown to the lions, going to be technical about 1,960 years ago is what was really going
on.
It was Christians said no to slavery in Europe and then finally here.
Now there's some Bohemian Grove footage from Dark Secrets Inside Bohemian Grove, we're
showing TV viewers.
The point is, is that if you're a new listener, yes, I snuck into Bohemian Grove where the
big boys of Skull and Bones go when they're old men.
And the point I wanna make to everybody out there who's watching, who's viewing us right
now is that even if you don't believe in a spiritual realm, you have to understand the
New World Order's greatest tool is convincing you it doesn't exist.
Because they don't want you looking into it because they believe all the power is there,
whether it's real or not.
They don't want you knowing about it and have written that they have pushed atheism and
agnostic stuff so that you don't even ever think about it.
It's like the Screwtape letters, a demon talking to a low level demon was written by a great
British writer, popped my head in a minute, C.S. Lewis.
They don't even want you getting into the big evils, they just don't want you ever thinking
outside the box and feeling that connection or they wanna misdirect it if you do discover
that.
But regardless, it has been the rapture doctrine that's, what, 150 years old max or so?
We got a theologian here who can break it down.
No Christians ever believed, I guess there were a few small groups later in Rome who
did for a certain period, that it was the end of the world or, don't worry about evil,
it's the end of the world.
Our founders are now criticized by TV preachers who are getting government funding and clergy
response team FEMA money to say, the Christians, I've got the clips, you can just go to YouTube.
TV preacher says that we shouldn't have, Christians should have obeyed and worshiped the gods
and shouldn't have been thrown to the lions, twisting Romans 13.
They teach our founders were bad, they should have followed King George.
That's all diametrically opposed to everything in the Bible.
So understand, if you wanna know why we got in this position where the government now
runs the churches that violates the First Amendment and common sense, this country was
founded on.
It's because the leadership got bought off by the World Council of Churches, the National
Council of Churches, the same Rockefeller groups, go look it up.
And so from an anthropologist or sociologist view, you need to see after the tribulation
because the Bible clearly states, the tribulation comes after the devil wages war on the saints
and overcomes them and chops off their heads by the millions and all of this.
And I understand why Christians go, no, no, I'm gonna get jet packed out of here, a golden
rope's gonna come down, Scotty's up there on the enterprise, he's gonna teleport me
out of here.
Well, let me tell you something, the Bible from front to back, nobody gets teleported
out except for one guy who'd been so good, God picked him up.
But the point is, and he wasn't getting teleported out to escape something, he'd already gone
through the fire.
Okay, so I wanna explain some, of course in Christ, of course he did as well, but that
wasn't really a man, you can go back and forth.
The point is, is God in man's body.
The point is, this is the real deal, ladies and gentlemen, okay?
And they hate Christians and they hate gun owners because they know we understand what's
going on.
That's the litmus test that we know they're authoritarians.
Now he's with us for this hour and a little bit into the next hour.
After the tribulation, a film that they even did an info war style trailer without us even
saying it, so I went ahead and tagged on my own promo onto it, it's up at infoawars.com
right now.
But after the tribulation, let no man deceive you.
Everyone needs to buy this at infoawarsstore.com and go give it to their pastor, their preachers
and others.
And again, Pastor Steve Anderson is famously 100 mile in checkpoints, he's been beat up
for asking questions, we'll play some of that later.
He's the guy that said he prays for Obama to be brought down, which is biblical, got
demonized for that.
The pastor of Steven Anderson was born and raised in Sacramento, California.
He's married with seven beautiful children.
At age 18, he traveled throughout Germany and Eastern Europe with Baptist churches studying
foreign languages and getting experience in the ministry.
Pastor Anderson started a totally independent Baptist church, Faithful World Baptist Church
on December 25th, 2005, so I guess seven, eight years old now and faithfulworldbaptist.org
is the website.
Okay, we're going to break in a few minutes.
Great to have you here, but let's get right in to this film and the scriptures and where
this doctrine came that it's a pre-tribulation rapture, so nobody's got to worry about anything.
All the other Christians had to go through the fire, but this generation, as it's all
coming down, we're going to be left alone.
Hey, thanks for having me on, Alex.
Good to be here.
I think this film is most important because if you want to know why Christians are asleep
right now, if you want to know why the vast majority of Christians don't want to hear
about the New World Order, they don't care when you warn them about global government
or police state, it's because of this doctrine.
This pre-trib rapture doctrine makes everybody believe that it doesn't really matter what's
going on because we're all going to be out of here.
And there was a pastor in Arizona that I know who recently said to me, as soon as he found
out that I didn't believe in this pre-tribulation rapture, he said, well, now I understand why
you're so paranoid about government.
Because he'd seen all the stuff with-
Yeah, that's sick that they don't care about, even if they were going to be teleported out.
Don't they care about all the people now?
No, they don't.
They sit around at country clubs.
Yeah, so he said, now I see why you're so paranoid about government, but I'd like to
turn that around on him and say, now I see why you don't give a rip about anything that's
going on.
Now I see why you trust the government so much because you believe this fairy tale that
we're going to be taken out of here before-
Homeland Security is now saying the number one enemy of the groups is the Christians.
Remember Janet Reno said, a believer that believes in the second coming of Christ, that
is a mentally ill cult member.
Yeah, and this is all prophesied in the Bible.
The Bible's real clear that eventually Christians are going to be-
The smart meters, the chips, the face scanning, the hands, all of it, world government, the
exact empires, the name of it, everything.
It's all in the Bible, and the amazing thing is that people 100 years ago might have read
the Bible and wondered, how could this be implemented?
How do you stop people from buying or selling?
How do you take this kind of global power over every single nation in the world?
But now we can see it happen.
The UN says 10 kingdoms, they call it 10 kingdoms.
Right.
It's all there.
It's all, I mean, they're following it.
The only other argument is, well, they're using it as a template of control, like it's
a science fiction book and they go, ooh, this is a good plan.
Oh, and they worship the devil on top of it?
But that's a joke too, I guess.
There's no way.
I mean, obviously the Bible has been talking about this stuff since hundreds and hundreds
of years ago.
It's crystal clear.
It's like reading a newspaper when you read the Bible about the one world government,
global warfare, the engineered famines that...
Bioweapons, weather control.
All of it.
Metal insects that drop things that turn into mountains of fire, columns, hydrogen bombs.
I mean, it's all there.
It's all there.
I mean, the people having these visions were like, I saw metal giant insects, mountains
of flame.
I mean...
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not going to want to miss this exciting message.
Here's why.
Our solar generators provide life saving electrical power and unlike gas generators, solar generators
run quietly, emit no fumes and produce electricity from the sun.
So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part.
Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of
each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait.
They go fast.
Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa where a nicely furnished cabin
with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine and laundry service awaits.
After a good night's sleep, your adventure begins.
We're on a golden stag safari for big game, but it's not Africa, it's Argentina.
One-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo, huger, bighorn rams, wild boar and the biggest
stag deer in South America, all gold medal quality, all the action you can handle.
Land rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages, hunting guides, ground
transportation included and more, all more affordable than you can imagine.
The adventure of a lifetime starts at goldenstagsafaris.com.
The big game hunting ranch, goldenstagsafaris.com.
Oh, great, now I've got to go to court.
Meet Tina, now facing a future court date.
I can't afford an attorney.
Then learn how to represent yourself in court step by step without a lawyer.
How?
Online at howtowinincourt.com.
Howtowinincourt.com was created by a 27-year veteran attorney, so you can know how to win
without a lawyer.
Now I can go to court with confidence.
Learn how at howtowinincourt.com.
The leader in lawsuit self-help since 1997.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson.
Have you ever wondered why banks, stock workers, investment advisors won't talk about gold
IRAs?
They've been available since 1986, yet the financial industry won't recognize the value
of gold for your retirement.
Gold has outperformed paper investments, yet no word about IRAs.
If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns, call 800-686-2237.
Secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
Hi there.
My name is Frank Bates.
What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble.
I just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are, incompetent, lying crooks
that are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high.
Some have called this a conspiracy, others have called it a cover-up, and you will be
shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy goes.
My video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them
and how you can beat them too.
Watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patriots have already seen
in the last three months.
Go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect
your home.
Go watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down.
Again, that's 123coverup.com.
Pastor Steve Anderson, who's one of the people in this great new film, After the Tribulation
is our guest.
Okay, I'm ranting and raving.
Starting with the points you were making during the break, and let's get into what the Bible
really says.
And again, even if you're not a Christian, this is what governs over two billion people
on the planet who say they're one form of Christian or another, and they're all being
told you're all gonna be raptured.
Hollywood loves to promote it, it's what all the TV ads say, and it turns out they're all
basically clergy response team federal agents.
Go over it.
Yeah, let me just start out by saying that this doctrine of the pre-tribulation rapture
is not found in the Bible at all.
It's not derived from any scripture, and it's like the emperor's new clothes.
Everybody goes around saying, of course we believe in it, all the pastors preach it,
but nobody ever stops to ask themselves, wait a minute, is this even taught in the Bible?
And it all is relying upon one key point, that they teach that Jesus can come back at
any moment.
And you'll hear a lot of TV preachers saying, he may even come back before I'm done with
this sermon.
Come like a thief in the night, no man know the time.
Send your money now, you don't need it.
We could be gone tomorrow.
So this doctrine that says that Jesus is coming at any moment is not found in scripture at
all.
And what they're twisting is where Jesus Christ said in Matthew 24, of that day and hour,
he said, but of that day and hour, knoweth no man, know not the angels of heaven.
But what they forgot to tell you is that a couple of verses before that, he said it was
after the tribulation.
So he said after the tribulation, he's coming in the clouds, the trumpet's gonna sound.
Then a couple of verses later-
And he said no stone will be left unturned in this war.
A couple of verses later, he says, but of that day and hour, knoweth no man, know not
the angels of heaven, but my Father only.
So they quote that one verse hoping that you're too ignorant.
Yeah, quote the other voice, the earlier part.
Okay, it says in verse 29 of Matthew 24, immediately after the tribulation of those days, shall
the sun be darkened, and the moon shall not give her light, and the stars shall fall from
the heaven, and the powers of the heavens shall be shaken.
You're gonna notice that.
This isn't some secret, left behind, everybody disappears thing.
It's talking about the sun and moon being-
Stop's gonna be blowing up.
And it says, then shall appear the sign of the son of man in heaven.
Son of man is what Jesus called himself on this earth.
And then shall all the tribes of the earth mourn, and they shall see the son of man coming
in the clouds of heaven with power and great glory, and he shall send his angels with a
great sound of a trumpet, and they shall gather together his elect from the four winds from
one end of heaven to the other.
The elect in the New Testament is always referring to those that are believers, those that are
saved, those who believe in Christ.
So they totally skip over that part, and they jump down to verse 36, where it says, but
of that day and hour, knoweth no man know not the angels of heaven, but my Father only.
And again, I've read the Bible, the whole thing foreshadows in the Old Testament what's
going to happen.
It says in the New Testament, it says in Revelation, over and over again, it describes how the
devil goes after God's people, and they have to stand against it.
Because it's not about what happens to their body, it's about their soul and having the
courage.
It's ridiculous, it is the emperor's, is totally naked here.
Exactly, and there's no basis for it.
But anyway, the scripture that I just read for you, where it said, after the tribulation,
Christ comes in the clouds, he gathers the elect, the trumpet sounds.
When you try to show this to one of these pre-trib preachers, they'll tell you, well,
that's not even about the rapture.
But then these same people will turn around and quote you that no man knoweth the day
or the hour all day long.
No, I've had them do it to me in person.
Even though it's just a couple verses later, so it's like they just take that one verse
out of context.
Now, you brought up the part about the thief in the night, where they say, Jesus is coming
as a thief in the night, he can come at any moment.
But here's what's funny, if you actually go to that passage where it says that he's coming
as a thief in the night, in 1 Thessalonians 5.
If you go down two verses, it says, but ye, brethren, are not in darkness that that day
should overtake you as a thief.
Ye are all the children of the light and the children of the day.
We are not of the night nor of darkness.
Therefore, let us not sleep as do others, but let us watch and be sober.
It's saying the dumbed down masses won't know what hit them.
Exactly.
He says that it's coming upon those that do not believe, those who don't know.
We all know it's coming, we all see the freight train.
Why would it come upon us as a thief in the night when he's telling us exactly what's
gonna happen?
He says you're not in darkness that that day should overtake you.
Totally clear, totally clear.
Exactly.
That's why you gotta stop listening to preachers and read the Bible.
It's gonna overtake them as a thief because the Bible says they're asleep.
We're not asleep as others.
He said wake up, watch, be sober, read the Bible, know this is coming.
He says when you begin to see these things come to pass, then lift up your heads, look
up, your redemption draweth nigh.
But there's nothing in the Bible that teaches that Jesus can come at any moment.
He said, look, X, Y, and Z has to come first.
And what's funny is the two main passages I encourage people to read are Matthew 24
and 2 Thessalonians chapter 2.
And in both of these passages, he uses the term let no man deceive you.
And then he goes on to explain how his coming is not at any moment, and that first the tribulation
comes.
First the sun and moon are darkened.
So that tells me something's out to deceive us.
Christ is even saying now I'm gonna tell you when this is gonna happen, but people are
gonna try to deceive you on this.
Exactly.
Listen carefully.
Right.
And a five year old could tell what he's saying.
And these preachers twisted.
I figured it out when I was 12.
Well, we're gonna come right back and talk about, as you go back to this, this got pushed
by the globalists about 150 years ago.
Exactly.
Because they were sick of Christians always fighting evil.
They said, don't worry about it, go have us go have some fun.
Scotty's up there.
He's gonna beam you.
We're on the march.
The empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver based products.
Our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two
ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well as our all natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and
leave the silver at the surface.
But rather, we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry
of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more
effectively.
Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver based products
are best for you.
That's www.silverlungs.com.
Introducing Pro One, all of your filtration in one system portable on the go.
No more do you have two or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride.
You have a system that cuts out the sodium fluoride and up to 95% of hydrofluorosolicic
acid.
Advanced manufacturing technology combines silver impregnated white ceramic with new
aqua medics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals all in one
filter element.
It is the only one that does it and out of the gates, we have it discounted at 10% off
with promo code water.
This is the only system that in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides, herbicides, chloramines,
ammonia and chlorine, hydrofluorosolicic acid, the most common form of fluoride not covered
by other fluoride filter brands and sodium hexafluorosilicate.
Get your Pro Pure with the new Pro One filters today at info war store.com or by calling
888-253-3139.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other
harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
Visit supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
You could accept the fact that this city is headed for a disaster of biblical proportions.
What do you mean biblical?
What he means is Old Testament, Mr. Mayor, real wrath of God type stuff, fire and brimstone
coming down from the skies, rivers and seas boiling, 40 years of darkness, earthquakes,
volcanoes, the dead rising from the grave, human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together,
the necessary.
I have sworn upon the altar of God, eternal hostility against every form of tyranny over
the mind of man, Thomas Jefferson, live from Austin, Texas, broadcasting worldwide, it's
Alex Jones.
Sean in Australia, we're going to get to you, John, who disagrees, will be a pre-trip rapture,
we're going to get to him, we're going to get to everybody, I know people were holding
over from the last interview, but it all ties together this total control grid and we're
not judging people out there who are Christians and think there's going to be a pre-trip rapture.
You guys are getting freaked out by it because it's now doctrinal that you're going to hell
if you don't believe in this.
It's not about Jesus and the blood of Jesus, it's about the rapture happening before and
this is universal now across the board, especially in the Protestant circles.
This is it, it's not saved by grace alone, there's a pre-trip rapture because you've
got to think this so you stand down and go along with it.
And boy, are people in for a rude awakening.
I want to talk about the history of this, where it came from, what happened to you as
a Baptist preacher, you said you knew this when you were 12, reading the Bible, go through
that and then we'll go to some calls.
It's all covered in the film After the Tribulation, available at Infowarsshop.com or Infowarsstore.com,
both URLs will get you there.
And you know what, it's important to talk about this and to look at it because Christ,
I know he's not the preacher so he doesn't really count, he's kind of the back of the
bust saying that.
And I know it says the beast will wage war against the saints and overcome them and all
that.
And then it clearly says at the end of the tribulation when Christ comes back, the dead
are raised and all that, but that's the Bible.
The Bible takes a backseat to the preachers who were the clergy response team on FEMA
payroll, violating the First Amendment with the federal government controlling them.
But I guess they are my Pharisee kings.
Okay, I'm sorry, go ahead.
Okay, so here's the history on this.
Before the year 1830, every denomination, every type of Christianity taught that the
rapture took place after the tribulation because that's what the Bible explicitly says.
Why would anyone teach anything different?
But in the late 1830s, a man by the name of John Nelson Darby started teaching a doctrine
of what he called the secret rapture, which is this idea that people are gonna disappear,
nobody knows where they went, nobody knows what's going on, it happens before the tribulation.
Okay, he promoted and taught that doctrine throughout the 1800s.
He put out his own version of the Bible, the Darby translation, where he tampered with
key passages about the second coming of Christ.
He's famous for that.
Oh, yeah.
And then later on, it was picked up by a guy named Scofield.
And this guy Scofield put out a Scofield reference Bible.
And that is what is responsible for getting it to all the Baptists, all the seminaries
started really pushing the Scofield reference Bible.
I just got a call this week of people trying to sell me Scofield Bibles.
And so the Scofield Bible is all about getting the pre-trib rapture doctrine out to people.
Now, because this doctrine is not found in the Bible at all, there's no clear scripture
that anybody can point to that shows you, here's where it says before the tribulation,
Jesus comes in the clouds.
They have to rely on a lot of fear and intimidation to make sure that all the preachers walk in
line.
Now, just in my own personal life, I started pastoring seven years ago, and I was sent
out to start an independent Baptist church in Phoenix, Arizona, the church that sent
me out as soon as they found out that I did not believe in the pre-tribulation rapture
because I preached a sermon, you know, where I explained why it was false.
They immediately cut all ties with me cut all contact with me disowned me effectively.
And honestly, any pastor who preaches against the pre-tribulation rapture is going to pay
a big price.
They're going to lose their preacher friends, they're going to lose any kind of funding,
because if you are not pre-trib, you are not in the club.
And they have to rely on that blackballing of anybody who will question it in order to
make sure that every Baptist and every evangelical is in lockstep teaching the preacher rapture.
Let me tell you something, every single Baptist Bible college or Baptist seminary or evangelical
Bible college that I know of teaches the pre-tribulation rapture and they demand that their graduates
believe it.
And they even have Hollywood movies where the aliens come and take the good people away.
Even the Hollywoods pushing this.
And every single church I've ever been in had people who believed right on this.
Because you know, there are people who believe it or not, there are some people actually
read the Bible and believe it.
You were saying when you were 12.
When I was 12, I believed it right on this since I was 12.
I grew up being taught the pre-trib rapture in every church I've ever been to.
But when I was 12, I decided to read the Bible or I'm sorry, the New Testament, I wanted
to read cover to cover for the first time.
I started in Matthew and by the time I got to chapter 24 and read what Jesus said, it
was clear to me and I've never believed in the pre-trib rapture since since reading Matthew.
Well what does your gut and spirit tell you?
I mean God is going to put us through the fire.
Now if we go halfway, God sometimes protects his people, but you just don't get out of
the whole deal.
I mean none of the prophets did.
The Bible says ye and all that will live godly in Christ Jesus shall suffer persecution.
And the Bible says, these things have I spoken unto you that in me you might have peace.
In the world you shall have tribulation, but be of good cheer, I've overcome the world.
The Bible warns us over and over again.
I would just encourage anybody who's listening and skeptical about what I'm saying, look
up in a concordance every time the Bible uses the word tribulation.
90% of the time the word tribulation is used in the New Testament, it's referring to believers
going through trials and tribulations and suffering and persecution because of them
taking a stand for the word of God.
Because if you take a stand and preach the word of God, you're gonna be persecuted.
The whole book of Acts is people being thrown in jail.
It's people being arrested.
Have you seen the big TV preachers, I played the clips now, saying the Christians were
wrong to not do what Rome said and worship those idols.
Romans 13, do what they say.
I haven't seen it, but I know from reading the book of Acts, the Jews were constantly
persecuting the Christians.
They were taking them out of the synagogues, they were beating them, they were putting
them to death.
And all throughout the book of Acts, every Bible-believing preacher is getting arrested,
he's getting beaten, he's getting persecuted, he's getting in prison.
And yet we're taught that before the Antichrist comes, before the one-world governments in
place, before they start this law that says that if you won't worship the Antichrist,
you're gonna be killed.
You know, we're all gonna be out of here because they say, God would never allow his people
to go through something like that.
God loves us too much to allow us to suffer.
He would never allow us to go through tribulation, but yet every other generation of believers
have gone through tribulation.
Well, look at Paul, his job was to hunt down for the Sanhedrin, hunt down Christians.
And let me make it real clear, I do believe in the rapture, I'm not saying that the rapture
is a false god.
I know, they'll spin that too.
Yeah, this is what they'll do, you're saying there's no rapture.
Or they'll say, well, here's people before 1830 teaching that the rapture existed.
No, that's not what we're saying.
Before 1830, there was not a person on this planet who believed that the rapture came
after or before the tribulation.
The Bible says that the rapture happens after the tribulation.
That's when Christ comes in the clouds.
I wanna go to some, the point is the film covers all this.
And again, even if you're not a Christian, you need to see it.
It's very well done, because it explains why Christians will go along with anything now.
Well, you know what, and the film is important for a Christian and non-Christian alike.
First of all, if somebody's not a Christian, they need to watch the film and become a Christian,
because honestly, and that's explained at the end of the film.
But honestly, I don't understand how you can look around and see all these things happening
in the world today, and then look at the Bible and see that it's exactly what the Bible said
would happen, and then see-
Well, see, what I do is I just point out what the New World Order is doing, and I just say,
hey, you wanna see it?
And people will actually watch it.
My experience is you're gonna see this or go to hell, and they don't watch it, you know?
But here's the thing, even if you're not a Christian, I'm sure you have some Christian
friend who just refuses to wake up and refuses to understand what's going on with the global
government, the New World Order, the food supply, the water.
This film is the ultimate film for waking Christians up, because it's packed with Bible-
Well, look at Revelation.
It talks about the different passages, how the kings of the earth and the sorcerers manipulate
the pharmacia, the drugs, to drug the public and make us drunk on the blood of the innocents
Pepsi puts the dead baby parts in.
It's like the golden child, they're trying to get him to eat the bad things they can
like spiritually get at him.
But the point is they're sitting there point blank saying that they traffic in our souls.
That's what they want.
The globalists want our minds.
They're not after treasure and power, their minions are.
The high-level Luciferians aren't even into materialism, they want our souls.
Exactly right.
And this film, we spend about half the film just demolishing the pre-tribulation rapture
lie.
And that's like taking candy from a baby, because I mean, it's so clear in scripture.
And then we spend the other half of the film just explaining how this is all going to play
out and showing examples from now about the implantable chips, about the cashless society,
about-
How are they going in?
I mean, it's total control.
They're having police checkpoints with scanners.
I've got articles targeting, they know veterans off their license plate, scanned, no criminal
record.
The police are, this is a courtesy safety check, let me search your car without a warrant.
And then they're getting, in New York State, five felony counts facing 20 years in jail.
And they're saying, I'm a decorated veteran, I didn't even know that the law said this
was illegal.
They're like throwing the book at him saying, we're gonna get you.
I mean, they're going after good people now.
Oh, yeah, and all throughout the Bible, going back to the very beginning, Cain killed Abel.
All throughout the Bible, it's the bad guys killing the good people.
And evil wants high office to abuse.
Exactly.
And again, the whole Bible's about don't trust the government, stand up against it.
Romans 13 is totally taken out of context is why we sell the book, Romans 13, the true
meaning of submission by Chuck Baldwin and his constitutional lawyer's son breaks that
all down.
Every church I go to, it doesn't matter, Pentecostal, Evangelical, Baptist, my wife wants to go
to church.
You know, Christian friends, I go in, and at the end of the sermon, they go, we need
to do what the government says, and they're of the Lord, and there's gonna be some times
coming when the government needs to do some things, but it's of God.
And I know their clergy response team, and I go up and say, were you told to do that
by higher ups for FEMA?
I'm not gonna talk about that now, sonny boy there.
It's a federal agent there now, so devilish, so unconstitutional.
And they're not even bad men themselves, but they are now agents of the New World Order.
Well, you know, I actually used to attend a really big mega-type church, and when I
went to that really big church, the pastor was literally called to a meeting with George
W. Bush in Washington, DC, with a bunch of other big-time pastors.
And they sat him down and told him, we're on your team, you know, but you need to help
us, and here's what, you know.
And basically, these pastors are literally getting their marching orders from the government,
because the government's not stupid.
You know, they know that these big pastors that pastor really big churches-
It's over 100,000 now.
It's little ones.
I've got the manuals.
I'm sure you've seen our clergy response teams that we broke seven, eight years ago.
And since then, it's been declassified.
They've got them ready that when the time comes, turn your guns in, take the shots,
go to the camp, let them take your husband, it's of the Lord.
It's action.
And you know what's sad about that is that-
By the way, I'm not just saying that.
That's in the manuals.
Go ahead.
Oh, I know.
They plan on taking us away.
I've seen the evidence.
And the thing is, the thing that's sad about it, though, is that it turns a lot of people
off away from Christianity, because they see how basically a lot of these pastors are these
minions of the New World Order, and these minions of big government and global warfare
and all these different things-
Minions of the devil.
And minions of the devil.
And then they look at that, and it makes them turn against the Bible or turn against Jesus
Christ or not want to hear about it, when in reality, that's not the Bible or Jesus
talk.
And these guys don't know the Bible, you know?
And so if we could get some preachers that would stand up and preach what the Bible really
says, and warn people about these things, then maybe people would, you know-
I agree.
I'm going to go to, and again, people out there are Christians, like, how dare you even
talk about this?
What's wrong with talking?
See, this is the big taboo.
Let me tell all the Christians out there something.
In your life, if you've done the right thing and stood up against evil, God many times
will protect you, unless it's part of a larger plan.
I don't pray to God every day, hey, give me this, give me that, protect me.
I just say, look, I'm a sinner, I'm a dirty rag here, I'm trying to fight evil, my heart
loves good.
Will you help me be strong?
Will you help me not be a bad person?
There's all these Pharisees out there that want to make you obsess on the law, but not
the heart.
And the issue is, I'm going to tell Christians something out there.
You are not going to make it through this evil that's coming, believing you're going
to be teleported out of here.
I assure you, that's just not justice.
God is not going to let you sit there like a coward and be ejected out of this if you
don't stand up against evil.
I'm not saying God doesn't deliver people, but they have to go through the fire first.
Is that not biblical over and over again?
It's the same stories over and over again.
It's definitely biblical that every single Christian, according to the Bible, is appointed
to suffering, to go through trials, to go through tribulations.
You know, yeah, he's going to see us through.
The Bible says many of the afflictions of the righteous, but the Lord deliver them out
of them all.
But it's not saying, you know, we're going to be delivered before the afflictions come.
You know, the Bible teaches...
What about Job?
You know, why did he just get delivered up front?
Exactly.
As Christians, we all have to fight.
And it's said he was as near perfect as any man.
He was the greatest man living on the earth at that time, is what the Bible says.
He was an upright man, and he went through the most suffering of anybody in the Bible.
Okay?
Because all that will live godly in Christ Jesus shall suffer persecution.
And Christians today, it's like you said, you know, the Christians today who don't see
this coming, they're not prepared for it, you know, it's going to catch them unawares.
It's going to catch them off guard.
They're going to panic.
They're going to be disillusioned.
You know, what happened to the rapture, I don't know what to do, I'm scared.
And you know, those of us that are awake, we're ready for it, you know?
They're already setting up checkpoints nationwide where they're looking for veterans, Christians,
landowners, second coming of Christ, believers, libertarians.
They know, I mean, the main homeland security and the same in Europe is for us.
I mean, there it is, these are really bad people.
I mean, I want to go to calls, we got a caller from Australia, he's been holding the longest.
I promise I'm going to get to you after the break, Sean, I'm going to give you time.
But John says he disagrees, he's listening on shortwave in Texas, WWCR World Service.
John, what do you disagree with, brother?
Hello?
Yes.
I'm approaching this conversation not hostile.
It's okay.
Tell us what you think, brother.
Okay.
I just didn't want you to understand I'm not coming at you hostile.
I don't mind that.
Go ahead.
Yes, sir.
In Pastor Anderson, in 2 Thessalonians chapter 3, or I'm sorry, chapter 2 verse 3, have you
ever read the Geneva Bible?
In that verse, they changed it in the Geneva Bible, and when they changed it in the King
James Version, they changed it to become a falling away.
And originally, it was a departing.
And that, to me, shows that there, you know, that there was, there has to be a departing
of something.
Okay, I've heard this theory that the falling away is actually a departure, meaning that
Christians are departing this earth.
The Greek word there is apostasia.
You actually expect me to believe that the Greek word apostasia should be translated
as departure, meaning departing in the rapture?
No, apostasy is when people fall away from the faith or depart from the faith.
The Bible says in the last days, some will depart from the faith.
Everyone knows a falling away means look at Europe, look at America, people, you know.
Look, I encourage you, the Greek word apostasia is where we get our English word apostasy.
And so when the Geneva Bible said a departure, it's talking about departing the faith.
Falling away means falling away from the truth.
And that's what we're seeing today, a lot of Christians.
How does the beast wage war on the saints and overcome them if there's, the Christians
are all gone?
But look, I've heard this so many times, wake up people, apostasy, apostasia, that is not
the rapture.
And look, this caller, I'm not trying to be rude to the caller, but this subject just
gets me fired up.
And let me tell you something, Christians today who believe in the pre-trib rapture,
this is the kind of ridiculous reasoning they use.
They're gonna take me to Second Thessalonians chapter 2 verse 3.
My gut in studying the world, they're planning to bring in world government and kill.
Their plan is over 90% of us, okay?
They're planning to kill people and they're a cultist and they're using microchips to
buy and sell.
I mean, it's on, folks.
So I'm here to tell you, all the Christians out there thinking you and your kids are getting
out of this.
There's none of you are getting out of this unless it means you die early before this
happens.
Okay, I got a warning for you right now.
You can put it in the bank.
Okay, you can put it in a pipe and smoke it.
Nobody, and I mean nobody rides for free.
Nobody's going in the kingdom of heaven without showing their metal.
The fire separates the garbage from the gold.
I'm gonna go back to that caller.
Stay there, sir.
I wanna give you a response back, John.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not gonna wanna miss this exciting message.
Here's why.
Our solar generators provide life-saving electrical power, and unlike gas generators, solar generators
run quietly, emit no fumes, and produce electricity from the sun.
So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now, here's the best part.
Every year, we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse, and we discount them heavily at the end of
each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait.
They go fast.
Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
It's time for a home security quiz.
Answer this.
What effective home security device is smaller than a coffee cup fakes up burglars into thinking
someone is home at your house while you're away, plugs into any wall outlet, is recommended
by many police departments, and sells for less than $35?
Yes, it's fake TV.
This year, about one in every 50 U.S. homes will have a break-in, with burglars usually
picking the easy target, a dark house that looks like no one is home.
Fake TV is a small electronic security device that makes it look like someone is home watching
TV by simulating the light from a real TV.
It's like a lamp on a timer, but far more convincing.
And for only $34.95, fake TV could be the difference between coming home to a secure
house or one that's been ransacked.
Go to faketv.com or call 1-877-5FAKETV, that's 877-532-5388, or go to faketv.com.
Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration.
As an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years and serving thousands of satisfied customers,
the Berkey guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration systems.
The Berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable black purification
elements that purify water by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria, cysts and parasites to
non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides.
Order the Berkey light system today, complete with two black Berkey elements for only $231.
And the Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge.
With the purchase of a Berkey light, the Berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride and
arsenic filters for only $39.99.
That's over 30% off the retail price.
Call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653.
That's 1-877-886-3653.
Or order online at goberky.com.
That's goberky.com today.
By the way, everything we've talked about unfortunately is now starting to unfold.
And all over the country, they're getting Homeland Security grants starting with New
York and LA.
They now have naked body scanners that the police force people into on the street randomly.
They're doing something like half a million a year random searches without warrants.
Now that's up at infowars.com in New York, and now they're having warrantless checkpoints
here in Texas.
I mean, this is just unbelievable.
Engineer files lawsuit against New York Street body scanners, violation of the Fourth Amendment.
It's just incredible.
MSNBC urges viewers to boycott gun manufacturers.
I mean, this is a full racketeering operation.
McCain and Schumer moved to force Americans to use biometric ID for employment.
After the tribulation sneak peek, got the trailer up there, Department of Homeland Security
targets gun collector, decorated combat veteran arrested, charged with five felonies for possession
of AR-15 magazines in New York State.
Now illegal.
They say they're gonna throw him under the jail.
This is how they're gonna come after us, folks, and it is pure evil.
And we can be like Nineveh, I believe, and get a reprieve if we push this back.
I had a sheriff on the one in Kentucky who's now got hundreds of sheriffs by his honor
going public saying, I won't enforce this, I'm gonna stand against the gun confiscation.
Now hundreds, prominent ones are coming out saying they stand with him.
He said, look, he said, we might have had all this happen in the 70s when people stood
up.
It would have had to happen last year.
We're in the game, folks, and it's all in the Bible.
Whether you believe it or not, it's amazing philosophy, amazing information.
The media puts it down all day because they're scared of it.
And read the Bible and tell me, how did it predict all this with such precision?
I wanna go to Sean in Australia who's holding super patient.
I promise I'm gonna get to you.
But John in Texas who disagrees, the pastor got fired up there with you, you're very nice
to call in.
Do you wanna have a counterpoint back to him?
Yes, yes, thank you.
Pastor Anderson, have you ever read the book, Why So Many Churches by Dr. Noah Hutchings?
The reason I'm bringing this up is because I believe that-
I've read it, everybody fights over doctrine until everything splits.
Exactly.
And I don't have a bone to pick either way on this side.
If we're raptured out of here, I'm happy, I just know I'm insecure in Christ.
That's where I'm coming from.
No, no, I think that's key, but we need to be fighting this thing.
Because what matters is people's souls.
Go ahead, Pastor.
Comments?
Well, I appreciate the call and I'm sorry that I got a little fired up there, it's just
I'm really passionate about this.
Falling away means falling down, not up.
Yeah, if things fall, they fall down, they don't fall down.
We're not gonna be raptured to the center of the earth.
So the apostasia or falling away or departure is not the rapture.
But as far as the idea of not fighting over doctrine, I disagree with that.
I haven't read the book, I can't comment on it.
But I'm gonna fight over doctrine until I die, because I do want to fight over every
little doctrine.
Because if it wasn't important, it wouldn't have been in the Bible.
And let me tell you something, it's the New World Order that wants to unite everybody.
Have you known World Council of Churches?
Yeah, they want to unite all the churches, World Council of Churches.
They want the Baptist- Ecumenical.
Ecumenicalism, they want the Baptist, the Methodist, Presbyterian, Catholic, Mormon,
Jehovah's Witness.
They want them all to join up.
That's the New World Order.
Let's go to Australia real quick.
John in Australia, thanks for holding her on the air.
Alex, how are you?
Look, I want to speak to another book, another book written by Carol Quigley that I'm sure
you're familiar with, Tragedy and Hope.
Yes, sir.
There's actually a passage in there that actually gives you the historical framework for understanding
why weapons are needed in times of human civilization when there is enemies.
Now, if you give me just five minutes to read it, you can use this against anyone who argues
against you.
No, no.
We're going to go to overdrive in a moment, but go ahead and tell people the passage,
the page.
We even sell Tragedy and Hope, it's like 1,100 pages long.
This is top globalist admitting the whole program, Bill Clinton's mentor at Georgetown.
Give people the passage and page number, we'll come back and let you read it on air.
No worries.
Okay, I actually don't have the page number, I've just got to print it out right now.
No, I understand, but I'm saying if you give me the page number, I can actually go grab
the book right over there on the bookshelf and then show people, give me a couple words
out of it and then I can go to the, give me a name out of it and then I can go look up
the page number in the back of the book.
Stay there, we'll be right back.
Thank you for listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
Looking back on 2012, I know personally I'm thanking God that my family and I made it
through the year from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer
drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy.
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
My friends at eFoods Direct hear from customers every day that are fortunate to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand.
Danny from New York City wrote in following Hurricane Sandy and said, almost all the grocery
stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my
sister and my niece.
Bottom line, it's better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
Feed common sense as warning and do what I've done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex.
They have the best tasting long-term storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 and ask about the Alex Jones special or go to eFoodsDirect.com forward
slash Alex.
Get self-sufficient today.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex.
Coast to coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, I was talking to Pastor Anderson.
He listens to us on XM 166, and they carry three hours that they come in at the second
hour to the second, third, and fourth hour.
For a while, I was doing four hours.
And a lot of days, we do do the fourth hour, and here we are doing it.
But we're talking to Sean in Australia.
This is about a five-minute segment, so you've got the floor.
Go ahead and read from Carol Quigley's Tragedy and Hope.
And then, guys, I don't see one over there.
Will you guys run me one in from the shipping department?
Thank you.
So, Sean, you've got four minutes.
Start reading.
Okay, so firstly, Colin, you've got to understand that this book was actually intended for the
intellectual community and for the elites themselves.
They never actually, really, it was never targeted for the general population.
So the general population can now use this as the weapon.
Yeah, this was a control manual for globalists to understand why they were left and right,
how they created the synthesis.
Go ahead.
Okay, so this is directly reading.
It's on the military level in Western civilization, the 20th century, that chief development has
been a steady increase in the complexity and the cost of weapons.
Weapons are cheap and easy to get and so easy to use that almost anyone can use them after
a short period of training.
Armies are generally made up of large masses of amateur soldiers.
Such weapons we call amateur weapons and such armies we might call mass armies of citizen
soldiers.
The age of Pericles in classical Greece and the 19th century in Western civilization were
periods of amateur weapons and citizen soldiers, but the 19th century was preceded, as was
the age of Pericles also, by a period in which weapons were expensive and required long training
in their use.
Such weapons we call specialist weapons, periods of specialist weapons are generally periods
of small armies of professional soldiers.
In a period of specialist weapons, the minority who have such weapons can usually force the
majority who lack them to obey, thus a period of specialist weapons tends to give rise to
a period of minority rule and authoritarian government, but a period of amateur weapons
is a period in which all men are roughly equal in military power.
A majority can compel a minority to yield and a majority rule or even democratic government
tends to rise.
So what you've got to realize here in this passage is he refers to specialist weapons.
Think about what we have right now.
We have Skynet, total lockdown of the skies.
We have specialist weapons, they're called drones.
We have the specialist weapons against us against our health, it's called eugenics.
So why do we need weapons?
Because as we all know it's not for hunting, it's to actually equalize power.
Now Carol Quigley characterizes that periods of specialist weapons which we are currently
in today, the present, 2013, it's a period of specialist weapons, tend to give rise to
a period of minority rule and authoritarian government.
Now the term authoritarian is actually incorrect.
Alex also uses it a lot.
You should actually refer to it as totalitarian government.
Now this totalitarian government is also in tandem with programs such as Agenda 21 and
everything like that and the underlying ideology of this I would actually like to speak to.
Alex was just talking before about how the elite or whatever you want to call them, worship
a specific religion, they worship certain ideologies.
They have basically, they recruit people into their organization through what I call the
most extreme form of nepotism where they actually recruit people based on their ideologies alone.
Now the undercurrent of ideology through all sciences, especially earth or environmental
sciences is actually something called conservatism.
The overwhelming belief from the scientific community is that the universe is entropic.
That means that with time, the universe eventually dies of a so-called heat death but if we look
at anything, anything in history, we actually see counter-entropic development.
Hey sir, let me stop you.
I've actually got the book here and its bibliography is big but not big enough.
I'm not finding the, I remember reading this many years ago.
Tell me where you found it.
Send your link to showtipsninfoawars.com or give me the basic page number because I want
to show TV viewers this.
You're right.
This is big news.
I'm going to come back to you.
Hello, I'm Alex Jones.
Myself, my family, the infoawars.com team want to relay to you and your families that
we are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front.
Infoawars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats but we can't do that without
your help.
By getting the films, bumper stickers and t-shirts at infoawars.com, you will wake up
people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before.
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here.
It's an info war.
The spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
My name is Steven Huir.
After 22 years of nutritional counseling, I've observed that most brain malfunctions
have at their roots some form of toxicity and brain damage.
So whether it is poor memory, poor focus, lack of creative thinking or more serious
matters like inability to focus, speak normally or remember things, the emphasis to getting
one's brain working optimally needs to be on detoxification.
One World Way supports your body's number one means of detoxification, which is glutathione
production.
My name is Angie and my son has suffered from borderline autism and constipation.
I got him on One World Way and in two months his constipation is gone.
He has become friendlier, he can carry on a normal conversation with me and he has made
his first friend.
He's doing great and he looks forward to taking One World Way every day.
You could offer him a present or a cake and he would prefer the One World Way.
Go to Oneworldway.com, that's Oneworldway.com or call 888-988-3325, that's 888-988-3325.
In this unpredictable world, disaster can strike anyone.
That's why an essential part of any emergency survival plan must be stove in a can.
When power goes out and gas lines are down, the portable, safe, easy to use stove in a
can cooks food up to four hours and boils water in as little as five minutes.
Stove in a can comes with everything you need.
The stove, fuel, even waterproof matches, all in a compact, durable, heavy-duty container.
Plus the all-natural, non-explosive, 100% waterproof fuel source can be stored indefinitely.
Say goodbye to the hassle and danger of propane, lighter fluid, or gas.
Stock up now and protect your family with Stove in a Can.
Starting out at $29.99, special bundle offers now available with a 100% satisfaction guarantee
or your money back.
Order yours today at StoveInACan.com, that's StoveInACan.com.
From his Central Texas command center, deep behind enemy lines, the information war continues.
It's Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Ladies and gentlemen, we're going back to Sean in Australia.
If you just joined us, he brought up a tragedy and hope written by the head of political
science at one time at Georgetown University.
That's where the globalists send their people to get the inside scoop.
And only 1,000 copies of this book were originally printed back in the mid-1960s to be given
to the CIA section chief, State Department people.
It was commissioned over a decade by the Carnegie and Rockefeller Foundations, Quigley later
when this came out, had to admit that.
And he brags in the book, actually, that he was commissioned and allowed into the Annals,
the Bilderberg Group, and others.
And he says, I believe this should be an open conspiracy.
It's a great idea to have world government to engineer everybody.
And the book is, let me tell you how many pages long.
It's over 1,350 pages long.
Now the plates got out.
And Patriot groups associated with the John Birch Society and others printed tens of thousands
of these up in the 70s.
And there were even threats of legal actions and things, but the point is they backed off.
And we found the publisher that republished it.
We do, I wasn't getting to sell the book today, but the caller from Australia called in and
said, have you read what's on page 1,200, The Unfolding of Time?
And I'm gonna show view, and it's also in chapter two, The Unfolding of Time, but also
in chapter two, they say similar things.
And yes, I read most of this book, I'm gonna be honest with you, it's 1,300 pages long.
I read most of it back in about 1996, and a few years ago, I tried to read it again.
I'm gonna be honest, I haven't read the whole thing.
But the whole deal is how we control the left and the right, we want there to be the illusion
of choice.
We wanna bankrupt people, make them dependent, only we'll be able to operate.
We like fascism, we like socialism, we like communism.
As long as it centralizes, we hate libertarianism, we hate freedom cuz it makes people uppity.
And this caller was bringing this up, and I remember reading this when he was saying
it, I knew he wasn't lying because I had the remnants of the memory of that.
I guess that's what the beginning of wisdom is.
You don't remember it all, you just remember pieces.
You know the person's being accurate.
And he says right here, we don't want the general public having arms because it makes
it a free society and we can't stand up against them.
We want specialized armies to basically oppress them.
And he goes on to talk about how basically the founders wanted a citizen army in Western
civilization and freedom, and they don't want that.
And the caller's like, this will defeat the gun control debate.
Point out the tyrants want our guns, well, that is what's defeating them.
Sure, you could argue let's put mentally ill people in a registry so they can't own a gun.
They already have that.
Adam Lanza tried to buy guns five times, he failed, okay?
So they don't care, they want our guns.
They're gonna use anything reasonable to enslave us, they're not reasonable.
So their reason to want our guns is to enslave us.
They're arming to the teeth while telling us it's bad for us to have any guns.
I wanna go back to Pastor, who's here in studio with us today, and he's got the new, well,
he's part of the new film, Pastor Anderson, Let No Man Deceive You After the Tribulation
film.
What is your take on this Carol Quigley passage and what the caller was raising?
Well, it's all part of the same agenda.
In order to totally enslave people, you're gonna have to take away their guns, you're
gonna have to take away their weapons.
The Bible clearly says that the Antichrist is gonna make war with the saints and overcome
them.
Well, how's he gonna do that?
Obviously, he's gonna put us in a society where we have no freedom, where we're completely
controlled, completely surveilled, we're not gonna have any weapons, we're not gonna be
able to defend ourselves.
And that's why the Bible tells us that Christians are gonna be beheaded en masse because of
the fact that the government's gonna have the control to carry out that.
The TV preacher told me that Scottie's on the Enterprise is gonna beat me up.
That's about as true as Star Trek is true.
You know, I mean, the idea of the rapture taking place before the tribulation is about
as biblical as the Starship Enterprise picking us up before the tribulation.
All right, I wanna go back-
Number one is found in scripture.
I wanna go back to the caller, but if you just join us, I'm gonna read the passage from
page 1,200 that the caller was raising.
When weapons are of the amateur type of the 1880s, as they were in Greece in the 5th century
BC, they are widely possessed by citizens' power is similarly dispersed.
So dispersed power is everybody being armed.
And that sound good?
No, the UN says they want the abolition of civilian ownership of firearms, quote, because
it threatens a legitimate power monopoly of the state, UN treaty on general, small arms
assignment, ratified and accepted for full attempted passage at the full UN assembly,
July 7th, 2001.
I mean, this is their plan, they say, cuz they know people aren't reading what they're
saying.
I mean, they're like, we're gonna enslave these people, we're gonna cut their food off
so we can sterilize whoever we want.
Once we got them all on welfare, they'll all be social engineered.
We can just give them shots to kill their butt.
But we wanna kill them over a couple years, they don't know we killed them.
But then the Africans know to run at the villages when the UN shows up.
Let's continue.
And again, let's show people from the actual book.
If you guys can document Cam in on here, I wanna show people this right here, right here.
When the weapons, thank you, when the weapons are of an amateur type as the 1880s, as they
were in Greece in the 5th century BC, they are widely possessed by citizens' power is
similarly dispersed.
And no minority can compel the majority to yield to its will, globalist foreign bankers.
With such an amateur weapons system, that's what he calls it, in other conditions are
not totally unfavorable.
See that's saying it's a problem for the elite if people are armed.
We are likely to find majority rule, this is a big problem, and a relatively democratic
political system.
But on the contrary, when a period can be dominated by complex and expensive weapons
that only a few persons can afford to possess, robot armies, drones, or can learn to use,
we have a situation where the minority who controls such specialist weapons can dominate
the majority who lack them, and the minority is a eugenicist, Luciferian psycho group.
You might not want them to be the only ones with weapons, just an idea.
In such a society, sooner or later, an authoritarian political system that reflects the inequity
and control of weapons will be established.
At the present time, there are systems to be little reason to doubt that the specialist
weapons of the day will continue to dominate the military picture in the foreseeable future.
And I'm gonna do a whole piece on this, cuz it's so important.
He goes on to say how terrible it is that in the United States, we have guns.
That's right over here, cuz they're not gonna be able to have their social engineering system,
because of the United States and the guns, and England.
Well, forget that, they got the guns in England.
I'm not gonna spend all day on that, Pastor Anderson, another comment there and then we'll
go back to the caller.
He talks about the distribution of power amongst a lot of people versus being ruled by a small
minority.
Well, when we look at the book of Revelation, we see the end of this is that all the power
is gonna be concentrated in ten kings or ten leaders.
And then all of those-
Who give power unto the beast.
Exactly, then those ten kings will further give all their power to one man, who's called
the Antichrist.
And this man's gonna be given all of the power, he's gonna rule over the entire world.
And he's gonna have cures and diseases, life extension.
It says his image will be projected into all places, a hologram TV, it describes that.
Exactly, and so he is going to rule over everyone.
And not only is he gonna have all the political power, but he's also going to be worshipped
as God.
And the Christians are going to declare him to be the second coming of Jesus Christ, the
apostate Christians.
That's because they believe this must be the rapture or something.
Yeah, this is the second coming of Christ.
And then the Jews are gonna say, this is our Messiah, we've been waiting for.
And then the Islamic people, they will declare him to be the fifth Imam or whatever, or the
Imam Mahdi.
And then the Buddhists are gonna say, well, this is the new embodiment of the Dalai Lama
or whatever.
And so-
That's why the UN already says, you can have your religion, but it's gonna worship this.
Exactly, all of the major mainline religions, including apostate Christianity, are all going
to be brought-
Well, the Pope's been saying we need a one world religion and all the same.
Exactly.
And they're all lining it up.
Exactly, and all of these major false religions, they're all looking for some Messiah, okay?
Now, yes, we are looking for the second coming of Jesus Christ, but we know it comes after
the tribulation.
We know that the imposter comes first.
Now think about how evil this is.
The Bible teaches us that before the second coming of Christ, there's an imposter coming-
And a great delusion.
A great delusion, and an imposter who comes first and claims to be Jesus Christ before
the real Jesus Christ comes back.
And what is this pre-tribulation rapture doctrine teaching?
To expect Jesus to come at any moment, who's really coming, the antichrist.
Now, exactly, now let's explain this here in overdrive, powerful information.
If you're looking at this, this is the only argument that people can say to shoot this
down.
The elites looked at this science fiction book, the Bible, and said, this is a great
idea, this hallucination, the guy on the Isle of Patmos had, John had, John the Revelator
and stuff.
This is a great idea, let's just use this.
And then, let's go ahead and worship Lucifer, cuz I've studied the globalist, they do, they
are into the occult.
So they've just adopted it, they've just adopted the bad guy of the book as a self-fulfilling
prophecy.
What do you say to that?
Well, I say the fool had said in his heart, there is no God.
I'm a Bible-believing Christian, I believe every word of the Bible.
And I think it's hard to look at all the evil in this world.
And it's hard to look at that.
Well, there is a design that's above humans.
There's gotta be a design.
I'm sorry, but I do not believe that if we travel all the way to the top, we're just
gonna get to the bankers.
I know they're at the top.
No, no, no, no, I've studied it, there is a spirit behind it.
You can see it animating and working.
This conspiracy is multi-generational, it's been going on for hundreds of years.
And it is magic, I mean, the enemy has over the horizon radar, they've got a lot of tricks.
It's not just one man or one group of men or one family, this has been going on for
hundreds of years because Satan is at the top of that pyramid.
And the bankers and Bill Gates and these high up globalists, eugenicists, they are working
for him.
They are getting their marching orders from him.
And a lot of people who don't believe in these quote unquote-
I've studied all these people, they're all into weird secrets and stuff.
And a lot of people, the reason why they don't believe in so-called conspiracy theories,
you can't tell me that these people have gotten together and orchestrated this.
No, no, it's Satan that's directing them, not all of them might even know what their
part is.
No, no, they're compartmentalized, yeah.
They're compartmentalized.
And the Bible says, for we wrestle not against flesh and blood, but against principalities,
against powers, against the rulers of the darkness of this world, against spiritual
wickedness in high places.
Perfect description.
Yeah, the Bible warns us, rulers of the darkness of this world, spiritual wickedness in high
places.
That's what needs to be preached from the- And look at all, look at how they keep busting
senators with underage kids.
Exactly.
I mean, you don't even get in the door unless you like to hurt children.
Unbelievable.
We'll be back, I promise we're going to go back to Sean in Australia, then a bunch of
other people, XM listeners, you name it, we'll see the whole hour overdrive, get ready.
This is Alex Jones with five good reasons you should consider buying a solar power generator.
Number one, new climate legislation could easily double or triple your electric bill.
Number two, our new energy czar wants to control how much power your electric company allows
you to have.
It's true, total government control of electricity in the name of smart grid technology is coming.
Number three, in some areas of the country, the power grid is dangerously overloaded and
now new socialist legislation is only compounding the problem.
Number four, dangerous weather is always a threat to local grids.
Every year, thousands of families lose their power from weather related onages.
Number five, a solar power generator provides powerful backup insurance and peace of mind.
Folks, I really believe in the solar power generators offered by Solutions from Science,
one of my oldest sponsors.
You can get more information at www.mysolarbackup.com, that's mysolarbackup.com.
Remember, the government doesn't own the sun, so go to mysolarbackup.com or call 1-877-327-0365.
Are you still a traditional smoker?
Now experience a new lifestyle and try vaping with e-cigarettes by LASIG.
Imagine no ashes, stains, nasty smell or coughing and hacking.
With LASIG e-cigarettes revolutionary micro-electronic technology, rechargeable battery and unique
replaceable cartridge, you'll get all the benefits and satisfaction of smoking without
the hazards.
Choose your taste from a wide variety of our new American-made vapor at e-liquids at LASIG.com.
And LASIG smokes the competition by serving thousands of worldwide customers with real
people customer service, fast, free, same-day shipping and a 30-day warranty and satisfaction
guarantee.
So are you ready for a new vaping lifestyle?
Then call 870-518-4307, that's 870-518-4307 or visit LASIG.com, spelled L-E-C-I-G.com.
LASIG e-cigarettes for today's modern smoker.
HempUSA.org has a revolutionary wonder food for detoxing the body and rebuilding the immune
system.
Micro plant powder can help unclog arteries and soften heart valves while removing heavy
metals, virus, fungus, bacteria and parasites.
Plus it cleans and purifies the blood, lungs, stomach and colon.
Keep your body clean with micro plant powder.
Visit us at HempUSA.org or call 908-691-2608 today.
Hi this is Ted Anderson.
Have you ever wondered why banks, stockbrokers, investment advisors won't talk about gold
IRAs?
They've been available since 1986 yet the financial industry won't recognize the value
of gold for your retirement.
Gold is outperformed paper investments yet no word about IRAs.
If you would like to have gold for your retirement call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns call 800-686-2237.
Share your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration.
As an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years and serving thousands of satisfied customers,
the Berkey guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration systems.
The Berkey light systems include a set of self sterilizing and re-cleanable black purification
elements that purify water by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria, cysts and parasites to
non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides.
Order the Berkey light system today complete with two black Berkey elements for only $231
and the Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge.
With the purchase of a Berkey light the Berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride and
arsenic filters for only $39.99.
That's over 30% off the retail price.
Call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653, that's 1-877-886-3653 or order online at GoBerkey.com.
That's GoBerkey.com today.
All right, Alex Jones back live here.
We have Steven L. Anderson, a pastor, and he's one of the very informative people in
this amazing film, After the Tribulation, Let No Man Seem You.
New film out available at InfowarsShop.com or link through at Infowars.com and also the
book by Chuck Baldwin and his constitutional lawyer son Timothy Baldwin, Romans 13, The
True Meaning of Submission.
Very important to get all your preachers out there, they'll probably curl up like snakes
and hiss at you and pull out a pitchfork, but no, most of them don't know.
It's our job to challenge them.
I'm not on some high horse either here, folks, I mean I'm Mr. Goody Two-Shoes, I know right
from wrong, I know deception from the truth, because I have discernment, I mean anybody
who has discernment would just be freaking out over all this, especially when you integrate
it with history and everything else and what the globalists are doing.
The more I learn about the New World Order and then the more I go to the Bible, it's
like oh my gosh, now I could only now, 38 years old, almost 39, 39 a couple days, actually
understand the Bible and it's just so deep now, unlike anything I've ever read, once
you understand that you know it is inspired.
And it is a warning, I mean God wouldn't put us through this to test us if he didn't give
us a handbook.
Okay, and I'm not trying to preach here, it's just that you have to understand, ladies and
gentlemen, we are facing an elite that believe they're being directed by spirits.
Skull and bones, Bohemian Grove, the UN has this Luciferian Chapel in New York in it,
it's real.
Okay, I'm gonna go to Ed, Eric, Nick, Nick, and others, but Sean in Australia, you got
us off on this thing about Carol Quigley's book, where they admit free peoples have weapons,
but we want a technocratic elite with super weapons because we want control.
Yes, amazing, here's one of their top statisticians, tacticians admitting this, but it's like admitting
the sun came up this morning, but yes, they want our guns to enslave us, not to keep the
children safe.
Go ahead.
Well, you see, this book, Tragedy and Hope, is an informed historical account, but what
it lacks is the actual understanding of the proper framework for understanding human history,
and that is looking at human history based on its developmental qualitative state.
Now, let me give the readers an example just based on this.
The point is they're saying we have the will to power, we're in charge, that gives us the
right to be authoritarian, as if some moral authoritarianism, it never works like that,
it always leads to total rot.
But of course, some academic feeling good about himself because he's invited into the
upper halls of power is delusional.
This person is not spiritually smart.
I gotta jump to other callers, go ahead and finish it up quick cuz we gotta go.
Let me give the callers a quick example, now for example, I'm talking about organizational
development in history.
If we look at his passage, he says, the medieval period in which the best weapon was usually
a mounted knight on horseback, clearly a specialist weapon, was a period of minority rule and
authoritarian government.
Once again, it should be totalitarian.
Even when the medieval knight was made obsolete, along with his stone castle, by the invention
of gunpowder and the appearance of firearms, these new weapons were so expensive and so
difficult to use until 1800, that the minority rule and authoritarian government continued,
even though that the government sought to enforce its rule, by shifting from mounted
knights to professional pikemen and musketeers.
Now this shift is a qualitative upshift in development.
You see, the new phase of technology, the gunpowder, is a higher-
No, I agree, this is all gonna leak out everywhere, the bioweapons everywhere, and they're gonna
kill everybody.
And is that where you're going, the elite are creating their own destruction by a global
arms race?
Well, where I'm going is that, if you look at human history, we see these changes.
Now, the scientists who actually have now taken the overall commanding, the overall
directing ideological position in this global-
Gotta finish up in 30 seconds.
They believe in something called, they believe in the second law of thermodynamics.
Now, I'll issue a challenge right now to every scientist worldwide who believes in the big
bang in the context of the second law of thermodynamics, if you want to hold me on for another-
Now I gotta go, listen, this is what I do with callers, I'll let one person on for a
long time and then everybody else can get on.
Sean, if I wouldn't have gotten to other callers, I never would have gotten to you, I gotta
let you go.
And we got a long segment coming up here, and I promise we're gonna get to Ed, Eric,
Nick, Nick, and then that's gonna be it for calls, our XM listeners and shortwave listeners
and AM and FM listeners.
We're gonna get to you, and then we're gonna give him some time to finish up some other
topics and some other news that I haven't gotten to.
But do you wanna comment on where he was going with all that?
Well, I mean, it's really interesting information and the Bible definitely is very clear that
every single person should have a weapon.
All the way back to the book of Deuteronomy, he talks about every single citizen having
a weapon and having a paddle on the back of their weapon and so forth.
Because it restrains evil.
And then also even Jesus Christ himself in the Garden of Gethsemane said, hey, if you
don't have a sword, you need to sell your coat.
And they try to spin that now and say it was misinterpreted.
He was talking about a literal sword.
They pulled out two literal swords and said, Lord, we have two swords, and he said it's
enough.
And so the disciples had swords.
Plus somebody just had their ear chopped off with a sword.
We're talking about swords.
Yeah, Peter pulled out a sword and chopped the ear off.
Don't tell me that was a metaphor for the Bible.
He didn't pull out his Bible and chop that guy's ears off with a with a paper cut with
a Bible.
It was a literal sword.
We'll be right back.
Stay with us.
We're on the march.
The Empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
Introducing Pro One all of your filtration in one system portable on the go.
No more do you have two or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride.
You have a system that cuts out the sodium fluoride and up to ninety five percent of
hydrofluorosolic acid.
Advanced manufacturing technology combines silver impregnated white ceramic with new
aqua medics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals all in one
filter element.
It is the only one that does it and out of the gates.
We have a discounted at 10 percent off with promo code water.
This is the only system that in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides, herbicides, chloramines,
ammonia and chlorine hydrofluorosolic acid.
The most common form of fluoride not covered by other fluoride filter brands and sodium
hexafluorosilicate.
Get your pro pure with a new pro one filter today at info war store dot com or by calling
eight eight eight two five three three one three nine.
You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa, where a nicely furnished cabin
with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine and laundry service awaits.
After a good night's sleep, your adventure begins.
You're on a golden stag safari for big game, but it's not Africa, it's Argentina.
One on one guided hunts for water buffalo, Cougar, bighorn rams, wild boar and the biggest
stag deer in South America, all gold medal quality, all the action you can handle.
Land Rovers top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages, hunting guides, ground transportation
included and more, all more affordable than you can imagine.
The adventure of a lifetime starts at Golden Stag Safaris dot com.
The big game hunting ranch, Golden Stag Safaris dot com.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book Cancer Step Outside the Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the president could obtain this world class healer.
Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally
occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune
cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VENUSFLY or order from Carnivora dot com, that's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A dot com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VENUSFLY or visit Carnivora dot com.
That's your immune system, it's the only one you've got.
I'd like to share a revelation that I've had during my time here.
It came to me when I tried to classify your species and I realized that you're not actually
mammals.
Every mammal on this planet instinctively develops a natural equilibrium with the surrounding
environment, but you humans do not.
You move to an area and you multiply and multiply until every natural resource is consumed.
The only way you can survive is to spread to another area.
There is another organism on this planet that follows the same pattern.
Do you know what it is?
A virus.
Human beings are a disease, a cancer of this planet, you are a plague and we are the cure.
Resistance to tyrants is obedience to God.
It's Alex Jones.
Yep, that's what the globalists think of us, but then they try to block development, so
it's a self-fulfilling prophecy that we are these dogs, they say we are, but I study the
globalists.
They're a bunch of inbred people that are psychopaths.
We're going to go to your calls right now.
We have a new t-shirt out.
We haven't sold this for over a year and a half.
We had a Obama joker symbol that went viral all over the world, and I said it was a limited
edition t-shirt of it, and we haven't sold it in over a year and a half.
So we've redesigned a new one because that was limited edition.
Janae Meadows, our star graphics person, they're all stars, but she's amazing.
She came up with this of a bunch that we did that is my favorite and it says, Tyrant Obama
and him as the Joker.
And Obama-noids will ask you what it means, others will, you can explain what a tyrant
is.
And in our most popular t-shirt and put it on the back, the come and take it AK-47 with
the right to keep and bear arms shall not be infringed, words inside of it.
This I believe is the best t-shirt we've ever come out with.
It is available at Infowars shop.com or Infowarsstore.com.
Both URLs take you to the same place or by calling 888-25-33139, and your purchase of
books and videos and materials funds our entire operation.
And look, I got 50 people here, 51, I wanna hire five or six more to quite frankly do
radio news cuz stations all want it.
And that first five, six minute segment, we're getting ready to get the show cut down to
its official version every day with the nightly news.
It's all happening.
It's all happening and we just put out 150,000 free bumper stickers in 50 packs with the
free shipping to anybody that wanted them at Infowarsstore.com.
I think all those slots are filled now, 3,000 of them.
I mean, I know it's coming down, it's in steps downwards.
We're gone into another big step and now another, and it's gonna accelerate, boom, boom, boom,
boom, boom.
So I'm just like, fire everything, hit them, go, boom.
My gut is what I follow, my spirit, and it tells me what to do off the intellectual things.
But what my gut tells me is also picked up by everything in front of me.
It's amazing, it knows what's around the corner and then boom, it's there.
And I trust but verify my gut, this will sell out as well as 30,000 of them available, 70,000
at the streets.
In key areas in Texas is the Infowar, but the tyrants, why the tyrants want the guns,
the new magazine, buy them in 10 up to 100 packs at cost or get a subscription.
And everyone that signs up at Infowars.com forward slash newsletter will get a free e-copy
where it's color, you can flip it, click on the links.
It's free, Infowars.com forward slash newsletter.
But you have to sign up to get it and we will send it to you and incidentally, we've got
the nightly news for subscribers.
We've got all the films, we're putting stuff up there in HD now, most of it.
We're putting a lot of old archive stuff, ten years of prisonplanet.tv in April, 17
years on air, a lot of old stuff we're now putting there.
But the goal is to reach people.
So we're gonna start in the next few weeks on a limited basis, I wanna make sure it works
well and doesn't bankrupt me.
We're gonna have the three hour radio show in a medium quality, the high quality would
be for subscribers.
But the goal is to get the word out to people, prisonplanet.tv, the video feed of the three
hour today, it's a four hour radio show.
That will be fed out to everyone that signs up at infowars.com forward slash newsletter.
In a week or two, you'll get a link to the test beta streamed to make sure we can afford
it and everything.
And so we're definitely gonna test that out over a few months.
So again, I want to encourage everybody to sign up at infowars.com forward slash newsletter.
Now I promise to go to your calls and Pastor Steven Anderson is here also in studio with
us today.
But other points you'd like to add, you wanted to get into Plato's Republic, which is a key
globalist model.
You know, Tarpley will tell you that that's the model of the oligarchy in the New World,
or Plato's Republic.
We're gonna talk about that after we race through calls here.
But it's important to read the globalist intelligentsia's own manuals to not just believe us, but that
caller called in and said, hey, Tragedy and Hope says disarm the people to make them slaves,
top globalist book.
I go pull it off the shelf, sure enough, what he reads there, trust but verify.
And again, it's hundreds and hundreds of books I've read where they admit their plan for
global government and global enslavement.
Ed in New York, thanks for holding, you're listening on shortwave, go ahead.
Yes, I heard you describe that you have different products you have for sale just now for a
while.
And over the years, I thought that I had something to contribute to your show.
I thought it was the technology that Pat Flanagan has described in the book by Nick Bejic, Towards
a New Alchemy, where the neurophone he describes, I believe is miniaturized.
Yeah, they're now selling neurophones, they've got all sorts of new products.
The new Google Glasses have a neurophone and broadcast into your skull, into the middle
ear.
So that's the big technology they're going for.
Yeah, do you have any comments on that?
Neurophone only receives, it doesn't transmit.
Well, I'm talking about, guys, just type it in right now, Google Glasses broadcast sound
directly into the middle ear.
The point is that 15 years ago they had Coke machines in Japan that projected you, nobody
else can hear it, and it goes through to the skull.
All right, I appreciate your call, I'm not sure we're talking about neurophone, write
me a letter.
Okay, about that, let's go to Eric in Wyoming, then we're gonna go to Nick listening on XM.
Eric in Wyoming, you're on the air.
Good afternoon, Mr. Jones, my name is Eric Miller, I'm not hiding my identity.
We had an incident here at 1006 Plum Street.
Hold on, hold on, sir, sir, let me put you on hold.
We don't like people, nobody does this to talk radio.
Sometimes we get a lot of great calls, sometimes we get calls that are interesting, but they're
all over the map, especially when I go into a fourth hour and people have been holding.
Listen, you call in, you could be saying somebody else's name, I don't think you're a liar,
you sound like a reasonable guy, but other people can spoof and call in and say, I'm
this person at this address, this is happening.
And then we can get in trouble for letting that information go out.
You understand that's a dirty trick people do, so that's why we don't like people giving
out their last name.
Now they're a public figure and they call in and we think we recognize their voice,
we put them on hold, call them back, verify who they are.
Okay, now I'm not saying you're doing this, but just tell us about the incident, what
happened to you?
We got smart meters, we have Agenda 21 in the capital city of Cheyenne, Wyoming, we
got smart meters, we have Agenda 21, we have international building codes.
And we were forced, all right, by three Cheyenne Lightroom power workers and a deputy while
I was away, they came and threatened my wife.
Yeah, they put the eavesdropping that dowels into all your electronics on record and is
gonna quote, control your temperature.
They put the little, that's a little robot, it's a drone.
It's a, they admit they're going to robots, it just hit me.
The smart meter is a little robot that's plugged into the side of your house spying on you,
it's a robot spy.
Okay, what happened to you?
We're seeing the videos of the police coming with the smart meters and some are saying,
we don't care if you even turn your power off, you're going to have it slave, go ahead.
Yeah, so anyway, they forced away and I referred to them as the four cowards while I was away
from home, they came and intimidated my wife or else, all right?
Now, no man wants to come home and see his wife staring out the kitchen window in tears
and wondering what happened, just happened.
Now we got our smart meter, they also put a lock on it, which they took off later on
and two tags, a tag for the lock.
In other words, they were trying to demonize us for standing up.
No, I know, it's so weird, you don't want a smart meter admitted to rip you off?
It's on record, they use them to rip people off, that's San Francisco Chronicle, you name
it.
It dials into all new appliances, have digital wireless and your TV, this dials into and
it's all these health issues, you're weird.
You care what we're putting on your house, you're weird, it's weird to care about anything.
You don't like the army checkpoints on your highways and drills in every major city and
TSA, two miles from here, TSA runs checkpoints on the road now, but that's no big deal, that's
freedom, Pastor Anderson.
So how did this end, sir?
Well this ended with them forcing their way into my home and putting in the smart meter.
Into the home?
Yeah, well, they had to go to my home to get to my backyard cuz we have a fence that has
high privacy fence that's over six feet and it says-
Excuse me, this is a major felony, you've got a file suit on, official oppression, civil
rights violations, just sue them, okay?
And sir, you know what, I can tell you're a real guy, you wanna give out your name and
info for any constitutional lawyers that wanna stand up for you and your family in the state
of Washington?
Yes.
Okay, give out-
And Wyoming we're in.
Okay, what?
We're in the state of Wyoming.
Oh, okay, Wyoming, sorry, go ahead.
Most conservative state and Cheyenne is the capital.
I know, but this is happening to everybody right now.
So they forced their way into the house?
Well, they said or else, I got the phone call while I was up at the farm-
Or else, or else.
Or else.
That's free country.
Or else, and-
You know what the answer is, go dark.
You tell them you come remove it, you send them a cease and desist cuz courts like that,
then you sue them when they don't remove it, go dark.
Make a stand in the local news, make a big issue out of it.
Believe me, you're the new Rosa Parks, this is the new civil rights issue, they want us
fighting over race and all this stuff, this is what's happening.
Okay, how do people, do you have an email address or something so lawyers can help you
in Wyoming?
Yes, I do.
Give it to us.
All right, it's ebmcat9msn.com, Echo Victor Motel Charlie Alpha Tango 29 at msn.com.
Yeah, what happened is Halliburton, not Halliburton, though they're involved, Ken Lay, I'm so tired,
Enron.
Enron developed this in the mid 90s as a scam, they're convicted of scamming, and they can
control the prices, manipulate, gouge, and spy, this is all their smart growth plan.
And so you just get that together, you fight it in your local community, everybody has
to fight this because it's diabolical, God bless you, and I appreciate your call.
They're also using the smart meters that are up on polls that dial into your smart meter.
Those are hacking in, just like Google's been caught doing with their cars.
Pastor Anderson comments on what he was saying.
Well, unfortunately, I think I might have a smart meter at my house already.
No, no, that's what they do, they just show up, they come across your yard, they put it
on.
Yeah, they never even asked me about it.
It's just something that I think has just been installed a long time ago.
And there it is.
I don't really, you know, I think what they do is they charge you more when they feel
like it.
They track everything you're doing, and they grab all your wireless data, and they hack
your computers.
Well, I already know that I've been under surveillance.
No, I know.
But the point is, is that it's this total grid, right?
Oh, yeah, definitely.
And I mean, it has to be that way.
You know, it's like the Bible says, all these things must come to pass, but the end is not
yet.
You know, it has to be in place.
The control grid has to be in place in order to get all the power.
But we have to resist it.
Absolutely.
Of course we can.
I mean, folks, if you won't resist now, you're not gonna resist when they got a gun to your
head.
Look, the Bible verse I quoted earlier says, we wrestle not against flesh and blood, but
against principalities, against powers, against the rulers of the darkness of this world.
So it's saying we do wrestle against the rulers of the darkness of this world.
We do wrestle against spiritual wickedness in high places.
But wait, I mean, but they twist Romans 13 to say that we should have submitted to Hitler.
You know, they now teach Hitler was of the Lord.
Well, you know, you can twist, you can take little tiny bits and pieces of the Bible and
twist them to say whatever you want.
But earlier in the chapter, it's all about resisting tyranny and people are being arrested
for not following orders.
Not only that, Romans 13 is really clear about what the purpose of government is.
The only purpose of government, which is the punishment of evildoers, evildoer meaning
someone, evil in the Bible means harming someone else.
So it's to punish people-
It's a libertarian-
Exactly, exactly right.
And so God never gave the government-
No initiation of force.
Exactly, and so God never gave the government the authority to regulate our lives.
But maybe Romans 13 and one of these mainline preachers say maybe the US senator caught
with all these little kids, maybe he's the government.
I mean, I don't agree with that, but I'm a devil.
See, I don't think that senator should be having sex with little kids.
I am now violating Romans 13.
Well, they try to claim that basically every single governor or government official is
ordained by God when what he's saying is that he ordained human government in general.
The Bible is teaching that God ordained, you know, parents to have authority over their
children and he ordained human government to be there to punish the evildoer.
You know, thieves, rapists, murderers.
But when it's an evil government, we have a duty to overthrow it.
Absolutely.
But wait a minute, that's of the devil.
I mean, Dominican prostitute says Senator Bob Menendez likes the youngest and newest
girls.
I mean, he's a senator.
I mean, maybe he's God.
I mean, they already say Congress is above the law.
According to a lot of these pastors, you know that guy, we need to submit to him and love
him and pray for him and think he's wonderful.
And bring him children.
If you read the book of Judges, all throughout the book of Judges, there are all kinds of
oppressive governments coming in, taking away the freedom.
And then men like Gideon and men like Samson are standing up to him.
Well, they were of the devil.
No, no, no, no.
They were devils.
Samson was of the devil.
Delilah was good.
She did what the government said.
Samson was bad.
Right.
And you know what?
They were coming to Samson saying, look.
The Pharisees were good and you know who else was bad.
And you know what?
They came to Samson.
The Israelites came to Samson and said, listen, Samson, you need to understand these people
rule over us.
The Philistines rule over us.
They're the government.
You need to obey the government.
And they're rebuking Samson.
But the Bible says that Samson was filled with the spirit of God.
And Samson brought freedom.
Now, he made mistakes along the way, obviously.
You know, his weakness was through women.
And that's what the government at the time, the Philistine government-
That was King David's weakness.
They exploited Samson's weakness of women.
But the Israelites are constantly telling Samson, you need to just shut up and do what
you're told.
These are our leaders.
These are our rulers.
And God's spirit was leading Samson to fight against the flu.
It's the same thing in Ezekiel where he says, God, they're going to kill me if I keep speaking
out.
But I can't help it.
It's burning in my bones.
Right.
Exactly.
Jeremiah, actually.
Yep.
Exactly.
Yeah, Jeremiah, you know, he finally-
But I mean, I think that's in Ezekiel, isn't it?
It's in Jeremiah.
But Jeremiah basically got frustrated with preaching and finally just said, I quit.
That's it.
And everybody was telling him to quit.
But then he said that the word of God was like a fire burning in his bones and he could
not stop preaching.
I believe you, I just-
That's the kind of preachers we need today.
We don't need-
That's Jeremiah.
Yeah, Jeremiah 20, verse 9.
We don't need these milk toast preachers that are prostitutes of propaganda of the federal
government lying to people.
We need people to preach the actual Bible stories and to take stands even that are unpopular
and to preach the truth today.
Because I tell you-
I just-
It's the pastors that are leading-
I just can't believe most people submit to evil just because they don't want to be looked
at bad by the world.
Right.
I mean, who cares what a bunch of idiots think about you?
Well, they crucified Jesus.
They killed all the prophets.
And you know, the thing about this movie after the tribulation is every Christian who's watching
it is convinced.
It's so clear.
When you show it to pastors, they're scared of it.
They don't want to accept-
Because they want their comfortable Cadillac and going to the cafeteria with a little-
And they're going to lose it if they take a stand on this because the pre-trib rapture
is the popular doctrine.
Well, what does it profit a man to gain the whole world and lose his soul?
Exactly.
Yeah.
We'll be back with some more calls.
Nick and Nick lined up next.
Stay with us.
Hello, I'm Alex Jones.
Myself, my family, the Infowars.com team want to relay to you and your families that we
are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front.
Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats, but we can't do that without
your help.
By getting the films, bumper stickers, and t-shirts at Infowars.com, you will wake up
people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before.
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here.
It's an Infowar.
The spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
In the US, one in every 50 homes will have a break in this year.
Burglars call it smash and grab.
Police call it robbery.
We call it avoidable.
We are fake TV, a simple electronic device that can fool even professional burglars.
Fake TV easily plugs into any outlet and simulates the changing colors of a television.
To a burglar, it looks like someone must be home watching TV, so they'll likely move on
to an easier target.
At only $34.95, fake TV costs less than a month of most alarm monitoring plants and
it's perfect if you're traveling or away from home.
Order your fake TV by calling 877-5FAKETV or go to faketv.com.
That's 877-532-5388 or faketv.com.
Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
Fall in love with food storage savings this February at beprepared.com.
Starting today, beprepared.com saves you over $300 with a premium 1600 one-year supply,
including 126 cans of freeze-dried and dehydrated food.
Or get the new gourmet 14-day food supply with a full 2,000 calories per day with pre-planned
menu.
Stroganoff and Noodles are 20% off with purchase of six or more.
Mountain House Pork Chops are back in stock at 34% off.
Pack your own low-moisture foods with our new do-it-yourself super pale combo on sale
at 22% off.
Add to your preparedness with minor surgery kits at 15% off.
And wool-blended blankets are only $11.89.
The February fall in love with savings sale starts today at beprepared.com.
For contents and details, visit beprepared.com or call 800-999-1863.
The choice is clear.
Be unprepared or beprepared.com.
We're going to go to Nick in California listening on XM 166 and one more Nick and we're out
of time.
But Pastor Anderson, you've been wanting to talk about Piers Morgan since you got here
and your take on that and you have a Bible scripture about that event.
Right.
So somebody sent me a link to your video of Piers Morgan and I just wanted to say that
I loved it because I know you were getting a lot of criticism, people saying you shouldn't
have gotten angry.
It was about 10%.
But let me tell you something.
We ought to get mad about evil.
And that's righteous indignation.
Jesus flipped over the tables.
I mean, yeah, we ought not get mad because of something small that, you know, our wife
squeezes.
Conscious evil is needs to be dealt with.
Read that verse.
Yeah.
So I found this verse for you.
Ecclesiastes 7-7.
It says, surely oppression maketh a wise man mad and a gift destroyeth the heart.
So the Bible says there that oppression makes a wise man mad.
And so it ought to make you mad.
Well, the media, the media, the staff tried to spin it like, oh, it was a defeat.
Alex got mad, but they don't have me back on.
They were scared.
They were upset.
They were shaking.
They were crying.
The head producer.
They know that they want to keep us in a calm coma.
Right.
They don't want us getting angry.
Well, and people get mad when preachers get mad and start yelling about sin.
Every preacher in the Bible yelled and raised his voice and and got mad and beat the pulpit.
That's the way the preachers in the Bible were.
Jesus was that way.
All of them.
But, you know, Jesus beat him with a whip.
Yeah.
He chased him out of the temple with a whip, flipped over the tables.
But, you know, every hair legged man that I know said that he loved that interview and
he loved to see somebody just take it to him.
Just just, you know, get mad.
And I mean, look, you were face to face with the enemy right there.
Oh, you should have seen it in the eye.
And you know, how can you not be angry?
The thing is, I'm real and he made me mad.
Let's go ahead and talk to Nick listening on XM, Nick in California.
You're on the air, Nick.
Go ahead.
Hi, Alex.
This is Nick.
Hey, buddy.
I'm calling about we're talking about religion and believing in God and everything, and I've
been praying a lot lately.
And I just wanted to bring this to your attention that maybe we could start a third party with
you in your camp and going back to his camp, because you both believe you both are against
abortion.
You're both against Agenda 21.
You both believe in God.
You both defend the Constitution.
Listen, Glenn Beck does a lot of really good work and he's gotten better over the years.
But he's done dirty tricks to us and I mean, I'm saying he is.
He's got some serious issues and he's always trying to paint it like I'm doing bad things
to people.
And look, I don't even attack Rush Limbaugh or people like Michael Savage or Sean Hannity.
I don't attack my quote competition because I'm not in competition with them.
I could care less about being a big shot.
I want to fight tyranny.
I'm risking my life.
And I wish Glenn would stop taking things out of context or twisting things.
And I'm glad he's been going in the right direction a lot.
And you want to say something, Pastor Anderson?
I don't like Glenn Beck at all.
And I do like you, Alex.
But to me, Glenn Beck is just too much of a neocon, Republican type.
And I- He's been getting better, though.
Has he?
Well, I quit listening to him, so I'm not seeing him.
Well, I think a lot of that's just like Gunners of America gets the NRA, to be honest.
That's what we're doing.
I mean, I hear stuff out of Limbaugh, him.
It's directly what I say.
And that's good.
I just, I really feel good when they rip me off.
But they twist it, so I don't like that.
Because wow, I'm getting a bigger megaphone.
I mean, that's me on the air now.
All those places.
I mean, that's really good, cuz I know we're forcing this stuff out there.
Well, it seemed like Glenn Beck was just trying to promote his fellow Mormon, Mitt Romney.
Well, he came out and attacked me when I went on Piers Morgan and said I was working with
him to discredit people.
Or what about in Police State Part 4?
Isn't there a whole- He says there's no FEMA camps.
There's no army plans.
It's all documented.
He says there isn't.
Well, does Glenn Beck stand for 9-11 truth?
Oh, he says Ron Paul supporters should have the army used against him.
Well, if he's not standing for 9-11 truth, then he's not standing for much as far as
a political talk show.
All right, listen, folks, we're out of time here.
Sorry to the other callers.
I wanted to go to Nick in Pennsylvania.
Last words from Nick in Pennsylvania, 30 seconds.
Take us out.
Nick, Nick.
Okay, Alex, I just wanted to say to you, God bless you.
God bless Pastor Anderson.
You, like Elvis, are a living legend.
No, no, you are.
See you this Sunday, 4 to 6 Central.
Thank you for listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.