Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
It's Friday, January 18th, 2013. It's the Alex Jones Show. I'm Paul Joseph Watson, writer
with Infowars.com, filling in for Alex today. And the second half of the show will be presented
by the health ranger, Mike Adams. He'll be joined by Representative Steve Toth to talk
about the latest with the gun grab news, as well as Dr. Andrew Wakefield, who of course
has been vilified for revealing the dangers of vaccines. And coming up shortly, CNN can't
get him, but we can. It's the controversial Florida professor who's basically been savaged
by the mainstream media for questioning the official narrative behind the Sandy Hook shooting.
It's Professor James Tracy, and he'll be live via Skype to take your calls. And of course,
if you've been living under a rock for the past few weeks, then the internet is basically
aflame with what they're calling Sandy Hook truthers. And there's actually one YouTube
video alone which has got over 10.6 million views in the last 10 days alone that talks
about some of these questions surrounding the Sandy Hook massacre. So basically, he's
been absolutely pillared by the mainstream media. I'm sorry, sorry about that. He's been
absolutely pillared by the mainstream media. He was on CNN's Anderson Cooper 360 last Friday,
I believe it was. And for 25 minutes, Anderson Cooper attacked him, put his picture up on
screen. Basically, it was a surprise that there wasn't a wanted sign next to his name.
I don't actually believe in all these theories that are circulating about Sandy Hook, but
we're going to talk to the professor before the bottom of the hour. We're going to go
over some of the questions that he and others have raised about the Sandy Hook massacre
and about the backlash that he's faced from the likes of CNN, from the likes of Fox News.
So that's going to be a fascinating talk. We're also going to go to your calls at the
top of the hour for Professor James Tracy on all things Sandy Hook. But the top news
at the moment on infowars.com and prisonplanet.com, we've heard about the Nerf gun. We've heard
about the kid, you know, being suspended for making a gun sign with his hand. But this
one really takes the biscuit. And this took place in Mount Armel, Florida. This is a story
just out today. Basically, a five year old girl, a kindergarten girl, had a toy pink
gun. It was a Hello Kitty toy pink gun that blew bubbles out of the gun when you pulled
the trigger. It's a toy gun for a kindergarten child. She joked with her classmates that
she was going to shoot them with her toy pink bubble gun. And of course, the teacher later
finds out in this school in Florida, the five year old girl is interrogated without her
mother being present for three hours by school officials over a Hello Kitty pink toy bubble
gun. And it gets worse. The girl told her mother that school officials actually threatened
her with jail time. This is a five year old girl, jail time for making jokes about shooting
people with a pink bubble gun. And she was actually suspended. This five year old child
was suspended from kindergarten. And get this, school officials as well in this story said
that she was making terroristic threats, terroristic threats with the toy pink bubble gun, the
Hello Kitty gun. So I mean, this again, just heaps on top of the craziness in the aftermath
of Sandy Hook. Is it really any wonder that the number of home school kids in America
has swelled by over a million kids in the last decade when we continue to hear stories
like this? I mean, you know, talk about the United States of hysteria. This is a five
year old girl interrogated for three hours, accused of making terroristic threats, threatened
with jail and suspended for a Hello Kitty toy bubble gun. The new year is a great time
to take charge of your health and well, get serious and make a stand with supernatural
silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural silver can be taken orally every day to help
fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds. Supernatural silver is also exceptional
for wound care and is highly effective for water purification. It is the number one choice
for thousands of people for immune system support. And it is also a perfect choice for
your emergency preparedness. Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones
a fighting chance. That's supernaturalsilver.com. Check out our new low prices and like us on
Facebook. Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct. Now
that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health. At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver-based products. Our most popular silver-based products are
the 32-ounce nano silver solutions, our 2-ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well as
our all-natural silver soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver
gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver
at the surface. But rather, we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the
silver more effectively. Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver-based
products are best for you. That's www.silverlungs.com. We are on the march. The empire is on the
run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network. We're back on the Alex Jones Show. Coming
up we've got the fact that James Tracy just talked about the Sandy Hook controversy. But
now we're joined on the line by Alex Jones with an emergency alert for gun owners. Alex,
welcome to the show. That's right. I've taken a day off to take my son camping and I got
up this morning and began reading the articles at infoawards.com and I had to call in here
to point out that even infoawards.com and even myself and my great researchers, we tend
to under or downplay the full magnitude of this. What's happening is so tyrannical and
so sensational in how over the top it is. The globalists have a good chance of actually
getting most of our guns if we don't completely wake up. What am I talking about? There are
two key articles right now on infoawards.com. What about Big Sis to use the see something
say something? Homeland Security spy grid on gun owners. The other, and I saw other
articles yesterday about police drills federally funded to take on disgruntled veterans and
gun owners. Now regular listeners know this is nothing new. The New York Times four years
ago, three years ago, scouts trained to take on terrorists and more. They trained to take
guns and kill veterans. The Homeland Security documents say returning veterans are the number
one enemy. Gun owners, conservatives, libertarians, constitutionalists, bonballs in the fetters.
We've known this was behind the scenes in the documents for at least the last four years.
It was going on before that, but it accelerated under Obama. Now I've had a chance yesterday
and last time this morning to read the executive orders to really drill into it and it confirms
everything they tried to push before all at once, hitting us from over a hundred angles.
33 executive orders, a bunch of legislation, a bunch of other actions. They are creating,
well they've created the giant Stasi spy force in the name of fighting Al Qaeda. Now they
say, don't worry about Al Qaeda. They're actually good guys. Our government's using them in
Libya and Syria. That's in the news and they're flipping the whole thing. Now people remember
articles we wrote years ago saying why Al Qaeda will be announced because we got the
new training manuals and we saw the new training videos where every terrorist is a white person
being, quote, reported by a minority. And now the initial scripts are out on four new
TV shows, Founding Fathers and others, where it's all white, racist with guns and minorities
taking them down. So it's a government organized attempt to push a kind of race war type deal
where it's the minorities in the government teamed up against, quote, whites. And that's
why you see them on Fox Sports saying all gun owners are racist Klan members. That's
why you see Bob Schaefer on CBS saying we've got to have a World War II operation against
gun owners like they're Hitler. Folks, you heard the clip. That's why you're hearing
that we murdered the children in Sandy Hook. This is a purge of libertarians and conservatives.
I'm not saying this for effect. The evidence is incontrovertible. It is an over the top
situation. They are definitely going to stage false flags and come after us. I already knew
this was happening last year when four TV shows were in development all green lighted
down to start airing this year where gun owners are racist murderers. So they're now going
to say gun owning is a white thing. And people say, well, that doesn't make any sense. They
don't care. This is how communists have taken down other countries. And the banks are using
the communist playbook. It doesn't mean they're communists. They use communism at the grassroots
with fascism on top of it. So I saw Steve Watson's article. I saw Kurt Nemo's article.
I saw him. And they're good articles, but they don't explain. Folks, it's now happening.
Everything we warned about. Everything we talked about. Now it's not going to be the
TSA is going to be on the highways to stop Al-Qaeda. It's now going to be, and it's
already started, gun checkpoints. It's going to be harassment of gun owners. It's going
to be saying we're mentally ill. They're already doing this. They already now have new gun
questionnaires coming out at the state levels that say, are you a conspiracy theorist? Do
you believe in a new world order? You can't have a gun. And if conservatives get into
this and go, well, I better just shut up or it'll take my guns, now they have the chilling
effect. This is what authoritarians have always done. Notice the world government's not denied
now. It's admitted. And they're saying you're a terrorist if you don't accept it. The mainstream
media, the government, all of it is an occupying force. We still have talk radio. We still
have a lot of the states. People are fighting back. But Paul, it is so over the top. So
over the top. And I'm standing on top of Mesa. I hope I'm coming through to you clearly.
I'm up here hiking. Can you hear me, Paul? Yeah. Loud and clear. Okay, good. I climbed
on top of a mountain, literally a small mountain. It's like a pretty good cell range. There's
no cell out here where I'm going to have to hike in with my family. So this is what it
comes down to, ladies and gentlemen, is that we are in deep, deep, deep, deep, deep emergency
trouble. Everything we've talked about is coming true. I'm not happy about that. I'm
not happy now that people all over the country are saying Alex Jones is the leader of the
resistance, Alex Jones, this and that. But I am happy that we at least got the word out
beforehand until we got a chance to beat these people. But I'm not happy it got this far.
This is not fun. This is real, folks. This is real. And a mainline conservative talk
show host won't realize how much trouble we're in and get hardcore now. It's over. Notice
they preconditioned us before all this happened. There's no world government. Nobody wants
your guns. The Federal Reserve isn't private. None of this is going to happen. There won't
be any carbon taxes. And now they're just doing it all. It is now all happening in mass.
I'm going to let you get back to the broadcast. The good news is, as you pointed out, there's
more than 30 million views, 10 million on one video alone on YouTube, about Sandy Hook
hoaxes. I haven't even gotten into the hoax. I think it smells to high heaven. I don't
know how deep it goes. I know they staged the Batman thing. Even Larry Pratt says it
has evidence of that. We know they staged Fast and Furious. They could stage anything.
Put nothing past them. But the fact that, and that's conservative when I say 30 million
views, one video's got like 11 million, one's got 10 million. I mean, in fact, the only
time I lie is I underestimate because I don't want to say the truth. There's like 100 million
views from what I've seen. Okay, I said 30, that was wrong. Okay, it's like 100 million
views of people saying they don't buy Sandy Hook. The media is panicking. No one believes
them anymore. That's why they're moving. They're not trying to take over because they're strong.
They're trying to take over because they are weak. They're trying to take over because
they know the people are waking up. So black, white, Hispanic, old, young, north, south,
east, west, we have been taken over. Obama got the taxes raised on poor people. Obama
promised not to come after the guns. Obama promised all this stuff. The Republicans are
going to go along with total open borders to gut the country. Everything's about to
happen this year. That's why they're trying to mobilize their minions and dumb down soccer
moms to go after our guns. We have to get back in their face and say, how dare you compare
gun owners to Nazi Germany and the government has to have a war against them. How dare you
call us Klan? How dare you say we're criminals? How dare you say we killed those kids? How
dare you try to put that guilt on us? They are branding us. Here's the key. I'm going
to get off. We are being branded as the terrorists right now. We are being branded. We are being
branded. The secret program that I discovered years ago that we forced out to go public
from our law enforcement sources that are patriots is now going public. They are going
ahead with saying gun owners and conservatives are terrorists and that we're not going to
be able to own guns. This is a Soviet-style purge like the Reds did to the White Russians
in 1917. Ladies and gentlemen, they are declaring a concerted homeland security program of harassment
and intimidation against gun owners. Obama must be impeached now. He is an absolute criminal
and you must call every member of Congress and let them know that you're fully aware
of what's happening because they know they've all committed crimes and insider trading.
They know that they're bringing the country down. They know they're imploding the derivatives.
They know they brought in the new world order. They know they've done all of this and so
they want to lock us up the opposition to their criminal activities. They want to say
that real Americans know what's happening are terrorists. This is so outrageous. We
have to use their leap, their power grab to boomerang back on them. They are going for
everything right now. They have overreached. But if we don't respond, they are going to
win. I'm telling you folks, they're going to come and arrest you. They're going to take
your property. Even if you've never fought for liberty and you've got property or a business
owner, they're going to take everything you've got. They want a hot, quick takeover of America.
Look how much has happened. The Obamacare, the bankruptcy, the NAFTA, the gap, the Chinese
owning our debt, the Chinese government saying they want our guns turned in a month ago,
the UN treaty, the UN running our military. You ain't seen nothing, nothing, nothing yet.
We are being declared terrorists on television right now. They are saying gun owners are
the Nazis like of World War II and the government can take us out. This is outrageous. They
are now branding us as terrorists worldwide. We are being branded to be hunted down and
arrested. Paul Watson, the magnitude of this is literally off the charts. What do you say?
Well, it's downright creepy, isn't it? Because everybody's been asking, well, if they get
the assault weapons ban through, how are they going to enforce it? How are they going to
confiscate these weapons? And big sis, DHS has announced that they're going to help expand
and prioritize the see something, say something campaign with the express purpose of aiding
Obama's gun control. So what does that mean? It was always set up for that. I'm going to
get off and let you continue with the article. We need to repost Kurt Nemo's article where
the bill is introduced where they make you turn your guns in and then you get a tax credit
for it on your taxes. Folks, it's happening. She's announcing that we're the terrorists.
In the training videos, every single person is white. I mean, folks, it is on. All you
guys that said give our liberties up because of Al Qaeda, you have been fooled. Just like
the Obama suckers that thought he was going to cut their taxes. Paul, go over all the
articles. Everybody, get them at infoawards.com, prisonplanet.com, get them out to everybody.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is it. And they are going to butcher everything else. They're
going to take the pension funds. They're going to gut everything. Paul Watson, big show coming
up today with you and Mike Adams is going to sit in for half the show coming up. God
bless you all. Ladies and gentlemen, this is it. Toe to toe with the new world order.
God bless you. There goes Alex Jones. And I mean, this is
an agency of the DHS. Let's not forget that put out a report last year, funded a report
that said Americans quote, reverential of liberty and Americans suspicious of centralized
authority were basically terrorists. They lumped them in with a bunch of hate groups,
racist clan members and terrorist organizations and said that Americans who held those viewpoints
were in the same league. I mean, this is an agency that's put out PSAs for the past three
or four years, whereas Alex said every terrorist portrayed as white middle class American.
That's who they're targeting. And we'll be back after the break with Professor James
Tracy. Stay tuned. Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how
did we ever survive from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer
drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out
to those that have lost everything at e foods direct. We hear from customers every day that
are fortunate enough to weather life storm by having a supply of food on hand after Hurricane
Sandy. Danny from New York City wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed
to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better
to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't
feed you. Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to
efoods direct.com slash Alex and build your food supply. It's the best tasting non GMO
long term storeable food on the planet. Call 800-409-5633 or efoods direct.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e foods direct. Weekend by GMO stressed out about money and blasted
by the electric environment. Hi, I'm Pastor Jenny and that was the state I was in back
in 2010. Then I learned about RNA drops. I learned that 97% of my DNA that scientists
have called junk is actually packed with millions of gene switches that play a critical role
in controlling how my cells, organs and other tissues behave. I learned I don't have to
put up with disease decay or decline like I've been conditioned to believe. I began
taking RNA drops, a 100% natural formula designed to turn on those switches and provide me with
amazing health and joy. Learn more about RNA drops and order a free sample today. Visit
RNAfreesample.com. That's RNAfreesample.com or call toll free 888-577-3703. Pay only
shipping and handling for a free 30 day supply of RNA drops. Get the information you need
and the health you want at RNAfreesample.com. hempusa.org has a newly designed website and
a new and improved detoxification product. Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded
with vitamins, minerals, iodine and probiotics and we'll send you our travel sized micro
plant powder absolutely free. Micro plant powder only at hempusa.org. Call 908-691-2608.
That's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder, seeds and oil can do for you. Only at hempusa.org.
Only this offer ends January 31st. Hi, this is Ted Anderson. Have you ever wondered why
banks, stock workers, investment advisors want to talk about gold IRAs? They've been
available since 1986 yet the financial industry won't recognize the value of gold for your
retirement. Gold is outperformed paper investments yet no word about IRAs. If you would like
to have gold for your retirement call 800-686-2237. Don't get left behind by rising inflation
and low returns call 800-686-2237. Secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237. It's
time for a home security quiz. Answer this. What effective home security device is smaller
than a coffee cup, fakes out burglars into thinking someone is home at your house while
you're away, plugs into any wall outlet, is recommended by many police departments and
sells for less than $35? Yes, it's fake TV. This year about one in every 50 US homes will
have a break in with burglars usually picking the easy target, a dark house that looks like
no one is home. Fake TV is a small electronic security device that makes it look like someone
is home watching TV by simulating the light from a real TV. It's like a lamp on a timer
but far more convincing. And for only $34.95, fake TV could be the difference between coming
home to a secure house or one that's been ransacked. Go to faketv.com or call 1-877-5FAKETV.
That's 877-532-5388 or go to faketv.com. Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
Back on the Alex Jones Show, Paul Joseph Watson filling in for Alex Jones, Mike Adams coming
up in the second half of the show. Top story on Drudge Report right now. TSA to remove
controversial X-ray scanners. This is out of the Associated Press. Transportation Security
Administration confirms that it is getting rid of airport body scanners that produce
a naked image of travelers. So that's kind of a partial victory. Of course, they're still
going to use the ones that quote unzip your DNA but apparently now completely phasing
out the X-ray body scanners, of course, as a result of numerous controversies over the
past several years, led in no small part by drudgereport.com and infowars.com. So that
is a victory on that front. Of course, before the break, you heard Alex. He was talking
about this new report out of Portsmouth, Ohio, which is up on infowars.com. Drill characterizes
disgruntled Second Amendment advocates as terrorists. Basically, they had a safety security
exercise involving the police, National Guard and local emergency responders there in Portsmouth,
Ohio. And the terrorists in this drill were portrayed as quote, two school employees who
are disgruntled over the government's interpretation of the Second Amendment. And in this scenario,
they had these pro-gun rights people building weapons of mass destruction, killing teachers
and using biological agents against the local community. So they're basically going full
lockstep now demonizing Second Amendment advocates amidst this national debate on gun control.
So that story is up right now at infowars.com. I'm delighted to be joined now by Professor
James Tracy, Ph.D. from Florida Atlantic University. He's a tenured communications professor and
he also teaches a class entitled Culture of Conspiracy. He's also involved with Project
Censored and his website is memorywholeblog.com. Professor, welcome to the show.
It's great to be here Paul. Thank you. Now, before we get into Sandy Hook, obviously
we're going to go in detail on that. I want to talk about basically the onslaught you've
received over the past week by the mainstream media and particularly CNN. As I mentioned
earlier, Anderson Cooper literally devoted half of his show last week to attacking Professor
Tracy. And then he had another ten minute segment just a couple of days ago doing the
same thing. Basically, as far as I saw it, he was trying to get Professor Tracy fired
from his position there at the university. So, Professor, CNN could have easily just
ignored all this. Why do you think they've attacked you so vigorously for asking questions
about Sandy Hook? I think basically to bring me into the news
frame and to personalize this between myself and the families of Newtown, it has nothing
to do with that. I was bringing up questions that were not raised, that were not addressed
by the media. Anderson Cooper is someone who says he's keeping them honest. Well, who's
he keeping honest? The poor parents about their grief, or is he keeping people honest,
the authorities and so forth there, that have dropped the ball with regard to the investigation
or perhaps even covered something up. They contacted me last Friday. I was frankly somewhat
exhausted from the entire week after the story went viral. Drudge picked it up on Tuesday.
And I spoke with my family members and my wife, and she didn't really want me to go
on the show. And so I declined from doing so, and they were very persistent. They in
fact actually sent their reporter out here who went to my place of employment, then filmed
out in my front lawn pretty much. I was not even aware of that, but he did call and say
that he was around the corner. He was a couple blocks away, I guess, wanted me to come out.
And I said, look, I'm really not into it. I'm tired. I will consider it in the future.
I will provide a statement to you. I provided an email statement. It took me an hour or
so to compose. They used a snippet of it or two on the air, and that was it. But other
than that, it was really an attack. I was really rather taken aback by the extent of
it. They contacted me again earlier this week, and on Monday I said, well, I will consider
it on Tuesday. They said, well, it's time. Do you want to go ahead and do it? And they
wanted to get me down to the studio right away. And I said, I've got to teach this evening.
I really don't have the time, but I will consider doing it. I've contacted them again and they've
not responded. So you're perfectly willing to go on there. You've contacted them and
now they've basically stopped talking to you. Is that the case? That's the case. Yes. So
maybe, you know, maybe they've dropped the story. I mean, to my, I watched the clip,
the 20 minute thing where Cooper's demonizing you. And it seems obviously he's using, you
know, you're insulting the victims as his platform for what he's saying. But he also
seemed just as annoyed about the fact that you were questioning whether or not the mainstream
media did its job in the first days after the event. So we'll go more into that. We'll
talk about Sandy Hook after the break. Stay tuned. This is The Alex Jones Show. We'll
be right back. Infowars.com. We're on the march. The empire's on the run. Alex Jones
and the GCN radio network.
Fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%. Easy to set up and use. Doesn't require
electricity. Purify water from lakes, streams, ponds and wells. This filter system leaves
in beneficial minerals which is key. Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid
BPA that leaches from the plastic. Propure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses. Infowars.com already has the lowest price on Propure, but if you
add the promo code WATER at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at Infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help
fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds. Supernatural Silver is also exceptional
for wound care and is highly effective for water purification. It is the number one choice for
thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency
preparedness. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones
a fighting chance. That's SupernaturalSilver.com. Check out our new low prices and like us on
Facebook. You prepare by purchasing gold, food and firearms. But if you don't have a home security
system, then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection. When you're
sleeping or away from home, who's watching out for intruders? Check out SimpliSafe. It's a new
do-it-yourself home security system that is completely wireless. Go to GetSimplySafe.com.
SimpliSafe is independent and off the grid. It runs on battery power, so even if the grid goes
down, you're protected. It's completely customizable, so you can use it in your home,
business, boat, trailer, storage unit or shed. GetSimplySafe.com. SimpliSafe is also ridiculously
easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes, so there's no need to let a stranger into your home.
If you move or need to relocate, you can take the system with you wherever you go.
You aren't always at home, but SimpliSafe will stand guard, protecting your property 24 hours a
day, 7 days a week. Again, that's GetSimplySafe.com. Rallying patriots worldwide in defense of human
liberty. It's Alex Jones. It's Paul Joseph Watson in for Alex Jones. We're talking to Professor
James Tracy about the Sandy Hook massacre. He's a professor who's caused no end of controversy over
the past week because he's been heavily demonized by the likes of CNN and Fox News. There's a video
on YouTube which came to my attention about a week ago. It's only been posted for about
10, 11 days. It's called the Sandy Hook shooting fully exposed. 10.6 million plus people have
watched this video in the space of the last 10, 11 days alone. That shows you how voracious the
interest is in this whole Sandy Hook issue. And I mean, I'm coming at it from a perspective of
there are lots of unanswered questions. I don't buy into the notion that this never happened or
that the parents, the family members involved were actors in some sense, which some people
have claimed. I think it was a real tragedy. It really happened. But there are plenty of
unanswered questions that go along with it that suggest more people than the accused shooter,
Adam Lanza, may have been involved. So we're going to get into that now with Professor James Tracy.
So Professor, you know, the Obama administration has built its entire gun control move on the
notion that Adam Lanza shot these children with an AR-15 assault rifle. They're trying to ban
the assault rifles now. Given that, wouldn't it be the perfect poster child to actually have
even a still image from a surveillance camera of Adam Lanza with this AR-15 assault rifle
when in reality we've seen nothing, no surveillance footage, no still images of the
shooter when in past, you know, mass shootings, school shootings, images of the shooter,
thinking about Columbine, Virginia Tech, have emerged within days. But of Adam Lanza,
we've seen absolutely nothing. Is that one of the questions that you've been talking about?
It's a central question, Paul. The Sandy Hook School District installed a new security system
in September. Now, this is a very affluent community and they would not have cut corners
in terms of video surveillance and the ability to be able to store that video that's taken.
So there's a glaring problem here with regard to what is actually going on. Where is that
video footage? I think we can safely conclude that there was video footage captured, but where is it
now? One scenario is that the one individual or team of individuals went in and went to the
main office and may have turned off the video surveillance. But we've not heard from the
officials whether or not that is in fact the case. If it was Adam Lanza, would he have had
the foresight and sophistication to be able to pull something like that off? If it was a crew,
you know, a team of shooters, that may have in fact been the case. That's the only thing that
I've heard about possibly explaining why there might not be video surveillance other than just
holding back on it and attempting to, for example, doctor it. That's something I believe that Mike
Adams had a piece a couple of days ago about where is the surveillance footage. It's a very
big question because if they want to put a lot of our queries to rest, they could release that.
We could see Lanza committing the crimes and that would be the end of it. Another thing that might
point to is that handguns were used because those were what the initial reports stated. In fact,
NBC News confirmed the reports from state and federal officials that there were four
handguns used. This was on the morning of December 15th, Pete Williams on the NBC Today show.
That was changed on the afternoon of December 15th by the Connecticut medical examiner H.
Wayne Carver to being the AR-15, solely the AR-15 that was used. That was at the press conference
at about 3.30, I believe 3.15, 3.30 p.m. on December 15th. And we had reports that the actual
assault rifle was left in the vehicle, but then the video showed the police removing what looked
like a shotgun out of the trunk of the vehicle. So do we know, have we pinned down exactly what's
going on with the specific weapons that were used or is that still contradictory?
I think that it's still contradictory. The footage looks as if it was a shotgun,
but altogether there were, I believe there were at least six weapons or seven weapons,
if you include at one point or another that somehow materialize on the scene and then disappear.
There are the four pistols, there's the AR-15, and then there are two Enfield rifles that are
referenced at one point or another in the reportage. So we've got a total of, I believe,
at least seven weapons that are mentioned, that are pointed to by officials in journalistic
reports and then somehow disappear. And then we are down to the one weapon, the AR-15,
which we might at the very least surmise that this is what was one of the things, one of the
weapons that looks the most dangerous and the one that might be targeted in legislation and
executive orders. Now we've got these reports of two men in the woods, obviously we've all seen
all seen the footage of them being apprehended in the woods. One has been explained as a parent who
went to the school to help his son bake, I think it was gingerbread men or something,
that's kind of been explained. He said he heard the gunshots, he was petrified, he ran away.
There was another report of a separate man in the woods though, and it emerged in a Newtown B
report, quote, a man with a gun who was spotted in the woods. So this is a guy with a gun around
a school massacre. A man with a gun who was spotted in the woods near the school on the day
of the incident was an off-duty tactical squad police officer from another town. So why is a
guy who's a police officer from another town in the woods outside where a massacre's taking place
with a gun? I mean, is that a place where people would go hunting right next to a school?
So Professor, just tell us about the reports of additional individuals that may have been involved
in this event. Well, the footage, the aerial footage that is taken by the Associated Press
shows at least one figure fleeing the scene being pursued by police officers. So if there was
someone up in the woods, they must have come back down and then been chased back up into the woods.
At one point, about a week or so ago, J. Paul Vance, the Connecticut State Police Lieutenant,
said that the individual up in the woods was just chopping wood, just happened to be there
chopping wood. Well, maybe they came down to the school and got a drink of water or something and
then went back up there. That footage also shows, you can see someone in the upper left-hand portion
of the video footage, someone who emerges behind a tree. And they remain unaccounted for, so
apparently they escaped. But of course, as you know, there's also the CBS footage of a bystander
who remarks that this individual was paraded by them and said to them, the onlookers, that
I didn't do it. And then they took the individual and put them in the front seats of the patrol car.
I'm very skeptical of accepting the Newtown B as a valid source for information after
the really contradictory reports initially from December 14th. First of all, quoting the principal,
Dawn Hawksprung, and then retracting that and never saying who actually was that they spoke to.
So I'm really very suspicious of that particular medium. And then apparently the individual that
was spotted in the parking lot was a parent. That as well, I've not really seen anything that would
confirm that. I know that that is out there, but this was an individual that was spotted by a
student who was being interviewed, who had experienced the evacuation of the building.
And I believe that would have been the alleged parent that somehow fled onto the scene
all of a sudden. There are also questions with regard to the alleged photograph of the evacuation
of the 15 or 16 students that were being evacuated that really did make the national
and international news. That was supposedly taken by one of the Newtown B associate editors
as she came onto the scene in the back of the first responders. And she said that she was
taking photographs left and right, and yet only two photographs emerged from that series of photos.
So there's this conflicting information as well with regard to the additional suspects on the
scene, but we've not really been given any conclusive evidence as far as I'm concerned,
really, as to who they were and what they were doing there and whether or not they may have been
accessories in the crime. Yeah, there are a lot of questions about the lack of children, the lack
of parents, the lack of teachers being seen in the actual surrounding area after the massacres
happened. Of course, the school was on lockdown for a time, but then everybody was evacuated.
I was thinking maybe that's only because the mass media showed up quite a while later after
everybody had already been evacuated. That may have been the case. If you note the school shooting
at Union, excuse me, Taft Union High School out by Bakersfield, there was media on the scene
there, and that's a school comparable in student body to the Newtown, to Sandy Hook. There are
about 850, 900 students there, and there's a very evident evacuation taking place there where the
sidewalks are flooded with students. But we see none of that in Newtown, and where the students
would have converged over at the fire hall, the fire station, there's a limited degree of activity
there as well. So some of these things also made me suspicious. Exactly what is going on here?
Is this an event that is in some way, shape, or form being embellished? Because I think that
something took place there as well, but I'm wondering as to what degree it may be somewhat
fortified, if you will. And also, there were these bizarre reports of people dressed as nuns
fleeing the scene in a purple van, and then we've got this photograph of these black veils being
found near the scene on the ground. Did you hear about that report? Well, yeah, I believe in fact
that it was someone who was calling the Alex Jones show on the morning of the incident that reported
this initially, and that's the first time that it emerged really on the news. And there was also an
article on the intel hub that delves into this to some degree. In fact, I believe there was a
photograph taken of these individuals, and they're wearing footwear similar to what police officers
would wear. Yeah, I actually saw that photo earlier today. It's definitely bizarre. But I mean,
the problem we've got is amidst all these legitimate questions about the narrative, what
happened, who was involved, there's a plethora of claims that are obviously either completely
baseless or are woefully reductionist. And I think the whole thing about Emily Parker supposedly
not being killed and then being included in that photo with Obama is clearly one of them, because
if you look at the high res images, you can quite clearly prove that it is in fact her sister, who
obviously wasn't one of the victims. So I mean, what do you say to the idea that, you know, some
people are really making huge leaps of logic, and in doing so, are detracting from any real
understanding of what happened? Because I've seen some really just crazy things like, you know,
Robbie Parker, one of the parents is actually Tony Hawk, the skateboard guy. So it's good. There's a
lot of people poisoning the well with bizarre craziness. And it's really not helping us
understand what actually happened, is it? Well, I've seen a lot of activity on my blog as well,
the comments and things of the like. And I, I think that there is definitely a lot of
information. There is definitely a program to sow misinformation in the stream of information in
order to muddy the waters. And in the process, discredit the research, really the research that
independent researchers and the like are putting together and alternative media. Because if you
can discredit it or muddy the waters to a limited degree in one area, you can paint with a fairly
broad brush, the mainstream corporate media can do that. So I, you know, I'm not very surprised if
if things like that are being are being spread. I'm also somewhat suspicious of the, you know,
some of the web pages, or some of, for example, a Facebook page that is created a few days ahead of
time. These are very curious, curious phenomena. I know less about the phase of the mechanics of
Facebook, and the extent to which dates can be changed to really draw any conclusions with with
regard with regard to that. And it's somewhat one has to be careful as well.
Well, I mean, that is interesting. But for me, it's not proof of anything, because you can create
a Facebook page, and then rename it to something else. So the original timestamp on the Facebook
page will say, you know, for example, December 10. And then you rename it to something else later
on. Also, obviously, I work in, you know, web publishing, and you can change your timestamp
as easy as anything. So I mean, that for me, that's, you know, it's quite bizarre, like a lot
of the other stuff, but it's not really proof of anything. We're going to get back into the details
shortly. I just want to get your take on this. Luis Tambasquio, who was a family friend of the
Lanzas, told 60 Minutes, quote, I know he was on medication. Professor, why over a month later,
do we not know anything about what psychiatric drugs Adam Lanza was on?
I think that this is a very valid question that journalists such as John Rappaport have asserted.
Why is it that we don't know what his physician's name is? If he was, in fact, under psychiatric
care, or the equivalent, and what types of drugs he may have been on. There's a drug that I've
never heard of called, I believe, Tamaft, that he was supposedly on. But again, there's a limited
amount of information that's been disclosed by authorities or otherwise.
There was actually, talking about disinformation, there was an individual who claimed to be Lanza's
uncle, who was circulating around the media a few weeks ago now. And he actually put out the name
of the drug that Lanza was supposedly on. Bunch of publications ran with it, including New York
Magazine, I think. And it was complete, this info is completely made up. So again, another example
of how people are poisoning the well to distract people from understanding what actually happened.
But of course, it took nearly six months to get confirmation that James Holmes was on psychiatric
drugs. But we still don't know exactly which ones. So again, as you said, I mean, these SSRIs are
the elephant in the living room, aren't they? Because while the media will talk about video
games and things like that, they won't address the psychiatric drugs that are prevalent amongst
almost all of these mass shooters throughout the last 20 years. Well, actually, Sanjay Gupta did
a piece on CNN. We'll talk about it after the break, got to leave it left now. We'll be back, stay tuned.
Now here's the best part. Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell
as new. We put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at the
end of each year. We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new. Each unit
comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe. Don't wait,
they go fast. Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com. For the craziest
offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
Is this the year you finally get serious about your family's drinking water? If so,
keep listening for a special offer from Big Berkey Water Filters. Did you know that over 60% of
municipal water is fluoridated? Berkey Water Filters distinguish themselves from many other
filtration systems with the capability to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine, fluoride,
arsenic, and disinfection byproducts from municipal water via the Black Berkey and PF line of filters.
Then there's affordability. At only 1.7 cents per gallon, Berkey Water Filters purify treated and
untreated water, even stagnant pond water. Stop and think how much money you could save by simply
reducing buying bottled water and using water filtered by your Berkey Water Filter. No need
to be constantly replacing expensive filters with a Berkey. A single set of filters can last
for five to 10 years. Choose the best size Berkey for your needs at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com. And
right now, all GCN listeners get 5% off all ceramic filter systems. Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY,
that's 877-99-BERKEY, or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
Free shipping on every order over $50. Big Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean water.
Time and time again. You need to come here and help us. We need assistance, please. Those we
should be able to depend on, let us down. Federal and state and local officials saying help is on
the way. Well, the folks here in Bell Harbor say show me. Don't depend on the government to save
you. Take action now so that you're prepared for the next disaster with MyPatriotSupply.com. Get
the best prices on storable food, non-GMO seeds, water filtration devices, home canning equipment,
survival and self-reliance books, and more at MyPatriotSupply.com. Call 866-229-0927.
We are hurting down here and we need help immediately. Before it's time to survive,
it's time to prepare. MyPatriotSupply.com. MyPatriotSupply.com. It's Paul Joseph Watson back on the Alex Jones show, filling in for Alex.
Mike Adams will be here in the second half of the show to take you to the end of the broadcast,
but right now we're talking to Professor James Tracy of Florida Atlantic University.
He's controversially questioned the official narrative behind the Sandy Hook school shooting,
and he's been demonized and attacked by the likes of CNN and Fox News for doing so.
I'm going to say your calls for the professor coming up shortly at 800-259-9231. That's 800-259-9231.
We were talking about some of the disinformation that gets mixed into all these questions,
which kind of poisons the well. And obviously, I believe that this was a horrible tragedy for
all the parents involved. And I believe that some of the people who are asking questions about this,
not the professor, but a lot of people on YouTube have handled it in a rather insensitive way.
Of course, we've had reports about them harassing some of the people who were involved.
And basically, it doesn't do us any favors. So we need to treat it, obviously, with extreme caution
because it's a very traumatic event. And I think one of the aspects of this, which a lot of people
have claimed, professor, is this whole idea that there were, quote, crisis actors who were working
with the media to create a fake narrative surrounding this event. And this is where we
probably differ. But just give us your take on the whole crisis actors angle. Explain what that is.
The crisis actors is a group based out of Denver, Colorado, I believe. And they work in association
with the Department of Homeland Security on active shooter drills. So they are involved
in playing the roles of bystanders, of perhaps the shooter himself, the victims in some cases,
the individuals involved posting things to social media. In other words, they are all encompassing
in creating an environment for a lifelike drill. Now, there was a drill that took place,
by the way, along these lines. Now, I don't know if crisis actors were involved, but this was in a
school for disabled children in Harlem. And the children were absolutely terrified. So in some
cases, it's not known whether or not an event is actually taking place, but it's made more lifelike
by the crisis actors. Again, I don't know if they were involved in that particular drill. And that's
an incident that's sort of foamed beyond the mainstream media radar. But these individuals,
they're deployed within the community and they go ahead and they embellish the particular event. So
if this were a drill that somehow went live, as we know that, for example, 9-11 and the 7705
bombings were, then it would have involved actors along these lines and they would not even know
whether or not the drill itself went live. One of the things that made me question in this regard
was looking at the video footage as well as the photographic evidence emerging from the scene.
And as you had alluded to earlier, there were just, you know, there were few bystanders and
the like. There were very few people actually being interviewed when you would think there
would be a great many people on the scene. Now, maybe what you say is correct. Maybe the media
got there late and there was no photographic or video evidence along those lines. There were just
a few people that they could actually interview. But that's one of the reasons that I actually
put that forward. The possibility of there being crisis actors. And I think it's probably been the
most controversial. Okay, we'll be back after the break. Stay there. Your calls for Professor
Tracy coming up. It's the Alex Jones Show. Stay tuned.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
We'll be back after the break.
Virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com
today and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off. That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on
Facebook. Waging war on corruption. Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
It's Paul Joseph Watson filling in for Alex Jones today. We're talking to Professor James
Tracy of Florida Atlantic University. He's questioned the official narrative behind the
Sandy Hook School massacre and basically being pursued by CNN as a result of it and other news
organizations. We're going to go to your calls shortly. The number is 800-259-9231. That's 800-259-9231.
Before the break, we were talking about the idea that some of these individuals involved in this
event may have been actors or participants in a drill. Of course, we know that drills
shadow both 9-11 and 7-7. And you have to frame all this while being sensitive to the
fact that it was, according to my mind, a very real tragedy involving very real victims. But
you have to frame it in the context that under Fast and Furious, the Obama administration
sent 2,000 assault weapons to drug lords in Mexico, resulting in the deaths of over 300
people, many of them children. So to claim that this would be beyond the government to
stoop to such a level to kill 20 kids to ram through their political agenda is somewhat
naive, given what we've seen historically with the likes of Operation Gladio and other false flag
terror programs, which are on the record all admitted. They've been subject to parliamentary
investigations in countries like Italy, admitted that government stage mass shootings, they stage
bombings, they bomb trains for their own political agenda. So asking questions about an event that
has been the fulcrum of the Obama administration's agenda on gun control is only sensible while,
of course, maintaining that respect, that dignity, that sensitivity for the victims.
But what sprung to my mind before the break is, professor, straight after the collapse
of the Twin Towers on 9-11, we had people on the ground who seemed to know, bizarrely,
intricate details of how that collapsed happened, which just happened to then morph almost
immediately into the official story. So I guess that's what you're talking about when you're
talking about acts as being involved. You're not saying there were no victims. You're just
saying that people may have been there to massage the narrative. Is that correct?
Yes, that's correct, Paul. I am simply posing questions, and I never said anything
declarative in any of my articles about this happened. I was saying, could this be a
possibility? And yet the media took that and ran with it, took my assertion as an allegation when
it was merely a question. And that, unfortunately, is how this has been framed and how I think
that it's been offensive, especially to the people that lost their loved ones up there in
Newtown. I never actually intended that in any way, shape, or form. But certainly, yes,
what you point out with regard to 9-11 is really right on, in that this idea that a
steel-frame building could collapse as a result of the heat from the airplanes, I think, is
something that was put out there at the time to sort of deflect any questioning as to how could
this have actually taken place, these buildings going down in such a way, in their own footprint.
Just got a minute to go to the break. We're going to go to your call, the first of which is
Adam. We'll go to him after the break. Other aspects that I want to get into, obviously,
we've got things about Adam Lanza's car, a picture with all four doors open. Why would that be the
case if he was just exiting the car on his own? As you mentioned earlier, the school principal
gives the quote to the Newtown B describing the attack, but she's actually the first victim of the
attack. That's another inconsistency that hasn't been explained. We'll go into it and more with
your calls. Professor Tracy, after the break, this is the Alex Jones show, infowars.com. Stay tuned.
We'll be right back.
No priming required. It's NSF 42 certified. Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride
up to 95%. Easy to set up and use. Doesn't require electricity. Purify water from lakes,
streams, ponds, and wells. This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic. Propure is the
best gravity fed filter out there. It's what my family uses. Infowars.com already has the lowest
price on propure, but if you add the promo code water at checkout, you get an additional 10%
off at infowars.com. You can also call to order 888-253-3139. Looking back on 2012, we ask
ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters like hurricane Sandy and the devastating
summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to
those that have lost everything. At eFoods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are
fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand. After hurricane Sandy,
Danny from New York city wrote, almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get
my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared
10 years too early than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings
and do what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today, or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex
and build your food supply. It's the best tasting non-GMO long-term storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cow
Ben Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth
friendly and safe. See them on the web at FiveStarSoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free
catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs.
This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap
makes you feel. See them on the web at FiveStarSoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover ups. You want answers? Well, so does he. He's
Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
It's Paul Joseph Watson, writer with Infowars.com, filling in for Alex today.
Got a headline up on PrisonPlanet.com. Holder begs courts to stop document release on Fast and
Furious. Basically, they're trying to stop a lawsuit brought by Judicial Watch asking them
to open records relating to Operation Fast and Furious, which, of course, was the program which
many view as a deliberate effort to undermine the Second Amendment, where the Obama administration
sent 2,000 assault weapons to drug lords in Mexico, leading to the deaths of 300 people.
If you think it's beyond the Obama administration to engage in murder to further their gun control
agenda, remembering the fact that it was Obama himself back in April 2011 who told Sarah Brady
in a White House meeting he was working, quote, under the radar to sneak attack the Second
Amendment, then we'd be very naive to think that they wouldn't engage in such activity.
We're talking to Professor James Tracy about the Sandy Hook Massacre, the questions that he's
raised about the event and subsequently being attacked by the media for asking. Adam in Canada,
you're on the air. Go ahead, Adam. Yeah, kudos for having the courage to cover this. I have a
couple questions. Go ahead. Yeah, I think it's great that he got the thing about the shotgun
in the trunk, right, and the dress with the daughter. Those are up there. But what I haven't
heard, I'd like to hear him talk about is the question of whether or not that was Adam Lanza's
car. And also if you've seen some of the rebranding of businesses in the area, if you go to
sandyhookhairco.com, Sandy Hook Hair Company, and see their whole image, their whole bloody
handprint and the white heart in the palm. And finally, of course, the whole thing about the
Batman map in the movie, the Batman movie, having Sandy Hook on it and also actually lining up to
the roads in Newton with a circle on the school, which is the stadium that's attacking the movie.
Go ahead, professor. Okay, well, there's quite a bit there. First, with regard to Adam Lanza's car,
this was apparently registered to a Chris Rodia. And yet there was an article that came out
arguing that this was not the case. I think it was in a Hearst paper that the car was not
registered to him. But in fact, it turns out that it was and that Rodia, you know,
he had a number of run-ins with the law. He had been involved apparently in drug
running and the like. So that's as much as I know with regard to the automobile.
And what were the other questions? Well, there's this crazy rebranding of businesses with
Illuminati symbology. I mean, it's totally out there, but go to sandyhookhairco.com and you'll
see their website with the bloody red handprint and the whole thing, white heart in the palm.
And then, of course, the whole Batman movie map, Sandy Hook. Go to YouTube,
Batman map, Sandy Hook, a strange comparison. You'll see this one-minute video.
I've seen that, professor, but I mean, there's a place, obviously, Gotham City is based on New
York City and there's a place in New York City called Sandy Hook. That's how I understood it.
Yeah, and that does come up, but I think one hour and 58 minutes into The Dark Knight Rises,
there's that specifically on the map, from what I understand. I haven't seen the movie in its
entirety. And somehow I saw that on my blog just recently, someone putting something in there with
regard to the hair salon or the hair company, but I've not seen the actual imagery itself.
So I can't really comment on that. Okay, thanks for the call. Yeah, I think the thing with the
car was, how I read it, it was like a bleed in the police transmission tapes, where he had been
apprehended in a completely different city and that bled through to their transmission, which
is why it got confused with Adam Lanza. That's how it was explained, whether that's true or not.
It was explained in a mainstream media outlet that he was mistaken, but whether or not that
is in fact the case is still somewhat questionable. But it's a very good question.
And the other stuff doesn't really, I mean, it's all very weird, but it doesn't prove anything for
me. Father James in California, you're on the air, go ahead. Good morning. It's good to talk
to you. I've been a listener of the show probably about a year and initially thought that Alex was
rather paranoid until I began researching everything that he was talking about and finding
so much support and information. I have family members that are educators. My father served
in special forces in Vietnam. And the kind of false flag attack is something that I've heard
about from him. In Vietnam, he said it was a common tactic for them to go into a Vietnamese
village, do attacks, leave evidence of it being North Vietnamese or Viet Cong, then come in
in subsequent days to respond to their outrage and recruit them and train them to fight against the
North Vietnamese. So it's a tactic that's been around for a long time.
And thinking about these questions, my thoughts have been that the conversation in the media,
especially as it's put out by the government, is how many lives will we save by banning guns?
And I think the question really needs to be turned around. How many lives are we going
to sacrifice if we limit or restrict guns from law-abiding citizens? And I think a very practical
way to arm our teachers, we have a lot of police chiefs and sheriffs that are standing up now
saying that they're going to defend Second Amendment rights. A very simple approach would
be for them to issue conceal and carry permits to teachers, and then to overcome the ban or
guns at school is to deputize them. Sheriffs, police chiefs can deputize citizens in service
so they can train them, license them, deputize them, and it'll be legal for those teachers
to have a firearm concealed on campus. Well, professor, would you, professor,
would you feel safer if your kids were in a school where you knew the teacher had a safely
locked away gun in the event of some crazed killer coming into the school? I mean, would
you feel safer? Well, I certainly know that individuals such as Barack Obama, his children
go to a school that is safe and secure in that regard and has armed guards. I think
that's likely the case with many of the, many of the country's elite and the, you know,
the elite of the world. They, most of their children go to, you know, go to facilities,
go to institutions that have that type of security. So why shouldn't the broader public?
And of course, Obama just signed the bill where he gets lifetime armed secret service
protection. While all the rest of you lowly peasant American citizens are disarmed, Jacob
in Illinois, you're on the air, Jacob, go ahead. Oh, hi. I've been a listener for a
couple of days now. I like the show. I was wondering what kind of gun was it again that
the kids were killed with? Like a big rifle or something? I was just wondering, how did he,
how did he get it into the school in the first place?
Professor, that's what the medical examiner addressed, isn't it? If you want to cover it
from that angle. Yeah, this came up, this is when the story was, was significantly altered
during that press conference from, as far as, as far as I can tell from the, the four handguns,
which is what was being reported at eight o'clock or eight thirty a.m. on the NBC Today show
to the single AR-15. And during that press conference, and it's important to really look
at that press conference, because I think that's really the most revealing piece of evidence and
information in this case, is that this is the weapon is almost changed immediately from the,
from the, from the pistols to the AR-15. And even a reporter says, speaks up and says,
but the, the rifle was found in the car. And at that point, the Connecticut State
Police Lieutenant Vance said, that's not correct, sir. That's not correct. So it's at that point
where, where things change. How he, now how he got the weapon into the, into the school? Well,
he, he approached the, according to the official story, he approached the entrance of the school
and he, he shot, shot out the, the front, the front door and with a hole big enough to,
to enter. Yet we've not seen any video evidence that that in fact took place,
nor has there been any video or photographic evidence of the, the door itself, the entry point
itself. Thanks for the call, Jacob. Josh in California, you're on the air with Professor
Tracy, go ahead. All right, Josh has dropped. Professor, tell us about the, this pejorative
term conspiracy theory you wanted to talk about, the dynamics between how that's being used by the
establishment media in relation to this event. Well, I think that as, as an academic, and I
think this is also the case with regard to journalists, they fear being called a, a
conspiracy theorist. That is the pejorative that's being used against me to make an example out of
me, to threaten my job, to get me to, to be quiet, to not ask questions. It's important to think
about the, the how this term originated, how actually it developed. There's an important
book called Conspiracy Theory in America that's being, that's coming out in April of this year
by a colleague of mine, Lance DeHaven Smith up at Florida State University. Now he helped to
devise the, the concept of state crimes against democracy. This is something that's wrong. We'll
be back, final segment, we'll finish that after the break. Stay tuned, Alex Jones showing. Looking
back on 2012, we asked ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters like hurricane
Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous
economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods Direct, we hear from
customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on
hand. After hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores are
closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It
is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't
feed you. Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to
eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply. It's the best tasting non-GMO long-term
storeable food on the planet. Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your
life on eFoods Direct. We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted
name in water filtration. As an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years in serving
thousands of satisfied customers, the Berkey guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water
filtration systems. The Berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable
black purification elements that purify water by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria,
cysts and parasites to non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and
pesticides. Order the Berkey light system today complete with two black Berkey elements for only
$231 and the Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge. With the purchase of a Berkey light,
the Berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride and arsenic filters for only $39.99. That's over
30% off the retail price. Call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653. That's 1-877-886-3653 or order
online at GoBerkey.com. That's GoBerkey.com today. On the average, Americans work between
45 to 50 years hoping to build up enough wealth to retire and live out their golden years.
Unfortunately, with taxation, the rising cost of food, energy, housing and medical,
many retirees are forced to live below the poverty line. Is this a flaw for the enterprise or is our
monetary unit we call the Federal Reserve Note forcing us into perpetual debt, ensuring inflation
and higher taxes? These questions and more can be answered by reading G. Edward Griffin's book,
The Creature from Jekyll Island. Congressman Ron Paul states it's what every American needs to know
about central bank power, a gripping adventure into the secret world of international banking
cartel. Hi, this is Ted Anderson. I will give a silver dollar from the early 1900s to anyone
who purchases this book. Call 1-800-686-2237 and order a copy today. It's critical that
the public be made aware of the system. Call and order your copy today at 1-800-686-2237.
That's 1-800-686-2237. Feeling like there are too many pressures and demands on you?
Losing sleep, worrying about tests and schoolwork, eating on the run because your schedule is just
too busy? You may be under too much stress and it may be affecting your mind. Get your mental
edge back with Neutropic Mind Power from mindregard.com. Neutropic Mind Power is not a
drug but a natural supplement. Its 12 powerful ingredients are natural and non-GMO plus it's
gluten-free, wheat-free, and formulated by Americans for Americans by an NSF certified
laboratory. Neutropic Mind Power is available at mindregard.com, spelled M-I-N-D-R-E-G-A-R-D.com
and comes with a 100% money back guarantee. Free your mind with Neutropic Mind Power,
cognitive supplement from mindregard.com. Mindregard, clearly see tomorrow and yesterday, today.
We're back on the Alex Jones Show, Paul Joseph Austin filling in for Alex, talking with Professor
James Tracy of Florida Atlantic University. Professor, just finish up your thought there
quickly about the term conspiracy theory. Yeah, in the mid-1960s, Paul, the US government,
the Central Intelligence Agency were concerned with regard to the, with regard to criticisms
of the Warren Report, so they issued a dispatch to all of their offices. And this dispatch right
here, it's number 1035-960, it's available at the JFK Lancer website, talks about how,
can I read a bit of this, is that okay? Yeah, we'll push for time, but yeah, quickly.
Okay, well it talks about the, how public opinion is almost 50% skeptical of the official
conclusions of the Warren Commission Report, and talks further about employing propaganda
assets to negate and refute the attacks of the critics. Talks specifically about conspiracy
theories and how to, the specific techniques that one could use in CIA asset publications and by CIA
assets themselves in the media industry to essentially subdue any sort of criticism.
And so what I'm getting at in that regard, and you could, again, go to the JFK Lancer site and
read it since we're pressed for time, but I believe it's a key document because this is
something that has, it has in many ways really created fear among journalists and among scholars
to address anything that might be considered a conspiracy theory. I think I know this more
intimately than anyone because I, you know, I can sense that fear among, among others. You can't
touch certain, certain subjects such as 9-11 because you might be accused of this, and this
is something that could, it could cost you your, your job and, or your credibility.
Okay. Todd in Florida, quickly, please. Final call. Go ahead, Todd.
Thanks for taking my call, guys. I got some points about Sandy Hook. Thanks so much for
talking about it today. I think it's something we all need to question. You mentioned at the
press conference, I feel that that is some very important information. Paul Vance dodged
blatantly a question when asked, what was Nancy Lanza's connection to the school? And I believe
that he couldn't answer that question because later it came out that she had no connection.
However, there was a report on the scene from Sally Cox, the 15 year alleged nurse at Sandy Hook,
who told a reporter that she knew Nancy Lanza and that she was an experienced kindergarten teacher.
I think we need to question those things very, very much. Are you also familiar,
are you also familiar with the fundraiser sites that the URLs were created before the event?
Yeah, we talked about that a bit earlier. I don't know if a medical examiner would,
would actually have that information. What I would expect of him as a professional is to have
information specific to the injuries, you know, the causes of death, the caliber of the bullets,
how many girls, how many boys were, were, were slain. These things are just basic and they were
not addressed by Dr. Carver, not in any competent way. And that's the, that's really the major thing
that contributes to my skepticism and caused my, you know, my, my, my initial questioning of the
event. Okay, thanks for the call, Todd. Professor, just tell people about your website, the other
work you do there, how people can find out more information. Yeah, memoryholeblog.com. I've been,
I've had the website since March. There's a lot of stuff on there, you know, primarily there's,
there are essays that, that I've written on, you know, political criticism and, and events such as
this and things that might be regarded as, as conspiracies, but attempting to analyze those
and develop those in a, in a historical context and in a more contemporary context. So it's
memoryholeblog.com. Okay, Professor James Tracy, Florida Atlantic University.
You won't be on CNN tonight then, but you may be on in the next few days.
Well, they've got to get back to me and I'm, I'm willing to, to go on and keep them honest.
Okay, we really appreciate your time. Fascinating questions raised once again,
and we hope to talk to you again soon. Thank you very much.
Thanks Paul. There goes Professor James Tracy raising
questions about the Sandy Hook massacre. And again, this has gone completely viral. It even
surprised me how crazy insane the interest in this is 10.6 million views on one video alone on
YouTube that was created just 10, 11 days ago. And in fact, we're probably going to try and get
the creators behind that video on the show. But tons of videos, tons of questions while
still trying to maintain respect, dignity for the realization that this was a very real tragedy,
but we'll continue to ask questions about it. Mike Adams coming up. This is the Alex Jones
show live. I've been Paul Joseph Watson, infowars.com. We'll be right back with Mike Adams.
Stay tuned. We're on the march. The Empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network. Alex Jones here with a message to fellow
freedom lovers. The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to
worse. The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they
acquiesce to the global takeover. That's why we've assembled the most vital and important
preparedness items at infowarsshop.com. These are items that I did research on that I personally use.
You've got the life straw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages are out in the
field. Strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen. When disaster strikes by Matthew Stein.
Thera safe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event. Hand crank
shortwave AM FM radios. Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available
at infowarshop.com and your purchase makes our info war possible. We're getting prepared. Are you
infowarsshop.com? Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds,
flu and other illnesses. Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver,
a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology
have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses,
mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough to
consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as
strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the
ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness
of colloidal or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest
germ fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
filters can reduce fluoride up to 95% easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity
purify water from lakes streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial minerals
which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid bpa that leaches from the plastic
propure is the best gravity-fed filter out there it's what my family uses infowars.com already has
the lowest price on propure but if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional
10% off at infowars.com you can also call to order 888-253-3139
from the front lines of the information ward it's alex jones
all right we're back here on the alex jones show and this is mike adams stepping in for
the next hour and a half here i want to thank paul joseph watson for his eye-opening interview
there i didn't catch all of it because i was obviously uh driving in for to be here but we've
got even more great information coming up this is just hard hitting day after day hour after hour
here's what we have coming up right now on the phone with us and he'll be joining us in just a
minute is representative steve toath from texas who is the person introducing the firearms
protection act that he was on the show i think two days ago here with alex and he's got more updates
for us and i have some new questions for him as well so we'll get an update on that we've also
got today i'm going to give you just a little commentary on lance armstrong and his now staged
confession that he lied all along and all the people that he bullied and threatened and
intimidated were actually correct in saying that he doped so give you a little breakdown on that
but i'm not going to spend too much time on that because there's far more important things happening
in this world than lance armstrong's career we've got smart gun rfid technology now being discussed
for uh firearms this is part of obama's 23 now famous or infamous executive orders new ways to
track firearms owners and the new york pd is also even now suggesting that they should put rfid
chips into your medication that's what they want to track is your drugs and your guns and your
money your cash and probably everything else oh it's getting crazy in any case let's go to
representative steve toath who is on the line with us and he joins us for an update mr toath thank
you for joining us once again here on the alex jones show thanks so much mike i appreciate it
it's great to have you on i heard your interview a couple of days ago i'm i'm very proud that you
are the kind of person who represents the state of texas you're a business owner you're a successful
person in the private space your private industry and you get it about the second amendment about
freedom you're well spoken you're highly intelligent i i think your bill is going to be
very successful what is your read so far on the level of support for this firearms protection act
well there think about this for a second there there there are two elements that are really
critical for this bill going through one is the people of the state of texas and the second is
the lawmakers here in austin and um we have all been shocked and it just i mean i knew it was
an issue and it's not just about the second amendment this is really more about the tenth
amendment than it is the second amendment this is about preserving states right this is about
this is about an executive order an edict by a king not having prominence over
um over the legislative process that's laid out in both the texas and in the west constitution
right and so where things are going really well with this legislation is out in the out in the
streets in in homes and businesses and restaurants all over texas people are talking about it
the problem is that there are compete there are going to be some competing bills that are more
moderate we don't need a moderate approach to a desperate problem that is facing america
um we need a strong bill that has real teeth that day one when it goes into effect
the obama administration is going to file an injunction in the fifth circuit probably
to put a stop to it so that this gets challenged all the way to the supreme court
and that's what we need we need this is what that is exactly what we need and so if a moderate bill
goes through without any teeth that they can just overlook and ignore then that's what will happen
so there are a lot of different bills right now but we need for people in the state of texas to
get behind the firearms protection act because that is the bill that is the legislation that
it has the teeth in it that the obama administration is going to force their hand
yes yes but what about what is the actual composition of support in the texas legislature
for possibly being able to actually pass this i mean i know the the the austin area representatives
we're going to get a bill through no no questions asked we're going to get a bill through in
response to what the president has done the problem is there are some more moderate bills
that have come forward um since you know since this whole thing since this media firestorm has
is erupted over the issue yes there are some more moderate bills that have come forward that are
that frankly are going to undermine what we're trying to do here when you say moderate for
example your bill makes it a felony crime for a federal official to try to enforce an
unconstitutional order in the state of texas are you saying that for example that felony is not
present in a less powerful bill it's not it's not present in either bill it's it almost looks more
like a suggestion or a house resolution than it does a bill you might as well just do a house
resolution we hate what obama's you know we we need a bill that has real teeth in it we we need
to draw a line in the sand and say enough we're done now when this was attempted drawing a line
in the sand i think roughly a year ago with the tsa tsa bill that david simpson said that
tsa bill that david simpson put through exactly exactly yeah you know the thing about that bill
is that it started too late if it had started in january like this one is then then that bill
would have had that bill would have had what what what our bill has right now which is it's got this
broad base of support from people all over texas yeah i mean my phone is being rung off the hook
right now we can't we can't get to all the calls as possible well i i'm sure that's the case if i
was in a gun shop just the other day and uh i asked i asked the the owner did you hear about
representative toath's bill and they said are you kidding me everybody that walks in our doors
keeps telling us about it yeah i mean it's it's it's really cool and you know i i don't know if
you've if i'm gonna get i'm gonna get on a faith-packed track here for a second but um this
has been so encouraging and the lord has so encouraged us over and i'll tell you why kendall
croaker is a really great guy he's the guy that that started this thing in wyoming i want to give
him credit for it yes kendall kendall's the one that started this whole thing well it was really
cool as our office got a call yesterday from kendall's sister and she said you know of all
the states that kendall's sister could live in what do you think the chances are that his sister
out of 50 states just happens to live in texas and out of 150 house districts across the state of
texas what are the chances that i live in steve's district wow she lives in district 15 huh she
lives in my district and she goes you know we just we're behind you when we're behind this legislation
you guys are trying to do it the right way and um we want the people in the state of texas to get
behind it because if if abraham lincoln said this he said if you don't have the people behind you
can't do anything great i don't want to do it i don't want to do something moderate i want to
do something great yeah if if you guys get fired up about it if you're willing to call your your
representatives and your senators about it then we can get a strong bill through that that is
a message and also because this is a national and even a global audience this matters to all of you
who are listening right now no matter what state you live in in the united states or even what
country you live in because if texas can set the precedent to standing up to unconstitutional
executive orders from the executive branch of the federal government that sets a precedent that
applies to all 50 states right mr toath yeah i mean think about this folks when you take your
kid to the pediatrician do you want the pediatrician saying to little johnny hey does
your mommy or daddy have a gun at home right i mean seriously i mean this is no different than
how things were in red china when they're turning kids against their parents this is no different
than how things were in the early days of of of uh nazi germany or stasi secret police under
muzalini or whatever yeah you're right it's it's the same kind of snitch society reporting people
reporting honest citizens to the feds to be disarmed or even jailed this is and that's part
of this you know here's how he did things when when he got obama care through it was this nebulous
3700 page we don't know what's in it until until we pass it we can't read it until we pass it
3700 pages of nebulous innocuous stuff oh don't worry about it it's fuzzy it's fluffy it's cuddly
don't worry about it there are no sharp edges to it whatsoever it gets passed now it's 37 000 pages
the only thing worse than a politician that's been in austin or washington too long
is an unelected bureaucrat that's been there too long and they are the ones they're the dangerous
ones that will put words that will put substance to these 23 actions that the president is handed
out yeah that's right folks you better be worried about it let me ask your your opinion uh attorney
general texas attorney general greg abbott put out an ad recently in new york and i love this
and i love what mr abbott has done here and this was written up in reuters with the following title
y'all come to texas state official tells new york gun owners it was a great ad by mr abbott or i i
mean he he helped organize it to say that if you want to come to a state where you have more freedom
and lower taxes and more liberties come to texas and bring your rifle and your ammunition i thought
it was fantastic what are your thoughts on mr abbott's actions in regard to that publicity
i mean i hit on that last night when i was on hannity and and i had a very close friend of mine
that saw the interview and he said if you'll get my resume martyred nile packer backs tomorrow
and and you know the reality here's the reality it's not just like as the governor told john
you're not going to be 15 off better simply because there are no state income taxes
our standard our cost of living is is is 30 lower yes so for those of you that aren't here yet
i i grew up in upstate new york i moved here in 1997 because i believed in my heart of hearts
this is the best place to raise my family and the people of texas have welcomed us and made a home
for us yes and uh i'm just going to tell you the quality of the living will be twice as good and
the cost of living will be a third of what you're paying anywhere else absolutely that's that's one
of the reasons i'm here and plus i just just love the liberty and i love i am proud of being in
texas and knowing that texas has people like you mr toath and people like mr abbott who i i hear
has aims maybe for the governorship which maybe he'd be the perfect person to do that down the
road when that opportunity arises but i am just proud to be in a state that says we we have
liberty here and we're going to stand for it we are going to stand up against tyranny we're going
to pass the laws that nullify unconstitutional orders we are texans and we're not laying down
for a bunch of tyrants i love that attitude we've got i mean yeah but we need to hear from all of
you i mean and let the phones ring right now call general abbott's office and let him know that
you're going to get behind the firearms protection act yes let him hear it he needs to hear from you
guys um they want to be about this isn't this isn't a lack of leadership this is they want to
hear from the people they need the people to be heard they want to hear from you guys which one
of these bills do you want something more more moderate they'll support something more moderate
but if they hear from the grassroots of texas that they want to build with teeth in it then
then tell the tell the attorney general's office that that you're going to stand behind the firearms
protection act and you want him to as well respectfully because he's a good man exactly
yeah and and that's the message all of you out there who are tired of being oppressed and having
your rights eroded by executive orders or the federal government in whatever way and there's
a lot of this happening in agriculture too with the the food safety modernization act that just
hammers small farmers in texas as well i've even covered that the time can i share another one
yeah sure go ahead please there is there is a terrible curriculum going through the schools
today it's called cisco it is an 80 of the schools across the state of texas parents are not allowed
to view it they're not allowed to go online to look at it's a portal online um curriculum parents
are not allowed to look at it teachers are are forced to find non-disclosure agreements about
what's in it really it's filled with islam um it is it is a it is it is the worst of the worst of
the worst when where did this come from well it's it started with um here's the problem when you
start a government agency you can't kill it so we have these education service centers in the state
of texas that 20 30 years ago when we're in when we're in school and you wanted to film strip or
you wanted a 16 millimeter movie you would go to the education service center where they they they
were you know the balls basically for all the equipment and all these great films and slides
and everything else but we don't need that anymore because we have this thing called the internet the
streaming video and audio and all that cool stuff we get it over we get it over the internet yeah
so like any good government agency it became a solution in search of a problem and so what they
did was they came out with this thing called cisco they spent millions of dollars of taxpayers money
on it and um it's it's not under the guise it's not under the supervision auspices of the state
board of education these liberals that are running it can basically say and do anything that they
want without the approval of the state board of education who are elected by we the people but
you see that's their attack point now is to try to indoctrinate the next generation it is exactly
what they're trying to do and with all these tv shows too that are coming out i don't know how
much you're aware of those but this show about they hate paul revere and a show demonizing the
founding fathers and most of these shows get this our founding the tea party the boston tea party
they're referred to in c scope as terrorists oh man yeah not surprising well they're going for
broke mr toad they're going for broke this is this is texas yeah yeah they're they're trying
to turn any person who just believes in the constitution and the founding fathers into a
total outright terrorist i mean that's right it's now in our faces there can no longer be any doubt
they're not beating around the bush so to speak they're going for your freedoms just outright
oh man unbelievable so unbelievable mr toad i let me ask you a question on different track
what are you doing to protect your personal safety and i mean this sincerely
uh i've been threatened before alex jones obviously has been threatened many many times
are you taking steps to make sure that they don't put you in a situation that could compromise
your integrity on spearheading this kind of bill well i mean here's the deal i i live my life with
a high degree of um accountability i live with uh my my legislation director is a guy that
i've known from church for years i live with him and his wife in austin yes i don't live in an
apartment by myself good um and uh michael and his wife britney uh carrie they have chls they both
carry my my chief of staff carries um my office would be the worst office to come into in the
capital if you if you want to inflict harm on good right good and plus there's a lot of concealed
carry patriots walking around that building as well i know because sometimes i'm one of them
yeah and you know that's just that hey here's the deal if if we don't stand up we have no future
we just don't our children will have no future and that's what this is all about um well you
know this this job only pay carries six you know pays 600 bucks a month you're not going to get
rich doing it in fact you're probably your business probably will end up taking a hit as
a result of it yeah right um but you know if we don't stand up all of us we've all got a part
to play even if it's just calling the attorney general and calling the governor and calling your
state representative to say get behind the firearms protection act absolutely absolutely
you've got to get a website going where we can you know publicize that url and build momentum
um i i'll i'll even donate some software technology to you by the way i i uh i i found that a software
company many years ago i'll donate that to your office so you can have an email with you
have an email list engine that works i mean you've got to get something going we could just give it
out on the air and get people to that website i'll have amy i'll have amy get going on it today
yeah and uh i mean if there's anyone out there that can help us develop a website that would
be great too all right all right uh well thank you for joining us representative toath we're
out of time but uh god bless you you're awesome thanks thank you take care we'll be right back
here on the alex jones show stay with us a lot more straight ahead that was representative toath
with the update on the firearms protection act in the state of texas if you've ever wanted one
of our best-selling generators but we're waiting for an offer so crazy you couldn't refuse then
you're not going to want to miss this exciting message here's why our solar generators provide
life-saving electrical power and unlike gas generators solar generators run quietly emit
no fumes and produce electricity from the sun so when the lights go out you'll always have the power
you need now here's the best part every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just
can't sell as new we put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at
the end of each year we call them scratch and dent units but they're really just like new each unit
comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe don't wait they
go fast go to scratch and dent solar.com that's scratch and dent solar.com for the craziest offer
we've ever made go to scratch and dent solar.com that's scratch and dent solar.com
hey there frank bates here have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out 280 million
americans this is really scary stuff defense experts warn that this odd device poses the
gravest threat we've ever known in fact just a few weeks ago former speaker of the house
newt gingrich wrote an op-ed piece for the washington post warning about this deadly threat
i can't believe that more people aren't talking about this it may be because the liberals and
the government are trying to cover it up that's why my friend just created a free video at
weirddevice.com that exposes this threat and blows the doors off the conspiracy
go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover exactly what it is plus
discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack i'm not sure how
long this video will be online so go to weirddevice.com before it's gone forever
again that's weirddevice.com
hello this is ty bolinger author of the best-selling book cancer step outside the box
i want you to know some very important information in 1985 president ronald reagan requested that
carnivora be sent directly to the white house at a time when only the president could obtain
this world-class healer now 27 years later carnivore capsules are used around the world
to keep people healthy now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of
superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only
without harming a single normal cell if you want to stay healthy now's your chance to literally
wake up your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body
call one eight six six venus fly or order from carnivora.com that's c-a-r-n-i-v-o-r-a dot com
that's one eight six six eight three six eight seven three five one eight six six venus fly
or visit carnivora.com protect your immune system it's the only one you've got
we've got it
we're continuing here on the alex jones show thank you for joining us we just finished up an
interview with representative steve toath from the state of texas and the firearms protection act and
i want to reiterate why this matters to everybody across the nation and wherever you may be listening
from this is a precedent-setting bill and it's based on the bill out of wyoming and that really
that the author of that bill deserves the credit but the language of this bill can be shared with
many other states and there are lots of other states who would like to get on board and stand
up to the federal government and say enough is enough we're not going to let our rights be
trampled on any longer because look where this is going folks if you don't stand up to this
second amendment is not the end of this they're going to come after your first amendment they're
going to come after your fifth amendment even more than they have already they're going to
obliterate states rights and basically say there shouldn't be any states whatsoever and with the
executive orders obama is going to be saying well we don't need congress either what's the point of
having congress when the president just writes law this is the basis of the downfall of our
free society and it has already begun we are we have already started to tumble down that pit
of tyranny and oppression and if we don't turn back from that right now it's over this is this
is it so you better get on the phone right now if you're in the state of texas you better get on the
phone call attorney general greg abbott's office and tell him yes you support the full the full-on
firearms protection act that makes it a felony for federal officials to engage in unconstitutional
gun restriction in the state of texas you better call your state representatives wherever you live
and tell them introduce the firearms protection act because if you don't if you don't draw the
line right here it's over and let me tell you my personal prediction of what i think is coming up
so why why didn't obama have a high-capacity magazine restriction in his executive orders
there was all this talk that he was going to do that but he backed off it seems he did not do that
why because he has full confidence that they're going to be able to get that through congress
through legislation so you have to ask the question then why does he have that confidence
when right now the the mood the the environment in congress is saying no to more gun restrictions
in congress why does he have that confidence the answer is because they are planning another major
false flag attack in america a major false flag attack and i'm here to tell you independently
independently at not even not even based on what alex said or infowars or anybody else but just
myself as mike adams as an intelligent investigative journalist with no criminal record absolutely you
know the cleanest cut guy you'll ever meet i don't smoke i don't drink alcohol i never have
a consumed alcohol just my personal choice clean cut guy super clean record passed all the fbi
background checks all the atf checks you know for class four gear you name it all right you're not
going to find somebody with with a cleaner record than myself by looking at the data i am telling
you i believe that they are going to stage another major false flag attack during the debate of gun
control restrictions in the u.s congress because they know that if they stage something big enough
and i'm talking about something like blowing up federal buildings more than what we saw in
oklahoma city something even perhaps bigger than 911 i'm talking about perhaps them doing a a dirty
bomb a radiological attack or a biological attack in a major u.s city and somehow finding some way
to blame that on patriots that's what is coming so you better be ready because if they do that and
if they can blame it on patriots and they get the media screaming again and again about how how the
patriots made this happen and killed a million people in some major city they'll declare
martial law there won't be another election you won't have any rights whatsoever and they'll drive
america into an all-out war and that's what they want so watch out that's what's coming all right
stay with me here on the alex jones show a lot more straight ahead including dr andrew wakefield
we'll be right back you are listening to gcn visit gcnlive.com today if you want an american
company with american products made by americans here is the cal ben soap company alex and his
staff have used these pure soap products for years these all-natural soaps are made from
the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and safe see them on the
web at fivestarsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog buy the one to two month sample
package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to
two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs this is an amazing deal you can save
thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel see them on the web at
fivestarsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog waging war on corruption alex jones on the
gcn radio network big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's alex jones on the gcn radio network and now live from austin texas alex jones
welcome to the third hour of the alex jones show this is mike adams
filling in for alex and i appreciate you joining us today we've got so much on our plates things
are moving very very rapidly now coming up in the next segment we've got dr andrew wakefield
joining us here live in studio here in austin texas to give us the latest information on the
u.s vaccine court admitting that vaccines cause autism plus we're going to get dr wakefield's
take on the new psychiatric police state that has just been formed in america by obama and his 23
executive orders there was an outstanding breakdown of those executive orders posted
filmed and posted by aaron dykes right here on the infowars team just i think yesterday or the
night before that went up seven of the 23 executive orders have something to do with mental health
so you can bet they're going to start using psychiatry as a weapon against freedom while
completely ignoring the fact that psychiatry actually creates violent shooters and has been
linked to most of these shootings that have taken place so wow what a what a total scam a total
racket they're making the problem worse while ignoring the real causes of violence in america
today two things i wanted to cover though real quick before we bring dr wakefield in studio one
is that you know you've got obama and all these people talking about background checks that we
need to have universal background checks why not have universal background checks for presidents
because let me tell you this you know that obama's birth certificate has i don't know
17 layers in adobe acrobat it's it's copied and pasted and the resolution is different in
different parts of the document the thing is a total fake it's so obvious anybody who knows
photoshop or acrobat can see that his birth certificate is a fake now if you or i submitted
a document like that as part of a background check to purchase a gun we would be arrested
for document fraud we would be guilty of a felony crime for submitting the same type of document
which is an obvious fraud that the president of our country is using the claim that he's qualified
to be president or that he that he uh meets the constitutional requirements so why not have
universal background checks for presidents for his cabinet members why not have background checks
for members of congress to make sure they can pass a quiz on the constitution you know what is
what is the 10th amendment ask your average congressperson in washington dc and they won't
know they don't know what it is or they'll misquote it they'll say oh the 10th amendment is
what gives the government the right to regulate all intrastate commerce what what that's not
what's written at all you people would fail you get an f okay you get an f on liberty and f on
the constitution you get an f in washington on just about everything you're doing today except
those few people that are standing up and a big thumbs up to rand paul by the way for his comments
on saying that we don't want a king in america today it's we've had enough of kings running our
lives so enough of the kingship one other comment here before we get into the next segment
lance armstrong uh i i wrote an article about lance armstrong it's posted on infowars.com right
now he came out last night and oprah oprah who's trying to save her network from terrible ratings
had lance armstrong on to have a staged confession during which lance armstrong
admitted that he's been lying all along he doped he doped with epo he doped with testosterone he
doped with his own blood injecting it back into his veins i mean that guy was not on a bike unless
he had a needle in his veins before i mean all the tour de france races he said he doped to win
those races and in the interview he didn't even think that it was cheating he just said oh it's
just leveling the playing field i mean the guy has no remorse he bullied people he threatened
people he filed lawsuits against a long list of whistleblowers who were trying to speak out and
now he goes on oprah and wants us to forgive him dude we don't forgive you why don't you give the
money back to all the people's people whose careers that you ruined or destroyed or threatened
with your lawsuits why don't you give them the money that you gained by cheating in sport why
don't you do that and then we might forgive you that's my comment on lance armstrong stay with us
we'll be back after this break with dr andrew wakefield in studio you may be arrested and or
subject to other police action tyranny is here the grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality
it really says that the state is god the united states is now recognized globally as one of the
most oppressive police states on earth this film conclusively proves the existence of a secret
network of fema camps now being expanded nationwide this documentary exposes how the
continuity of government program has established an all-powerful shadow state police state four
chronicles the sickening depth to which our republic has fallen prepare to enter the
secretive world of emergency dictatorship body scammers sound cameras citizen spies
stage terror and cameras on every street corner it's only the beginning of the new world order's
hellish plan the police state isn't coming it's here secure your copy today at infowars.com
or see it online in the highest quality at prisonplanet.tv
now that we have moved into the winter season there is an increased need to support our immunity
and health at silver lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection
of silver-based products our most popular silver-based products are the 32-ounce nano
silver solutions our 2-ounce nano silver nasal applicators as well as our all-natural silver
soaps just released is our 100 natural silver gel our new silver gel is not based on synthetic
gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface but rather we have
formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly
penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively visit www.silverlungs.com
and click on our store page to find what silver-based products are best for you
that's www.silverlungs.com the new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness
get serious and make a stand with supernatural silver this is a breakthrough in silver technology
that is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver can
be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds supernatural
silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water purification it is the
number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect
choice for your emergency preparedness go to www.supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself
and your loved ones a fighting chance that's www.supernaturalsilver.com check out our new low
prices and like us on facebook in the councils of government we must guard against the acquisition
of unwanted influence whether sought or unsought by the military industrial complex in dallas
texas three shots were fired at president tennedy's motorcade in downtown dallas the first
report to say that president tennedy has been seriously wounded by this shooting it is a big
idea a new world order it was almost as if they were a planned implosion it just pancakes
either you were with us or you were with the terrorists
but i also believe a lot of gun owners would agree that ak-47s belong in the hands of soldiers not
the handsome criminals for many of the police and guard troops it is an uncomfortable job to do this
in an american city global governance at last is it one world the central bank is in charge
but aren't we all just living and dying for what the central banks do and for me give me liberty
or give me death live from the infowars.com studios it's alex jones
all right welcome back to the alex jones show this is mike adams the editor of naturalnews.com
filling in for alex today and in studio joining me now for the rest of this hour is none other than
dr andrew wakefield with some breaking news on the u.s vaccine court and its recent decision tying
vaccines to autism without any question whatsoever so he'll be breaking that down for us in some
detail also we're going to get dr wakefield's take on some of the possible implications of
the recent executive orders focused on mental health and psychiatry and i've even got a copy
of the psychiatry bible so to speak here with me and we're going to cover oppositional defiance
disorder odd which is actually in the psychiatry manual even though people said i made that up
i didn't make it up and i'm going to show it to you in the book as we continue here plus we're
going to be taking your calls so if you've got a question for dr wakefield i'd like to take your
call go ahead and call it's 888 isn't it no 800 i'm sorry 800-259-9231 if you've got a question
on psychiatry or dr wakefield if you called earlier for paul watson's guest or representative
toath i'm gonna have to drop you and and take new calls on psychiatry and questions for dr wakefield
so go ahead and clear the board guys and let let new people call back in and i apologize if you're
on hold but you know things are moving very quickly so dr wakefield welcome to the alex jones
show it's good to have you in studio again it's great to be back thank you well a lot has been
happening since the last time we spoke right here in the same spot you've got the the british medical
journal still has not retracted their slanderous statements about you and your research is there
any update on that front yes brian dear and the editor of the british medical journal and the bmj
themselves are being sued here in the state of texas we're going through a jurisdictional battle
at the moment they're saying you don't have the right to sue us here in texas this is a british
journal these this is a british journalist but we do there's a long arm statute and they sell their
wares and make a profit out of texas so um on the technical aspects of this we're confident in
winning and getting brian dear here before a texas jury and that is the key really brian dear might
be here in austin texas that is what this is all about i want the american people to see and judge
this man for themselves and to judge the quality and the veracity of his story and they will see
how flawed he really is or he could just remain a fugitive from justice i guess and refuse to come
and and what you might have to go into extradition proceedings in the uk or how would that even work
well it's interesting and it's probably a technical aspect of law but i would imagine
that we would then file a case in england and he would then be in contempt of the uk courts but
that's another matter the the bmj themselves have to come because they sell here this is
one of their outlets so um they have they're obliged if we win the jurisdictional battle
well excellent i appreciate your veracity your dedication to pursuing this and not allowing them
to just steamroll you with their slanderous completely false analysis i mean they they
literally just invented things about your research that they pulled out of thin air yeah i know what
the problem here mike is so much bigger as you probably know there is a an increasing level of
attack on scientists and physicians who are acting in the best interests of their patients and not in
the best interests of the government or the pharmaceutical industry and there is a relentless
assault on the few perhaps five ten scientists in the world who are prepared to work on the possible
association between vaccines and childhood developmental disorders like autism and if we do
not protect those scientists and doctors then you're going to find nobody who's prepared to
stand up in vaccine court to protect these children because that's the end of their career
you're going to find no scientist who's prepared to do the valid safety science on vaccines because
it'll be the end of their career they lose their grants they'll lose everything just as i did and
so we have got to stand up as a body as scientists as a community as a people and say these people
are valuable and need to be protected and that is exactly what we're doing well said this is
about the integrity of science i mean this is you know this is not a personal uh a revenge
attack on brandy that's it's so much more important than that and the community actually
said to me andy we need to fight this case we will raise the capital to help you because as you know
mike justice belongs to those who can afford it yes so we need to take this battle to them in the
u.s court well let's talk about the u.s vaccine court now also there's been significant breaking
news that you brought to my attention an article published at huffpost vaccine court awards millions
to two children with autism the court has made the determination that there is a causal link
between vaccinations and the development of autism in those children and they were given an award
give us a breakdown of that story well it's this is fascinating it's huge it's a game changer and
it comes on the back of an italian decision in the remedy court which made an identical decision here
we have a child who was developing perfectly normally in italy who had the mmr and regressed
into autism he developed all the typical characteristics that we described originally
in lancet including gastrointestinal symptoms encephalopathy in other words generalized brain
dysfunction and his final diagnosis was autism they settled that case in italy the government
importantly did not fight it they agreed that the mmr had caused his autism they thought it on the
basis that they do not make mmr vaccination mandatory in in italy whereas the judge said no sorry you
put so much pressure on parents to have this vaccine you are to blame now we have this ruling
in the u.s vaccine court where you have exactly the same sequence of events normally developing
children get the mmr plus another vaccine in each case of these two children they then regress into
they have this encephalopathy a rash of fever loss of language loss of speech loss of interaction
with their siblings and a regression into autism they are linked and what this brings to the public
attention once and for all is that the american uh vaccine court the department of justice have
been hiding behind the vaccine court for so long oh yeah take behind their table injuries now we
have a clear sequence of events which links vaccines mmr in particular to autism all right
if you're just joining us this is the alex jones show mike adams filling in an interview with dr
andrew wakefield live here in studio in austin texas and a lot of breaking news on the vaccine
front now we published a story not too long ago dr wakefield where the cdc admits on their website
and we you know took a screenshot quoted their information they admit that vaccines contain
mercury aluminum msg monosodium glutamate and formaldehyde now these four substances should any
doctor in any circumstance ever inject a child with aluminum mercury msg or formaldehyde
no it would be unthinkable if you took these substances on their own and gave them to someone
you would be you would face criminal prosecution and yet right they're saying that this is safe no
it isn't it's never been tested for safety we just got a a recent report from the institute of
medicine saying that there is a parlous lack of information on vaccine safety science both in
terms of the schedule of the dose that children get and when they get it we simply do not know
there is no science and so if people are telling the public that vaccines are safe because they've
been shown to be safe that is not true right right exactly but brings up the question why
won't the cdc the fda and the the pro vaccine doctors out there why won't they say let's make
a clean vaccine let's make clean vaccines with no mercury no thimerosal no msg no formaldehyde
nothing like just single dose vials right so they don't need a preservative because they're
not used for multiple doses why won't they do that there are two parts to this answer mike in
my opinion and one of them is accountability if you make a change then it's a tacit admission
that there was a problem with the vaccine that you had before so they'd rather keep harming
children rather than fix the problem that seems to be the case and the other problem mike is that
they don't want to lose the public to lose confidence the vaccine schedule the vaccine
policy of any country depends upon the compliance of the populace in other words people having
enough confidence in the vaccine regulators to say yes we'll take your your word for it and if
that goes then it's it's to try to cross the board you know people will lose confidence in vaccines
right across the board and we will have problems well they are they are losing confidence in
vaccines no mike they've lost it they've lost 89 percent of american parents in a recent study from
uh university of michigan said the vaccine safety science was their number one medical research
priority 89 of parents wow so the majority of parents have major concerns they do not believe
the cdc they do not believe what their pediatrician is telling them they're saying in their in their
communities on their streets in their schools so many children who are being damaged by these
vaccines with autism at the sort of spearhead of all this that they do not believe what they're
being old and it's obvious that they damage children i mean i remember even donald trump
said on the air a couple of months ago that his employees perfectly healthy children took them
into the pediatrician they got vaccinated the next morning lights are out the child's autistic
and it happens to people over and over and over again there is a temporal correlation between
getting the vaccine and getting autism how can the scientific community even call itself scientific
if it dismisses all of this powerful evidence it is extraordinary to me clinically it is so obvious
my job as a physician and a scientist is to look for patterns in disease patterns in clinical
presentation and the pattern here is so common so similar and it's exactly as you heard in these
court settlements normal child vaccine prolonged fever rash debilitation the child goes downhill
their immune system goes to pieces all right hold on never the same again hold that thought
dr wakefield we're going to continue after this break this is the alex jones show and an interview
with dr andrew wakefield we'll be right back after this break with more plus your calls so
don't go away we'll be right back hello i'm alex jones myself my family the info wars.com team
want to relay to you and your families that we are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on
every front info wars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats but we can't do that
without your help by getting the films bumper stickers and t-shirts at info wars.com you will
wake up people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level we need
your help to spread the word like never before they wish to hide themselves during this tectonic
battle between the forces of freedom and darkness you are the response to the globalist technocrats
and their program of global eugenics dehumanization and ultimate extermination the war
is here it's an info war the spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984 hi there my name is frank
bates what i'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble
i just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are incompetent line crooks that are
counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high some have called this
a conspiracy others have called it a cover-up and you will be shocked to find out how deep the
conspiracy goes my video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how i beat
them and how you can beat them too watch the controversial video that thousands of other
smart patriots have already seen in the last three months go to 123coverup.com and discover one
weird trick to slash your power bill and protect your home go watch my video now at 123coverup.com
before they force me to shut it down again that's 123coverup.com
plan a healthy garden easy and fast with organica seed.com easy because organica seed.com offers
one of the largest online selections of organic heirloom non-hybrid and untreated seeds as well
as tobacco and cotton seeds at low prices go to organica seed.com spelled o-r-g-a-n-i-c-a seed.com
organic seed.com remember organic seed is healthy seed. Hi this is Ted Anderson have you ever
wondered why banks stock workers investment advisors won't talk about gold IRAs they've
been available since 1986 yet the financial industry won't recognize the value of gold
for your retirement gold is outperformed paper investments yet no word about IRAs if you would
like to have gold for your retirement call 800-686-2237 don't get left behind by rising
inflation and low returns call 800-686-2237 secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237
don't throw away leftovers instead throw all your leftovers vegetable peels egg shells coffee
grounds pizza crusts and more into the bokashi if you love to garden and compost but don't like the
hassle of turning a compost bin or the smell then check out the em bokashi food waste recycling
system from tereganics finally a way to recycle all your food and plant waste safely and effectively
and stop using fertilizers the em bokashi food waste recycling system rather than decomposition
the bokashi system uses fermentation to break down waste so it takes less time to create
nutrient-dense humus for crops or gardens with no turning and no obnoxious odors to learn more and
order your bokashi online visit tereganics.com and click on the orange button that's tereganics.com
spelled t-e-r-a-g-a-n-i-x.com or call 866-369-3678 that's 866-369-3678 recycle all your food wastes
in about six weeks with the bokashi food waste recycling system from tereganics.com tereganics
life's getting better
i read the news today
all right and we are back on the alex jones show thank you for joining us
we are continuing our interview here in studio with dr andrew wakefield yes the dr wakefield
the champion of academic integrity when it comes to on scientific integrity actually more importantly
when it comes to vaccines and investigating with a sense of scientific skepticism
what could be the links between vaccines and childhood development disorders such as autism
but not limited to autism and dr wakefield continues with us in the studio right now dr
wakefield what kinds of i i want to get the word out about how people can help support your efforts
because this is an important victory and you mentioned a website during the break can you
give that out on the air certainly in order to protect doctors and scientists who are acting in
the interests of their patients but who are being attacked by what is whatever mainstream medicine
is by the pharmaceutical industry by the media because they are not complying with the rules
that protect the stock price of of various pharmaceutical products then what we've done
is to set up what we call the academic integrity fund academic integrity fund.org and this
is a fund that people can pay into which will protect the legal rights will allow the
people who are coming under attack to fight back whether it's in the courts or elsewhere
and it's starting with my case right here in texas in an attempt to get brian deere and the
british medical journal in front of a texas jury and are there are i know it takes money to fight
for justice big time is are there some attorneys also doing some pro bono work as part of it or
discounted work i have an outstanding group of attorneys who are working at a discounted rate
because they believe very strongly in the merits of this case well i'm going to make a donation
by the way i've been doing a lot of donations lately i donated to gun owners of america
i gave 500 to that group i just larry pratt you rock i gave him 500 bucks i'm going to donate to
your group academic integrity fund.org is the web address we've got to put the money where it
matters i call that uh revenue activism so we take money from our store sales and we just push it
into all these things that need support but uh thank you for mentioning that website but
continuing on what do you think about this flu so-called flu pandemic almost a fear-mongering
thing the cdc is doing right now saying oh the flu is terrible everybody should go get vaccinated
isn't that a too simplistic of an answer we've seen this time and time again mike and i'm not
an expert on flu vaccine but i do know that for example flu mutates at a phenomenally fast rate
so predicting which vaccine is going to work against the current flu is such a hit and miss
affair and we've seen from analyses detailed comprehensive scientific analyses of all the data
on flu vaccine around the world in the cochran review that these vaccines are their their
benefit is minimal at best and restricted to certain groups not seen in high-risk groups
and therefore there is no merit in those high-risk groups getting them and the canadians showing
that if you get the flu after being vaccinated because it does not work well then it is worse
you develop a more severe pattern of disease but you have been vaccinated the cdc which i am
convinced just invents numbers out of thin air i mean they just pull these out of their hats and
they they say if you get the vaccine your flu will be less severe but they have absolutely
no data to back that up and they say the vaccine is now i think they're quoting it's 62 effective
that number has no basis in anything they make it up i'm sure they do and they have the ability to
make a sows ear out of a silk purse i think that's what they've done here they've made numbers up
for so long what are we to believe and when you hear these numbers about the people who've
had to go to the hospital because they've got flu how many of those people were vaccinated
were they part of those group that group that the canadians say exactly are going to be worse if they
get the flu after having been vaccinated we don't know we're not told i did a little bit of a survey
on that and i found that about two-thirds in my group of you know friends and employees and so on
about two-thirds of the people who went to the hospital with influenza i'm not talking about my
employees they're they're typically healthy but people they know you know two-thirds of them have
been vaccinated against the flu so how can that be if the flu works i mean if the flu vaccine
works then how can two-thirds of the people in the hospital with the flu be people who got
vaccinated it's not logical yeah there's something very bad going wrong here and the idea that you're
going to give mercury containing flu vaccines to pregnant women and to children over the age of
six months this is unacceptable tell me about when you were trained in med school weren't you taught
never give a vaccine to a pregnant woman absolutely i mean it was you never gave anything
to a pregnant woman unless absolutely necessary you know you've no antidepressants absolutely
you've got a very very vulnerable fetus there a lot of these compounds are sequestered they're
taken up preferentially into the fetus the fetus does not have the ability to get rid of them for
example mercury if you give a mother mercury that mercury is going to be uh is going to get into the
fetus and it cannot it doesn't have the excretion mechanisms to get rid of it so it's going to
accumulate but the cdc and the vaccine pushers they engage in what i might call magical thinking
where they say the mercury doesn't harm you because we say it doesn't we wave a magic wand
we do a little voodoo big pharma profit voodoo and suddenly the mercury is safe magical so they've
said the science shows that the science is in two years ago the paper came out showing that 74 of
the published science shows that there is an association between heavy metal containing
vaccines and autism all right well said dr wakefield we'll be right back here on the
alex jones show and your calls straight ahead we're on the march the empire's on the run
alex jones and the gcn radio network
you prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms but if you don't have a home security system then
you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when you're sleeping or away
from home who's watching out for intruders check out simply safe it's a new do-it-yourself home
security system that is completely wireless go to getsimplysafe.com simply safe is independent
and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if the grid goes down you are protected
it's completely customizable so you can use it in your home business boat trailer storage unit
or shed getsimplysafe.com simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under
20 minutes so there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you move or need to relocate
you can take the system with you wherever you go you aren't always at home but simply safe will
stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days a week again that's getsimplysafe.com
looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters like
hurricane sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous
economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at efoods direct we hear from customers
every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand
after hurricane sandy danny from new york city wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed
but i managed to get my efoods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece it is better to
be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late i can warn you but i can't feed you heed the
warnings and do what alex has done call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoods direct.com slash alex and
build your food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet
call 800-409-5633 or efoods direct.com slash alex you can bet your life on efoods direct
millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses don't
be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad spectrum
antibacterial solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that
can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing
supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the
causes of many serious diseases such as strep staph pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens
this new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions the science digest journal
says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder
of modern medicine go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20%
off that's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on facebook
defending the republic from enemies foreign and domestic it's alex jones
welcome back your calls straight ahead as we continue our interview with dr
andrew wakefield right here on the alex jones show this is mike adams the editor of naturalnews.com
filling in i guess i i am as alex called me the unofficial crew member around here i come in and
fill in from time to time whenever i'm needed for that purpose and dr wakefield once again thank
you for being here hope you're ready to take some calls is that are you good absolutely i'm ready
to go all right you got your earpiece in yep you're ready to go i'm good all right let's do
it let's go to greg in utah greg you're on the air with dr andrew wakefield welcome to the show
well thank you you know there was a small uh health uh natural health company here that was
exposing all this information on a daily basis and the ftcs went after them it was called daniel
chapter one and basically if yeah they attacked their first amendment rights and and if they were
to say anything about this anymore they're basically going to put them in prison so they're
they ended their radio program you know we need the support of the people that's the problem
is they're attacked they're killing the messenger you know they're going after the messenger
and they're doing it i mean the federal trade commission is who went after them not the well
not the not the cdc yeah no i'm very familiar with that case that's a good point uh daniel
chapter one was actually a ministry and they sold some cancer therapies herbal and they dared to go
on the air and to say that you know some of these herbs are mentioned in the bible and they you know
they they can actually help you heal from cancer and yeah the ftc came after them what do you see
happening dr wakefield and thank you caller for your call but what do you see happening with
attacks on the first amendment rights of people who are attempting to to raise awareness among the
public of alternative or holistic healing therapies there are myriad cases of of local
health authorities local regulators going after alternative practitioners i mean these attacks
are going on all the time in fact texas is probably one of the worst states in the country
for that the state medical board absolutely yeah and dr brazinski absolutely a classic example
where i gather that they've now tried uh the fda are trying to get the patent on his products you
know having attacked him for years now that's what i've heard through the grapevine yeah whether it's
true or not it would be a wonderful irony to conclude that story as long as he comes out of it
um well well but um one of the greatest uh groups guilty of of bio biopiracy is big pharma they will
attack an herb and say it's useless it's useless it's useless and then they will steal a molecule
from that herb like turmeric for example they'll modify it patented and then say this is the best
drug ever oh yeah they're in the jungles now collecting a number of plants and herbs that
they believe may be the future to their success because they run out of other things apart from
vaccines to profit from um but uh the biggest impact i see is in the media you know here we
have a case where a classic case a groundbreaking case two cases where uh the the vaccine cord
awards uh for children who develop autism following mmr vaccine it's picked up by the uk
media it's reported they're not a single word in the mainstream media here why because their
revenues derived from advertising dollars from the pharmaceutical industry and that was a 1997
decision i believe from the fda that legalized pharmaceutical advertising on mainstream television
because before that it was illegal and it remains illegal in most every other nation around the
world and what they did mike is i think quite a smart thing is that they they paid a lot of money
and so that the the the media became dependent on that income you know it's like you kind of
ramp things up according to the income that you get and yeah you can't do without it and so
suddenly they've got them right where they want them got them got them yeah well we'll just leave
it at that all right let's go to the next call rob in texas you're on the air rob go ahead what's
your question sir well good afternoon gentlemen uh my statement actually speaks to psychiatric
psychiatric tyranny that i see and to vaccines um my son who is on the spectrum with asperger's was
vaccinated um he has depression and sometimes anger issues we take him to see a counselor we
were going to take him to see a child psychiatrist and so my wife was getting that set up he asked
sir you know do you have insurance she naively says well yes what kind okay we accept that she
goes but we want to pay for this out of pocket he says no you can't do that if we accept your
insurance they have to pay or it's insurance fraud this is new you can't pay cash no they
wouldn't let us pay cash needless to say we didn't book an appointment yeah well well good question
rob go ahead there's a big issue several big issues here actually one is um are the origins of
your child's anger and violence or aggressive issues due to um underlying pain or discomfort
one thing we've discovered in fact we reported years and years ago 15 years ago is these children
have an inflammatory bowel disease in many cases and that is a cause of gastrointestinal symptoms
constipation diarrhea alternating constipation and diarrhea pain kids in pain sudden outbursts of
anger and when you correct that abdominal inflammation that intestinal inflammation
all that goes away in other words is there a need for a reappraisal of children for medical
problems underlying medical problems do they not need to be on pharmaceutical agents for
uh for anger and depression at all and that's my belief very good source of problems yeah if
someone has chronic ongoing pain in digestive pain or even musculoskeletal pain whatever the
case may be you know they're going to be kind of crabby or maybe depressed in a bad mood that's
not a psychiatric problem that's a physiological problem it's absolutely essential to rule out
physiological medical problems before you resort to the belief that this is a psychiatric problem
and then put them on major medications which have may have any number of adverse effects and for
what we are not indicated for autism or asperger's disorders in these children so there may be an
alternative approach mike is it mike yeah no sorry no the man on the phone rob rob i thought
you're asking me my name yeah i'm mike what are you what you forgot me already what's going on
so rob if there are you know if there are any underlying symptoms that might be corrected please
bear that in mind and get take that approach first all right very good very good question rob thank
you for your call and by the way here over overhead cam shot this is the dsm right here
dsm for the diagnostic and statistical manual of mental disorders the so-called bible of modern
psychiatry and check it out here it is page 100 oppositional defiant disorder oppositional defiant
disorder right here there we get in view check this out dr wakefield you can be diagnosed with
this and i imagine you and i have both been quote diagnosed with this by simply disagreeing with
someone in a position of authority it's just written right in here oh and they're probably
drugs that they can oh look often argues with adults something that's in the first amendment
i think that um often blames others for his or her mistakes well we don't do that but
uh easily annoyed by others i'm annoyed by liberals who are trying to take away our rights
i'm easily annoyed by gun grabbers uh i don't know i don't know who you're annoyed by uh journal
journal editors who slander how long have we got yeah well anyway there it is it's real folks uh
people said i made this up no it's right there and there are a couple of people it's right here
from it right in this room but i exactly i think that manual is it's it underlies everything that's
wrong with this disorder particularly autistic autistic spectrum disorders the worst thing
is that it ever firmed at the hands of child psychiatrists i'm afraid that's my opinion and
it's one i strongly strongly believe and what we see is a revision of this document time and time
again dsm when they should be focusing on the real issue what is driving this epidemic of autism for
a child born today the risk of an autistic spectrum disorder is going to be one in 25
that is unacceptable and when what you find is the psychiatric psychology community spend their time
revising this document not everyone yeah but a lot of people focus on this and it's a displacement
activity it's moving away from what is really essential about this how do you stop this epidemic
and how do you treat kids effectively you've already got it you know what this reminds me of
i mean look at this manual this thing is huge i mean check this out that's how big it is it's a
massive thick manual and it's getting bigger in version five all they do is they they they observe
a lot of nutritional deficiencies a lot of underlying problems and they give it a bunch of
different names this is like physicists looking for the god particle and naming all the little
things they spot in the super collider saying oh that's the muon that's the gluon that's the
blue on whatever they name it it's like no people it's there's there's one unified theory underneath
all this you're just naming things to try to make it sound scientific there's really only
a couple of basic core fundamental physiological truths or physical truths underneath all this
yeah one of the great truths mike is you go back and you talk to the mother what happened to your
child and mothers have got a trust in their instincts because their instincts are the reason
we're on this earth at the moment not the dsm manual so that can go in the trash all right let's
let's trash it there it goes off to the mother off and say what happened to your child very good
let's take another call i'm getting i'm getting excited here because i'm suffering from oppositional
defiant disorder jesse from new orleans you are on the air with dr andrew wakefield jesse welcome
to the show mike how you doing i'm doing great man so right in line with your conversation about
the dsm i was a victim of doctor uh doctors who basically use that book as their bible when i was
a kid i uh my my parents made me go see a therapist and uh i basically started making things up
based on what i was reading you know his diagnosis for certain things i actually read
a book about michael crayton's terminal man and uh basically just started telling him i was having
all the symptoms that the main character in that book had really and they completely took my word
for it so what were you diagnosed with psychiatrist who then gave me some medication and then they
inevitably i started telling him i was hearing voices even though i wasn't and because you know
i was 13 so they admitted me and by the time it was all said and done i was on well butrin when
it first came out depa coke now veins and they would give me thorazine whenever i acted up
so and also probably those records could then be used against you now to deny you access to
purchasing a firearm also i was a minor and interestingly enough i was still allowed to
join the military at 17 so you figure that out but um beyond that uh my my kids i have two twin
boys that were born eight months ago yeah seven months seven weeks premature and of course they
were the whole time my wife was pregnant you know you need to double up on your flu vaccine you need
to do all this and that and the other thing and i was like no we're not doing that so were you able
to keep her protected from vaccines during pregnancy well i've exposed her to a lot of
your research and and you know alex's research and all that stuff and i've shown her the numbers and
one of the greatest things after the kids were born i was able to you know read up on a lot of
different things and i showed the doctors because you know you can never get a doctor when you need
one but you know you tell them you don't want the kids to have the vaccines you'll see everybody in
the whole hospital and uh they started showing us all the documentation and i was like well you
know i'm reading here that there's a fund that the government has for families who have adverse side
effects from vaccinations how many incidents do you think have to happen before the federal
government puts a fund together like that all right good question jesse thank you for your
call dr wakefield let's talk about the pressure that physicians and even physicians assistants
and so on put on new moms to to be injected even before childbirth during childbirth and after
childbirth even the medicalization of childbirth in our country today what's around the world all
of western medicine well mike any pressure any pressure at all in the absence of informed consent
and adequate safety studies is too much there is huge pressure and there are no safety studies
particularly of giving the vaccines to mothers during pregnancy where it's been
specifically contraindicated in the past yeah causes stillbirth or causes spontaneous abortions
yeah and there is no informed consent a friend of mine went to uh for a vaccine in fact uh to go
into nursing school the other day and she was given two mmrs just a month apart there's never
ever ever ever been a safety study of that procedure when asked why should i have a second
mmr after the first one just a month ago and she said well the mumps vaccine doesn't work therefore
you need another one booster and well then why do i have to have measles and rubella at the same time
you can see this cash cow for the pharmaceutical industry right just because that's all they've
got because that's all they're prepared to manufacture well and also what about vet
veterinary medicine because if if the theory behind vaccines is that you inject your dog
with a vaccine and the dog's body builds antibodies to that vaccine why do you get a card or an email
from your vet every year oh your dog needs the same vaccine again every year i thought the
i thought the theory was that the antibodies are there they don't go go away at least not i mean
they're not supposed to it's supposed to build a database your immune system database right yeah
you could argue that your immune system database needs boosting every every so often but there's
no science on this so when they introduced mmr in the uk the minister who was responsible said
this is one dose for life okay so people believe them and so people did it what happened is they
found it didn't work neither the measles no the river the mumps vaccine uh lasted for very long
so now it's two doses three doses soon we're going to be on this treadmill of having to have these
vaccines every year because they do not work in other words here's the irony particularly for
mumps vaccine the vaccine is successful for the pharmaceutical industry precisely because it
doesn't work and then exactly volume of sales goes up dramatically that's exactly it because
by when people go get the mumps vaccine they have a false sense of security thinking they're
protected from the mumps and they might thereby not take other precautions such as boosting
vitamin d intake which is very powerful for preventing mumps and many other infectious
diseases so you're right the vaccines not working is what makes themselves so well and it allows the
cdc to put out another fear-mongering announcement oh there's another epidemic of mumps better go get
vaccinated even though it doesn't work that's right we're seeing mumps outbreaks in highly
vaccinated populations now precisely because it doesn't work and it was a vaccine that was
never needed in the first place not my word the cdc's word and the department of health in england
why doesn't the media i mean i guess we already know the answer but it's just it's a shame the
media never ever reports that in every outbreak they cover most of those who suffer from the
outbreak whether it's mumps or flu or something else have already been vaccinated against that
very thing they never report that yes the uh reporting in the media of the vaccine issue is
so one-sided so distorted so pro uh the cdc prove the pharmaceutical industry pro uh more and more
vaccines we're not going to get the truth from the mainstream media i'm afraid and that's going
to last for some time yeah we're not going to get it from truth from them on any front let's go to
another caller nick in pennsylvania nick welcome to the show you're on the air go ahead sir mike
first of all i want to say i think that you're doing a great job for filling in for alex thanks
and uh and you're you're doing a heck of a good job i'm just doing my best here man we're all
we're all fighting for the same liberties that's all that's all there is to it absolutely and dr
wakefield i just want to say it's really a pleasure sir to be talking to you i myself
actually i'm one of america's few remaining pioneer research scientists and it's such a
good coincidence that you happen to be on because there is a couple subjects that i'd like to talk
to you about of a very important concern yeah go ahead let's hear it okay one of the subjects is
i definitely agree with the vaccine problem especially being given to children infants babies
there's definitely a problem with mercury and heavy metals and i think that they're absolutely
positively is a link to autism because of that mercury that's why as far as tuna fish is concerned
that has finally been brought to light that you have to be careful with certain fish you eat
because of the mercury levels that are high in certain types of fish but another problem
is also the fact that and it figures that there happens to be a phone ringing in the background
as i my call comes no go ahead we're getting close to break go ahead with your question
i apologize but but the other thing that i wanted to bring up you know what let me unplug this other
phone well let me just ask dr wakefield to comment on that so the fda at one point did say you
shouldn't eat too much tuna fish because of mercury but they even backed off of that so it's
so it's suddenly like mercury is the the favorite element of the scientific medical corrupt
community what's what's up with that i'm told by the experts that mercury is second only to
plutonium on this planet as a as a toxin so um it's not safe in any form uh or in any dose there
are no safe levels no safe forms the idea that one's better than the other um we'll be right back
if you've ever wanted one of our best-selling generators but we're waiting for an offer so
crazy you couldn't refuse then you're not going to want to miss this exciting message here's why
our solar generators provide life-saving electrical power and unlike gas generators
solar generators run quietly emit no fumes and produce electricity from the sun so when the
lights go out you'll always have the power you need now here's the best part every year we
accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new we put them in a special spot
in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of each year we call them scratch and
dent units but they're really just like new each unit comes with a full factory warranty and
special bonuses you just won't believe don't wait they go fast go to scratchanddentsolar.com that's
scratchanddentsolar.com for the craziest offer we've ever made go to scratchanddentsolar.com
that's scratchanddentsolar.com you land in buenos aries then our shuttle to santa rosa
where a nicely furnished cabin with all amenities wi-fi executive food and wine and laundry service
awaits after a good night's sleep your adventure begins you're on a golden stag safari for big game
game but it's not africa it's argentina one-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo
huger bighorn rams wild boar and the biggest stag deer in south america all gold metal quality
all the action you can handle land rovers top rental guns with scopes all food beverages hunting
guides ground transportation included and more all more affordable than you can imagine the adventure
of a lifetime starts at goldenstagsafaris.com the big game hunting ranch goldenstagsafaris.com
injuries slow healing aches and pains constipation weakness fatigue are all common the older one gets
the progressive deterioration of the body that occurs almost universally the older one gets
can partly to significantly be prevented with conscientious attention to nutrition if the
hanzo men can play rugby in their 90s then it is possible for everyone in north america to
experience a more youthful life as well one key ingredient to warding off aging and reversing some
of it is the type and quality of protein consumed all protein foods or supplements you currently
consume are heat damaged destroying 50 to 75 percent of your ability to utilize the bodybuilding
amino acids one world way is not heat damaged and allows your body to utilize 100 of the amino acids
this feat no one else has achieved the results to your health can be amazing call 888-988-3325
that's 888-988-3325 or visit one world way.com that's one world w-h-e-y.com
and we're back on the alex jones show thank you again for joining us on our final segment today
and by the way don't miss the alex jones show sunday 4 to 6 pm central time and also
monday i know there will be some big breaking news monday on obamacare and some hidden
payoffs to big pharma that we have located in the obamacare so-called affordable health care act
which has made health care unaffordable for almost everyone but dr wakefield continues with us in the
studio here for this last segment so let's get right to the question of psychiatric drugs and
their links to violent shooters time and time again dr wakefield although i know perhaps
psychiatry obviously is not your specialty but you are well-trained m-d or you're skeptical
thinking scientist what are your thoughts on psychiatric drugs and violent shootings
well you know it's interesting because it comes it brings in the subject of autism again when
back in 1996 i got i was first introduced to this i don't remember the port arthur massacre in
tasmania a guy in the early morning shot over 40 people 45 people dead in a cafe and it was said
at the time that he had asperger syndrome high functioning autism in fact he didn't at all and
when you go back and read the psychiatric records from the prison psychiatrist who assessed him
there he had symptoms which specifically precluded asperger's in other words the common denominator
was not that they had a psychiatric or a an autistic spectrum disorder so i went back and
i reviewed so many of these cases that have occurred of multiple killings actions of mass
violence in schools or some shopping malls i'm looking for a common denominator it comes down
to this mic looking for patterns what is the pattern is it an autistic spectrum disorder
no is it a personality disorder no what was the common denominator was that they were all taking
psychotropic medications and in many cases psychotropic medications that were not licensed
not indicated for the particular problem that they had there is no site or there certainly
was at that time no psychotropic medication that could be used for treating asperger's and what we
now find is that in the last few years jansen pharmaceutical subsidiary of j and j abbott
laboratories and glaxo smith klein have been pushing these drugs off label to vulnerable
children in many cases and they've been sued by some states for the off-label marketing of their
drugs as well absolutely and i've seen this at first hand i've seen violence in children with
autism at first hand not because they're autistic but i believe because they're being pushed these
drugs off license uh for inducements like going to a gulf day or going to the spa it's absolutely
farcical and disgraceful that doctors have uh put children at risk giving them these powerful drugs
that were never indicated for the problems that they have and i believe that a large part of the
risk factor for these outbreaks of mass violence is the drugs that they're on well well said and
just to clarify when i say they they've been sued by the states i don't know if those you mentioned
have been sued but i know by and large big pharmaceutical companies have been sued time and
time those three have okay that's good to confirm one of the things we know about these drugs is
they tend to create a sense of cognitive detachment from reality so for example the columbine shooters
said that they believe they they were playing out a first-person shooter video game so some people
might start to blame the video games but i think more is the mindset the the the detachment in the
mind that's caused by the psychiatric drugs so is this detachment something that you've also seen as
a pattern in other violent outbursts well it's difficult to tell exactly what's going on in the
mind of people when they're having for example violent ideation are they playing a game do they
suddenly feel the world is against them with the ssris the second generation antidepressants it's
often violence and those people who have no history whatsoever of violent behavior they
suddenly have these violent outbursts and i've seen it in some of our patients and it stops when
we stop the drug and isn't it interesting that obama's 23 executive orders not one of them
looked at the link between psychiatric drugs and violent shootings so he may be ignoring
the actual cause of all this he may be i don't know you don't know but we do know that that's
a common denominator and to miss it out in trying to find the culprit for these outbreaks means that
there are going to be more and more of these attacks because they're not getting to the heart
the core problem that is causing them the first well they want more attacks dr wakefield they
want more attacks because it'll let them ban more firearms knives hammers you name it thank
you for being on the show dr wakefield retransmission begins now and thank you
for joining us today here on the alex jones show this is mike adams take care