Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
I spent some of the morning watching C-SPAN and Rand Paul grilling Hillary Clinton,
pointing out that if he was the president, he would have relieved her of her position.
We have that clip coming up. And that's the point. When quote, government screwed up in the past,
or in any other country for that matter, the people responsible for it resign or go to jail.
But nowadays, the answer is give us more funding. And that's what Hillary Clinton said.
That's why whenever FEMA ordered the police to stand down during Katrina on Bush's watch,
FEMA then got even more funding saying we need more power.
They've engineered that into the system. It's just an amazing level of corruption.
But you see, watching the Senate hearings with Hillary, only part of it is being covered.
Because our government armed the Libyan al-Qaeda rebels out of Saudi Arabia,
who first came from Saudi Arabia and other countries, into Benghazi two years ago,
to destabilize and take down Libya. They were on the BBC saying, next stop, Damascus, Syria.
They've been there. They've been given heat-seeking missiles.
Some numbers are as high as 15,000. Most numbers are around 12,000.
10,000 of those heat seekers, pretty high tech. Take down any jet airliner you want.
They've been attacking jet airliners, shooting them up, passenger liners.
And then the media thinks you're so stupid, they go, we have to give our rights up and
invade all over Africa and Algeria and Mali because al-Qaeda's there.
And then our criminal-occupied government uses that as a pretext with NATO and France
to invade Mali and Algeria and other areas. I mean, it's amazing. We predicted,
four years ago in the Obama deception, they would use al-Qaeda that they control
to invade all over Africa because we know how they operate. And we saw the buildup of AFRICON.
So the truth is 100% in plain sight. The truth is 100% in plain sight.
The truth is 100% in plain view, but it's so over the top, everyone would have to say,
you're right, Alex, we apologize. The globalists have hijacked our country around al-Qaeda.
And the media spins that and says, you're saying George W. Bush had a plunger at the World Trade
Center. You're saying everybody in the government, the guy that delivers letters to your post office
box, he's behind it. That's the games they play. No, criminal, globalist, cartel elements,
infiltrating the CIA, FBI, NSA, the National Security Council.
They financed the politicians that get into power, the foreign banks.
They have put their people in, and they're using al-Qaeda to destabilize and overthrow governments
or attack Western governments as a pretext for the Western government to then crack down
the general population. And I've been saying that for 11 years, and now it's all public.
Oh, don't worry about al-Qaeda. This is now for the general public.
So we're going to be breaking all of that down today. And then there's articles like
this out of CNS News. Former Special Forces Commander, top general, was US running guns
to Syrian rebels via Benghazi? CIA says no. General Boykin goes on to say that the evidence
points towards them doing this. Well, the evidence doesn't point towards it, it's on
record that our government, NATO, all run by the mega banks, on record, brought al-Qaeda
into Libya, then brought them into Syria, invaded from three different countries, and
have had Turkish artillery backing them up, and CIA commandos, and British commandos,
and Saudi Arabian commandos, in there, helping attack, over the last 20 plus months, Syria.
I mean, the Turkish ambassador was there, the missile cache was there, there was some
double cross, or they wanted to get rid of the witness to it, and they killed the ambassador
in order to stand down for eight hours. And the people they used to kill in the al-Qaeda
forces were the US certified, NATO certified security for Benghazi. Okay, that's what happened,
open and shut, period, done, and the whole government knows it.
Destroy the causes of many serious diseases, such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds,
flus, and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the ability to terminate entire
colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic
silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go to
supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off. That's
supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Fluoride up to 95%. Easy to set up and use. Doesn't require electricity. Purify water from
lakes, streams, ponds, and wells. This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is
key. Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
Propure is the best gravity fed filter out there. It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on Propure, but if you add the promo code
water at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at infowars.com. You can also call to order
888-253-3139. If you want an American company with American products made by Americans,
here is the Cow Ben Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for
years. These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that
are earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free
catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs.
This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap
makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance.
Rallying patriots worldwide. You're listening to the Alex Jones Show.
Welcome ladies and gentlemen. It is the 23rd day of January 2013 on this Wednesday edition.
Coming up at the bottom of the hour because we're tracking it live right now. We'll give
you the latest on Hillary Clinton's testimony to the Senate Committee. Rand Paul to Hillary
Clinton. If I were a president, I would have relieved you of your post. We're going to be
going over that. Former Special Forces Commander, retired General William G. Boykin,
who literally was at the heart of the CIA and black operations, is saying that he believes
that they were funding and giving missiles and weapons to Al Qaeda-based Syrian rebels.
Well, I mean, that's not even debatable. That's like saying, I believe the sun came up this
morning. I mean, it's New York Times, Associated Press, LA Times in the last six months, Council
on Foreign Relations. We told you about it 22 months ago when the whole thing started.
It's a plan to turn the entire Middle East over to Wahhabist, Al Qaeda run by Saudi Arabia,
itself run by the mega banks. So at the bottom of the hour, I'll do a special report on that
and give you the latest. In fact, we have a skeleton crew today. One of our guys is out
taking care of a sick child. It's in yesterday's stack. Can you guys re-pull the London Independent
and a couple others where the Prime Minister of Algeria is saying the West is behind these
stage terror attacks as a pretext to invade our countries? There's guys with blonde hair and blue
eyes attacking our facilities. And then they pull out and then the West gets to come in.
See, I've seen this over and over again. Operation Gladio, Ajax, Tonkin,
staging events are even having real attacks. Northwoods talks about shooting up Americans
in shopping malls and movie theaters and on the streets. Declassified in 2000, September 2000.
And the plan was killed by President Kennedy, but later given a new name and engaged him.
That's why we have to say, could these events be staged? And then when they have the telltale signs,
then it moves into, it's a probability they are, especially Colorado. I mean, that is cartoon level
where he's getting DARPA funding and mind control. He's got a top Air Force psychiatrist who'd been
the head of whole operations at entire bases in San Antonio. Over him, meeting with him multiple
times a week. They're talking about national security and the police don't want. It released
his workbook with her, where he reportedly was planning to do all this. You want me to keep going?
Witnesses of multiple shooters, all the rest of it. Him in the jail saying, I don't remember who
I am, obviously drugged out of his mind. I mean, we already knew this, but it came out in the LA
Times that Theodore Kaczynski, the Unabomber, was under CIA mind control. And it was declassified
that he had been a volunteer to MK Ultra and had disappeared into the program for close to 30
years. He entered it in the mid 60s as a PhD student, disappears for decades, and starts
bombing prominent scientists and people. And his letters are how we've got to exterminate
the majority of humanity or they're going to destroy the Earth, but the elite are planning
to kill us anyways, so we've got to stop that. I mean, what is this?
And the media is like, Alex Jones thinks it's mind control, no such thing. I mean,
they probably had more than 30 mainstream articles, Daily Beast, you name it. Time
Magazine saying for some reason, Jones went and watched Batman and found Sandy Hook in it,
and now says it's behind it. No, no, we said before Batman came out that from analyzing it
and the previous franchise, it is a film full of psychological triggers.
And then the movie comes out and Sandy Hook's in it. And then we find out hundreds of media people
were mailed Bain command charts showing the mass terror attack points like Sandy Hook and others.
They're like, well, this is bizarre. I know it's bizarre. This is the gang signs
the globalists also use to communicate with each other. I don't believe in all this,
they do. I don't go to Bohemian Grove and worship a big owl.
I'm not Jimmy Savelle, the top royal confidant, who it turns out is a Satanist and a mass child
molester running big children's charities and hanging out and having keys and the highest
national security clearances into the royal family and bragging, I supply them things.
And they've declared national security on that. They just declared national security on him,
quote, supplying things. He publicly brag at elite parties with the Prime Minister's
and the Queen and Prince Charles and all of them. And the guy is a devil worshiping pedophile.
And by the way, I've analyzed that the main banking structure is moving to Frankfurt,
Germany. This is high level blackmail by the European Illuminati against the British Empire.
High level wars going on. That's why this is being released now that he's dead.
This has been known for decades at the BBC where he worked. And they're now going,
you're gonna do what we say, we're gonna run the New World Order. Cuz the Skeksis are all battling
over the throne right now. The New World Order is almost complete. It's entering the endgame.
It's entering the endgame. And now they're gonna start battling over who gets the throne,
who gets the ring of Mordor, of Morgoth.
And you wonder why everything they do is so diabolical and so twisted and so
evil and so sick and so filthy. I mean, if you're a new listener and you're like, well,
who's Jimmy Savelle? Well, who's Jerry Sandusky? Raping children in front of people at high noon
in a field house, which is like the main entrance of an airport.
You've never been inside a field house. I mean, it's people coming and going constantly,
even at night, especially to college.
And then of course it came out higher, the whole top of the university was covering it up.
Of course, he was just the procurer of the children. You're like, man, Alex,
why are you telling us this? Because they're monsters, that's why. You don't get into the
club with these people unless you are very, very, very, very sick.
And I've talked a lot about this because he wrote about it. Hitler loved to go to the front
in Poland and France and then with Russia until they started getting beaten.
Then he pulled back to the wolf's lair, the wolf's den,
his forest bunkers. And he would sit there with big telescopes from 10 miles away.
But with a big telescope, crystal clear, watching people getting killed,
watching things burn, watching people jumping out of tall windows. And they say he would stay up
sometimes for days taking amphetamines and eating pastry after pastry. He could not draw himself
away from watching his bombers bomb and burn major cities. And he just described it as absolutely
beautiful. And so you need to figure out, folks, if you don't tie government down with the chains
of the Bill of Rights and Constitution, if you don't put government on a very short leash,
it will put you on one. And I just went off into,
and I'll cover it at the bottom of the hour after I get to Nightline at the bottom of the hour.
I heard that last week, but then I was leaving town Thursday night to go out to the desert to
do some hiking with my son and others. And would have brought my daughter, they're too
little to hike four miles up a mountain. I'm surprised he did it, he did a pretty good job.
We were ready to turn back anytime he wanted to, but he said he wanted to go to the top.
Rob Dew's son, who's even younger, climbed it too. So I heard you had Nightline
did a piece on you, and I just figured it would be the piece they did two and a half years ago.
And it is the old piece, but they added some new stuff to it.
And it's another window into the mindset of these guys, because in the piece coming up,
and I'm gonna recap this, you'll notice that he says, now I say, well, first you guys said
there wasn't a world government. And now you're just saying, well, it's not a bad world government.
And he goes, I'm not even saying there is a world government. Like what he says is what makes
reality. Like when your child tells you, I didn't drink milk out of the jug, and you've got a
mustache, I just saw you do it. Don't lie to me. And it's the same thing, and I say, that's why
you're discredited. See, what you don't know is, 30 minutes before, they wanted to go shoot outside
of the local park. 30 minutes before, we're in my office, right in out there, with a bunch of clips
lined up of world leaders describing world government, congressional record on world government,
CFR quotes, where they said it, what bi-monthly foreign affairs journal they said it.
And I had it all for him, and he watched a few clips, and he goes, well, that's a different
world government. That's a good world government, not the world government you're talking about.
So 30 minutes later, I'm out there in a park where they wanna do a different part of the interview.
And I go, first you say there's no world government, now you're saying it's not a bad
world government, it's a different world government. He goes, no, I'm not even agreeing
that there is one. And that's why I say, that's why you're discredited.
But people watching that, see, I'm talking to him like he's a real person. And then he said,
I went to dinner with him and I was nice. So that discredits me cuz I'm not this wild man
in person. I was trying as a human to communicate with them cuz the guy's the host of ABC Nightly
News. And that's still got four or five million viewers a night.
That's still got some of the big old numbers of Dinosaur Media, one of the only bastions
of it. Nightline has got two or three million. And I'm sitting there, and I'm sitting there
like, and then they use that in the piece like, behind the scenes he was nice. And look,
here he is throwing a football and he doesn't know anybody's watching. And my memory serves,
they go, what's this football? You play football like that was bad. I go, yeah, with my son.
We're like, here, let's toss it. I mean, they knew that that was being videotaped.
They imply that I was secretly throwing a football. I mean, it's bizarre.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters like Hurricane
Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous
economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods Direct, we hear from
customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food
on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late. I can warn you,
but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today,
or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply. It's the best tasting,
non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on eFoods Direct. Feeling like there are too many pressures and demands
on you? Losing sleep, worrying about tests and schoolwork, even on the run because your schedule
is just too busy? You may be under too much stress, and it may be affecting your mind.
Get your mental edge back with Neutropic Mind Power from mindregard.com.
Neutropic Mind Power is not a drug, but a natural supplement. Its 12 powerful ingredients are
natural and non-GMO, plus it's gluten-free, wheat-free, and formulated by Americans for
Americans by an NSF-certified laboratory. Neutropic Mind Power is available at mindregard.com
spelled M-I-N-D-R-E-G-A-R-D.com and comes with a 100% money-back guarantee. Free your mind with
Neutropic Mind Power, a cognitive supplement from mindregard.com. Mindregard, clearly see
tomorrow and yesterday, today. Making the right decisions is a challenge to investors. Are we
going to see economic growth, slide into a recession, or at worst, depression? Hi, Ted
Anderson from Midas Resources. We all know when a company acts irresponsibly, divesting ourselves
in a move towards safety is prudent. When the market becomes volatile, US Treasuries are a safe
haven. But what do you do when the US government overextends itself and spends beyond its means?
Many investors are turning toward gold as a common sense alternative to traditional paper investments.
Midas Resources has put together a powerful book titled 10 Reasons to Own Gold, discussing costs,
benefits, risks, featuring full-color illustrations, weights, and measures. The book
is free and can be yours by calling 800-686-2237. Paper investments are dwarfed by gold's 6,000-year
history. Discover how gold may be right for you and your IRA by calling 800-686-2237. Whether
buying or it's time for you to sell, the book is free. Call 800-686-2237. We can buy GMOs stressed
out about money and blasted by the electric environment. Hi, I'm Pastor Jenny and that was
the state I was in back in 2010. Then I learned about RNA drops. I learned that 97% of my DNA
that scientists have called junk is actually packed with millions of gene switches that play
a critical role in controlling how my cells, organs, and other tissues behave. I learned
I don't have to put up with disease decay or decline like I'd been conditioned to believe.
I began taking RNA drops, a 100% natural formula designed to turn on those switches and provide
me with amazing health and joy. Learn more about RNA drops and order a free sample today.
Visit RNAfreesample.com. That's RNAfreesample.com or call toll-free 888-577-3703. Pay only shipping
and handling for a free 30-day supply of RNA drops. Get the information you need and the
health you want at RNAfreesample.com.
And when the system honors people that are subservient and go along to get along,
it creates a perfect environment for the pathogen of very despotic megalomaniacal
tyranny and tyrants to take control. And that's history. And that's what's so frustrating is that
I sat there this morning for about an hour playing with my four-year-old daughter.
And playing with the stuffed animals and playing with my little pony and playing hide-and-go-seek.
And I sat there while she was in her room after about an hour of playing with her. And I was
going to tell her I had to go. I knew she was going to beg me not to leave. And I just thought,
how do I take this stillness, this understanding that I have right now of how the world works
and this deep sorrow and pain that is such a strength? And how do I transmit that and
decipher that and encode that in words so that the general public can understand what I'm saying?
But I know that by saying that fathers and mothers and grandmothers and grandfathers
and brothers and sisters and sons and daughters, once the man, twice the child taking care of
their parents, you know what I'm talking about, that all I wanna do is protect her.
All I wanna do is have a good world for her. All I wanna do is lift up others so that she can
commune with them and her grandchildren with their grandchildren and their grandchildren with
their great-great-grandchildren. And it hurts me to my core that humanity may not make it.
We may not get to the point of a type one civilization, meaning we could survive if
this planet was destroyed, and the incredible destiny that God has for us. If we don't stand
up and do the right thing, God gave us a brain, God gave us a soul, a heart, and the power of
his image as creators to build amazing things. And I know how great humanity is.
And I can't imagine the world we would be in if the leaders of this planet were actually trying
to empower humanity. They claim all day that their mission is to empower people. They claim
all day, I watch clips, I've already seen them, but I watched a compilation
at about 7 AM this morning of Joe Biden, we have it, if we have time later, we're gonna play it.
Joe Biden, we have it, if we have time later, we're gonna play it.
Of Joe Biden with relish, I mean, when you have discernment, it's not even discernment,
anybody would see it. The relish he has when he talks about these beautiful children,
shawl, shot up, just riddled with holes, riddled with holes. And he's clearly using it,
pressing on the wound, putting salt in the wound, feeding off of it.
I know his history, I know his background, I know how evil he is, I know how he works to
deindustrialize America. I know how bad these guys are, I know their mindset, their code.
And he's sitting there just sticking his finger in the wound like a bullet hole.
And you say, I know it hurts. We finally, the image of these four-year-olds aren't even four.
All shot up full of bullet holes. This with the parents, we're gonna get this done. And I realize
they got drones killing in one country alone last year, 200 plus kids, Pakistan. Just seeing all
collateral damage and putting al-Qaeda in Libya and Syria, 40,000 dead at least.
Lining up blacks, videos of black men, women and children with al-Qaeda, because it's cheaper to
use machetes. And plus they have more fun doing it, just hacking them up, just hacking their
noses off, hacking their arms as they beg. I mean, stuff we won't even show you, it's on YouTube.
They try to take it down as fast as they can, taking Christians and throwing them off
five-story buildings and chopping their heads off and celebrating and saying,
we're gonna destroy America, a la Akbar 9-11. We're coming, we've got the missiles,
we're gonna kill you next. And our government, foreign banks, that's who they are, the occupiers,
are doing this. And then I go and TSA wants me to take my shoes off and grope me to see if I'm
al-Qaeda. I mean, I'm like, look, game over, joke over, scam over, no, no, no, no.
And I realized why I blew up at Piers Morgan, I am physically angry.
And not even at a hate level, it's more of just the anger of trying to burst through a foot of
ice that you're trapped under. If you fall through a frozen lake, I mean, it's that kind of anger.
I want out of here, I don't like this, get off my back. It's that feeling where two or three bullies
are beating you up, and they get you down and they got you tackled. And you get beyond mad,
you go, these people aren't gonna be on me in a minute. And you just decide to get up and stomp
them. It's that kind of feeling like, I don't care anymore what happens to me. You people want
to abuse children. You're a bunch of sick filth, and I will not stand here and watch you like
ghouls use those little kids' deaths to disarm the American people. By the way, Australia took
everything but single shot bolt action. They're now set to ban those. It's always the same story.
We'll be back. We're on the march. The empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action.
Tyranny is here. The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality.
It really says that the state is God. The United States is now recognized globally
as one of the most impressive police states on earth. This film conclusively proves the
existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being expanded nationwide. This documentary
exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all powerful shadow state.
Police state four chronicles the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen.
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship, body scammers, sound cameras,
citizen spies, stage terror and cameras on every street corner. It's only the beginning of the New
World Order's hellish plan. The police state isn't coming. It's here. Secure your copy today
at info wars.com or see it online in the highest quality at prisonplanet.tv.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our immunity
and health. At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection
of silver based products. Our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver
solutions, our two ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well as our all natural silver
soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic
gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface. But rather,
we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera
to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver based products
are best for you. That's www.silverlungs.com. The new year is a great time to take charge of
your health and wellness. Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a
breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or
ionic silver. Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses,
infections, yeast and molds. Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly
effective for water purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune
system support, and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to
www.supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's www.supernaturalsilver.com. Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
That's www.supernaturalsilver.com.
dot com is really on top of it. They're not bringing up, hey, why did our government use
al-Qaeda to overthrow Libya to begin with?
I mean, it's on record that NATO is arming them, and our military is the heart of NATO.
So we need to be honest with ourselves about this, because if all this information is forced
out there into the general consciousness and general awareness, it's game over. The establishment
thinks you're so unconscious, so stupid, they're using real al-Qaeda out of Saudi Arabia, Qatar
and other countries, brought in over two years ago to Libya to start a almost year-long civil
war with air raids and bombings of major cities and laying waste to whole neighborhoods.
And it was called humanitarian because Obama is a Peace Prize winner. Just amazing. And
then they use that same group and publicly exported them to Turkey, Jordan, and other
areas to have them infiltrate the country publicly in attack. And they've got, this
has been admitted for over a year in mainstream media, but it's back in the newspaper that
Western commandos are advising them and training them. I mean, there are US bases in Turkey
right on the border, and then the Syrians battle back against them.
And so they open up for a few weeks with artillery to clear the area to send in the jihadis.
And then I've seen some conservatives go, well, good, we got Arabs killing Arabs. And
that's some bad karma right there. I don't mean karma in the Indian fashion, but you
reap what you sow, what comes around goes around. I mean, really? That kind of so-called
conservative is not a conservative.
They are a fascistic, warped, dehumanizing person who has visions of power and reflected
glory by smart bombs and artillery. I bet you a million dollars if you took one of those
so-called good old boys, cuz most of them aren't really good old boys. And you stuck
a gun in their hand and lined up ten little Afghan kids with snot coming out their nose
or little eyes looking up at you.
So ignorant that most of them can't even find the US on a map. I mean, these are like cavemen.
I bet you those people would not have the nerve to pull the trigger on one of those
kids, much less all ten of them. And if they did, they'd be basket cases and commit suicide
later, like our troops do, by the way.
You're not meant to go and kill a bunch of innocent kids. Your body, unless you're a
full-born psychopath, genetically, if you're not totally evil and totally given over to
evil from birth, doing evil things like that will destroy you. You will destroy yourself.
Your body will hit the self-destruct switch. When you do good, you feel empowered and the
universe opens up to you. When you do evil, you destroy yourself. That's a universal law.
You don't have to even believe in God to know that that's the case.
And our military men and women, most of them got in because they were poor or they had
military background families or they genuinely cared about society and wanted to help. A
small percentage, they become the contractors in a lot of cases, enjoy psychopathic killing.
It's a place where they can go out and kill and get paid to do it. And they believe it's
manly. Well, it might be manly if you've got to fight for your tribe to fight other men.
But it is not manly to be like basically aliens from another planet with incredibly super
high-tech weapons to come into Stone Age areas with people that don't even know who you are
or your country is. They've done studies who will fight you just because they're still
humans.
They're primitive humans, but they still have their human programming. If there are invaders,
I better fight them, which is what any group of humans has always done. And the globalist
hire a bunch of Muslim terrorists to stage attacks, to carry out real attacks, or to
take the Blamford attacks to attack the West so they can take all of our liberties.
And I'm already getting into Benghazi now. We got two big guests today. We have Dr.
Jim Garib, who's run the program to save 30 plus thousand Chinese girls. He's been nominated
for the Nobel Prize. He says he's talked to a top military retired officer who told him
that Obama is doing a litmus test, will you fire on US citizens?
Now I believe he talked to this person, they told him that. In the article he wrote about
it, adds the fact that they're buying a billion six bullets, armored vehicles, and the new
army manuals. And so 10 say, train them to court in cities, confiscate guns, and shoot
Americans. I can play ABC Nightly News in Katrina with the army officer saying, if you
don't turn your guns in, we kill Americans.
And by the way, a lot of that went on. It's the same ABC piece where the police chief
says, all the guns will be taken, no one will be allowed to be armed. You just type in gun
confiscation, New Orleans, there's NRA videos with millions of views on YouTube. If you're
a new listener, I'm not gonna play it again, I've probably played it 100 times in the last
six, seven years since Katrina, I'm not playing it again.
You know it's there. For a couple of weeks, people denied gun confiscation was even happening.
So he's gonna be joining us and then the main host of the Young Turks, Sink, is gonna be
coming on the broadcast. We look forward to that for a lively discussion. And if we have
time while he's on, Melissa Melton, I told her, one of our reporters and researchers,
she actually in college, part of her degree is stats. So I said, listen, I just guesstimated
off these FBI numbers, 49% and 21% drop in overall violent crime and gun crime.
So I had her spend the last couple days breaking it down at FBI.gov. She's trying to export
the video right now for radio. Listeners will post on Infowars, where we can show you that
indeed my mental math was correct. Of course, I also saw them flash the numbers on Fox News
and went and double checked it.
They didn't even show the graphs. We're gonna show all those off FBI.gov. 49% drop, and
I was wrong. I misunderstood it when I saw it on Fox. When I looked at the numbers myself,
they just showed numbers. It's 49 in violent crime total in the last 20 years since 1991
because the numbers are always about a year behind.
Last numbers we have is 11, so they say since 1991. And then we have the other numbers.
It's even higher. Illegal acts with guns has gone on even more because America's swimming
in guns. Criminals have got their heads down. They go into immigrant areas where they know
people aren't armed. The Chinese triads go and feed on the Chinese immigrants they know
don't have a gun culture. The Mexican mafia goes and feeds on the poor Mexicans they know
most of them don't have guns.
Chicago, New York where the guns have been taken, the correct criminals go and feed on
you and your family. I mean criminals do not do home invasions. I was looking at the numbers.
It was over 100 times more common in Chicago than say in a small town in West Texas or
even a big city like Dallas. I mean, they don't home invade while you're there. They
make sure you're not there and then they still don't cuz I mean every day I read in the back
of the paper where people kill somebody in their house.
These criminals are so dumb the ones that are dumb enough in her house. They'll be like
stop I have a gun and they keep coming with a machete or whatever. And they're always
whacked out on drugs and they die. The criminals are on the run and that's why they're big
overlord criminals. The big daddy criminals like Chicago mob boss, the godfather as he's
called, Emanuel and Obama.
Their instinct is don't hurt our criminal brethren. And they want the fear, they want
to lock doors. They want you to have to call for more police which they then hire their
own criminals to eat and then dominate you. They don't like the fact that most police
are awake now. They don't like the fact that most forces aren't corrupt in the country.
They want to convert us to a mafia system where they're above the law and safe and our
gun culture is winning and taking over. Even Clinton said this last week, I'm yet to play
the video, it was up at mfallwars.com.
So they understand this is a desperate gamble for them. They've gotta kill the gun culture
now because it's cancer to them, it's growing. This is a big surgery, they don't know they're
gonna make it. They're in their doctor, can we cut out the Constitution? Rangel said it's
our ultimate goal to get over the Constitution and Southerners.
I love how they try to say it's Southerners that want guns. Folks, it's people all over
this country want guns. I just saw a Tiananmen Square video from one of the hundreds of gun
rallies of people with guns at the capitals, loaded in many cases, exercising the right.
See, the system can't stand that. They wanna shame you and act like guns are already illegal.
So when the carpet cleaners at your house, they call the cops on you. That's what these
new laws they're proposing and new executive orders say is that if someone feels threatened
by a gun at your house, go ahead and call the cops.
They'll go ahead and take your guns, and then they'll make you go to a psychological evaluation.
And they say just wanting guns is a sign of mental illness or not trusting government.
Well, then America was founded on mental illness, and then we just got all the wealth and all
the power cuz we had the liberty. I guess mental illness, you know what, if that's crazy,
throw me in there, okay? You're right, you control free criminals, I absolutely hate
you and know who you are, and I want nothing to do with you.
And if you call that crazy, you bet I am. I'm as crazy as the day is long, you bet.
Now let's go to this piece. This is Nightline. And this was two and a half years ago they
came here. And you notice they don't even say, at least on the version I saw, yeah,
and point out this is two and a half years old.
It's like, we went and talked to Alex. And then they cut in the Piers Morgan appearance.
And at the end they say, he'll now be under a lot of scrutiny, implying it was evil for
me to say I have 50 guns. It was just a guesstimation, as if, my gosh, he's dangerous.
And then they show me throwing the football. And then they imply, he's not always this
crazy in person, it's all an act. Because there's a football in the back of the car
and we're getting in it.
They're like, you got a football, what's that? You relax. I go, well, yeah, of course I do.
I have children, it's my son's football. And I'm like, here, you wanna catch it? And they
cut it in going, when he didn't know the camera was rolling, he was playing football. That's
not true.
And then they say, he talked about many things with us not related to the New World Order.
Talked about their family, stuff like that, went to dinner with them. I've told that story.
But the point is, well, let's go ahead and start the piece. Here is Nightline implying
I take bits and pieces. Here's that clip.
We begin with America and its guns. As President Obama prepares to announce his sweeping plan
to curb gun violence tomorrow.
It paused, it paused. Back to the start, I've gotta just analyze the whole thing. I'm sorry,
it'll take a few segments. Talk about a woman who loves the sound of her voice.
America's guns, President Obama, President Obama. It's like some kind of weird confidence
game. These people are a joke, reading off her teleprompter. And then they cut to the
host of ABC Nightline as you came down here.
And again, listen to this. And then they say, hey, that CNN piece about one child policies,
that was tongue in cheeky, jokey. And you read the article, no, it wasn't. They just
held turning like, yeah, drones are killing people. It's real cool, yeah. Yeah, we're
setting up checkpoints on the highway to take blood, see, it's all done.
That's part of their psych warfare. Everything's fine, see. Let's go back to the clip. Here
it is.
We begin with America and its guns. As President Obama prepares to announce his sweeping plan
to curb gun violence tomorrow. Across the country, millions have already rushed out
to buy a record number of new guns. And one man who thinks that's a very good thing, radio
shock jock, Alex Jones.
He made national headlines last week with a fiery pro-gun tirade that quickly-
Backing up a few seconds, thank you. I'm a shock jock cuz, I mean, I think it's shocking
that Rangel says we've got to overcome the Constitution and that Southerners are just
bad people, period.
I mean, wow. Imagine if he said Northeasterners, they're trash. I mean, it's just, it's ridiculous.
And the Constitution is bad. I mean, Australian gun grabbers target bolt action rifles. They
always take the semi-autos first, then the handguns, then the pistols, then the bolt
actions, then the single shot.
They want all guns turned in. We knew that was coming, they do that everywhere. This
is how they do it. See, I find that shocking. I find it shocking that they pass the NDAA
to secretly arrest and kill and disappear US citizens. I find it shocking that mega
banks have been caught laundering hundreds of billions of dollars of drug money and don't
get in trouble.
But see, I'm a shock jock cuz I'm here going, wake up America, we're going into tyranny.
But they just want you to be easy and cool and go watch a sitcom, have a martini. Hey
man, everything's fine. I'm here to get you out of your coma. You see, that's why it was
so shocking.
They thought I was gonna come on and debate the First Amendment and should he be deported
and they wanted talking points and we're gonna stick to this, aren't we? And he had Alan
Dershowitz ready in the next segment. I went off the script, folks. It wasn't, they got
me on there cuz they knew I'd blow up.
They picked that up and broadcast that everywhere before they realized, wait a minute, this
is actually waking people up, which it did, see. No weapon formed against us will prosper.
Let's go back to Nightline with a recycled, re-edited piece. Here it is.
Headlines last week with a fiery pro-gun tirade that quickly went viral. And that's not all
he's got to say. Here's ABC's Dan Harris.
Are you for Hitler or against Hitler? Whatever they say is the opposite. They never tell
me.
Let's just back it up to, I mean, what does that even mean? My point was you're either
for Stalin or against Stalin. You're either for Hitler or against Hitler. You're either
against this New World Order and all this ternary, or you're either for it or you're
against it.
It's very simple, but they just have a thing about Hitler. So people go, Hitler. I saw
a piece David Knight did. It was one of the crew about Martin Luther King, it was Mike
Adams. Martin Luther King and how he wouldn't support Obama. And I saw people commenting
in there and they were serious. They go, are they bashing Martin Luther King in this piece?
Because at the end, Mike Adams says America doesn't want kings anymore. And we're talking
about King George III and we don't want King Obama.
And then people thought it was code against Martin Luther King. I mean, whoa, New World
Order is coming down on people at a million miles an hour and people are looking for codes.
But I'm gonna shut up though, cuz I wanna break here in a minute and a half. Let's start
with this clip. Here it is.
Are you for Hitler or against Hitler? Whatever they say is the opposite. They never tell
the truth. Tonight as millions of Americans worry about the government taking away their
guns, this man, Alex Jones, is pushing a lot of buttons.
And I'm here to tell you, 1776 will commence again if you try to take our firearms. We
will not relinquish them. Do you understand? The republic will rise again when you attempt
to take our guns.
When Jones went on CNN's Piers Morgan Tonight, to discuss gun control in the wake of the
Sandy Hook massacre, he created a sensation. This video went massively viral.
And I wanna say this right here. You think you're a tough guy? Have me back with a boxing
ring in here.
But who is Alex Jones?
We've got ABC Nightly News slash Nightline here.
Despite his mistrust of the so-called mainstream media, Jones agreed to let us into his world
for a day.
Hey, we're just soldiers looking across each other on the picket line here.
America has been captured. America is being robbed. We are now being looted like a third
world nation. Well, I'm not gonna sit down and shut up.
Jones is arguably the nation's premier purveyor of what could be called paranoia porn.
All right, applause. Yeah, we were paranoid porn pushers when we said they were gonna
come for your guns. We were paranoid porn pushers when we said that they would raise
taxes on poor people, which they've now done.
We were paranoid porn pushers when we said foreign countries would take their gold out
of the US. It's all happening, all happening.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not gonna wanna miss this exciting message.
Here's why. Our solar generators provide life-saving electrical power. And unlike gas generators,
solar generators run quietly, emit no fumes, and produce electricity from the sun. So when
the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part. Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't
sell as new. We put them in a special spot in our warehouse, and we discount them heavily
at the end of each year. We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like
new. Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait, they go fast. Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com. For the craziest
offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
American gardeners and fellow patriots, make the right choice with your money, time, and
your family food supply. Choose 100% pure heirloom seeds in the survival seed vault
from mypatriotsupply.com. Why spend more? The survival seed vault from mypatriotsupply.com
is only $37.95 and includes 20 varieties of pure, hardy, easy to grow heirloom seeds.
Yes, only $37.95, that's 70% less than our competitors. You could buy three survival
seed vaults for less than one of theirs. The survival seed vault from mypatriotsupply.com
includes detailed planting and seed saving instructions and ships same day. Plus, all
orders over $49 ship free. Mypatriotsupply.com is American owned by patriots like you, passionate
about freedom and preparedness. Call now, 866-229-0927, that's 866-229-0927 or discover
more emergency preparedness items when you order at mypatriotsupply.com. Choose the original,
choose the survival seed vault at mypatriotsupply.com. We all know that Berkey water purification
systems are the most trusted name in water filtration. As an authorized Berkey dealer
for over six years and serving thousands of satisfied customers, the Berkey guy offers
amazing specials for Berkey water filtration systems. The Berkey light systems include
a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable black purification elements that purify water
by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria, cysts and parasites to non-detectable levels
and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides. Order the Berkey light system
today complete with two black Berkey elements for only $231 and the Berkey guy will ship
your order free of charge. With the purchase of a Berkey light, the Berkey guy is also offering
a set of fluoride and arsenic filters for only $39.99. That's over 30% off the retail
price. Call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653. That's 1-877-886-3653 or order online at goberkey.com.
That's goberkey.com today. Ease the T-Rex of political talk. Alex Jones on the GCN radio
network. Don't forget, ladies and gentlemen, this broadcast and our entire news organization
is funded by American patriots like you and not by government or Rockefeller funds stolen
from taxpayers like NPR and others. So be sure and buy the books, the videos, the new
Come and Take It best-selling T-shirt at infowarstore.com. And be sure to get the best gravity-fed stainless
steel filters out there at infowarstore.com. Propure, 10% off the already lowest price
out there with the promo code water. Infowarstore.com or infowarshop.com are linked through at prisonplanet.com
or prisonplanet.tv right over to the shopping cart. And again, I wanna thank everybody for
their support out there. We could not do it without you and also supporting our sponsors.
We have some new skateboards that we got contacted. I shouldn't even talk about this yet, but
the point is they're up there on the site. So I need to discuss that probably at another
point. Great way to wake people up is to have skateboards with infowars.com and the Alien
Workshop artwork on it.
Okay, let's get back to the night line and I gotta get into Benghazi after this guest
comes on. And we got the head of the Young Turks coming on the broadcast here today and
a lot of other important economic news. But first, let's go ahead and go back to the night
line piece. Here it is.
The truth strikes back. I'm live in 30 seconds. All right. Out of his studios near Austin,
Texas, his radio show and webcast reach an estimated 1 million people a day.
This federal intrusion is out of control.
And on YouTube and elsewhere, Jones estimates 200 million people have seen his various documentaries.
No, that's one YouTube channel.
You're taking our destiny back. You're not our gods or our masters.
With titles like The Fall of the Republic, Endgame, Blueprint for Global Enslavement
and The Obama Deception.
Do you actually believe everything you say?
I believe all of it, absolutely. What I'm telling is the truth.
None of it is, you know, a shtick, a show at all?
No, it's all true.
You think Obama is a criminal?
Barack Obama is definitely an unconstitutional criminal.
Jones espouses a litany of conspiracy theories, although he thinks that term belittles his
reporting.
FEMA is running concentration camps?
Shutting them up.
They have designated sports stadiums. They have designated fields for the American people.
The manuals are public. I gave them to him.
The government's poisoning the water?
Absolutely. I have all these other government documents where the government...
Hit pause.
And again, I sat there and showed them the book, showed them the clothes, showed them
the plans, and they didn't want to look at it.
So they cut all that out when I'm giving proof.
Just this guy's crazy.
Next, they're going to say they injected black people with syphilis.
Oh, they did that.
Next, they're going to say that they and a bunch of kids just got paralyzed again from
the Bill Gates meningitis shots.
Oh, never mind.
Oh, next they'll say they radiated the troops and killed a bunch of them.
Oh, they did that.
Next, they'll say they sterilized a half million women without their consent.
Next, they're going to say that the troops were exposed to sarin gas and it got covered
up in the Gulf War, and tens of thousands died.
Oh, that happened.
Let's go back to it.
Here it is.
Government think tanks propose poisoning the water to dumb down the population, make it
more easily manageable.
9-11 was an inside job?
Yes, 9-11 was an inside job.
It was a staged event to launch the Iraq war and to set up a domestic police state here
in the United States.
All I'm calling for is a real investigation, and the people of Oklahoma City have been
calling for an investigation.
Jones, who's 38, got his start with a local cable access show in the 1990s.
He now has a huge fan base, which at various times has included celebrities like Willie
Nelson, Jesse Ventura, Charlie Sheen.
We want our country back, Mr. President.
I'm calling on each and every American citizen to wake up, stand up, and demand the truth.
And reality stars Spencer Pratt and Heidi Montag.
Spencer Pratt, good to have you on with us today.
Thank you so much.
I'm so honored to be on with you.
You are a true legend, a true man.
All right.
That's enough.
The whole video's online.
It's called The Return of Alex Jones, but I mean, I didn't have time to get to it where
I'm throwing the football.
We'll have to play it later.
It's like, this is secret footage of him throwing a football.
I mean, it's just unbelievable hit piece.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
You prepare by purchasing gold, food, and firearms, but if you don't have a home security
system, then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection.
When you're sleeping or away from home, who's watching out for intruders?
Check out Simply Safe.
It's a new do-it-yourself home security system that is completely wireless.
Go to GetSimplySafe.com.
Simply Safe is independent and off the grid.
It runs on battery power, so even if the grid goes down, you are protected.
It's completely customizable, so you can use it in your home, business, boat, trailer,
storage unit, or shed.
GetSimplySafe.com.
Simply Safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes, so there's no
need to let a stranger into your home.
If you move or need to relocate, you can take the system with you wherever you go.
You aren't always at home, but Simply Safe will stand guard, protecting your property
24 hours a day, seven days a week.
Again, that's GetSimplySafe.com.
Waging war on corruption.
Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Earlier in the last hour, I said our guest has saved 35,000.
That was an old number.
It's 45,000 Chinese girls.
They estimate there's something like 20-something million more men in China.
Last time I saw, it may even be higher than there are women, because they're killing the
young women.
Supposed to be about 51% women.
Women live a little bit longer, so that goes into the actuary, but also, there's slightly
more.
If you do international studies, baby girls born than baby boys.
Kind of something God designed in there, so there's more women out there.
So we can have a leg up as a mammalian species, but that's a side issue.
Again, Alex Jones here.
Thanks for joining us, Dr. James Garrow, PhD.
Well-known, I've heard of him many times, Canadian teacher and businessman who founded
a big institute in China back in the 60s, discovered how they were killing the children
with the one-child policy, which is now on record.
In fact, his work helped expose that.
He's coming up in the next segment, because he was told by a retired high-level military
officer that the litmus test is, will you fire on US citizens?
And I just thought, I probably should have done more research, not more research, more.
That's not the work, cuz I've done the research.
I should have done more polling data and sources to show you here, because I can show you all
the army manuals where they're training for gun confiscation.
I can show you all of that where they're training to shoot Americans.
I mean, that's on the news now.
So you understand, it's not just him talking to this source we're gonna try to find out
about.
It's that it's already hiding in plain view.
And the 1.6 billion bullets and the end deposit commentatas and the troops on the streets
and all the rest of it, that's coming up in the next segment.
He'll be with us for about 35, 40 minutes.
And then I will get into Benghazi, cuz that's very important.
And I wanna break down what's really behind that.
I mentioned some of it last hour, but it's key that's coming up.
And then I'm seeing articles like this every two or three days, well, actually every day,
really.
Cuz every couple days I'll see two or three at one time, so I guess it's about every day.
There's probably seven of these stories a week I'd have to guesstimate.
Elementary school girl threatened with arrest over paper gun.
And you hear about people saying, career day, right about your dad or mom.
Well, my dad's in the Marines, here's a picture of him with his M-16.
Boom, you're arrested, take it in for psychiatric questioning as a 10-year-old.
Doesn't matter, you're the star quarterback or whatever, I've never been in trouble.
It's just crazy, or you bring a Dixie plastic knife to spread butter, your mother drops
in the lunchbox.
My mother did that, boom, you're arrested.
But government stomps around in Darth Vader outfits all day.
Elementary school girl threatened with arrest over paper gun hysteria and aftermath of Sandy
Hook reaches new heights.
That's an Infowars.com article out of Philadelphia Elementary.
Now, of course, in Philadelphia, came out five years ago, they've got laptops they give
you, watching you at home.
And they're the ones that announced that, they're very proud of it.
We play the clubs for the teachers doing interviews, that's how it broke going, yeah, we watch
you when you're at home, what you're doing, look out.
Like there's Santa Claus or Demon Claus or something.
This is the total demonization of a boy's playing with an orange and green Nerf gun
in his front yard with kids, SWAT team is called.
The anti-gunners are so anti-gun, they say they don't believe boys should be able to
play with guns.
You hear about kids getting in trouble for making bang bang, using their fingers as a
gun.
But the so-called leftists who are really authoritarians, they want checkpoints, they
want a billion six bullets, they want armored vehicles, they want TSA hands on the pants.
They wanna bomb Benghazi and bomb Syria, they wanna do all this, they love force.
Some Belgrade, go after the Serbs, but that cuz it's loving when they do it, they love
force.
I mean, you know these people when they see an orange gun and kids running around the
front yard, you see everywhere.
You know that they know that's not a real gun when they see a six year old doing it
and they call the police.
It's like neighbors in Oklahoma saw the upstanding middle class families, three year old pee
up against a tree in the front yard.
They came and they gave them a ticket and threatened them with arrest and stuff, and
they fired that cop and they should have.
I mean everybody knows that three year olds pee in the yard, but again it's this idea
of get us all in the system, get us in trouble.
I mean, fucks, I'll be honest with you, I pee in my backyard, I mean who doesn't?
Of course this was in the front yard, I don't know.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy.
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e Foods Direct.
Tons of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu, and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold, and food poisoning, and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day, while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as stress, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus, and
other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
Visit supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth-friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now.
Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, we are into the second hour of worldwide broadcast.
The main host of the Young Turks, Sink, is going to be joining us in the next hour.
Coming up in about 30, 40 minutes.
I'm going to break down the latest on what really happened in Benghazi and the aftermath
of Hillary Clinton's ridiculous testimony and Rand Paul saying that if he was Obama,
she should have been relieved of her office, of her position.
I mean, they're all in on it.
They ordered a stand down in Benghazi to cover up what was really happening there.
Eight hours.
Their own Al-Qaeda security they hired to run Benghazi are the ones that killed them.
I mean, this is incredible.
And none of the senators will bring that up.
I mean, it's hiding in plain view, but their whole narrative falls apart.
And they can't take our rights anymore if they point out that elements of the government,
criminal elements, are running Al-Qaeda.
Not the whole government.
See, they go, you're a 9-11 truther.
You're not saying there's not any Muslim extremists.
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm saying our government uses them to take down countries and uses them to then menace
America and take our liberties.
That's coming up.
Now Dr. James Garrow, PhD, is a Canadian teacher and businessman.
And in 1968, he founded the Bethune Institute, legendary language school, the People's Republic
of China, named after the Canadian surgeon, Dr. Norman Bethune.
I think I'm pronouncing that right.
One day in 2000, Dr. Jim Garrow, executive director of the institute's popular Pink Pagoda
schools in China, found his assistant weeping.
The woman told him how her sister's husband was insisting that the couple's newborn daughter
be smothered to make way for a son under China's one-child policy.
And this has now all been confirmed.
Years ago, they would deny it.
Garrow's promised to help and was able to place the infant with an adoptive couple.
That's why you see so many Chinese girls in America now, mainly adopted by evil white
people, of course, because all whites are evil, according to people like, I've got a
bizarre Daily Beast article here, we're gonna get to later, where they, well, just wait
till I cover it.
It's absolutely, absolutely astounding when you see it, admitting that they're getting
rid of America and getting rid of our sovereignty.
It's incredible.
I've got to cover that today.
But Dr. James Garrow joins us because if you're up at Infowars.com, you can see this article,
also punch it up for people watching on television.
Nobel Peace Prize nominee Obama asked military leaders if they will fire on US citizens.
Shock claim purported to come from one of America's foremost military leaders.
Well, we've already got General Boykin, former head of Special Forces, saying our government,
he believes, was giving weapons to Al-Qaeda.
And that's what Benghazi is, is a cover-up.
He believes, it's admitted.
That's what's so incredible here.
We don't know if it's Boykin.
I'm gonna try to find out here.
The point is, if you go to our article, and there was other articles that actually broke
it in the Examiner and a couple others the day before.
And I'm giving them credit.
Our articles, they'll back it up with the Army training manuals from 2010 FM 3-39.40
internment resettlement.
It also has gun confiscation, how to take over cities.
You can click on that and read that.
The clergy response teams, the backup that, hey, this guy's credible.
That's why we got him on.
And I believe he's telling the truth.
But I've talked to Colonel Roberts, whose nephew graduated from West Point, was in these
Army meetings telling him, 10 years ago, we're training to confiscate guns.
I've been to the urban warfare drills.
I mean, there's hundreds of data points.
The Army National Guard trained in Iowa and Arcadia to confiscate guns.
That was in the news.
You know about this.
You saw Katrina.
But the litmus test is, will you fire on US citizens?
And they tried it in Katrina.
They're doing the drills everywhere.
But now they've bought the 1.6 billion bullets.
Now they're hiring people out of the military to move them into Homeland Security as a militarized
domestic force.
New York Times, scouts trained to fight terrorists and more three and a half years ago.
Those 14-year-old explorer scouts are now 17 and a half, training to, quote, take on
disgruntled vets that wouldn't turn their guns in.
First paragraph of the New York Times, with dozens of color photos showing the simulated
killing with paintball guns of veterans in America.
I've talked to ROTC people on air and confirmed, they don't train to fight Al-Qaeda, they train
to fight US militias.
They've got four TV shows coming out this year, demonizing American gun owners and how
we're gonna be the new terror force.
Homeland Security is now converting over to the American people.
Now I'm gonna shut up and go to our guest.
I wanted to back that up for people.
So you can go to our article, Nobel Peace Prize nominee, Obama asked military leaders,
they will fire on US citizens.
Now we're gonna find out from the man himself who talked to this individual, Dr. James Garrow,
PhD.
Number one, I would say this military officer, he says the foremost out there, needs to go
public or they may die in a kayak accident like the former CIA director who exposed Waco
and leaked the Fleer footage because he was upset about it.
A, he better go or she better go public with this right now.
And I think it's better for you to do that because the system knows when a general or
even a Pat Tillman, someone well known comes out, that's the danger.
If I'm up here showing army manuals, they know the average person isn't gonna go look
those up and find that I'm telling the truth.
So I'm gonna go to you, Dr. James Garrow, PhD.
Tell us how the story unfolds, what you were told, then I wanna get into saving Chinese
girls before they get smothered or used for medical experiments.
Thank you for joining us.
Well, thanks, Alex.
I hope you can hear me fine.
Yes, sir.
We got your video Skype and got you on phone.
Tell us a little bit about yourself, for those that don't know, and then get into what this
military officer told you, this individual.
Well, okay.
And first of all, I'm an educator, but a businessman.
I operate schools in China.
And in the past, I've been a college president and the teacher's college principal here in
Canada.
My background is education, but I also am involved in business, of course, in the country
of China.
I probably have the largest network of schools, foreign language schools, in China.
And the elites send their kids to our schools.
So we know a lot about what's going on directly from the Chinese elite, the leaders.
Hu Jintao's niece was in one of my schools, and the current leader, Xi Lingping, his daughter
was in one of my schools, and of course, is now in Harvard, but that's beside the point.
So that gives you a little bit of background on me.
And I should have added, you've gotten 45,000 plus, and we actually, David Knight has adopted
children from China who would have been disposed of girls.
So he vouches for you as well, and I mean, I know who you are, but he says you're certainly
the bona fide.
So thank you for that information, saving 45,000 girls at the UN and the eugenicists
say are worth nothing, because they're such big feminists.
Now let's get into this officer, what they told you, and elaborate on this information.
Shall do.
I got a call the day before yesterday in the morning from this officer, a former officer,
he's retired, but he was quite upset that one of the people he'd encouraged to join
the military was being squeezed out, that he was forced to resign his commission.
And it was because a question was asked of him.
Now I've called it a litmus test, but basically what it is, he was asked if in a scenario,
if in a situation where the military was called upon to go and confront people who were armed,
American citizens who would not relinquish their arms, in spite of the second amendment
right to hold arms, would you fire on American citizens?
This gentleman related to me that the officer was totally flummoxed that he would be asked
this question, and he said his answer was no, I would not fire on American citizens.
And he was forced to resign his commission immediately.
Amazing.
Tell us more about, I mean, to quote you here from the article, you basically described
him as one of America's most foremost military heroes.
Can you give us an idea about this person?
Is this person going to go public?
Can you tell us what else he relayed to you?
Well, we had an hour long conversation, so it ran the gamut from talking about the transparency
or lack of, the manipulation of the mindset of the public as a result of a media that
no longer actually reports news, but now spouts the Obamaism, there was that part of the conversation.
His concern though was that the military was going to be put in an awful position where
they had to look at the oath they had taken, look at the officers who were also required
to give an oath to obey the orders given by those above them, including the commander
in chief, which would make it Obama.
And if those orders were in fact to kill American civilians because they would not give up something
they had a constitutional right to in the second amendment, namely their guns, he was
afraid that so many would be leaving the military that it would leave a vacuum actually in fact
for people who would really be swearing allegiance to a new king, a new dictator, Obama.
And that was his concern.
This man is a legend, yes, you would know his name, every American would know his name,
and no, he will not be coming public, he'll not be bringing it out in public.
He thought that the best thing he could do is put it out in a different way.
I was honored that he called me.
So it's not somebody like Boykin?
I can't give you the name, he's asked me not to, so in honoring that request, I won't
answer that.
I know several generals and he'd be at the top of the list, and by knowing them, I know
people that have worked with them, made films with some of these generals, and there's only
a list of four or five that I know that would probably start talking about something like
this.
I know they're training for it, I have the video, I have the training manuals, it's really
not a secret.
And I've had military call in who said, we've been asked, are we gonna fire on citizens,
and then we're shipped overseas if we won't, or kicked out.
And they're forming, and then basically sheep dipping, making them quasi-CIA, Homeland Security,
domestic, kind of NKVD units.
And I got news for the establishment, you'll be able to kill Alex Jones, take out Ron Paul
in the first wave.
But once you kill the Canaries, I would not wanna be anybody in a government uniform at
that point.
And that's part of the plan too, a civil war.
I wanna talk about your hour long conversation with this person, and where the military's
trying to kill us and take our guns.
I mean, obviously, Obama's controllers, the foreign globalist, they know this is designed
to destroy the military and police, which is what you said.
It gets rid of them, because you're still gonna have bad officers commanding them, and
then brings in the new forces.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not gonna wanna miss this exciting message.
Here's why.
Our solar generators provide life saving electrical power.
And unlike gas generators, solar generators run quietly, emit no fumes, and produce electricity
from the sun.
So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part.
Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse, and we discount them heavily at the end of
each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait, they go fast.
Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
Is this the year you finally get serious about your family's drinking water?
If so, keep listening for a special offer from Big Berkey Water Filters.
Did you know that over 60% of municipal water is fluoridated?
Berkey Water Filters distinguish themselves from many other filtration systems with the
capability to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine, fluoride, arsenic, and disinfection
byproducts from municipal water via the black Berkey and PF line of filters.
Then there's affordability.
At only 1.7 cents per gallon, Berkey Water Filters purify treated and untreated water,
even stagnant pond water.
Stop and think how much money you could save by simply reducing buying bottled water and
using water filtered by your Berkey Water Filter.
No need to be constantly replacing expensive filters with a Berkey.
A single set of filters can last for 5 to 10 years.
Choose the best size Berkey for your needs at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
And right now, all GCN listeners get 5% off all ceramic filter systems.
Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY.
That's 877-99-BER-KEY or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
Free shipping on every order over $50.
Big Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean water.
Stop the pain from broken, chipped, and damaged nails and eliminate toenail fungus with a
revolutionary new nail hardener, Nails of Steel.
Just apply one drop of Nails of Steel over natural or polished nails and go.
With Nails of Steel, there's virtually no drying time and it's guaranteed.
Apply this all natural, antifungal, and herbal formula for women and men.
Call 816-896-8307 or get free shipping at NailsofSteel.com.
NailsofSteel.com.
It's like a salon in a bottle.
We the people grow cotton, we fabric, engrave ink, embed strips and fibers to protect from
counterfeit then carting to a private bank, having it lead back at interest, forcing taxes
to service debt.
This capitalism or was Jefferson correct when stating a central bank issuing the public
currency is a greater menace to the liberties of the people than a standing army?
Hi, Ted Anderson.
I'm placing a silver dollar in a book explains our monetary system.
Call for your copy, 800-686-2237.
It's time to understand the system.
Call 800-686-2237.
That's 800-686-2237.
You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa where a nicely furnished cabin
with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine, and laundry service awaits.
After a good night's sleep, your adventure begins.
You're on a golden stag safari for big game, but it's not Africa, it's Argentina.
One-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo, huger, bighorn rams, wild boar, and the biggest
stag deer in South America, all gold medal quality, all the action you can handle.
Wide rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages, hunting guides, ground
transportation included, and more, all more affordable than you can imagine.
The adventure of a lifetime starts at goldenstagsafaris.com, the big game hunting ranch, goldenstagsafaris.com.
Pagodagirls.com is the site, the foundation and organization that saved over 45,000 Chinese
girls that would have been smothered, ground, or medical experiments.
Now they just come and pick them up, the state picks them up, and they just disappear off
into a labyrinth of hell, just like the Falun Gong being blood-typed and harvested for the
elites for their organs.
We're going to get into that in the next segment with our guest, Hunter James Garrow, PhD,
very highly respected individual.
My guess, if I have to say who it is, is that it'd be somebody like General, Lieutenant
General William Boykin, who's also exposing right now that our government's giving weapons
to Al-Qaeda.
And that's in the news today, that's coming up after our guest leaves us, and by the way,
that's in the film, Behold a Pale Horse, America's Last Chance, starring country music legend
Charlie Daniels, and Boykin is in that film.
That's why I'm guessing it'd be somebody like Boykin, because you can disagree with some
of his views in the past, but he is overall a patriot who's anti-New World order and pro-sovereignty
and that's about the only kind of guy I'd see exposing that.
Somebody like Dr. Paul Craig Roberts, who was in government, exposes this type of stuff.
Another Roberts, Lieutenant Colonel Roberts out of Oklahoma, he's exposed things like
this, but it's all out there.
We're going to get into China coming up in the next segment, but what else, Dr. Garrow,
can you relay to us in this hour-long conversation, and why did this senior household name for
anybody that knows military, one of America's foremost military heroes, to quote you, why
would they come to you, I mean, I know he knows you, and tell you this information,
and then say, get it out there, but I can't say, and then relay other things that he told
you?
Well, I would suggest that he's talking in fear, that he knows that the Obama administration
has a circle of death around them in terms of, I use that term because that has been
said to me, because there are people who have met with an unfortunate fate, who have dared
to cross Obama, but this gentleman came to me, I've known him for about 17 years, and
he came to me as a result of the fact that he had read the book that I had just written
about my work, Saving Baby Girls in China, and he had called me about three months ago
saying, hey, I bought a copy of your book, it's wonderful, da-da-da-da, and that made
the connection, so the other day when he called me, he was just saying, Jim, look, I know
you're connected with all sorts of people, you're on the net, you know how to do all
these things, would you put this out for me?
And I said that it would be an honour for me to do that.
Well obviously, he's risking his life putting this out, because the info's out there, and
a lot of these older generals, and it came to you because he doesn't understand the internet
completely, and how it works, they still, I mean obviously he knows the NSA's gonna
track this back, they're gonna know the relationship, Obama knows, and I mean, I guess he thinks
that if he just puts it out there in intermediary, they won't go after him, the danger is now
not going public full bore, that's when they come after you.
But if they kill this foremost military hero, living hero, then everybody will know.
So I mean, in a way, I guess it's good that he did talk to you, but what else did he say
about this other person he got to join the military years ago, now being asked if they'd
fire on US citizens, I mean, what else did he tell you about the plan to come after us?
Well that's basically it, he was reflecting back to me what was being said to him, about
this poor fella who he'd encouraged to get involved in the military, and the man who'd
gone up the ranks, suddenly this litmus test was being put in front of him, and it was
either, you know, you're gonna agree or you're not, you're gonna get squeezed out.
So his concern was that good, loyal Americans who had decided to give their lives to the
country in the service of the country, were being put in such an awful position.
I mean, this is the kind of thing that you would expect to have, a test of loyalty as
it were, for people who were involved in Mao's regime, or down in Chavez's regime, or somewhere
else, like the Nazis, this is the kind of thing they would have done, this isn't what
happens in a democracy, this isn't what happens with people in the services, serving the nation,
putting their lives on the line, this is just not what happens.
So the shock here is the knowledge that this isn't just one person it's happening to, this
person came forward, this person is somebody of integrity, but my goodness, it's not just
this one gentleman, it's others, and women who were put in this position of, and are
now being asked the question, would you in fact do this?
And that was the shock for this well-known American hero.
We're gonna go to break, come back in a long segment and get into what's happening in China,
and the authoritarianism over there, and what you've dealt with, with the killing of these
little girls that you've been saving.
But the countless millions you haven't been able to save, unfortunately.
But I'm gonna briefly, when we come back, break down for people, and then get your take
on this.
That the military, and I've noticed even senior brass, they're experts in their area, but
not in full spectrum.
I know what the globalists are planning, cuz I watch their propaganda, and they prepare
the ground first before they do it.
They have billed Obama as Lincoln.
And now they're, and I said this four years ago, now they're saying that he's gonna have
a civil war and be our god, be our king, that they've got this set up.
We're on the march, the empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support, and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver-based products.
Our most popular silver-based products are the 32-ounce nano silver solutions, our 2-ounce
nano silver nasal applicators, as well as our all-natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and
leave the silver at the surface, but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the
natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the
skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.SilverLungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver-based products
are best for you.
That's www.SilverLungs.com.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At eFoods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all of the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
From the front lines of the information war, it's Alex Jones.
I'm going to get into what we're facing here in just a moment.
And I tell you, I know about some of the few generals that have actually been anti New
World Order to some extent.
I know about a few of the generals that have met with people that I know who've been woken
up now, mainly retired generals.
I know about generals and admirals that have been shot and killed in the chest and in the
head multiple times and it's ruled suicides the last few years.
All the generals you've seen having to resign, having to step down or resign their commissions,
admirals, heads of CENTCOM.
The truth is our military keeps saying no, no, no, no, no.
Even handpicked guys from West Point in the military 30 years who've got whole careers
and everything ahead of them the last few years.
They are resigning.
We're going to talk about that in a moment.
Briefly, we are a listener supported radio, filmmaking, news organization and when you
buy books and videos and materials at Infowarsstore.com, you get the very lowest prices on things like
propure stainless steel water filters with promo code, water you get 10% off.
And you support the transmission.
Wars are not cheap.
Wars take money and this is an infowar.
We know the truth will set us free and that all the evil men in tires need to flourish
is that good men and women do nothing.
So again, we have the new t-shirt, come and take it.
And inside the AK-47 it says, the right to keep mere arms shall not be infringed.
And we also have behold a pale horse that has General Boykin in it, a patriot exposing
agenda 21 and the entire New World Order system.
So be sure and get all of that at Infowarsstore.com and spread the word about the broadcast.
I'm up here risking my life to get the word out because I realize how evil the globalists
are.
I realize there's no future if we don't beat them.
They plan and now shifting gears back to our guest, Dr. Jim Garrow, the big plan is this
and I've studied history.
I've studied the Rand Corporation's writings.
I've studied the writings of the leftist finance by the big banks that want to collectivist
system for the grassroots where the globalists are exempt from all the laws offshore.
So they can then take our tax money as corporate welfare offshore, invest our pension funds
in their fraudulent derivative scams to hold the entire financial system hostage.
That's it in a nutshell.
It's a corporate fashions system, a crony anti-free market capitalist monopoly system
sitting on top of a lower tier socialism communism, social engineering program.
And I started seeing this five years ago and I'm on record in Obama deception four years
ago.
I'm on record in Fall of the Republic three and a half years ago, two films about Obama
saying they're building him up as a messianic Christ.
They keep saying he's Lincoln.
He's Lincoln.
He's somebody like Lincoln.
You'll see.
And I said, they're doing that to later if they decide to bring in martial law, say he's
Lincoln who will crush the states.
Then he creates the 10 region governors to say, I don't need 50 states.
I've got 10 appointed governors.
He creates the rural council over communities all over the country and I get our guest take
on this.
And says Homeland Security and the Pentagon is over that and then we get the training
manuals for it.
It's gun confiscation, okay?
So this is totally, absolutely creepy.
And I've done reports on this, we're gonna do another this week cuz it's Paramount.
They're saying he's Lincoln, let the states, and I even have an article here today.
Let the states not turn their guns in.
Let the legislature say no.
He's Lincoln and will crush a new civil war.
Well, we're not gonna start a war.
They're gonna go out and try to take the guns, provocateur stuff, a new Waco if they have
to.
And they're going to try to elicit a 1776.
So that's why I got it out in the open on Piers Morgan.
And said it will trigger a new 1776.
Not to cause one, but to point out to everybody out there in TV land, hey, this isn't gonna
be fun.
Now, I'm gonna shut up and go to our guest.
As we went to break and I said that, he was nodding his head going, absolutely, that's
what he said.
So what did the general, cuz we know who you're talking about, I know who goes in these Christian
circles.
I went and did some searching.
I think I know who the foremost military hero is.
But again, I think he's made a mistake only going through you as 17 year friend.
The system, if I can figure this out in about five minutes, the system knows without even
using phone tracking systems.
So tell the general, he's not stupid that he needs to go completely public.
But going back to you here, sir, what is your take on what I just said of the master plan?
They plan to start a war using guns to then label all conservatives and libertarians the
enemy, which is in all the Homeland Security training manuals that we got from state police
and federal marshals.
Go ahead.
You know, Alex, the only time I've ever seen you, and I'm not a watcher of programs like
yours.
But the only time I've seen you was when I went and did a little bit of research and
I ran across this thing where you took on this British guy, Piers Morgan.
You just mentioned him.
And I thought, you know, you just fried the guy.
You just fried him.
But you put it out there with such intensity that thought, you know, maybe I'm going to
get fried today.
I don't know.
But you know what?
You're hot, man.
You're on the money.
When you talk about them setting it up to take away the guns and they're looking for
the crisis.
Come on.
That's what Valerie Jarrett has been pushing Obama to create a crisis.
And your military friends, they all are aware of what's going on.
The nightmare for them, the nightmare scenario is having to turn their guns on American civilians
because the new emperor, or at least the guy who thinks he's the new potentate, thinks
that he can just go out there, crush the Second Amendment, crush the Constitution, and then
crush anyone who gets in his way.
What's been the pattern, Alex, so far?
When people get in his way, what happens to them?
And that's because the globalists are taking over everywhere.
He's their puppet.
I saw a video of the Speaker of the House at a dinner groveling to Michelle Obama and
her rolling her eyes and batting him away.
It is pathetic how Congress, sycophantically through fear, is lining up to serve Obama.
What did your military source say?
Because when I walked out after the break, you were saying, that's dead on.
That's what it is.
Was the military source saying they want a civil war?
Or were you agreeing with my analysis because we have all these top Democrats saying, we
need a big crisis to make you king?
Alex, it was my military contact who said it is so obvious to him, so obvious to the
man that was resigning, that what they were setting up was a takeover, a total takeover,
by Obama, and using the military to have it happen.
And if the military will not, if they'll not give the right answer to this litmus test,
they've got a whole army of young kids who don't know any better, ready to move in.
And keep in mind, who are the people who get away with in the despotic times?
Who are the ones that they rely on in the end?
It's the young kids who don't know any better, but who can point a gun and kill people.
Wait a minute.
So your military source knows about the FEMA Corps.
Now, this isn't secret, but it's not well known to the public.
Describe what he told you about that, about the Uighan squads from about 17 down to 14.
Well, his words exactly were.
Here's the Hitler Youth being resurrected now under this name of Obama Corps.
That's exactly what he said.
Mike, this is devastating.
This is devastating.
Because I've gone and looked this up before I got you on, and I know the big Christian
circles you're in.
99% I know, and I've talked to you off air, and you're just like, nope, I'm not talking.
But I know who this is.
And I know other military officers, colonels and others that are saying the same thing.
I've got family that told me years ago I was right about everything, but now won't even
talk to me who's in the army.
I mean, this is because they've been passed over promotion just because they're related
to me.
And I mean, this is amazing that this is going on.
I mean- Are you armed?
Are you armed?
Do you have armament?
Yes, I do.
Do you have guns?
Well, you need them.
And you know, the vice president of my company in the US is a guy named Eric Rush, who happens
to be a black guy who's a journalist in your country.
Well, you know what I did for him yesterday?
I purchased him an AR-15 and a sidearm because I am so worried about the things that are
being said right now.
He's out there putting it out through WorldNetDaily, I think's the name, putting the word out,
letting people know the dangers of what, are you ready for this, what China is demanding
of Obama.
No, no, no.
China, China, we broke it a month ago, the Drudge Report, DrudgeReport.com linked to
it.
They're People's Daily.
I know you're in China and been there, you know it.
Their TV said, you will, quote, have a war against your gun owners.
We're ready to back you.
They're the biggest owner of the debt.
And then I've got a Daily Beast article where they said, it's good that Piers Morgan is
leading the anti-gun deal.
We need to get Americans used to foreigners running things.
I mean, this is insane.
Break down what's happening in China.
What's happening in China is they know, well, first of all, do you know that the Chinese
call Obama the monkey man?
Do you know that?
I've seen that in the news, yes.
It has nothing to do with him being black.
It has everything to do with the way they treat monkeys.
Monkeys are like puppets in China.
So Obama is looked upon as a puppet of China.
That's how he's looked upon.
And they know full well that when he comes hat in hand begging for more dollars, they're
going to make more demand.
Were you the one who broke the news about the fact that in Idaho, they've set up this
thing very much like Shenzhen, China, a special economic zone?
Was that you, Alex?
Yes, we're one of the ones, and now Jerome Corsi has confirmed that all over the US,
I actually visited some of these in my first film, they're setting up these economic zones
where the government lets the Chinese government be tax free, but then citizens aren't.
That's the model in the future.
Globalist will be tax free, but we will be under Agenda 21.
Well, you know, I've talked to Joseph Farah about that.
I've talked to Jerome Corsi about that very thing.
You know, Jerry Corsi, he endorsed my book, and my book came out through Joseph Farah.
But I'm telling you, the information that's available to some people about what's going
on in China and how they're treating the American land and the American resources,
they're treating it as something which they will be able to grab sometime soon.
And so the fact that they now have five special economic zones throughout the United States,
you've got to be aware of what's happening.
The fact that discussions have taken place with Obama and some of his officials in China
to talk about...
The NAFTA superhighway is their invasion route from the Pacific side of Mexico right into
the US, and they're going to be brought in.
I've talked to top officers, let's see, in the Washington Post, agreements to bring in
under NLE 09, troops from 15 nations to quell domestic unrest.
That's at FEMA.gov.
And guess who was on the list of the 15 nations?
Who?
Wouldn't be China, would it?
Oh, yeah.
That's what I'm telling listeners.
It's all...
And people say that'll never happen.
Once they start a civil war, it will.
Yeah, it's already happening.
They're setting it up for civil war.
They're setting it up to take away the freedom of the American people.
And Obama, he doesn't believe in freedom.
He doesn't believe you should ever have a gun.
What else is your military source?
Because, again, if you're a new listener, folks, China officially said, quote, have
a war against your gun owners, we will back you, in their biggest TV state run and the
People's Daily.
I mean, they're openly saying this and saying, we own your debt, you take their guns.
I mean, and then I've got a Daily Beast article saying it's good that foreigners are telling
us what to do.
I'm going to dig it up here, I'm trying to find it.
No, and you're absolutely correct, Alex.
It's exactly what's going on.
The Chinese are demanding that Obama take control of the guns because as they move in
and steal the resources of America, buy them, buy them out in satisfaction of the debt,
which Obama knows full well he cannot pay.
When you know you're not going to be able to pay your credit card, why don't you run
it up as far as you can, as long as they're saying yes, get as much goodies as you possibly
can.
That's the mindset of Obama.
Well, he knows full well he will never have to actually pay the debt.
All he has to do is say, hey, we've already shut down the oil industry.
They're not drilling, we'll give you permission to drill.
We've already destroyed the coal industry in America.
So come take the coal, you can use it, it's a better coal than you have in China.
They need it, they need the resources of America.
And that's what they are demanding from Obama.
And let's be clear about this.
China has been maneuvered to be the biggest owner of our debt by the Federal Reserve who
set this up when they could have just monetized and paid the debt that way.
Instead, they had the Chinese communists come in who kill millions of their dissidents on
record because they're the model of globalism.
We're told by the CFR, China is the model, not the Chinese people, the authoritarianism.
They use the slave wages, the Apple factories with the suicide nets, so no one can compete
in the West to consolidate power in globalist hands.
And then the Chinese People's Daily and their biggest TV station, we did a news article
linked to it.
Paul Watson was aware of it because his wife is Chinese and she first alerted it.
Paul went and found the actual English version of it.
And they say, I've read this on air, listeners can go pull it up.
In fact, guys, the headline's something like Chinese state-run media tells Obama to take
the guns.
Pull up the info words for me, guys, good job.
I wanna show viewers, radio listeners, pull it up.
And they say, quote, wage war against the gun owners, do whatever it takes, it's key.
We've given you money, and again, they're gonna be given the national parks, the land
is collateral, that's all official.
The Chinese communists were being conquered and they're saying, hey, we own your people
now, you take their guns.
And now the UN treaties coming up, this is the master plan, it's so evil.
Yeah, you know, it's funny, but I was told, when I checked with my friends, I said, have
you ever heard of this guy, Alex Jones?
And one of my American friends said, well, you know, he's a bit of a conspiracy theory
nut.
And, you know, now I've come on, I've listened to what you've had to say, and I'm sitting
here going, wow, this guy's not a nut?
You have the information.
I don't know where you're getting this, but I'm telling you, you are right on the money.
And keep in mind something, Yamamoto was right when he said, you don't wanna invade America
because behind every blade of grass, there'll be a gun.
And you know, the Chinese know full well, that's exactly the situation with America
right now.
Obama knows, he's got his marching orders.
He's been told to take your guns, he's been told to have your people crushed so that the
Chinese can do what they want.
You're right.
And we did find that People's Daily, one of the articles where it says innocent blood
demands gun control, and then it talks about waging war against American gun owners.
So here's the article, peers pressure, believe it or not, Morgan is a great spokesman for
gun control.
And the article goes on to say, he is globalization 2.0, you know, teaching us to basically go
under global government, and it will only survive if we submit to this.
I mean, this is amazing what they've done to us.
Oh, absolutely.
You've been manipulated every which way but loose.
They know full well that the, here's the other thing, the United Nations and the World Bank
in collusion with Obama, suppose he turns around and says to them or to the world community,
you know what, we cannot meet the debt.
Could you help us out here?
Could you help us broker a fair solution and pay off the debt in some way possible in whatever
way possible?
And the United Nations and the World Bank will be glad to say yes, we'll come in.
In fact, let's just do this.
Let's look at Idaho.
Look what you've got out there.
You got all this open space.
Let's look at Kansas.
We need the breadbasket.
We need to be able to grow great.
And that's why they've got to have Obama as the head of the UN Security Council violating
Article 1 Section 9 Clause 8.
That's why they admit in this Daily Beast article by Peter Beinart, who really shows
he's a globalist, they've got to get us used to this.
They've got to get us ready to go under world government.
It's so incredibly sick that they've maneuvered us to this point.
And by the way, they found it in the People's Daily.
Punch it back up for me, guys.
They found where it said Obama needs to engage in a protracted war.
You guys just had it.
You had it right on the spot with the war part.
That's what I wanted to read on air.
TV viewers saw it.
There it is.
Action speaks louder than words.
If Obama wants to take practical measures to control guns, he has to make preparation
for a protracted war and considerable political cost.
Then they go on to say the Chinese government's ready to help.
What do you make of that?
I mean, that is just in our face.
Yeah, well, keep in mind, yeah, it's an incremental thing.
And that's what this guy is.
Obama's all about incrementalism.
What's he done to the American public?
If you ever would you ever countenance for one minute, any man putting their hands on
your wife?
Would you ever wouldn't you detect the person who do that?
But now you do TSA.
Every time you go into the airport, every time stay there, we're gonna come back, we're
gonna come back.
You know what's going on.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive?
From natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the
family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy.
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At eFoods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Hey there, Frank Bates here.
Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out 280 million Americans?
This is really scary stuff.
Defense experts warn that this odd device poses the gravest threat we've ever known.
In fact, just a few weeks ago, former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed
piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat.
I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up.
That's why my friend just created a free video at WeirdDevice.com that exposes this threat
and blows the doors off the conspiracy.
Go watch the shocking video at WeirdDevice.com right now to discover exactly what it is plus
discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack.
I'm not sure how long this video will be online, so go to WeirdDevice.com before it's gone
forever.
Again, that's WeirdDevice.com.
Food storage?
Check.
Survival tools?
Weapons and water filters?
Check.
But what about a permanent source of cooking power that can run forever without buying
fuel or paying for maintenance?
Introducing Afterburner Stoves, home of the original patented rocket stove, the Kelly
Kettle and the Solo stove.
Afterburner Stoves has what you need and now offers all GCN listeners our complete preparedness
package with the means to cook meals and sanitize water.
Whether you dig in or bug out, cook almost any meal with just a handful of sticks.
We already have the lowest online prices guaranteed, but if you enter coupon code GCN at checkout,
we'll knock off an additional 15% and send you our amazing six-hour solar rechargeable
light bulb absolutely free, all for only $249.
Visit AfterburnerStoves.com or call 866-716-5214, 866-716-5214, AfterburnerStoves.com.
Cook hot meals with just a handful of sticks.
Well, this is the end of our interview.
You're in about six minutes with Jim Garrow, but I want to get him back on for a full hour
next week or as soon as he can.
He saved over 45,000 young newborn baby Chinese girls that would have been killed.
And he joins us right now.
Here's the Daily Beast, okay?
And there are literally dozens of similar articles by Peter Beinart, how you pronounce
it, and this is, of course, Newsweek's biggest publication online.
And they say, we got to get Americans used to globalism, you got to go read it.
And that we're preparing everybody and that America's power is in decline, globalization
means that other nations will influence and judge us, and we must basically do what they
say.
And they go on to say, Chinese officials are lecturing us, and that's good, that's a quote.
Mexican billionaires are lecturing us, that's good, you got to go read this.
And then it goes on to say Al Jazeera's purchased current TV, that's good, it's good for us
to go under foreign control.
And then he says somewhere, Alex Jones is readying his flamethrower, let him.
Because in the next round of the culture war, we will likely not just pit black and brown
versus white.
That's why they get on the news and say, gun owning is racist, we're gonna get the whites.
That's why Rangel's saying, whites are the enemy, southerners are the enemy, gun owners
are the enemy.
And you're like, that's really crazy.
Political correctness teaches everybody to be nice, but then again, this is all a plan.
It's secular versus religious.
It will pit those Americans who can't accept the increased, let's just go to our guest.
It says Alex is readying his flamethrower, let him, they basically just say they're gonna
smash us.
I'm seeing this everywhere, and I've seen this in the Weatherman FBI trials where some
of them admitted to being in these meetings, where they said, we're gonna kill the libertarians
and conservatives.
They said, we're gonna put them in reeducation camps, we're gonna bring the Chinese in to
do this.
I mean, this is insanity.
But they're really, it looks like going to try it with the Civil War as the cover kicked
off by taking the guns.
I just read that where they say, Alex showed us our enemy, don't worry, we're gonna get
him.
I mean, Piers Morgan has said he wants to shoot me.
What do you make of these people?
Well, the founding fathers knew exactly what was going to come down the pipe if ever people
lost sight of why the Constitution was built the way it was, why the Republic was framed
the way it was.
And what you're doing, you are actually, again, I'm back to this thing of where is this nut
case, Alex Jones, coming from?
Well, you're not.
You're on the money.
And you are providing the protection that the Fifth Estate, that the people in the media
should be providing the people of the United States by exposing the very things that you're
talking about.
There's a huge, I'm gonna say it because there's the word, there's conspiracy, there's complicity
all over the United States.
And you know, your poor military people are sitting there, they know, they are aware,
they know the manipulation, they know the expectations that they will be called upon
to move against the American people.
These people are heartsick.
They're heartsick of the portent of having to turn their guns against their own people.
And so they're walking out in droves, Alex, which is part of the plan because they already
have the collaborators lined up ready to take over.
That's right.
One of the first people-
Well, they should say yes, they will.
They should say yes, they will in this situation and infiltrate the New World Order.
I mean, that's completely biblical, just like the spies visiting the city and I mean, that's
gotta be done.
I say, just say, yeah, I'll fire on them, and then sit there and warn everybody behind
the scenes.
And I think that's the answer here.
Well, it would be great if they were left to that, if they weren't put in positions
where they have to actually say no all over the place.
And remember, these people are crafty.
Look at Obama.
Has anyone ever made Obama stand up in public where he was actually questioned about everything
in his past?
No, everything's always staged.
I mean, he's got three different names, everything's sealed.
Yeah, what's with this?
What happened to a legal system that pulls back the onion and everyone has justice applied
to them equally?
Well, Obama, golly, gee, what's gone on with him?
Amazing.
So we've got to have you back up again soon.
Thank you so much, sir.
Thank you, Alex.
PinkPagottagirls.com.
You are listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at InfoWarsShop.com.
These are items that I did research on that I personally use.
You've got the life straw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages are out
in the field.
Strategic Relocation, third edition by Joel Skousen.
When disaster strikes by Matthew Stein, TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself
during any radiological event.
Hand crank shortwave AM-FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at InfoWarsShop.com
and your purchase makes our InfoWar possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you?
InfoWarsShop.com.
Reaching war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
That was such an amazing interview with Jim Garo.
And we've done some research on him the last 48 hours and were able to connect dots and
I was able to talk to him off air and get his response.
And I believe with about 97% certainty, actually I'm completely certain, that the individual
that told him that high-level military people that he recruited and gotten in special forces,
that the person that they're talking about is the man that's in the film Behold a Pale
Horse, available by the way at InfoWarsStore.com if you wanna get it there and support us.
But we're talking about retired former head of special forces, General William Boykin.
Because of the Christian circles and I happen to know Boykin's been involved trying to help
get Chinese girls out of China so they're not aborted.
After birth, they kill them up a couple years, parents hide them and stuff.
And it kind of freaked him out out there when I went out there and said, is it Boykin?
And the guy's like, I'm not gonna sit there and do this question and answer.
Boy, you really are smart, how do you know?
So the point is, is that, well, there's not many people that even have the courage to,
and of course, it's on record that he runs in the circles of Boykin and they know each
other.
And obviously, Boykin knows, the government knows that.
And I'm not saying he's not a really smart guy, but at the same time, he went to this
fella because he's like, well, you know about the internet, can I work through you?
We need to get a hold of the filmmaker, he's been trying to get a hold of me, I've just
been too busy to talk to him.
I've been too busy to even call my other source, I'm just completely overwhelmed at this point.
I mean, I'm gonna be honest with everybody, but I already know their battle plan.
And I just continue to get more intel and more data on them and it's a bold move.
Fortune favors the bold and the globalist are bold, that's why I'm bold.
And Pat Tillman found out they were growing drugs and doing all this evil stuff in Afghanistan,
he was gonna go public.
So they killed him.
And I think General Boykin, he's already gone public and behold a pale horse.
He's already exposed.
Well, actually Boykin is in CNS news today saying our government is arming with Al-Qaeda
and giving them weapons in Syria.
So that's actually in the news today.
So it's Boykin, 97%, and I guess we need to get a hold of Boykin.
We know who to call to get his number.
I don't know why I haven't tried to get Boykin on to begin with.
And we need to just, I need to talk to him and go, look, General, it's time to just go
all the way.
It's time to get your missiles launched before they blow you up on the pad.
And I'm just telling you right now, ladies and gentlemen, that's what we gotta do.
And me, I'm in God's hands, I'm not worried about it.
He said the military living legend is scared.
And I guess when you're an old man admitting all that combat earlier and it's not even
scared, it's sad, freaked out.
It's like, wow, it's really happening.
They're really getting the military ready to come confiscate guns, have a civil war
and bring in the Chinese communist.
Let me tell you, a lot of mainline conservatives are all talk folks, they'll get out and salute
the Reds if they came in here, I'm telling you right now.
I mean, they'd line up, I mean, look, all the TV shows bad mouth George Washington.
I mean, if they had a public hanging in Austin, for me, people get out there and salute while
they hung my butt.
I guarantee it, most people are cowards and they love evil, but I got news for the New
World Order.
There's a good 15% of people aren't gonna back down, and they're men and women.
And so good luck with that big highway that just got completed, almost all of it from
the southern Pacific side of Mexico right up into Texas.
And they've built it right up into San Antonio and right up to the extension around town.
And we stopped it just north of here, fighting it as hard as we could.
That globalist taxation control grid to run the Chinese troops up, we killed it dead just
north of Austin.
And here we are fighting as hard as we can.
And most people cannot believe how serious this is, how real this is, but you're gonna
find out.
We're trying to stop them, but if we don't stop them, boy, just remember you were warned.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu, and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold, and food poisoning, and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day, while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases, such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus, and
other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support, and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action.
Tyranny is here.
The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality.
It really says that the state is God.
The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most impressive police states
on earth.
This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being
expanded nationwide.
This documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all
powerful shadow state.
Police state four chronicles the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen.
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship, body scammers, sound cams, citizen
spies, stage terror and cameras on every street corner.
It's only the beginning of the New World Order's hellish plan.
The police state isn't coming.
It's here.
Secure your copy today at infowars.com or see it online in the highest quality at prisonplanet.tv.
Crashing through the lies and disinformation.
That's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
All right.
Students, what they think of President Obama's assault weapons ban.
If the feds start confiscating assault weapons, will you turn your guns in?
Absolutely not.
No chance.
I completely disagree with what President Obama said the other day in his order and
all that.
And I will not turn any of my guns in and there's nothing they can really do that will
change my mind about that.
Well, personally, I don't have any guns on me, but if I did, I probably wouldn't.
Just a matter of protection for myself or if I had a family for my family.
I don't own any guns, so I don't have any to turn in.
Do you think other people should turn them in?
I do.
I think you should follow the law and also I'm kind of against assault weapon guns and
guns in general and I don't see that there's that much of a need for them.
If everyone turns them in, then you won't need them to defend against other people with.
I don't own any assault weapons, but I am a gun owner and my guns would be in compliance
with those new laws and so it wouldn't personally affect me.
But if I did own assault weapons, I would comply with the law because I don't think
that other than the headstrong southern attitude that what's mine is mine, there's no reason
to be owning assault weapons in a just personal setting.
How do you feel about President Obama bringing children on stage as he talks about gun control,
yet he's killed at least 168 kids in drone attacks in Pakistan?
I think national security and domestic security are two different issues and that security
abroad is a separate issue entirely from security inside the nation.
I feel that's kind of almost super critical in a way.
Yeah, I don't agree with that.
I think that dragging kids into it and having them listen to all this stuff, they do need
to be educated, but I think they're way too young and I think that's wrong.
I don't agree with that at all.
I mean, I don't think it's fair to bring kids onto the stage as he talks about it.
It's kind of unfair to make his point that way, but I think a life's a life and it shouldn't
be lost either way.
So I think it needs to be on both sides.
It needs to value the life of the children as much as Pakistani civilians.
Maybe he feels bad about all the kids that he has unintentionally killed and he's trying
to make up for that by saying that, by bringing the kids on stage.
No one is... He's not... In the way of asking the question, that way you're making the blame
go specifically on a single person on the President of the United States when it's a
much more complicated and complex issue and then in those sort of situations you can't
place the blame on one person.
Yes, people have died, but people die in any sort of conflict.
I don't personally agree with our presence in the Middle East, but I'm going to support
our President in the sort of decisions he makes and I think that having drones in the
Middle East saves American lives and when it comes down to it, American lives are what
our policies are about saving.
Now do you think it's un-American if local or state governments push back on the feds
in relation to the assault weapons ban?
No.
I don't think it's un-American just because I think that within America each state does
have its right to make their own laws.
I don't think that it's un-American.
I find that states, when they have enough reason to stray away from the national government,
it is their right to do that.
I guess it would be considered un-American to push the feds back because these are the
same people that we expect to protect us and we're the same people who we expect to watch
our homeland security.
And lastly, can you recite the Second Amendment?
The Second Amendment.
No, I cannot at this point.
I forgot clearly.
On the first one, freedom of speech, the second one should be right to the press, isn't it?
Right to press.
Or it's probably that.
I should feel ashamed of myself, though, wanting to be a lawyer.
The right to bear arms.
Every citizen should have the right to bear arms.
And it mentions in there something about a militia.
I used to know it.
I'm sorry.
The right to bear arms.
Okay.
And it mentions something about a militia in the Second Amendment.
No, I have no idea what it is.
Could you say it to me?
I cannot.
Reporting for InfoWars Nightly News, I'm David Ortiz.
There will be pundits and politicians and special interest lobbyists publicly warning
of a tyrannical all-out assault on liberty.
Alex Jones here for InfoWars.com with a special report.
Most people that watch television or even YouTube know that last Monday I debated Piers
Morgan and got in his face and said, look, you're coming for our guns to enslave us.
America is becoming a police state tyranny.
Back off.
Hitler took the guns.
Stalin took the guns.
Mao took the guns.
Fidel Castro took the guns.
Hugo Chavez took the guns.
And I'm here to tell you, 1776 will commence again if you try to take our firearms.
Doesn't matter how many lemmings you get out there on the street begging for them to have
their guns taken.
We will not relinquish them.
Do you understand?
Two days later, Ron Paul came on my show, outgoing congressman, and he agreed.
He said, if they come for the guns, it's going to cause a civil war, 1776, part two.
Will you turn in your semi-autos?
Well, I might not even have anything to turn in for that purpose, but I don't think the
American people will.
I've always assumed that the line in the sand may well be drawn.
If the federal agent marches in unannounced and they say, well, give me your gun and give
me your gold, I don't think that we'll do that, you know, in a calm way.
I think the American people will highly resent it and resist.
Now, as soon as I got off Piers Morgan, the White House released a press release and said
they were watching and responded to our petition, your petition, to deport Piers Morgan for
engaging in political subterfuge and trying to overthrow our Bill of Rights and Constitution.
So we know they were watching.
It became the biggest story in the country and the biggest story on Twitter for two days
straight.
It's had like 15 million views online on YouTube alone.
So we know the White House is watching.
We also know that it's come out in Homeland Security documents that myself and Matt Drudge
have been basically investigated and surveilled and are in secret documents concerning the
TSA because we've been covering their out of control violations of the Fourth Amendment
and conditioning the public to basically be slaves.
But then today I'm watching his speech while I'm live on the radio playing it.
And he talks about these pundits out there who just want to make money.
And they say that.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, we had some technical difficulties with the Skype, but
he's with us via phone.
So we were doing a retransmission of some special reports there for the rest of the
hour.
He's a busy guy.
Cenk Uygur, of course, founder and host of The Young Turks, theyoungturks.com, is on
with us.
He, of course, left MSNBC for several different reasons we're gonna talk about.
He went over to Current TV with Al Gore involved and the Hyatts and others.
And then now that's been bought out by Al Jazeera.
And he joins us.
He has one of the biggest media networks on the Internet out there, probably only rivaled
by Infowars.com or what Glenn Beck has developed over there with The Blaze.
And then, of course, there's the big granddaddy of all the real alternative media and that's
DrudgeReport.com.
But, Cenk, it is good to have you on with us.
I was looking forward to the full hour, but you promised to come back soon, as soon as
we can get your Skype going for the TV viewers.
But the radio listeners out there excited to hear you on the broadcast.
Where should we begin in this discussion today?
You tell me, Alex, we can talk policy, we can talk shows, politics, you let me know.
Let's talk about you a little bit.
Most of the audience knows who you are.
But, I mean, how did you get started?
How did you form your political beliefs?
Good question.
So when I was growing up, I was a liberal Republican in the Northeast that, of course,
doesn't exist anymore.
But it did back in the day.
I voted for Tom Kane.
Not voted for, I was too young, but supported Tom Kane, Whitman, etc., right?
And then the Republicans lost me during George W. Bush.
Gore was actually the first Democrat I ever voted for in 2000.
They lost me on a couple things.
The Clinton affair was fun and funny, but I thought it was crazy to impeach a president
over that.
Then they really lost me during the Iraq War, and then they really lost me during torture,
and then they went down the spider hole of, you know, warrantless wiretapping, gigantic
abuses of our rights and civil liberties, etc., and I consider myself an independent.
The Democrats drive me absolutely crazy.
I am a progressive, meaning that I believe in expansion of freedom.
I believe in protecting the middle class, etc., and there are some progressives in Congress,
but not much, and Obama, I think, is nowhere near a progressive.
So that's your, in a nutshell.
All right.
We got you on later today, I'm gonna skip this network break coming up, because I wanna
get down to brass tax with you.
You're obviously a smart guy, and so you know that both parties are bought and paid for
by some of the very same globalist above the law, don't pay taxes interest.
And that, I mean, who can deny the police state has been continued and accelerated by
Obama with NDAA, they found torture camps in Benghazi, the rendition flights, all of
it is continuing.
And I've seen the so-called left suddenly become cheerleaders for it.
You not so much, but I mean, still, it's just another wing of the same carrion bird.
And then I come on your show and you're like, man, do you need mental help?
You're so upset about all this, I don't think it's a conspiracy.
Well, it's an open conspiracy.
I mean, don't you care about your family, Cenk, you're a smart guy.
You've got to know that if you've looked at history, the United States is absolutely headed
over the edge of a cliff, politically, economically, culturally.
I mean, this country is rotting socioeconomically on so many fronts morally, and the police
are dressed in Darth Vader outfits, the NSA spying on us.
And they're talking about Obama's gonna be the new Lincoln and crush the states, I mean,
this is creepy.
All right, so, Alex, I actually totally agree with you on three out of four things.
It's just the fourth one, we have a wild, complete disagreement, okay?
So let me tell you what I agree with you on.
So does money control politics?
Of course it does.
And watching television drives me crazy, where they talk about, oh, Joe Lieberman had this
policy idea and Senator X cares about this ideology, that's nonsense.
The only thing that matters is what their donors tell them to do.
I mean, New York Times had a brilliant article about how this pharmaceutical company, Amgen,
just bought a $500 million exemption in the latest fiscal cliff deal.
It makes me sick.
And by the way, who'd they buy?
They bought Republicans and Democrats, Max Baucus, Obama, McConnell, and Orrin Hatch.
So I totally agree on that.
Well, take Al Gore, take Al Gore getting all that oil money.
I mean, how many, tens of millions, what is it, 100 million some estimates?
And we all know that Al Jazeera is backed by a government.
Well, let me leave that aside for now.
We can get back into it because I don't think it's as directly pertinent to our current
sitting politicians that take the money for specific acts.
But let me just finish real quick.
Police state, I agree with you, the NDAA, warrantless wiretapping, it's encroaching
power begets power, and there's never an end to how much power they can have, okay?
So I agree with you on that, too.
But the final piece of the puzzle, when you talk about the reasons why, that's where
we have the huge disagreement, Alex.
And look, I think the reasons are super obvious.
I mean, you said a conspiracy out in the open, I mean, if you want to talk about a conspiracy
out in the open, the lobbyists say, we will give $100,000 to this guy, and we will hire
his chief of staff, and we will hire him after he retires.
They funnel all this money, and then they get the money back.
And then you've got Congress insider trading, so the power is all massing, and foreign corporations
and global corporations are taking control.
Don't you see then the wisdom for the people to be armed as a balance of power, as a check
and a balance?
I understand what you're saying there, Alex, but I think it's unrealistic in a couple of
different ways, and I think it has a huge downside, okay?
So number one, when I say it's unrealistic, look, man, we can have all the guns you want,
and we could be out in the woods when the government comes with drones, if they want
to do that.
I don't think they're gonna do that, but if they wanted to do that, I mean, they'd blow
us out of the sky.
You can have 28 AK-47s, you're never gonna be a drone.
Really?
200,000 US troops couldn't hold Baghdad.
I believe you're wrong about that, and our people are inside the military.
If they start trying to use the drones, even if they're automated and controlled by the
globalist, the people in the military are gonna wreck those systems.
Humans are powerful machines, there's hundreds of millions of us, again, I've been to the
urban warfare drills where the military trains against US role players to confiscate guns
in US cities, Cenk.
I have the army manuals, in fact, I can give you one of them for gun confiscation in FEMA
camps and how to round up civil disturbance operations, FM3-39.40.
I mean, there I am giving you the actual document number, you can look it up.
This is real is what I'm telling you.
The 1.6 billion bullets the government bought.
I mean, if they've got drones, why do they want 1.6 billion bullets?
Because it's boots on the ground, they're gonna have to come in our houses.
Well, I can answer why they want the 1.6 billion bullets, cuz somebody made money off of it.
There's a bullet maker, they bribed the legalized bribery that they do of politicians, and so
the government bought 1.6 billion bullets they don't need.
Like, there's one other point of agreement we have, which is that I think there's gonna
be a gigantic collapse coming, and I think what happens after the collapse is enormously
important.
And we might disagree as to why that collapse is coming, but our main point of disagreement
is when you start talking about the FEMA camps, et cetera.
Look, I don't think there's a government plan to put us in FEMA camps, or to kill us, or
to take us over, cuz they don't need it.
They already have the government, look, Alex, the only thing they care about is making more
money.
And right now, they have almost 100% control of the government, and they can make all the
money they want.
Why would they wanna disturb that system?
They're milking us dry on that count anyway.
Well, I get the points you're making, and it's true that we've already been taken over,
they're already looting us, so why physically do it?
It is the instinct of tyrants to fully dominate.
I mean, why did Hitler, after he'd already taken France, just not stop there?
Why did he turn off into Russia, where Napoleon and every other empire went to die?
It is the nature of these people, so you come off as a real guy, and I'm a pretty good judge
of people, and so you are judging other people by how you operate.
And I don't blame you not wanting to talk about Al Gore and people, but I mean, Al Gore
has the carbon trading company over in London, and would literally make money off of every
human activity we make if he gets carbon taxes through.
I mean, that isn't about the environment, it's about a power grab.
No, no, Alex, I don't mind talking about Gore, I wanted to talk about your specific question
first.
But look, I don't know all the investments that Al Gore has at all, right?
I do know somebody comes in, like Al just heard, and they make an offer that appears
to be fantastic, above market value, if you ask me, and I don't know the specifics, I'm
just guessing from the outside, I'm not involved in the deal at all.
Anybody would have taken it.
So does that, I mean, he's not in power anymore politically, I don't, you know, so there isn't
any, I don't think any extra favors to be had, he just got an awesome price and he took
it.
Now, the carbon tax thing, look, I just don't believe at all that it's meant to be a money-making
enterprise, and I've talked to him at length for a long, long time, the man deeply cares
about global warming.
Now, you might disagree with him.
No, he deeply cares about the carbon's writing he'll make billions off of, of course he does.
He deeply cares about the Apple, Foxcom, suicide nets.
Does he deeply care about the-
Now, you told me you do the same thing, though, and here, let me explain what I mean by that.
Like, for example, you think the economy is in trouble, so you invest in gold, right?
We talked about that before.
Yes.
So then you make money off of that.
Well, if that makes sense to you, that's where you thought the economy was going.
I don't even blame the hedge fund guys like John Paulson, who thought, wait a minute,
these toxic mortgages are crap, I'm gonna bet against them, and they made billions off
of that, right?
So if Al Gore sees that this fossil fuel industry is unsustainable, and he's right about that,
and it's hurting our health, our wealth, everything else, and he bets in the opposite direction,
well, that's logical, I'd do the same thing.
Yeah, but carbon taxes are selectively enforced only against the West and designed to shut
down our development, and then move it to Chinese investments and Indian investments
that people like Al Gore have.
It's a managed crony capitalist economy, and it's completely cold-blooded.
It was Gore that got up there on Larry King Live and said, it's a great deal, Larry, I
deeply believe in NAFTA and GATT.
How has NAFTA and GATT been for us?
Well, look, I was in favor of NAFTA, and I thought, even though I was a Republican at
the time, I thought Gore clearly won the debate against Ross Perot on that issue, et cetera,
but NAFTA has had some significant downsides, there's no question about that, and I'll tell
you, at this point, I get that a lot of the global trade deals are done for the benefit
of corporations, and to our great detriment, I mean, look, I'll tell you, I'll give you
one example that really proves that case, it's the Panama deal, there's almost no trade
with Panama in terms of business, commodities, et cetera, but Panama protects the bankers,
and so recent trade deal that Obama did, he included Panama in the deal with other countries,
why?
Because it created a giant loophole for the bankers to pay no taxes.
Now, come on, why would you do that?
I mean, especially if you're claiming to be a progressive, liberal Democrat, and you give
the bankers this giant, multi-billion dollar loophole, no, it's because the corporations
run the place, Dick Durbin said it, he said, the banks own Capitol Hill.
So on that count, there's no question.
We're talking to the founder of the popular internet and TV and radio empire, Jink joins
us right now, theyoungturks.com is the main website, one of many they have.
Look, here's how my brain works.
They're sitting there going, come on.
So Goldman Sachs, JP Morgan, a few others, they knew the derivatives were garbage, so
they bet against them.
Yeah, but they also sold them to their clients and originally got the law changed in 99 to
be able to sell the crap.
So they-
Totally true.
That was fraud.
And so when you talk about the guys who sold it to their clients and then shorted it and
then bet against it, well, that's just outright fraud.
Those guys should be in jail and Goldman Sachs and all those guys did it and then John Polson,
so I might've picked a poor example because he worked with Goldman Sachs to sell the toxic
stuff to other people while he was betting against it.
But there were some people, like if you read the big short by, was it Michael Lewis?
Stay there, Jink, Uger is our guest and we're going to be right back, founder and head of
the Young Turks.
We're going to get into a whole bunch of other issues, second amendment, you name it.
And what he thinks the collapse is going to look like.
And is he worried about martial law?
All this and more coming up.
We're on the march.
The empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e foods direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York city wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Read the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today, or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting non-GMO long-term storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e foods direct.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now.
Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other
harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
We are on the march.
The empire is on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Jinky Uygur of the Young Turks is our guest and they've had a lot of fun with me over
the years making jokes out of things.
Talk about the CPS taking people's kids, we can discuss that.
Also the so-called liberal media is running like a four year old video of me talking about
juice boxes to make you gay and they take it out of context.
I'm pointing out that animals, mammals, you name it, are becoming sterile or bisexual
or having both organs.
Girls are going into puberty now at average of age 10, used to be 14, boys, testicles
are not dropping, genitals are smaller, they're becoming feminine, women are becoming hyper
feminine, the bisphenol and other things are directly linked to cancer and infertility.
All of this and the media just says, you're making fun of gay people, it has nothing to
do with that.
It's a way to get the news out to say, are the juice boxes making you gay coming up?
And then I'm like, well, actually it's doing a bunch of stuff.
But what's your take on that, Jink?
All right, so first of all, I'm joking around with stuff and we drive people crazy and people
don't like it when we joke around about them, but we do it all the time and we do it to
everybody.
Okay.
And the audience likes serious stuff, but they like lighthearted stuff too.
And so, and Paul Krugman the other day got all hurt over John Stewart making fun of him,
but that's just life and everybody's got to get used to that.
People make fun of us all the time and that just rolls off my back.
No, no, I don't mind you making fun of me, I mean, I'm a funny guy as well, I think you're
a funny guy.
I mean, how does that tie into the juice box stuff?
Okay.
They're really saying that I'm-
Okay, so on that front, on that front, look, you know, you mentioned three different things
there.
Let me take child protective services.
Now, this is, again, it goes to our fundamental disagreement, Alex, like if you say that child
protective services goes too far in some instances, I'm going to totally agree with you.
And I bet you could find five, 10, 20, 100 cases throughout the country where you say,
look at this, look at this, look at this.
Now, if you think child protection services is some sort of conspiracy where they're all
coordinating with one another to take people's kids, that's where I totally disagree with
you.
I got a neighbor who's in that, my wife used to be in that, there's no conspiracy.
They're trying to do the best they can, and a lot of times people screw up.
That's it.
Well, let me add my point.
Half of CPS roughly, about 54% nationally, people can look these numbers up, turns over.
Because people get in it for the right reasons, and it's so bad most people quit.
Sounds like your wife did.
I know there's about 50% or more that are good people.
But you are five times more likely, according to the Justice Department, even Time Magazine's
covered this, to be abused in government custody, CPS, than you are in anybody else's custody.
They put the average foster child on seven psychotropics, 67% are on psychotropics.
I mean, it is a mill.
But Alex, that's not a conspiracy.
So they over-prescribe, I agree with you, and if you're talking about, hey, there's
a financial incentive for the drug companies to set up an incentive system so they over-prescribe,
I'm with you.
And I think they over-prescribe, right?
But it's not like the government's saying, okay, ha, ha, ha, we will get these kids and
we'll put them on psychotropic drugs and we will, you know.
It doesn't work on that way.
It's actually in some ways more malicious than that in the sense that once you set up
a machine to do X, it will keep doing X.
And so they've turned government into a money-making machine.
So there is no smoke-filled room where CPS got together and said, let's drug up the kids.
It's just, if the drug companies have the financial incentive, they buy the politicians,
the politicians write the rules-
Okay.
Then my point is-
They wind up having more drugs.
Regardless then, it's going on, we should stand up and say it's wrong.
But the Democrats generally are pro-government and so, no, let's not criticize the government.
Let's just let it continue on.
The Republicans are pro-government to their buddies.
They don't want their stuff cut either.
And all I'm saying is, like Nixon said, it is a big out of control beast.
It is an out of control machine that nobody can control except the establishment on top
is trying to ride the beast and we're being trampled under it.
Yeah, and look, when people ask, is government too big, too small, that's my favorite question
because it makes no sense.
It's like saying, all right, how big a pipe do you need?
Well, I don't know.
What's the job we're doing?
Are we carrying oil?
Are we carrying a tiny amount of water?
What do you mean?
Well, how big is the pipe you want, right?
So it depends on the job that the government is doing.
So is the government too large when it has this enormously bloated Defense Department?
It starts aggressive wars?
Hell yeah, it's too large.
Is it too large when it gets into our private lives?
In my case, I think, you know, I'm pro-choice.
I think them getting between us and our doctor is way too large, you know, and so you can
list a dozen ways that it's too large.
You can also list a dozen ways that I think it's too small.
Like, for example, the whole reason why I'm not a small-time olive picker in the middle
of southeastern Turkey is because the Turkish government allowed my dad to get a free education
because he scored high on an interest exam.
That's the government saying, hey, we're going to give everybody an opportunity with their
poor...
They do that to find, under the eugenics model, and I'm not saying, I'm not judging Turkey's
models.
I'm not enough of an expert on it, you know, 60 years ago or whatever, though I know quite
a bit more than the general public does about the history of it.
My issue is they do that to pick and find the brains to make sure that there aren't
what they call wild sons or bad sons out there that grow up and get power outside of the
power structure.
Let's expand on this.
Golfer Phil Mickelson pays over 63, 64% in federal and just state income tax.
If you add in the property tax and all the other taxes, it's over about 74% for somebody
making as much money as he does.
Come on.
I don't believe that.
Well, I mean...
I don't think that's accurate at all.
I pay close to 60% in taxes.
Yeah, I mean, look, if you're adding everything, if you're adding local taxes, property taxes,
which is a whole different ballgame, sales tax, you might get the 60%.
But if you've got the 60%, that means you're making a hell of a good living.
I mean, I got friends making millions of dollars and then they say that in the end, and they
live in New York, which is heavily taxed, they're at around 50%.
Yeah, worse than that.
Are you kidding?
In New York?
Hey, Obama just hired that French researcher, top economist lady, to help tune international
economics with the US.
That woman is somebody pushing for the 75% taxes on top of everything you make above
75%.
I mean, the government needs 90%.
France is the model.
Futile serfs only paid 10% in ancient Europe.
But Alex, if you remember the golden years of America from about 1945 to 1980, when our
economy did the best, more accurately, probably 45 to 75, the tax rate was anywhere between
71 to 94%.
But the loopholes were so big, that's not actually the case.
Kennedy cut some of the highest tax rates by 35%.
The median tax income by 50%.
Tax receipts doubled.
Why does government want higher taxes when they know generally tax cuts increases revenue?
Or do you disagree with that?
I do disagree with that.
So when Kennedy cut taxes, they were still above 70%.
And remember, that's for the highest marginal tax rate.
So that's for every dollar above whatever the threshold is, right?
So if Kennedy doubled the revenue and he was at 70% for the highest marginal tax rate,
well, that's not so bad.
Now, look, I think that's too high.
For my personal taste, I think, and that's why my family supported Reagan when we first
came here.
Because at that time, if you remember before Reagan, the highest marginal tax rate was
70%.
I thought that was outrageously high.
But now we've got it to a point where it's far too low.
Look, when Clinton raised the taxes to 39% for the top rate, what happened?
The economy, boom, we added 23 million jobs.
Bush cut it, also Obama cut it.
And what happened?
We lost jobs.
We didn't gain jobs.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Obama promised not to increase payroll tax, and he increased it on 77% of Americans.
People making $30,000 got an increase, what, 3.8%.
There's all sorts of taxes being increased.
Here's my big issue with taxes.
If you had an angel, a good angel, distributing it all, it would still make people slaves
in the final equation and not make you independent and make you domesticated.
The establishment, the richest people in the world, come and lobby for higher taxes cuz
they know they're always gonna have loopholes and are exempt, Warren Buffett and people
like that.
And then they end up getting the money in banker bailouts and corporate welfare.
They're trying to shut down the Small Business Association in the federal government administration.
They take our tax money and then they give it back to select insiders.
I mean, that's what's going on here.
Some of that is true.
For example, the role of how big business crushes small business is one of the most
underreported stories in the country because they want a competitive advantage so they
set the rules in the government so that it is to their advantage and against small businesses.
But no, overall, most of the rich don't want higher taxes at all.
Warren Buffett is someone that everybody talks about cuz he's such an exception.
All the hedge fund guys, the private equity guys on Wall Street, cry bloody murder if
you touch their taxes by 1% and they're paying 15%, which is outrageously low.
Yeah, they wrote the laws.
They wrote the laws.
And it's the very same mega banks and Wall Street people that fund the Democrats and
Republicans.
I mean, look at Romney.
He was funded by the exact same groups, except for the Koch brothers, so you guys always
use them all day.
But the point is, is that now they flipped against the Republicans.
I mean, it's just such a cynical game and any big government is gonna create that trough
for the fraud, waste, and abuse to take place.
That's totally true.
And the Democrats and Republicans are playing us all day long and Fox News and MSNBC set
up this false debate, this false drama, my God, is it gonna be the Democrats, is it gonna
be the Republicans?
What difference does it make?
Obama renewed, in fact, he didn't just renew, he made the Bush tax cuts permanent for 99%
of Americans.
So that's the 1% change we voted for.
I mean, look, you're upset.
If you're a progressive, we're 10 times more upset cuz they never do anything progressive.
Never, why?
Cuz Wall Street and the guys who pay the politicians aren't progressive at all.
They're massively conservative.
No, they're selective.
They selectively enforce it on the general public and then they're exempt from it all.
So cynical with Bill Gates and all them up there talking about, race taxes, rich people
don't pay enough.
Knowing it's all written where they can be tax-free in their tax-free foundations.
Look-
Alex, let me ask you a more fundamental question, and I always wonder this about libertarians.
So how much government do you believe in?
So I mean, you gotta have some government, right?
You gotta have police, firemen, teachers, etc.
So we obviously have to have some taxes to support that government.
So what do you think is an ideal tax rate and how much government would you want?
Well, that is a huge discussion, incredibly complex.
Cuz like Ron Paul stated, we've gotten so domesticated, it'll take 50 years to even
wean off this.
But if we don't turn the ship around and start going back at least in a partially different
direction, we know it's all going bankrupt and gonna collapse and then there'll be nothing,
Cenk.
Yeah, but it isn't gonna collapse because of these things.
The main reason that it's gonna collapse is because we allow the banks to do unlimited
gambling.
And unfortunately, they control such a huge percentage of our GDP.
And then government backs and guarantees it, government then backs and signs us onto it.
No, look, again, that's our fundamental agreement.
They've captured the government and JP Morgan alone, and this is in an Atlantic article
you can read, well, it's public in a range you can see anywhere, trades $74 trillion
worth of derivatives.
Now, that doesn't mean they're risking $74 trillion.
But it does mean that is the number of the amount of trading they're doing.
So any slight error is gonna lead to enormous uncontrollable losses.
And any gambler will tell you, if you take enough risks, at some point, you're gonna
blow it.
And these guys are definitely going to blow it.
Your $74 trillion is five times the size of the US economy, and that's just one bank.
By the way, you know worldwide, it's estimated by the Washington Post to be 1.5 quadrille.
Yeah, it's insanity.
So that's gonna blow up.
It's gonna take the whole world economy down with it.
What I'm afraid of is that people are gonna take that and then misinterpret what happened
there.
And the answer in that case, Alex, isn't less government.
The answer is more regulation, more honest government.
Yeah, after the bankers have collapsed and taken everything over, they shut the game
down so nobody else can even basically do anything.
See, that's the problem.
They know this is gonna screw up.
They signed us onto it.
Then they implode it, then they pose as saviors, then they bring government in.
We go from 25 million on food stamps to 50 million to 100 million, and then we're all
completely domesticated, and the social engineers win.
Let me shift gears with you.
General Boykin, former head of Special Forces Command, is in CNS news today talking about
how there's evidence that our government's arming al-Qaeda.
Well, come on, that's in the New York Times even, against Libya, in Benghazi, now in Syria.
They're doing horrible things.
They're making sure the Arab Spring doesn't become something good.
They're making sure that Saudi Arabia runs it.
Where you're from, Turkey, so I know you have knowledge about this, is helping bring them
in with the US and NATO.
And I'm not saying Assad's a good guy, but compared to al-Qaeda, he's a wonderful guy.
And they are killing Christians, they are killing Alawite minority Muslims.
It is unprecedented.
Obama, it was called peace bombs when he did Libya.
I mean, what is your take on where this is going, where the TSA wants to look for bin
Laden in my underwear, and in my wife's brassiere, and in my daughter's underwear, and my son's
underwear, but then the government is openly funding and CFR admits those groups are led
by al-Qaeda.
I mean, what about that?
I mean, should we give Obama another peace prize?
How about 10 more?
I'm really conflicted on this one.
I'm not conflicted on this peace prize.
That was insanity.
He hadn't even done anything yet, and once he did something, we found out he wasn't altogether
that interested in peace.
But look, when I see Qaddafi oppressing and killing and butchering his own people, and
I see it with Assad, I want to do something about it.
But doing something is a really hard question.
What are you supposed to do?
And I totally understand that the more we get involved, and I think here Ron Paul makes
a lot of good points, the more blowback we get, and we constantly seem to be funding
and training the wrong people.
Look at what happened in Mali.
We trained some of the guys in Libya.
They go over to Mali, and then they turn off.
Oh, it's all an accident.
Then we got to invade.
Oh, we got to invade all of Africa with Africa now.
I said four years ago in Obama deception, they'd use al-Qaeda to invade those very countries
and do this.
You know how I knew?
There's Pentagon public white papers.
They think we're so, see, Cenk, I've got West Point documents from four years ago, and last
year, and now this year, where they're trying to take on gun owners and take our guns.
That's why I know, Cenk, they're coming, because I have the army manuals.
I have the army sources.
Do you understand what's gonna happen when they come for the guns, bro?
Okay, I just, I keep going back to it.
It is totally unnecessary.
What they would do if they came for guns is they would stir up the biggest S storm you
ever seen-
They're trying right now.
The five star-
Why would they bother doing that when they've already got the whole system on lockdown?
I mean-
They're not.
No, no, you don't know about the-
They can't bring a single dollar out of us if they possibly can.
Mao said political power goes out of the barrel of a gun.
Our four founders knew that as well.
They just wanted the people to have the power.
Don't you get that, man?
Don't you trust yourself?
I mean, Alex, think about what kind of, look, you can't do through guns and violence if
you're gonna fight back against the government.
You've gotta do it the King way, the Gandhi way, because if you try to outgun them, you
know what Gandhi said?
He said, part of the reason we didn't use guns is because we didn't have them.
Now, you would take that as an example for your side.
I actually say, well, of course Gandhi was never going to beat the British with weapons.
They have so many more weapons.
The way you beat them is by other means.
And so if you do it democratically, you do it politically, and you get people riled up
and you say-
Cenk, Cenk, how much military history have you studied?
Listen, we couldn't, our entire military couldn't defeat the North Vietnamese cuz they had a
will to fight.
The rifleman is the power, okay?
There are 160 million gun owners plus in this country.
Alex, you're gonna give them an excuse to kill you, okay?
I mean, the minute you pick up a gun, they're gonna feel absolutely justified in striking
back against you everywhere possible.
Cenk, Cenk, there you go, there you go.
I'm not picking up a gun.
I don't wanna have a physical conflict.
They are preparing to try to confiscate the guns and demonize gun owners as in the Homeland
Security documents that we broke three and a half years ago.
They wanna start a civil war and then call us terrorists, and you'll be like, well, they
killed Ron Paul and Alex Jones.
They had to, they were gonna lead a revolution.
See how that spinning works?
I wanna give you some statistics when we come back.
I can't wait to have you back on Skype.
I saw how great your Skype looked before it failed.
There in your Young Turks studio, theyoungturks.com, I'm Alex Jones.
It's time for a home security quiz.
Answer this.
What effective home security device is smaller than a coffee cup fakes out burglars into
thinking someone is home at your house while you're away, plugs into any wall outlet, is
recommended by many police departments, and sells for less than $35?
Yes, it's fake TV.
This year, about one in every 50 US homes will have a break-in, with burglars usually
picking the easy target, a dark house that looks like no one is home.
Fake TV is a small electronic security device that makes it look like someone is home watching
TV by simulating the light from a real TV.
It's like a lamp on a timer, but far more convincing.
And for only $34.95, fake TV could be the difference between coming home to a secure
house or one that's been ransacked.
Go to faketv.com or call 1-877-5FAKETV, that's 877-532-5388, or go to faketv.com.
Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
Hi there.
My name is Frank Bates.
What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble.
I just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are, incompetent line crooks that
are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high.
Some have called this a conspiracy.
Others have called it a cover-up, and you will be shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy
goes.
My video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them
and how you can beat them too.
Watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patriots have already seen
in the last three months.
Go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect
your home.
So watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down.
Again, that's 123coverup.com.
Digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of toxins.
That bears repeating.
And ProEM-1 daily probiotic cleanse is the key to digestive health.
ProEM-1 is a powerful liquid probiotic, strong enough to cleanse, gentle enough to use every
day.
ProEM-1 is dairy, wheat, and soy-free, contains all-natural and certified organic ingredients,
contains no preservatives or animal products, supports a healthy digestive and immune system,
supports weight loss, improves absorption of food nutrients, aids in controlling yeast
infections, is never freeze-dried, and uses three groups of live, viable, beneficial microbes
to cleanse and remove toxins.
Order ProEM-1 daily probiotic cleanse at Tereganics.com, spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X.com, Tereganics.com,
or call toll-free, 866-369-3678.
That's 866-369-3678.
ProEM-1, the raw probiotic.
All right, we got him five minutes into the next hour, and he promises after he does his
big DC trip next month, he'll come back with us in March or so via video Skype.
This is the last sin that you've ever seen that has ever been revealed.
He's going to be immediately confirmed.
You can go to the network on YouTube, you can watch this.
He's going to be a man in a car, he's going to be a woman in a car, who's going to get
But I brought Melissa Melton in because she was gonna be on earlier today, but then I ran out of time and Melissa
We've got FBI statistics from fbi.gov for TV viewers. We're gonna be putting these up on screen for radio listeners
The video will be posted later today and info wars calm go over these statistics for jink so he can respond
Well, the situation is that we have a lot of media and politicians that are throwing out statistics and they don't cite their sources
So we don't know if those are coming from think tanks or special interest groups. This is from the fbi.gov
They collect this data from 18,000 law enforcement agencies across the country every and private groups have studied
It's some of the most accurate numbers out there what they're not usually fans of government numbers
But but this is this is what we have
It's the most consistent over the years and using basic calculations for percentages
You can see by that their own data that goes back to 1992
the uniform crime report shows violent crime has been cut in half since 1992 and if you take the
1992 violent crime rate per 100,000 people of seven five seven point seven you subtract the 2011 violent crime rate of
386 point three you get three seventy one point four if you divide this by the original 1992 rate you get point four nine
Oh two multiply that out and you're gonna have a decrease right there of forty nine point zero two percent in violent crime between
1992 and 2011 and the murder rate shows the same decrease as well. Actually we can go to that
So people think it's the end of the world and everybody's dying
But the truth is the only thing going up is mass school shootings and that's 88 a year about half of those gangbangers killing each
Other it's still a bad thing. But I mean Biden going riddled with holes beautiful children. I mean, it's so exploitive
We're gonna go to more numbers here in a moment. Hit pause on that but jink rubbing respond
I mean almost a 50% cut as more guns get bought as the criminals get scared in the last 20 years
So Alex, there's about 12 different possibilities as to why the crime rate started going down in the early 1990s
I wrote a I should say I read a brilliant article in Mother Jones about this
And we have the Kevin drum on the show to talk about it and I was really skeptical about it
But it turns out the one thing that correlates with crime increases and decrease is lead
Okay, and so the leaded gasoline really screwed this country up in a big big way now
To me I get that the crime rate is going down and that's terrific thing
And again, there's a lot of is that why we all beat the hell out of each other in the 80s
Anyway, I'm sorry. Go ahead
but
the problem with with the guns isn't
necessarily the crime rate as much as it is gun homicides and of course these massacres and then you know
You look at the international rates and you know, you've got Japan you've got
Australia and you know, they've passed the their ban in Australia in 96. They haven't had a single massacre since in Japan
Oh, yeah, now they're trying to take the bolt-action guns now there. Okay. Let me throw this at you long after leaded gas was out
They did concealed carry and that's when the real drop started. So it's not the lead. That's a small part. I agree
I've seen the studies. That's a small part from the complete rage of the 70s and 80s
Okay, but but in the 90s, it's concealed carry more guns less crime
You can use Japan where nobody robs each other when there's a tsunami and say look they have lower crime
I mean, it's just it's a different culture is my point
Look at Japan for one second. They they have in the ballpark of two to ten gun homicides
Over the last six years or so. Okay per year, which is and and Japan is a smaller country than us, but
They're significantly large and if a samurai told a villager to get on their knees
Because they had disrespected him and to let them cut their head off
They would not resist that has been a programming and the culture of feudal Japan
They're great smart people, but that's leftovers of that the total submission
And and and they don't have guns Alex
But they got guys that go in schools and stab people with knives the government wants the guns to enslave us stay there back in
60 seconds
Thank
You for listening to GCN visit GCN live.com today
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness
Get serious and make a stand with supernatural silver
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver
the supernatural silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses
infections yeast and molds
Supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
Purification it is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support
And it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness
go to supernatural silver calm today and give yourself and your loved ones a
Fighting chance that's supernatural silver calm check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook
Coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the alex jones broadcasting network network
Big brother
mainstream media
Government cover-ups you want answers
Well, so does he he's alex jones on the GCN radio network
And now live from Austin Texas alex jones
All right, it is our final little segment with jake huger of the young Turks calm to the kid radio TV host
And star of YouTube with their news
Pretty entertaining, but I don't agree with a lot of it. I mean, I'll say that up front because oh, it's an accident
Oh, it's corrupt. Oh, whatever
But at least the guy is not one of these Skeletor demons like the mainline Democrats are that I've met behind the scenes
I mean, at least you'll admit that it's wrong that Obama. I mean, did you think that was sneaky how he said don't worry?
I'm gonna veto
NDAA so you don't have to fight it and then he blamed the Senate so they released the letters where his lawyers wrote it
And Obama demanded it then he said don't worry. I won't sign it and he did
I mean, it's the way Obama gets you to feel good when he walks you out behind the barn and slits your throat
I mean, it's it's really creepy
It is a great show or there was on stars called boss Kelsey Grammer was the star
But I don't agree with Kelsey's politics, but damn he's brilliant
I thought he was the best actor on TV and there's a great line in there about politics
They say the donors say we want change on the outside and continuity on the inside
And that right there is Obama in a nutshell
He sells you change and then he just keeps the machine rolling
We give kind of wrestling nicknames to people sometimes Obama's nickname is the establishment
and God, he does a brilliant job of pretending he's given you historic change while he
Ups the ante honestly on the police state and the warrantless wiretapping and the NDAA. I don't know why he does it
I mean, you know, I'm not a psychologist, but I do know he does do it
Well, he's bought and paid for by the very same interest
I mean we already went over that but I would just ask you to do this because I know you care about the children
The vaccines in most cases like flu do not protect you from what it does on the insert
It says it can kill you give you narcolepsy
you name it and all over the world with the
Meningitis and and other shots they're giving kids polio shots. It's killing them. I've got articles up at info wars calm right now
Well, if I send you the actual studies and reports about vaccines killing kids
Well, will the young Turks cover that or would you get kicked off the Al Jazeera TV?
Well right now we don't have any deal with Al Jazeera
I mean, I'm continuing on my old contract and I'm I've never been worried about getting kicked off of anything as you might know
But but on the police, so will I read it? Of course. Will I cover it?
I don't know. It depends on what's in it because you know, look, I don't know anything about it
I'm not an expert on it, but every single doctor I know says that they believe in the vaccines
They think a polio vaccine is enormously important before they've been brainwashed
They've been brainwashed by it and they're told to do that by the medical companies
They work for I have to know doctors that are pushed and given kickbacks for how many people they give shots
Well in closing tell us about young Turks calm and now what you guys are going to be covering tonight
So, you know, we do our live show 9 o'clock to 11 o'clock Eastern on the young Turks calm
You could also see it on youtube.com
Slash TYT and especially on youtube.com slash TYT. You got all the clips
so if you like a story about guns or you like a story about the NDAA you will
Be able to watch that in about five minutes and not necessarily have to watch the whole show and we do all the news
So we got pop culture. We got policy really really serious
politics foreign policy and
We and then we've got a network of about 20 channels on YouTube as well
So you can watch sports or any of the other topics that you like. So youtube.com slash TYT
Yeah, you certainly pioneered things Glenn Beck's trying to copy what I've done, but also what you've done in closing
Look, I know the New World Order is real. I've studied what they plan. It's a eugenics program
Just like injecting black people with syphilis
That's the tip of the iceberg and I'm telling you they're evil if you care about your children you have children, right?
Yep, if you care about your children the GMO the top companies are on record
It's designed to sterilize you if you care about your kids look into the vaccines if you care about what's happening
I'm telling you. This is not my opinion
The reason I get so upset jink is because I know this stuff's real and I think you might have a heart and a soul
So I'm asking you don't sell out to the New World Order
You've shown you left MSNBC because you were against the war and stuff and the things they're doing
Go all the way. You don't need the system come out against the New World Order. I'm telling you look into what I've covered
It's real
So far I disagree with you on that Alex, but I'm always open to reading things all right jink
I'll say bye to you during the break. Thank you for spending so much time us
We're gonna come back with a special report more on those statistics on the guns
Hello, I'm Alex Jones myself my family the info wars dot-com team want to relay to you and your families that we are
Intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front info wars dot-com is leading the fight against the technocrats
But we can't do that without your help by getting the films bumper stickers and t-shirts and info wars
Dot-com you will wake up people in your area and support our
Operation as we move to the next level we need your help to spread the word like never before
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics
dehumanization and ultimate
Extermination the war is here. It's an info war the spirit of
1776 versus the mindset of
1984 my name is Stephen Huir after 22 years of nutritional counseling
I've observed that most brain malfunctions have at their roots some form of toxicity and brain damage
So whether it is poor memory or focus lack of creative thinking or more serious matters like inability to focus
Speak normally or remember things the emphasis to getting one's brain working optimally needs to be on detoxification
One world way support your body's number one means of detoxification, which is glutathione production
My name is Angie and my son has suffered from borderline autism and constipation
I got him on one world way and in two months his constipation is gone. He's become friendlier
He can carry on a normal conversation with me and he has made his first friend
He's doing great and he looks forward to taking one real way every day
You could offer him a present or cake and he would prefer the one real way go to one world way calm
That's one world WH e y.com or call eight eight eight nine eight eight three three two five
That's eight eight eight nine eight eight three three two five. Hello. This is Ty Bollinger author of the best-selling book cancer
Step outside the box. I want you to know some very important information in
1985 president Ronald Reagan requested that carnivore be sent directly to the White House
At a time when only the president could obtain this world-class healer now
Twenty seven years later carnivore capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17
Naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single normal cell if you want to stay healthy
Now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body
Call one eight six six Venus fly or order from carnivore calm
That's car ni vo ra dot-com. That's one eight six six eight three six eight seven three five
One eight six six Venus fly or visit carnivore calm protect your immune system. It's the only one you've got
He's the t-rex of political talk Alex Jones on the GCN radio network
All right, if you just joined us from the last hour we had Jake Uyghur of the Young Turks on
And I don't think he's an evil person a bad person at heart like appears Morgan
but
he just makes excuses after the excuses after excuses and I was talking to Melissa Melton during the break and
We were talking about how everybody's getting these allergies and they're getting worse and worse people that never had them are getting them to like
Normal foods even stuff that isn't GMO and it's because we're being biologically manipulated and I have
More than a hundred eugenics books written by the top scientists the heads of IBM the the White House science are
How they would engineer this in the 30s 40s 50s 60s 70s 80s 90s
We're gonna do some gun statistics here as we go into the fourth hour of overdrive with Melissa Melton
But you were telling me a story and I said, well, can you tell that story on air?
And you said yes, you would you had to take your son to the emergency room last night and I'm telling Jake
I'm going listen. Don't give your kids vaccines
I'd like to send you the inserts and and listen this GMO was really designed and he's like
I don't believe they want to do that to me. I'm like, what about black men and syphilis? What about the atomic soldiers?
They're just not listening. Okay, there's a global scientific
Dictatorship, it's a plan and
99% of people are not in on it. It's a very small technocratic group
But just like they have the times of London Bill Gates Oprah Winfrey
Warren Buffett Soros about 30 of them met at
Rockefeller University quote secret meeting to discuss global government to reduce our population that it's always the same
I mean when I say I've read a hundred books, okay, I'm not exaggerating a hundred books
They've read it's more than a hundred where they admit their global government plan where they admit they're killing us
cancer is I mean that that Miss America contestants having both her breasts removed and
She's wondering why her mother and all her family's dying of breast cancer. Why is breast cancer up 3,000 something percent?
Why is the u.s. Leading it worldwide in the increase? There's never discussion. Why is it exploding?
Why is it exploding? Why are all these other autism all these other cancers?
Why why why why why why why but you give your kid a vaccine they have a convulsion right there now the doctors are taught
This is in the news to say that's normal to have a convulsion really and your two-year-old never talks again
Now and again, it's around 18 months to two years when they all build up the 50-something vaccines now
it's gonna be a hundred and then 200 they're talking about by age two and
Yeah, let's turn her mic on go ahead and say what you said again
Oh, the u.s. Has the most aggressive vaccine schedule in the world. It's unprecedented
We have so many vaccines that are given and it is amazing. I think it's like 69 by 18
You're supposed to take now 50 something by two
Yeah
It just keeps going up
So and they just keep adding more and Bill Gates is funding putting it in the food
Pears and bananas where you you're gonna take and mosquitoes that come bite you you don't have a choice Bill Gates says he even has
A clothing thing now that's gonna have nanotech in it. That's gonna dispense medication. Oh, that doesn't sound like it's dangerous
Yeah, that sounds great. No, everything's fine. There's not a plan. You know, the globalists just took over and are launching drones
They admit humans won't even be in the equation soon. Only the elite let's build giant robot armies for eugenics-based elite
That sounds wonderful. Yes, and then we'll all wear their Medicaid tell folks what happened to your son
My ex decided to take him to a well-known fast-food restaurant and get him say the name Burger King
It was Burger King and get him some onion rings and within probably 20 minutes of eating these onion rings his whole body just
welled up with huge rashes and blisters and he had to go to the emergency room because his eyes were swelling shut a
Couple years ago, we'd be on a road trip and you know now we always pack all our food period period and find out
We're you know, at least semi-organic
Store is somewhere around there or we pack it all on a road trip
Because every time I give in all right
I guess we'll pull into one of the big names my children get sick and act like demons
Mm-hmm. And the thing is it's been shown to be addictive because McDonald's and others by law
They call it an additive. It has silicone and a lot of the frying agents says I mean silicone silicone
And then high fructose corn syrup and everything too and it's just the whole combination of all those chemicals all at once hitting a small
Child, it's just amazing. But yeah, I've never I mean even when we've ever gone there
I mean we eat it
We always feel crappy like you said
But this is the first time this has ever happened and I we will not be eating there ever again
I mean it was scary. It really scared me. They thought his throat might swell shut
They had to give him two medications and the hospital said it was an allergic reaction
It was an allergic reaction and that was the only thing that he'd ingested or any and again 20 years ago
There might have been one or two food allergies. Now. It's hundreds of things eat a mango die
One in five Americans are allergic to wheat. They have wheat gluten issues now
And again didn't used to be the case my grandmother almost nine never had allergies has horrible ones always lived here
It's everybody I know I mean listen, I've been exercising
I've been eating almost no GMO really working hard to do this up when I'm on the road then it's hard
It's a habit
I have been swimming two miles a day back when I could still go swimming for it was too cold
Jogging hiking climbing mountains my muscles get bigger and stuff
But I've got allergies now to cedar where I may have to leave in the winter and go remote do the show from another city
I mean, I'm actually looking at it and nothing will get rid of it. I just gnashed my teeth together
I'm so angry about it so bad. I mean I mean this whole thing is out of control Melissa
Well, and then when you go you have all these random symptoms
And they want to give you more and more medications and tell you you have more and more disorders and not tell you what it
actually is
Well, I mean the doctors don't know they're not specialists
But the endocrinologist the allergist the the the the scientists that study the brain blood barrier
Dr. Blaylock all of them will tell you this stuff is killing us
I mean listen take all the different BT varieties of corn and stuff
There's a bunch of companies put it out on just Monsanto it all is designed where when bugs eat it they die
They die, but they say but it's safe for you to excuse me, and they go well. It's natural
They took a fungus or in one case of bacteria and soup it up thousands of times
The the poisonous bacteria or fungus and then it's two different varieties, and then we're supposed to eat that everything's fine
Don't matter all the bowel diseases are exploding does it matter your IQs are dropping doesn't matter
You're getting cancer doesn't matter of the studies that killed all the monkeys and rats everything's fine, Melissa
Everything's okay tune into the Young Turks man the government loves us
Yeah, why wouldn't you want to eat a food that produces its own pesticide that sounds great. That's healthy for everyone
I actually read one of the people from the American Academy of Pediatrics said that there's no long-term study to show that eating less
Pesticide is healthier for you
So if there's no long-term study to tell you that it's bad for you
Then that means it must be good for them, and they don't do the human studies
But then they do the monkeys the guinea pigs the rats the mice within three generations with with multiple new
GMO potatoes you name it the rats are almost all sterile or mentally retarded or dead or have giant cancers or no
Genitals or genitals on their head. I mean it is stuff you can't it isn't and it's all
All these companies Monsanto on the board of McDonald's tied into Bill and Melinda Gates
Bill Gates bought into Monsanto
And then you go track the founders and the heads all eugenicist all going and giving speeches how they want to kill us
Exactly Bill Gates gets up at TED TV
We've got to lower this h2o equation from the humans down to zero that means zero this shows zero humans and the whole crowd laughs
and gets off
Knowing they're in on the joke that thrills them as little control freaks
Because they don't like going to the Grand Canyon and seeing you see zero right there on screen
Now the numbers up to 80
European children develop narcolepsy of receiving h1n1 vaccine, and then you go back boom Bill Gates
It was 60 something thousand India got sterilized 50 African children paralyzed after receiving Bill Gates
Back to meningitis vaccine. Oh, but everything's fine
Everything's good isn't that just precious Melissa. Yeah, when you look into his foundation
They own stock in all the companies Monsanto McDonald's Burger King big he owned and then he owns stock in the pioneering companies who treat
Autism and treat gut disorders, so they hit it on both sides
They're gonna suck the money out of you while you're debilitated and tortured so they don't want to just kill you
It's important to watch humanity mutate and die and be in pain
Because I mean that's why Joe Biden talks about those beautiful children riddled with holes
Have you seen that where he's like obviously getting off on it. I mean anyone can look and go perv
Perv perv. I saw him in a park. I would creep away from him. Yeah
I wouldn't want to go down a dark alley with that guy
I haven't seen that particular clip, but I can barely watch it. I mean it's so hard to even see you guys
Have the Joe Biden I sent you
Cue it up. This is just part of it all right
And we're gonna go to break and cover the statistics in the five minutes after that
You know we were giving those statistics most the drop was not in the 80s. No. It's consistently over the last 20 years
Yeah, and I phased the lead out starting like 180 to 86 or so the lead study
Yeah, but that can't be accounted for it
Just continually dropping for the last it accelerated the last nine with the proliferation of concealed carry
And they have the local we took stats in college
Yeah, I mean to say that that's all it is is just I think there's no way you can do that when you look at
The whole big picture of all of well they can't stand it
They're like look at the children like Stalin said one person dies
It's a tragedy a million die or 10,000 die different quote its statistics
They know that I mean they got drones murdering blowing kids lower mandibles off hell-raiser type stuff
It's all cute and funny, but then all the children give us your guns. It's for the Obama
I'll get the guns for you the little kid high-five me. I mean the exploitiveness of it well
He's killing hundreds of kids in other countries. That's fine. No one cares about that. We have the perv Club
Okay play the perv here's the pervert different meetings
There is nothing that has gone to the heart of the matter more than
The visual image people have a little curve next to his riddle
Not shot in the street
Riddle and one of the guys in that meeting son planned a mass shooting the local cops stopped see how this works
It's like he's salivating over the word riddle. He don't know he has that look
We're gonna riddle you once we get him that's the kind of person you got cranking back up
Have you heard all the clips of piers morgan? I'm not killing Babel. Yes
I mean riddle riddle riddle kids riddle riddle
That's the kind of person you get up on if you're sitting next to on a bus and look at the guy next to it
These are government control freak pervs my pervs. They want to pervert liberty look at that pervs smacking his lips
next to him
With that guy Melissa, oh god, I'm so sick of these people that guy it's like it's like general boy gets scared of him
I don't I'm just way past it. You guys don't control me. I don't care what you do
I'm gonna make sure you go down with me. How's that sound?
All right, that's enough of pervo. All right, we're gonna mean is it fine
Did you see him during the speech with Obama last week the salivating and the he kept fighting the small going?
I
Gotta feed the trolls here on here when I do these little pieces they take it out of context
They've got it clipped together and dubbed my voice saying racist stuff, too
Oh wonderful, but it doesn't all it does is just credit them. Basically. It's a good way to spend your time
Hey good for them. Yeah, they're gonna die cancer early, too
They probably when they beg retching their guts out about to take the all express elevator straight to hell
where the devil and all his angels are waiting to roll with your soul like a
Millstone and take you right to the center of the frozen lake in the Ninth Circle
Gun statistics if you've ever wanted one of our best-selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer so crazy
You couldn't refuse then you're not gonna want to miss this exciting message
Here's why our solar generators provide life-saving electrical power and unlike gas generators solar generators run quietly
Amid no fumes and produce electricity from the Sun. So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need now
Here's the best part every year. We accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of each year
We call them scratch and dead units
But they're really just like new each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses
You just won't believe don't wait. They go fast go to scratch and then solar.com
That's scratch and then solar.com for the craziest offer we've ever made go to scratch and then solar.com
That's scratch and then solar.com
Looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves
How did we ever survive from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy in the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a?
Disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at e foods direct
We hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm by having a supply of food on hand
After Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed
But I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late
I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what Alex has done
Call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply
It's the best tasting non GMO long-term storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four zero nine
Five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct
hemp USA org has a newly designed website and a new and improved
Detoxification product order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins minerals iodine and probiotics
And we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder
Absolutely free micro plant powder only at hemp USA org call nine oh eight six nine one two six zero eight
That's nine oh eight six nine one two six zero eight and see what our powder seeds and oil can do for you only at hemp
USA org this offer ends January 31st. Hi. This is Ted Anderson
Have you ever wondered why banks stockbrokers investment advisors won't talk about gold IRAs?
They've been available since 1986 yet
The financial industry won't recognize the value of gold for your retirement gold is outperform paper investments yet
No word about IRAs if you would like to have gold for your retirement call eight hundred six eight six two two three seven
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns call eight hundred six eight six two two three seven
Secure your future and call one eight hundred six eight six two two three seven
We all know that Berkey water
purification systems are the most trusted name in water filtration as an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years in serving thousands of
Satisfied customers the Berkey guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration systems the Berkey light systems include a set of self
Sterilizing and re-cleanable black purification elements that purify water by removing chlorine pathogenic bacteria cyst and parasites to non-detectable
levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides order the Berkey light system today complete with two black Berkey elements for
only
$231 and the Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge with the purchase of a Berkey light the Berkey guy is also offering
A set of fluoride and arsenic filters for only thirty nine ninety nine
That's over 30% off the retail price call the Berkey guy at one eight seven seven eight eight six three six five three
That's one eight seven seven eight eight six three six five three or order online at go berkey.com
That's go berkey.com today
Now I want to go over these gun statistics with Melissa Melton here from FBI.gov I've talked a lot about these
I just looked at some of the statistics
21% drop in violent crime the last seven years
And then I saw Fox say 49, but they didn't give the actual proof. I went looked it up
They were being accurate 49 plus
Percent since 1991 Melissa Melton's here to cover that that'll hit a few of the headlines up at info wars.com for TV viewers
We're putting graphics up
Showing from FBI.gov and then we break down the numbers and again
This is what you went to college for along with journalism
So you've been helping us crack these numbers, but anybody can go check them for themselves
And then some will say I thought you don't like government numbers
We know which ones are fake from economists and others like the unemployment numbers
Or numbers on inflation they used to be accurate 20 years ago, and they've gotten worse and worse
So we know how they cook them the crime statistics are very accurate as they're compiled locally
And then they're cross referenced by a lot of different universities and others
But the uniform crime statistics go over these for people well these statistics come from
18,000 law enforcement agencies across the whole country and you're talking City College County State
Tribal federal agencies all over so 18,000 they compile this data every single year, and they've been putting it up as from court records
It's all filed the arrest that what was reported to the FBI their reporting system that they've had for many decades
So you got 18,000 groups that can cross-check their info
It's been found to be some of the most accurate numbers out there
Everybody uses this is our most consistent crime data that we have in this country it comes from these numbers in fact
Do they do anything they've been caught inflating it to get money, so it's probably even lower than what they're saying but go over it
Well, okay, so what they have up right now is is from 1992 and if you use the basic calculation for percentages
You'll see that violent crime will start with that has been cut in half since 1992 the 1992 violent crime rate per 100,000 people was
757.7 if you subtract the 2011 violent crime rate that's 386.3 you get 371.4
You divide this by your original 1992 rate that gives you 0.49
Oh to multiply that out to find your percentage, and you're gonna have a decrease of forty nine point zero two percent in violent crime between
1992 and
2011 incredible and the murder rate shows the actually the same decrease from 1992 to 2011 in 1992 the rate was
9.3 in
2011 it fell to 4.7 if you subtract you get 4.6 divide that by your 1992 base rate and again you get a
49% decrease in murder rates in this country from 1992 to 2011 so it's cut in half we have half and
Actually all the major crime categories that the FBI does
Collects all this data for have dropped significantly between 1992 and 2011
As you can see here
I've got all the numbers up there every single one of those numbers has dropped every single one every one the only crime statistics
We see another report on this is the petty crime because criminals are afraid to home invade
Karjak now or knock a woman on the head and that was just
Prolific decades ago because they're scared of getting blown away now you look at
What you ought to do in the next few days is do this versus British crime rates
They've got those numbers just the muggings the stabbings are just off of the charts a much higher rate of rape there than we do
Here also their rape is going off the charts. I mean a lot of their stuff their violent crime is going off the charts
It's much they estimate many states a third of women are packing heat in their purse
You're gonna try to rape her in the parking garage
Well, they're there
They've calling Britain the violent crime capital of the UK because it's higher their rates are higher for violent crime than I believe
Australia South Africa here and Canada so we cover all the statistics
Yeah, that's and that's all the the graphics that I have here all these different statistics
But I mean all of these are consistently down every single thing is consistently down anybody can go they can get these reports
They can see they've put them up every year for the last 20 years
So they can go to the FBI they can download all of it. They can download it for their state
They can look at all of this different information right down, and then you can double-check. Let's say you live in
Fresno, California, or let's say you live in get your specific city, and you can clear water, Florida
You can go check those numbers check it with the newspapers 20 years
You can look at that and they do this every single year and like I said this is used every time a criminal justice study
Is done it's pretty much used every class
I had in grad school we use this data because this is the most consistent data that we have and some people like to detract
And argue about this data and say well it crime is underreported, but if anything I would say
This is the bit was underreported them, and there are obviously some unreported crimes, but that's a constant
Yeah in the pool a lot of statistics
I've read of show it's more reported now
It's easier to report as the internet or report and they let you do it with anonymity which is
unconstitutional in the past you had to go face your accuser right and over the years the FBI has made their system of
Reporting from these local agencies easier for them to report their data as well and have a much more consistent
Well everybody knows there's less crime when I was growing up in Dallas
I remember some weeks when they were like 60 something dead
And because you know in the 60s and 70s everything got real anti-gun and gunnership went way down
They were winning their war body was getting rid of their guns crime exploded all over
But then guns came back and criminals are scared, but any police will tell you that I mean look
You come you you home invade in Texas. You're probably gonna die
Yeah, I mean I've read I read a statistic say and I didn't bring this one in here with me
But assault weapons are only used in what 0.6% of all murders
I know and I kept trying to tell it's kind of kept trying to tell pierce morgan
Hey, these aren't even used you're using this as just a tiny example to blow it up to pull on people's heartstrings
He's like how many murders in England with guns, and I'm like how many murders with knives
And he didn't even cite his sources and then Ben Swann went on and did a report to show all of his sources were incorrect
Anyway, that was a lot higher in England than what he said great job