Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, we interrupt the normal intro to the broadcast to bring
you the would-be dictator-in-chief, shamelessly exploiting children, looking like a bad guy
of a dystopic movie, Barack Obama up there with the other thug, gangster Joe Biden, just
getting ready with 23 executive actions.
And yes, they're now leaking, and he's about to announce it. They're gonna go after gun
owners. They're gonna try to ban our ammo. They're gonna try to make you register. They're
gonna try to make you come turn your guns in. They are gonna release hell on us and
try to get a bunch of bans passed in Congress on top of it. So it's on.
First they take your guns, then they take your property, then they take your children,
then they put you in a forced labor camp, then they take your life. And they are collapsing
America. You see the militarization of police. Dressing like Darth Vader, you see the 1.6
million bullets. We are going into a total collapse and they wanna get our guns beforehand,
or at least say all gun owners are terrorists.
This is the way they're gonna designate conservatives and libertarians the enemy. This is the plan.
We've got to impeach now. I take you to the scumbag in chief, the fraud, the New World
Order minion that's gutting this country and raising taxes on poor people to mercilessly
bankrupt them.
They've got laws passed, so companies cut people's hours from 40 to 29. Just the man
who wants you bankrupt, Mr. agenda 21, himself using dead children. The sickening vampire,
the psychic vampire pig, Barack Hussein Obama with his other thug, Biden. Here it is.
One thing we can do to reduce this violence. If there's even one life that can be saved.
We've got to please Biden this.
Then we've got an obligation to try. Really, all the Prozac the kids are on? Number one
cause of death, now suicide, cuz you people putting 60 million people on psychotropics.
At that desk and I will sign a directive giving law enforcement, schools, mental health professionals
and the public health community some of the tools they need to help reduce gun violence.
The Federal Thought Police, it's the New York bill.
It will make it easier to keep guns out of the hands of criminals.
The New York bill.
By strengthening the background check system.
Oh really, this guy tried to get a gun five times.
We will help schools hire more resource officers.
And couldn't.
If they want them.
Resource officers to spy on the kids, not to protect them.
We will make sure mental health professionals know their options for reporting threats of
violence.
That's right.
Then the more more psychiatrists in the schools are more likely kids on psychotropics than
the perpetrator.
They're gonna stage more shootings.
They're behind it.
You can just see.
Year after year.
Those who oppose even modest gun safety measures have threatened to defund scientific or medical
research.
This guy has always said he wants to take all our guns.
They want all the guns.
It isn't reasonable what you want, you liar.
There's ways to reduce it.
And Congress should fund research into the effects that violent video games have on young
minds.
They'll never stop them.
We don't benefit from ignorance.
We don't benefit from not knowing the science of this epidemic of violence.
You know the science.
You know they were developed for murder fantasizing.
These are a few of the 23 executive actions that I'm announcing today.
But as important as these steps are.
You know they're murder simulators.
They are in no way a substitute for action for members of Congress.
You know they were given to the military so they'd kill up close.
To make a real and lasting difference.
Get the Prozac heads off the Prozac.
And Congress must act.
Stop pushing murder suicide pills.
You new world order scumbag.
I'm calling on Congress to pass some very specific proposals-
Take the floor out of the water.
Stop giving kids blue shots.
It's killing them.
Stop killing kids with drones all over the world.
First, it's time for Congress to require a universal background check for anyone trying
to buy a gun.
That means transferring it to your family.
That's right.
General control.
Shutting down.
And they're going to say guns are retroactively illegal.
That you legally bought.
Look at that parade in those little kids.
They're already required as licensed gun dealers to run background checks.
And over the last 14 years that's kept 1.5 million of the wrong people from getting their
hands on a gun.
But it's hard to enforce that law when as many as 40% of all gun purchases are conducted
without a background check.
Yeah, they're going to start raiding people.
They've already announced this.
That's not safe.
And saying your guns are illegal and saying where'd you get them?
It's not fair to responsible gun buyers or sellers.
And he's going to talk about expanding the size of the ATF.
If you want to buy a gun, whether it's from a licensed dealer or a private seller, you
should at least have to show you are not a felon.
We're going to break here.
We'll come back with more of the aftermath.
This is common sense.
You notice I'm wearing camo.
I'm part of the citizen militia.
I have a right to own guns.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now.
Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy.
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At eFoods Direct we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all of the grocery stores
are closed but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared ten years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Crashing through the lies and disinformation, it's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
The right to keep and bear arms shall not be infringed.
It is the 16th day of January, 2013.
We have been watching and taking notes, it's exactly what we thought, 23 devastating attacks
with executive actions and executive orders on the Second Amendment.
Doctors are going to spy on people and report to the CPS.
If you own guns in the home, even though they're not illegal, they are to harass gun owners.
They are to swat team gun owners' homes.
If you sell a gun to any friends or family, they're gonna claim that's a felony.
They're gonna try to make you retroactively prove the providence of your guns.
They are going to try to put taxes on ammo.
They're gonna massively expand the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco and Firearms so they can
ship more guns into Mexico to kill more people in false flags so they can blame the Second
Amendment.
He's rattling this all off while pimping out poor little children that he's exploiting
up there on the stage, knowing the federal government made the schools gun-free zones.
And then the media hyped, hey, an option for crazies on Prozac or other drugs who play
shoot-em-up games all day, go to the school and kill people.
And they're trying to put, collectively, the guilt of dead kids on us for our Second Amendment.
Because they want us to live like folks do in Chicago and New York with the highest crime
rates in the world.
Because the victims have been disarmed with thug cops everywhere, feeding on people along
with thugs in the streets.
Meanwhile, good cops all over the US in cities and towns saying, we're not gonna enforce
this, guns make us safer.
They want us to be like they are in other areas like Chicago and LA, where everybody
lives in fear.
And they're like in Oakland, big shoot-em-ups every night.
Because they're a mafia, let's go back to this thug exploiting these children.
When he swore to never go after our guns, here it is.
The only way we can change is if the American people demand it.
He wants to rally everybody.
And by the way, that doesn't just mean from certain parts of the country.
They're organizing on a jihad after our guns.
We're gonna need voices in those areas, in those congressional districts where the tradition
of gun ownership is strong.
The fight is on folks.
To speak up.
If they can take the guns, they can take everything.
They're gonna take the pension funds.
It can't just be the usual suspects.
They're gonna totally bankrupt us.
That's why they're militarizing the police, armored vehicles, billions of bullets.
We have to examine ourselves and our hearts.
Yeah, examine your hearts.
We have to examine ourselves.
Just cuz you got a peace prize and you're supposedly half black, doesn't mean you get
to be a dictator.
This will not happen unless the American people demand it.
All the stupid trendies think it's so cute.
Yeah, and you know what?
They put themselves in the moral high ground position knowing there's gonna be more mass
shootings.
And if they have to, they'll stage them.
Like Larry Pratt said.
Responsible gun owners, if Americans of every background stand up and say, enough.
If they'd staged fast and furious, they'd stage this.
They'd stage Aurora.
Too much pain and care too much about our children to allow this to continue, then change
will come.
Look at Biden.
That's what it's gonna take.
On the letter that Julia wrote me, she said, I know that laws have to be passed by Congress,
but I beg you to try very hard.
Julia I will try very hard.
Folks, this is so sick.
He's now looking at the little children.
Now the children are gonna tell us turn our guns in.
The government- They need to bring these proposals up for a vote.
Goes and says the kids say do this.
Make sure that they do.
Unbelievable the president rallying to overturn the Second Amendment and using five and six
year old children.
No background checks to keep guns out of the wrong place.
Fade that down.
Ask them if they- That's killing private transfer, giving guns as gifts, which they know.
Ladies and gentlemen, this government shipped guns into Mexico to cause carnage.
The CBS News got the memos to blame the Second Amendment.
They killed thousands over there, hundreds over here, including five police officers,
three of them border patrol, conservatively.
They are so cold blooded.
And these sweet little kids up there he's using, again, this is what Al Gore said a
few years ago.
He went to public schools and said, you heard the audio, you tell your parents pay carbon
taxes.
You tell them, you know best.
Every authoritarian society goes to the kids and says, you tell your parents what to do.
This is outrageous.
And so they handpicked kids' letters that have been mailed in, Million Mom March kids
and other people.
And then they sit there and display them and go, I'm gonna get the guns for you, little
kid.
And now you're against the little kids if you don't take the guns.
I mean, this is so transparent.
This is a guy that lied to everybody and said, I will not raise taxes unless you make a quarter
million a year.
And he raised it on people making 30,000 a year.
And even lower in some actuaries, Obama phone lady got her latest paycheck.
And they took even more out.
Everybody in my office gets more taken out now.
And that's just the beginning.
It's all these lies.
It's like being informed is like torturous.
Let's go back.
Let's go back right now back to the would be dictator who again is saying Congress needs
to do this.
But I do have-
The right to worship freely and safely.
That right was denied to Sikhs in Oak Creek, Wisconsin.
The right to assemble peaceably.
That right was denied-
Now he's saying the Second Amendment is attacking all our other rights.
No, the drug war has created a thug culture.
The giant prisons are colleges of crime.
And we've got guns that are holding your crime wave back.
Fading down.
That were denied.
We are holding your crime wave back and you hate the fact that crime using guns in the
last 16, 17 years has dropped 49%.
And that overall violent crimes dropped 21% fbi.gov.
Real local numbers compiled and filed.
You hate that concealed carry is pushing back your urban crime wave.
You hate the fact that people in big cities illegally have guns to protect themselves.
You hate it.
You want total control to do to us whatever you want, you gangster thug.
And that's why I've written a citizen's move.
And people ask me, well, how are you saying citizens, like citizen arrest?
I filed articles of impeachment publicly at prisonplanet.com and infowars.com that I wrote
last night in consultation with Paul Watson and Aaron Dykes.
Where I lay out where congressmen and others have shown we're in the Constitution.
Obama is done impeachable offenses clearly on their face.
Saying the UN runs our military and Congress isn't over war now.
Saying he can shut down coal power plants without a law, telling Congress to fly a kite.
Saying he can launch Libya and Syria attacks and telling Congress to go to hell.
Saying he's gonna have orders to restrict guns outside of law.
Running fast and furious, caught lying about that.
It's all listed there and that's meant now to get that passed around.
It's kinda like when a state passes a law and then other states pick up the law.
And even if that state doesn't pass it, the law being written may be adopted by others.
I've just put out a basic template to everybody and god bless drudgereport.com last night
for linking to it and getting it up there.
Infowars is getting its record all time, 15 year traffic right now.
That Infowars 15 years but on there 17.
Record since 1997, record traffic right now and the site is up and down.
And I'm trying to hire more IT folks to help the guys I got, they're like Scotty in the
engine room.
And we're hiring consultants, you name it, but I mean, it's just sustained set of a million
visitors between the sites every day that we normally get.
It's like two, three million a day.
And so we're trying to keep it up, but my citizens petition.
Citizen files petition to impeach Obama.
Citizen files, in fact, let me give you the exact headline.
Here it was up on Drudge Report, it was up there since last night, it may have been taken
down.
My own headline is on there because my site had gone down.
The point is that it's up on infowars.com and it is right there.
Citizens file articles of impeachment against Obama.
We can actually put that up on screen for everybody and it goes through it all.
Right there, ladies and gentlemen, the government is massing armaments against us, illegally
spying on us, buying billions of bullets, launching drones in the air, training kids
to spy on their parents, turning the entire system on its head, going down a list of tyrannical
actions and just checking them off.
Training the police and military for gun confiscation, in official army manuals.
In fact, we need to add that as articles of impeachment.
Since 2010, Obama has directed the Secretary of Defense to add this training for domestic
operations.
Here he is shaking hands with the poor little kids, let's put it back up there.
Those poor little victims, take the guns or you don't support these kids, totally disgusting.
We've got it all recorded.
We're gonna be playing clips of this throughout the broadcast, but citizens file articles
of impeachment against Obama.
It is up on infowars.com and again, if the site is down for you, you can simply type
in citizens file articles of impeachment against Obama and it's signed by Alex Jones.
Just like I can go in and swear out an affidavit that I saw my neighbor burying somebody in
their backyard, just like I can go swear out an affidavit that I saw my neighbor dumping
poison in the well.
Just like you can swear out an affidavit that yes, you saw this guy run out of the liquor
store with a bag of money in his hand.
Well, I've seen treason, I've studied the Bill of Rights and Constitution, and I've
gone and seen what the constitutional lawyers are saying and members of Congress.
This is all impeachable.
He's already done a bunch of impeachable stuff.
We're always like, if you do more, we're gonna start impeachment.
If you do more, and they tell people in Congress, you want your airplane to blow up?
You want your car to run off the road?
Because these are gangsters.
Well, you know what?
I'm here.
You know what?
They kill me.
That's the way it is.
I'm like my forebears.
I cannot be a slave.
I know tyrants when I see it and I am not gonna, let me tell you this.
You either leave the country and it's a global government, they're taking over everywhere.
The same corporate fraud, the same corporate fascism, using socialism to indenture us,
to enslave us, to domesticate us.
You either leave the country or you fight back.
Because let me tell you something, they are gonna drop the hammer.
Folks, they've signed us on to 1,500 trillion.
The Chinese government, communists that have, folks type in Bloomberg, I wanna show them
a photo of it, suicide nets at Apple factories.
The 20 story factories where they drug them and they do forced abortions.
So all they do, by the hundreds, we're jumping off to commit suicide.
So they put nets there.
One person jumps, everybody copycats and goes up to jump because they're there.
They're drugged.
They're made to work 18 hours a day.
They put help me notes in the packages inside Apple's Foxconn factories that Al Gore's on
the board.
He's the one that demands they have the worst pay in China, slave labor.
Suicide nets installed at the dorms, okay?
They live in 100 square foot cubicles just like Bloomberg wants to set up.
This is a plan.
The globalists made a deal with China in the 70s to have the lowest standard in the world
to leverage out the United States and to buy our debt.
The globalists are clients with the Chinese government against the American people, against
their own people.
And the Chinese government came out three weeks ago and said, we own your debt, take
the guns.
That's an order.
That is a UN order through the Chinese.
I mean, they said, you will take the guns, we own your debt.
And Obama is hell-bent to get them.
Of course, they sent mercenaries in there to do that.
It's the oldest trick in the book.
Same thing with Colorado, has all the signs.
You send in the shooters, have the mental patient saying, I don't know who I am drugged
up in the parking lot, or you shoot the drug head in the back of the head and your guys
get out.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
a life storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all of the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e Foods Direct.
Is this the year you finally get serious about your family's drinking water?
If so, keep listening for a special offer from Big Berkey Water Filters.
Did you know that over 60% of municipal water is fluoridated?
Berkey Water Filters distinguish themselves from many other filtration systems with the
capability to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine, fluoride, arsenic, and disinfection
byproducts from municipal water via the black Berkey and PF line of filters.
Then there's affordability.
At only 1.7 cents per gallon, Berkey Water Filters purify treated and untreated water,
even stagnant pond water.
Stop and think how much money you could save by simply reducing buying bottled water and
using water filtered by your Berkey Water Filter.
No need to be constantly replacing expensive filters with a Berkey.
A single set of filters can last for 5 to 10 years.
Choose the best size Berkey for your needs at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
And right now, all GCN listeners get 5% off all ceramic filter systems.
Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY.
That's 877-99-B-E-R-K-E-Y or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
Free shipping on every order over $50.
Big Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean water.
HempUSA.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine, and probiotics.
And we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder absolutely free.
Micro plant powder only at HempUSA.org.
Call 908-691-2608.
That's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
Join this offer ends January 31st.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson.
Have you ever wondered why banks, stock workers, investment advisors won't talk about gold
IRAs?
They've been available since 1986, yet the financial industry won't recognize the value
of gold for your retirement.
Gold is outperformed paper investments, yet no word about IRAs.
If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns.
Call 800-686-2237.
Secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
American gardeners and fellow Patriots make the right choice with your money, time, and
your family food supply.
Choose 100% pure heirloom seeds in the Survival Seed Vault from MyPatriotSupply.com.
Why spend more?
The Survival Seed Vault from MyPatriotSupply.com is only $37.95 and includes 20 varieties of
pure, hardy, easy to grow heirloom seeds.
Yes, only $37.95.
That's 70% less than our competitors.
You could buy three Survival Seed Vaults for less than one of theirs.
The Survival Seed Vault from MyPatriotSupply.com includes detailed planting and seed saving
instructions and ships same day.
Plus, all orders over $49 ship free.
MyPatriotSupply.com is American-owned by Patriots like you, passionate about freedom and preparedness.
Call now, 866-229-0927.
That's 866-229-0927 or discover more emergency preparedness items when you order at MyPatriotSupply.com.
Choose the original.
Choose the Survival Seed Vault at MyPatriotSupply.com.
I'm gonna try to settle down here and be as calm as I can about all of this, but you have
to understand something.
They have passed laws, what, five years ago where they can basically take private pension
funds.
They haven't started the full move to get them.
They've done some tests.
They're talking about taking federal pension funds.
You notice in Europe this is happening.
You notice that they got massive tax increases through, including on the poorest working
Americans, 14 different taxes in the last raft of legislation that they rammed through
in the fake financial cliff.
Now they're back saying, we're in debt again.
Bernanke, the real head of this country, the head of the private Federal Reserve said yesterday,
let's just get rid of a debt ceiling entirely.
They've decided to go Weimar Republic.
They've decided to go Zimbabwe.
And do you know what that means?
It means hyperinflation.
But stag hyperinflation because you're not gonna have jobs on top of things increasing
in price.
And you're going to go from 25 million to 50 million on food stamps.
We've now crossed that Rubicon to 100 million.
And crime is just going to explode.
But see, these big city mafia types, they know what they do.
They shut things off, get people dependent, ship in the drugs.
Government ships in most of the drugs.
That's on record congressional hearings, 1997, Solicitor General, the CIA, it's on record.
Everybody knows that.
They destabilize the society, the working people, the middle class gets scared to say,
take whatever rights you want, just keep me safe from the street thugs.
And they know exactly what they're doing.
The problem is, you've had gun ownership in all 50 states go off the chart in the last
20 years roughly.
Gun ownership has exploded, the gun culture has exploded.
And so you've seen a 49%, I did a report on this last week, I'm gonna do another one today
or tomorrow with the fbi.gov numbers.
Cuz you know, I kept showing violent crime down 21% in the last 15, 16 years, 11 points
of that in the last, what, since 2007, last six years roughly.
So it's accelerating the drop in overall violent crime, mugging, stabbings, beatings, shootings.
And then I was there watching Fox News, and they were at fbi.gov, and they showed crime
with guns down a whopping 49%.
You go to fbi.gov, I know the media is listening, go look it up, Fox News had it on.
I got my iPad, typed it in, went and found it.
People were saying to me, Alex, it's higher crime rate drop than what you said.
Why are you putting out this info?
I was going off one statistic, 49.
They cannot stand that, folks, that you're in charge, that you've got a gun, that criminals
are scared, that every day there's a new 911 tape in the news.
But it's always just local, never national, where the woman's on 911 going, don't come
in.
Okay, he's busted down the front door.
I'm going in the bathroom.
911's like, yes, yes, don't engage him, go in the bathroom and hide.
He's busting down this door, his arm's coming through a hole, he opened it.
I'm gonna shoot him, boom, boom, boom, boom, dead.
Or the guy crawls out and dies on the street, or crawls out and is bleeding and the cops
come and get him.
That's what we're talking about.
You see it constantly because of sites like infowars.com and worldnetdaily.com and drudgereport.com
that break the establishment media blockade.
ABC, NBC, CBS, they will never, ever, ever, ever, ever show you that information, 49?
I didn't even know that.
I mean, I'd heard the numbers and seen them over the years, a 20 plus percent reduction
in violent crime within three years after a concealed carry went in in Florida, same
number in Texas.
But I guess it's been compounding now over the last decade or more, 49.
I was sitting there and I go, that can't be true, 49.
That's almost a 50% cut in crimes using guns.
And this criminal is up there on TV using kids, and let me tell you, I had him faded
down.
It's a good thing when it was live.
During the break, they were queuing it up back there, we're gonna get it ready for you.
Instant high def off the TV, we gotta break it down to play it here on the radio and streaming
on the web.
Point is, we can't just instantly convert that high def.
We should set up where we can instantly play high def out here once it's been taped, but
whatever.
The point is, you saw it, he high fived the kids with a big stinking smile, and Biden
could hardly stop smiling.
He was trying to have a serious look, and I wanna do a piece on that, alert to the real
media out there.
Biden, a bunch, was going, especially when he was first introducing Obama, he was trying
not to smile.
He was going.
Yeah, I'm gonna get that gun, baby.
Yeah, I'm a gangster, I mean, Biden is a gangster, he is a thug, and so is Obama.
They're a bunch of slick thugs.
Let me tell you something, your Chicago, New York gangster crap doesn't fly in Texas.
You got that, scum?
We're on the march, the empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver-based products.
Our most popular silver-based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two
ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well as our all natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and
leave the silver at the surface, but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the
natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the
skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver-based products
are best for you.
That's www.silverlungs.com.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die?
Start purifying your water with ProPure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none
is ProPure and it's available discounted at infowars.com.
These filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified.
Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%, easy to set up and use, doesn't
require electricity, purify water from lakes, streams, ponds, and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
ProPure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on ProPure, but if you add the promo code
water at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support, and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
I was trained in firearms.
I carried a concealed weapon.
I made the determination that if somebody was going to try to take me out, I was going
to take them with me.
If I could have gotten 51 votes in the Senate of the United States for an outright ban,
picking up every one of them, Mr. and Mrs. America, turn them all in, I would have done
it.
Defending the Republic from enemies foreign and domestic.
That's Alex Jones.
I'm going to try to settle down here as best I can.
I want to open the phones up so you can respond to this.
David Knight's got the transcript, one of our reporters in there, of Obama and Biden's
speech.
There were 23 executive actions and executive orders.
They didn't give any particulars.
Well, here's the deal.
If you go watch the two hour long C-SPAN last week of Rahm Emanuel and others at that socialist
think tank.
We posted the whole video on Infowars.com a few days ago.
They lay out the whole plan.
He says we're just gonna let police take the guns.
We're gonna just target gun owners and claim they have the guns illegally.
We're gonna shut down the gun manufacturers, we're gonna lean on the gun sellers.
We're gonna use mafia tactics, that's what he's saying.
And again, they're gonna deputize the medical tyranny, the same people that are already
giving kids shots without parental consent, to basically call in endangerment orders when
they call your kid aside and ask him about guns.
They had to pass a law on the healthcare bill that conservatives put in there to where it
made it illegal for them to do that.
But Obama doesn't care.
He says I'm telling doctors you do this.
It was doctors that put that guy Lanza and Holmes on all those psychotropic drugs and
Harris and Kleibold and the list goes on and on.
And nothing was said about drugs in that speech.
I've got the transcript.
I didn't watch the whole thing cuz I was talking over it, but correct?
And I mean, let me have that transcript, I forgot and left it out there, thank you.
I mean, that is just amazing.
By the way, drudgereport.com, it has all the latest stuff on this, so does infowars.com.
The problem is infowars is up and down because of the incredible traffic.
Kurt thought it was a denial of service attack.
They looked at the traffic, no, it's all time record traffic, which I'm not happy about.
If we turn this country around, I would literally have a show about science and a show about
literature and movies and about camping and stuff.
I would have a once a week, three hour radio, TV show, variety show.
I mean, I'd have like magicians on and stuff.
I would have a interesting, it'd be like a Johnny Carson show, okay?
I don't like having to do this, but I am completely possessed with resistance to tyranny.
I am completely animated.
I cannot control myself.
I can hardly sleep because I know we're dealing with criminal tyrants.
Drudgereport.com, there it is, citizens file articles of impeachment against Obama.
And then you go to infowars.com and it is right there.
And again, I wrote this, I wrote articles of impeachment a year ago that didn't get
any attention.
I wrote this with Paul Watson over the telephone last night because he can type better than
I can.
It would take me five hours if I typed it myself cuz I just make mistakes and go back
and use a spell checker.
So we wrote this in about two hours together on the phone, but I think I probably need
to get Watson on the phone during a break.
And just add, so people understand, the original Declaration of Independence started as citizens'
petitions called Bill of Particulars in all of the 13 colonies circulated listing the
crimes that government was committing against the free rights of an Englishman that they'd
fought in 1215 to get and then again with the Parliament Act.
Most of the Parliament supported our secession until the King of England basically threatened
to arrest a bunch of them.
And King George III rode to Parliament and addressed Parliament that was unheard of and
said your duty as Englishman is to get in there and take down these rebels.
And they again threatened to arrest more people if they didn't get in line.
So the king bullied, they would have kept the colonies, we'd still be part of England
folks if they, but hey, I'm a British citizen.
My ancestors fought for the right for me to have guns and swords and cannons.
And I need these to protect myself from the French and the Spanish and the Indians.
They were all fighting each other.
They were all teaming up together at different times.
I mean, it was amazing.
There were wars where you'd have 10,000 people get killed.
I mean, the westerns all advertise everything that happened from the 1860s on with the Comanche
and the Apaches, that was nothing.
There were wars with weird rebel settler groups like something out of Conan the Barbarian.
And 20,000 Indians with groups of whites and escaped slaves in Andrew Jackson's time and
before that would come pouring down out of the Illinois territory.
And just huge wars and whole towns and cities burned and tens of thousands dead.
No one even knows this history.
I mean, it was just Conan the Barbarian.
They never make movies out of any of that because that's not what they wanted to popularize
because the real history is so incredible.
My point is nobody was good in that.
Everybody was barbarous.
Everybody was making side deals.
This Indian tribe coming and saying, English, help me take out these guys with the French
and I'll help you divide and conquer the whole nine yards.
And the redcoats came and said, we're coming to confiscate your guns.
And another thing is the Englishman didn't like the militarized police and the checkpoints
and their wives being searched physically.
And so they would go and beat up redcoats and redcoats would come and shoot the brigands
as they call them.
And then the men would go ahead and shoot back.
And then the redcoats said, that's it, people are starting to shoot back.
We're coming to take your guns, line up and turn them in.
And about half the population turned their guns in.
But if they were Tories, pro-king, you can keep your gun.
In fact, you're now in the king's militia, go and kill whoever you want.
And it was the abuses and it was the outrages and it was the king's militias abusing and
raping and burning and stealing and shaking people down that turned the colonies against
the king and the redcoats.
This went on for 15 years roughly.
Imagine you're taking apples to town for sale and you come up and there is a government
auxiliary SWAT team aiming a cannon at you out of the back of the wagon and they got
guns and they say get out.
And they come and they steal your apples and they reach into your purse, your wallet and
take your money.
And you're like, I've got to have that to buy seeds for next year.
That's everything I've worked for for a year.
And they're just like, stand him up, break his jaw.
And if you complained about it, they take your wife and kids and they put them in stocks
till they died.
A torture apparatus with your head and arms in it.
You know how Andrew Jackson, Andrew Jackson, you know how his mother and brother died?
In a concentration camp.
So he joined the rebellion when he was 11 years old and ran messages and he wouldn't
brag about it.
So the history is 100% nailed down, but also snipered British soldiers.
He's 11, 12, 13, 14 years old, okay?
That's where our country came from, ladies and gentlemen.
That's what our country was born out of.
People's mothers tied up in a concentration camp to die, okay?
And that's where every government ends up going.
In Russia, in Germany, in China, in Cuba, and in England has had these wars over and
over again.
The reason the British are so polite is that it goes back to the age of chivalry in the
15th, 16th, 17th century.
If you were rude to someone, and it all came out of the enlightenment and people becoming
free, it was I don't care who you are, you insult me, you be a lord, you be anybody.
You're gonna get in a fight with me, I'm gonna call you out.
And no one's gonna associate with you ever again if you don't pull your sword or walk
your 20 paces and we're gonna fight to the death right now, okay?
You just insulted me, you just acted like a tough gang banger, get out in the street,
somebody's gonna die right now.
An armed society is a polite society, and if you're watching me on TV today, if you're
watching the radio streams on TV right now, you notice I'm wearing my camouflage duck
hunting jacket.
And of course, in a real urban warfare situation, camouflage would be a sports jacket, suit
and tie, all right?
With a collapsible rifle in the small of my back.
I am not an offensive military person, even though I have the basic skills of a rifleman
passed on since the founding of this country and before.
But the reason I'm wearing camouflage and the new t-shirt that we're selling that by
the way has blown away any shirt we've ever sold, it's an AK-47 says come and take it.
What my ancestor said at Gonzales, Texas, you come and take it.
You wanna take our guns, Santa Ana, you come and take them.
That was only 50 years or less after the Revolutionary War.
And it says inside the AK-47, the right to keep and bear arms shall not be infringed.
Boom, that is the all time bestseller and you support our info war, it's a war bond.
It's got infoawars.com on the back, wear your colors proud, meet like minded patriots.
And let me tell you, the reason I'm so focused, the reason I'm so angry is also I am risking
my life, my treasure, my name to be out front and say, let's have the second American Revolution,
have the state secede, pull out, re-upload the republic, which is in the Declaration
of Independence.
It's not our right, it's our duty to absolve the government and then create a new one.
Well, we want our republic back.
So you're not real, you're global sympathizers, you're Vici French to the Nazis, get out.
We re-upload the republic.
And I've had top constitutional lawyers that advise Congress, advise Ron Paul, Harvard
lawyers on, they agree with my analysis, okay?
Cuz it's not my analysis, it's 1776, it's Declaration of Independence, it's July 4th,
it's everything.
But I gotta tell you, it's inbred, all these Texans that you see, like Stockton and Toth
and all the rest of them, I've gone and looked into these people.
They've all been five, six, seven, eight generation Texans, who were the very frontline of the
most radical, violent, but smart and aggressive, adventurous Americans in frontier expansion.
And some of the most vicious ongoing wars went on here, Indian wars, you name it.
And so it's not a macho thing that Texans are saying.
And notice it's Texans saying, hey, it isn't happening, it's that it's genetic.
I don't care if you're black, white, Hispanic, who you are.
If you're a Texan and your ancestors go back, you are hot blooded and you're ready because
your ancestors were willing to be in the violent frontier.
You know Pancho Villa, there was a long civil war in the north of Mexico.
The Mexican government tried to take their guns, and what was it, a ten year civil war?
Killed hundreds of thousands of people, it's estimated, it was incredible.
Because up in the north of Mexico was just as wild as Texas.
People are like, you're gonna take my gun when there's wolves and coyotes and bandits
and everybody?
You're not taking my gun?
And the central government said, we are gonna take your guns.
There was a civil war in Mexico, a couple of them.
You know what, they didn't win, Mexico didn't win against Guatemala and they had guns.
That's why Guatemala is Guatemala.
The point is everybody wants their guns.
Because folks, it's bold that he's going after the guns.
When he wants the moral high ground, they're gonna stage something else.
White House readies 23 executive actions developing, press doctors to ask patients about guns at
home, healthcare providers to offer gun safety tips, counselors in schools.
It'll be a big gun demonization thing where kids say bang, bang with their fingers, have
a Nerf gun.
They shut down whole blocks and arrest the kid, I mean, at least 4.5 billion in new spending
to demonize and prosecute and harass gun owners and hold us up like we're child molesters,
which is what the Attorney General said they do.
Ignores violent movies, video games, pro-gun senator vows to push new gun laws.
See, there's all these disgusting defections.
White House releases letters from pleading children and then high fives them.
They couldn't help but smile.
Hospitals to stop delivering babies because of Obamacare.
Man, that's incredible.
Look at this.
NRA plans fight of the century.
Citizens file articles of impeachment against Obama.
Again, that's top right hand side of drugsreport.com.
Easiest way to find it, get it.
And again, I'm gonna call Watson during a break.
And I'm going to basically add the point at the top so that laymen out there don't understand
that I've had constitutional lawyers on that agree with this premise.
You've got to first put out what's impeachable, and then we link to proof and lawyers and
news articles admitting it's impeachable.
I mean, him becoming the head of the UN Security Council, which they admitted on the news,
violated Article I, Section 9 of the Constitution, to serve a foreign power or to hold another
office at the same time of government.
Totally illegal.
I mean, it's a felony.
Article I, Section 9, boom, got you right there, boom, got you right there.
I mean, we got you over and over again.
It'd be like a cop driving by and seeing somebody cooking methamphetamine in their front yard
in a bathtub.
And you can smell it.
You walk up.
Is that methamphetamine?
Yeah, it's methamphetamine.
Boom, you're going to jail.
I mean, it's an absolute red-handed.
It'd be like catching Jerry Sandusky in the showers raping a kid.
Of course, he didn't get in trouble cuz it was a giant pedophile command base.
But the point is, that's what it's like.
I mean, it is in the act.
It is caught in the act, caught in the bank with a gun saying, give me the money.
And an off-duty cop pulls a gun or a concealed carry person and says, hands up.
And you got security cameras, you got witnesses, you got everybody sought, forgotten country.
You were in there saying, give me the money or I'm gonna shoot you.
Boom, you're going to prison.
There's no doubting it, okay?
All we've got to do, see, this is what dictators did.
Hitler did it, others have done it.
Lenin didn't grab all the power right away.
They slowly get away with whatever they want.
They slowly do whatever they want.
And listen, even in East Germany, one of the greatest police states ever, they had all
these great rights and liberties in their constitution, just no one followed them.
And it took citizens not complying, saying no, criticizing the system, whisper campaigns,
supporting good police, going against bad police, until it finally just collapsed.
I'm gonna take a few phone calls in this segment and the next, then we're gonna get Pastor
Manning on with his take on this show.
He prayed for me when I was in New York and he prayed when we were getting stalked by
Bloomberg thugs.
And I wanna get his take on all this cuz he said, you watch, Obama's gonna try to become
a dictator.
And I was naive four years ago.
I knew he was bad, but I didn't think they'd move this quick.
And then we're gonna have Representative Steven Toth, or Toth as he pronounces it, on, who
I just saw on, and that is somebody who needs to be in Congress, he's state rep.
I just saw him on Wolf Blitzer when I was in the coffee room for about two minutes.
And I mean, he was well-spoken, had incredible demeanor, looked super sharp, that is what
we need.
And he explained, look, I don't care if you pass laws in Congress saying you can take
the guns, it would take an amendment.
And even that would be unconstitutional cuz it only points out on the right that already
exist.
We're not gonna put up with this, and Texas is gonna nullify this.
And Wolf Blitzer's like, you can't do that.
Really, how come all these states then let the illegal aliens be not arrested?
He knows what he's talking about, and I haven't talked to him yet, but it sounds like he's
a listener.
So again, that's what I'm doing here.
Let me tell you the real power of this broadcast, by the grace of God.
For all my problems, I am a real person who loves liberty and is willing to die for it
if it takes that.
And I'm on the line here, and the info I'm putting out more and more is getting to other
people.
And that's exactly what's happening right now, thanks to DrudgeReport.com, Citizens
File Articles of Impeachment Against Obama.
And I need to write a first line in there that I'm gonna add just explaining.
This is how our original Declaration of Independence started.
They were Bill of Particulars passed around showing the use of patience in crimes.
This can now be picked up by Congress or added to.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but were waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not gonna wanna miss this exciting message.
Here's why.
Solar generators provide life-saving electrical power, and unlike gas generators, solar generators
run quietly, emit no fumes, and produce electricity from the sun.
So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part.
Every year, we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse, and we discount them heavily at the end of
each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait.
They go fast.
Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
Don't throw away leftovers.
Instead, throw all your leftovers, vegetable peels, eggshells, coffee grounds, pizza crusts,
and more into the Bokashi.
If you love to garden and compost but don't like the hassle of turning a compost bin or
the smell, then check out the EM Bokashi Food Waste Recycling System from Tereganics.
Finally, a way to recycle all your food and plant waste safely and effectively and stop
using fertilizers, the EM Bokashi Food Waste Recycling System.
Rather than decomposition, the Bokashi system uses fermentation to break down waste, so
it takes less time to create nutrient-dense humus for crops or gardens with no turning
and no obnoxious odors.
To learn more and order your Bokashi online, visit tereganics.com and click on the orange
button.
That's tereganics.com, spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X.com, or call 866-369-3678.
That's 866-369-3678.
Recycle all your food waste in about six weeks with the Bokashi Food Waste Recycling System
from tereganics.com.
Tereganics, life's getting better.
Weakened by GMOs, stressed out about money, and blasted by the electric environment.
Hi, I'm Pastor Jenny, and that was the state I was in back in 2010.
Then I learned about RNA drops.
I learned that 97% of my DNA that scientists have called junk is actually packed with millions
of gene switches that play a critical role in controlling how my cells, organs, and other
tissues behave.
I learned I don't have to put up with disease decay or decline like I'd been conditioned
to believe.
I began taking RNA drops, a 100% natural formula designed to turn on those switches and provide
me with amazing health and joy.
Learn more about RNA drops and order a free sample today.
Visit RNAfreesample.com.
That's RNAfreesample.com, or call toll-free, 888-577-3703.
Pay only shipping and handling for a free 30-day supply of RNA drops.
Get the information you need and the health you want at RNAfreesample.com.
Well, the globalists have really gambled.
It was mentioned 49 times and drugs were mentioned zero times, when the drugs are the main cause,
the main cause, guaranteed, on record.
And Representative Steve Stockman of Obama violates the Constitution, a lot of people
will call for his impeachment, NRA ad we're gonna be playing, Obama is elitist hypocrite,
toll-free number to join us, 800-259-9231 for you to respond to what the globalists
are doing.
I just wanna say this, I wanna thank God for my provision and protection, and I wanna thank
all of you, the listeners, and I wanna thank our AM&FM affiliates, because I know reality
is a crazy thing, and I know it sounds wild even having me on the air, and I appreciate
all of our stations, we're getting a lot more by the grace of God.
I wanna thank the real media, not the state-run media, that have helped us over the years,
George Norrie really helped us get to a higher level, DrudgeReport.com just obviously resonates
with our analysis, and it's just turbo charging, it's not even the word what we're doing, probably
get me killed, this keeps going, but whatever, at least we're gonna beat the globalist.
Because I mean, can you imagine, it's like Alex Jones at Infowars.com, it's already a
force with a giant rocket strapped to its butt.
And so I'm like Wile E. Cody on top of the big rocket lighting the fuse, or Matt Drudge
is back there.
So I wanna thank you for loving liberty, and listen, when it's all said and done, I know
we don't do this because of ego, we do it because we don't wanna be slaves.
It's our instinct to get really upset about a bunch of lying crooks trying to disarm us.
But when it's all said and done, the people that have fought this tyranny, none of us
are perfect.
But the folks over at WorldNetDaily, people like Drudge and his crew, my crew, man, there's
so few.
I mean, I've gotta be honest, there's so few that really are hardcore, that really know
what's going on.
He's not perfect in many ways, but he defends the Bill of Rights, Michael Savage, I mean,
there's just not many.
Glenn Beck does nasty stuff to me on the side, but he does a lot of good work.
So you know what?
As long as he doesn't say Ron Paul's supporters should be arrested again, like he said four
years ago, I wanna bury the hatchet with Glenn Beck.
I say that a lot and then he comes out and says I'm a fascist, but you know what?
Fascists wear fancy suits, they don't wear camo.
The devil comes as an angel of light.
The devil comes acting all fair and friendly and beautiful, but can you smell the stench
of death?
I mean, listen, this is so real, folks, we've got to circle the wagons if you want any future.
And the issue is we resonate with the public, the public.
But the public that's awake and has street smarts.
And when you look at the general public, I mean, they're putting out all these fake polls
saying only 15% wanna keep their guns, pure bull.
I've got scores of scientific polls where the vast majority are pro-gun.
The gun culture has been taking over, but people emotionally when they say if it stops
the death of little children, would you want more reasonable restrictions?
And they call telephone trees of people they know have answered questions before, that's
how Rasmussen and all these guys work.
And they call up the welfare lady and say, do you want less gun violence?
I sure do, take the guns, it doesn't matter if 99% said that I had to be fed to the sharks
for no reason, you can't do that in a republic, we're not a pure democracy.
The Greeks had a pure democracy for a while in some of their city states, they'd have
a bucket of white rocks for a yes vote, black rocks for a no vote.
And the voters would go and put their rocks in there.
Only the upper gentry got to vote, but that was a democracy of the elite.
And who doesn't like what Aesop just said?
I don't like it, well, the rocks say, 90% of the rocks say, Aesop, we're gonna throw
you off that cliff, we're gonna make you drink hemlock.
I mix them all together, most of the famous philosophers you hear about were killed.
You know what, we don't like what you say, you're gonna die.
How's that sound, see, cuz the pen is mightier than the sword.
But when they come for the sword, you know they're dropping the hammer.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarshop.com.
These are items that I did research on, that I personally use.
We've got the life straw, so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out
in the field.
Strategic Relocation, third edition by Joel Skousen.
When disaster strikes by Matthew Stein.
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Hand crank shortwave AM-FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com,
and your purchase makes our Infowar possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you?
Infowarshop.com.
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN radio network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, we're going to be taking your calls now, and when Pastor Manning and when the
state rep comes on, who's been fighting the globalist.
Most of the resistance is right here out of Texas, Wyoming, a little bit out of Tennessee.
And it's all people who know that their ancestors fought to protect the Second Amendment.
And there's resistance out of Kentucky, there's resistance out of Oregon.
Let's go to some phone calls right now.
Remember folks, if we beat these people, you're all gonna be remembered as the next generation
of founding fathers and mothers.
I mean, this is the same kind of battle against even more evil people.
I mean, and the King of England was a cupcake compared to what we got.
Patriot poet in Michigan, you're on the air.
Yeah, Alex.
Go ahead, sir.
Hey, this is Google Bomb guy, man.
You're from Michigan.
Yes, sir.
You're the guy that came up with the idea for the Google Bomb.
How you been?
I had to take a break, Alex.
Things got so crazy.
But I got back as a member.
I can't get on the site.
Prison Planet's just jammed up.
I had you on through Infowars.
That's the only way I could get a feed was to listen, and I'm a member on prisonplanet.tv.
Well, I'm sorry.
You need to send a customer service email over there, and they'll try to get back to
you on that.
We've changed the configuration of it, works a little bit better, but thank you for the
support.
Listen, we're going to run out of time real quick.
It's good to talk to you, like we're sitting around here at the gas station on the bench,
but do you got any comments about what's just been announced that happened?
Yeah, what I wanted to share with you is how far they've reached in, not just only with
the Second Amendment, but a total takeover.
I want to show you how far this tyranny has reached in.
This happened this morning, Alex.
I got to share this with you.
The big conglomerate in Michigan for energy is DTE, which was Detroit Edison, right?
Well, they've got this program running where they'll come in your home, and they'll change
all your light bulbs out to those energy star compact fluorescent light bulbs.
No, no, no, no.
And then later, they come by law, and you get fined if you don't have those light bulbs,
and then it's forced from inspections.
They're just getting you used to it.
Right.
And they tried to walk, listen to this, with the maintenance man, they came trying to enter
my girlfriend's apartment without her permission, they were with the maintenance guy with the
keys to their apartment without even calling her, and they tried to just literally walk
to her-
No, no, listen, we're about five years behind Australia and England.
They always start this stuff as voluntary, then it becomes mandatory.
I appreciate your call, brother.
Good to hear from you.
Send an email to customerservice at prisonplanet.tv.
Okay, let's go to Shannon in Ohio.
You're on the air.
Yeah, I'm here.
Go ahead, sir.
Yeah, I've been listening to you for about five years now, Alex, and I woke a lot of
guys up.
I wasn't being a freak.
I come at them slow just to open them up a little bit, and I bet with just me reaching
out, I probably touched like 2,000 people.
I've got some guys that are ready.
We're all sitting back waiting.
We're all fathers.
We take care of our kids, and we're ready.
We know that we all got to stand up.
I've been a boxer my whole life, I've fought professional fighters.
All I can tell these guys is don't be scared.
Once you break the ice and stuff hits the fan, just be ready, and trust me, the spirit
of our founding fathers will be with you and give you the strength to see you through,
okay?
Well, that is the good part about a fight, not that I'm a professional fighter, but it's
like that in anything.
You're concerned until it starts, but boy, once it starts, it's like a duck to water,
isn't it?
Yes, it does.
It's just your body takes over, and you're capable of doing so much that you just got
to break the ice.
Don't be scared.
Don't be scared, anybody, because I tell you what right now, I'd rather stand and fight
than get down on my knees like a coward and let them do what they want to do.
Well, here's the deal.
They're not well-meaning, reasonable guys that want to take guns for little kids.
They have those little kids up there to make them look like good guys.
These are mafia scum that have sworn to get all our guns to make us slaves.
And listen, I know you're ready to physically fight.
Put that energy like you already said you did, my brother, into info war.
Redouble, redouble, redouble again, waking people up.
You are the Paul Revere.
You are the resistance.
God bless you.
Shannon, good to hear from you.
George, Andy, Bill, Chris, your calls are all coming up, and Pastor Manning as well.
Tons of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu, and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold, and food poisoning, and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day, while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus, and
other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
Get SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Also call to order 888-253-3139.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy.
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all of the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e Foods Direct.
In the councils of government, we must guard against the acquisition of unwarranted influence,
whether sought or unsought, by the military industrial complex.
In Dallas, Texas, three shots were fired at President Kennedy's motorcade in downtown
Dallas.
The first reports say that President Kennedy has been seriously wounded by this shooting.
It is a big idea, a new world order.
It was almost as if there were planned implosions.
It just pancakes.
Either you were with us or you were with the terrorists.
But I also believe that a lot of gun owners would agree that AK-47s belong in the hands
of soldiers, not in the hands of criminals.
The guns will be taken.
No one will ever be armed.
We're going to take all guns.
For many of the police and guard troops, it is an uncomfortable job to do this in an American
city.
Is global governance at last?
Is it one world the central bank is in charge?
But aren't we all just living and dying for what the central banks do?
And for me, give me liberty or give me death!
Live from the InfoWars.com studios, it's Alex Jones.
I am committed.
Give me liberty or give me death.
And now we've got police chiefs, sheriffs all across the United States from Texas to
Washington State to Kentucky, sending letters to Obama saying, I am declaring a declaration
of independence against your tyranny.
I will not follow unlawful orders.
And we need more towns, more cities, more county judges like Judge Head in Lubbock,
who were getting on the show, talked to his office yesterday, to stand up and say, we're
not going to comply with this.
And when Wolf Blitzer and people say, well, you've got to comply with whatever the federal
government says, why, Obama's the second coming of Abraham Lincoln.
Notice they've been saying that for five years.
And I said, because they're getting ready for insurrection in the states.
And now they're saying, yeah, he's gonna be Lincoln.
He's gonna do whatever he wants.
They want to cause a physical civil war.
I got an idea.
How about we have an info civil war?
Okay, how about we stand up and say no?
Just like what Pastor Manning did last year, where he had a public trial that got a lot
of the news, laying out Obama and his criminal activities.
People go, well, what's the point of his citizens trial?
You put publicly out there what the person's done.
Many times people write a book exposing some criminal thing someone's done, and years later
they get brought to justice.
We've had police officers and others on that are trying to bring Bill Ayers and others
to justice for bombings.
They have evidence they were connected to but didn't stay in prison for.
And they've got witnesses, and it's the same thing.
You've got to keep going after them, and that's why I put out a citizen's filing of articles
of impeachment.
Because it lists from deep research from constitutional lawyers, all of the different things he's
done that are impeachable on their face and beyond that.
There's a new hostage crisis, Al Qaeda Link Group says seven Americans among 41 hostages
seized in Algeria attacked.
Our government is giving unlimited weapons in Libya and Syria to Al Qaeda jihadis who
were then running all over Africa attacking people.
I mean, that's one of the articles of impeachment, it's admitted.
Our government is giving heat-seeking missiles to these people.
They're putting the Muslim Brotherhood in all these countries.
And then saying the TSA needs to go down my pants because of them.
Look at DrudgeReport.com, citizens file articles of impeachment against Obama.
Second congressmen suggest impeachment, see, one said impeachment yesterday if he tries
executive orders.
And see, notice Obama made all these announcements, but he won't say what the particulars are.
Well, guess what?
We've written the articles from the different Democratic Party meetings they've had with
Emanuel and Attorney General Holder, and they've said what it's gonna be.
Okay, so he's gonna do executive orders on ammo, on importation.
I'm gonna go over that after Pastor Manning leaves us cuz I don't wanna hog the time we've
got with him.
But citizens file articles of impeachment against Obama.
I put out the fact that I'm a citizen, Alex Jones, signed by me.
I'm putting out in the court of public opinion in the decade leading up to 1775, 1776.
That's what the colonies did is they circulated petitions to government saying you better
stop, you better stop.
So I'm putting out what you've done.
I have a media platform like a newspaper and I'm saying you're committing crimes, I want
you impeached.
My name's John Hancock, my name's Alex Jones, and I don't wanna be a founding father in
Rebirth of the Republic.
I'm just doing my job, but believe me, all of you fighting these tyrants are the John
Handcocks, are the Patrick Henrys, are the Sam Adams.
All of us that are in the media are like Sam Adams.
The folks at The Drudge Report are like Sam Adams, people at World Net Daily are like
Sam Adams.
You're like Sam Adams, you're like Sam Adams.
We've gotta hit them with the info war, the truth.
Now I give you James David Manning, a chief pastor at the Atla World Missionary Church,
reaches millions of people every month online in a big church there in town and has a huge
soup kitchen program.
It's non-government run for the citizens of the area.
And of course, they attacked the welfare state, that's why the establishment hates them, on
the 123rd Street in New York City and has been an atlas since 1981.
And he's a very well-spoken gentleman and very knowledgeable.
I didn't think Obama was as bad as he was saying five years ago when I had him on and
then three years ago, but it's certainly starting to get really scary.
And he prayed for me, and I appreciate that, when we were in New York.
And he prayed because what he laid out is exactly true, and I wanted to repeat that.
Because I had that same feeling before I saw his video, I had this thought.
God laid it into my mind, my spirit, hey buddy, you're anti-gun.
You're fighting the anti-gun guys.
They will use a anti-gunner to kill you crazy to then say, see, even this pro-gunner got
killed by somebody with a gun.
And he said God laid that upon his heart, so I wanted to get him on to talk about this
and give his basic take on what's happening.
Pastor, thanks for popping in with us today.
Thanks, Alex, thanks for having me today.
Glad to be on your broadcast.
Well, I've been ranting and raving.
You've just seen the speech, high-fiving, using kids.
What is your take on what's happening?
Well, several things have happened.
Let me just point out the fact that I am convinced that the CNN conference panel, the interview
that they had after you were being on there with Piers Morgan, was a direct attempt to
suggest to some crazy loon out there to take you out.
I'm confident of that.
And that's the reason why I prayed.
I think all Americans need to understand what they're trying to do.
They want to silence you.
You have become the voice for patriots and Americans, for gun owners and Americans, for
the Second Amendment.
You are indeed the spokesman for that.
I'm surprised that the NRA has not called you over and enlisted you to help them to
protect Americans and their rights to own guns.
You are the spokesman for a well-armed militia.
And Obama doesn't want that.
We need to be aware of the fact that Obama is the type of person, and the people we're
dealing with at present, they are the type of people that will take you out.
They have no problems seeing you put in a grave and sending someone to take you out,
or even sending someone perhaps from the military or some other organization to take you out.
So that's the reason why I prayed, Alex.
Now, you asked me another question a few moments ago about what's happening with Obama using
children as a shield, like Saddam Hussein did in his conference today.
Is that what you're asking me about?
Yes, sir.
Yeah.
That's what he did.
I think that he is tear-jerking the American people, tugging at their heartstrings by putting
those children up there and using them as pawns.
It looked like a chess game with Obama being the king and Joe Breakdancer Biden being the
queen and those little children being the pawns around him, pushing forward his executive
orders on gun control, taking our weapons.
That's what that was all about today.
How did you know Obama was gonna be so bad?
Because I mean, I didn't support him, but I didn't imagine he was this evil four years
ago.
You know, one of the things, Alex, I tell people all the time that I am a spiritual
individual and a lot of people have problems with that, some people are able to understand
it.
But I saw spiritually, Alex, in this band, the depths of the evil that he represents
and that's what he would do to this nation.
And I began to scream as loud as I could when I first saw him appear on the scene and then
as he moved closer to winning the office of presidency, although illegally, and the hysteria
around him.
I saw that this is an evil man and, Alex, it ain't over with yet.
It ain't hardly over with yet.
We have a lot more evil coming from this man that we have to endure.
But I can say this, I'm confident that we will prevail, that he will not win.
We will get the victory in this process, but it will not be easily won.
And it will not be for the faint of heart to persevere against what Obama is trying
to do to us as a people.
Did you notice that Biden could hardly stop smiling?
He was fighting, smiling, and Obama was trying to act sad, but he acted like that, you know,
he was at the Kentucky Derby in front row seats.
I mean, he acted like a pig and you know what?
Well, I think that Biden finally feels that he's given some recognition, something that
will give him a legacy.
I'm not sure exactly what Biden was up about today.
Obama was very coy today.
He was not his usual, I bully himself, and he wasn't quite as arrogant today as he normally
is as well.
I'll have to look at that again and really read what went on there.
Well, I saw the cover he was acting coy, but in the eyes, he looked evil.
I mean, in fact, we're hearing more of this from his people.
You saw the nice Obama.
Now you're going to see the real Obama.
Well, that's the thing.
I think this this so-called second term that he is employing, that we're going to see the
real Obama.
We're going to see really what he's made of and the evil.
I don't think he's going to make any attempts to hide anything.
I'm not surprised that he's not probably promoting Muslim Brotherhood and Islamic ideas more.
We're going to see who he really is in this.
I saw this four years ago.
It's amazing.
We're going to go to break, but I want to ask your take on ways to oppose him and to
push for impeachment.
I mean, don't we need to list all the impeachable crimes he's committed and really press Congress
to start the impeachment trial?
Well, you know, I had a CIA Columbia Obama Sedition and Treason trial regarding his forged
certificate of graduation from Columbia.
I explored in depth, Alex, his participation with the CIA, with the Mujahideens in Afghanistan
when the Soviet Union invaded them back in nineteen seventy nine, I think it was.
I went through that step by step and I discovered that Obama...
Stay there.
I want to talk about this.
You got a federal visit.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At E Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, Almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my E Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on E Foods Direct.
We travel so much and having a fake TV, well, it gives added peace of mind.
Burglars look for houses that appear to be easy targets, but fake TV can fool even professional
burglars into thinking someone is home watching television.
As a recent widow living alone, it gives me great peace of mind to set my fake TV near
a window and know that passing motorists and pedestrians will think someone is home watching
TV when I'm actually away from home.
Fake TV easily plugs into any outlet just like a light on a timer.
And they're so easy to use.
You just plug them in and they're ready to go.
Plus, they're so affordable that we have one upstairs and downstairs.
Fake TV is only $34.95.
Order your fake TV by calling 877-5FAKETV or go to faketv.com.
That's 877-532-5388 or faketv.com.
Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
Join a healthy garden easy and fast with organica seed.com.
Easy because organica seed.com offers one of the largest online selections of organic,
heirloom, non-hybrid and untreated seeds, as well as tobacco and cotton seeds at low
prices.
Go to organica seed.com, spelled O-R-G-A-N-I-C-A, seed.com, organica seed.com.
Remember, organica seed is healthy seed.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson.
Have you ever wondered why banks, stockbrokers, investment advisors won't talk about gold
IRAs?
They've been available since 1986, yet the financial industry won't recognize the value
of gold for your retirement.
Gold has outperformed paper investments, yet no word about IRAs.
If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns, call 800-686-2237.
Secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the President could obtain its world-class healer.
Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally
occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune
cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VENUSFLY or order from Carnivora.com, that's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A dot com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VENUSFLY or visit Carnivora.com.
That's your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
Pastor Manning is our guest for one more segment.
I want to get him back in the next few weeks for a full hour.
ATLA.org is his website, A-T-L-A-H.
In the next segment, we are now analyzing the vague statements of Obama, but they track
and follow exactly what we thought in the proposal.
I have this from the Washington Times, where they're just gonna take guns whenever they
find them in your car, even if they're legal, and you have no warrants.
And then they're going to decide if you get them back, and it's a no-fly, no-buy list.
They're just gonna put you on a no-gun list.
And it's official, DHS to expand and formalize coordination on gun control efforts.
Homeland Security is the takeover arm, and it will now be used to go after gun owners.
Okay, Pastor Manning, you got cut off by the break, and you were getting into the public
trial you put on to demonstrate all this.
It's the same thing with a move towards impeachment, getting behind congressmen that are talking
about it, getting the points out about why we should impeach.
We've got to get on the offensive.
What is your take on ways to turn the tide, because these guys are coming for us?
Well, the impeachment idea is a good idea.
Whether or not we can succeed with that is the question, because the Senate has to approve
of it.
And the Senate is right now controlled by the Democrats, Harry Reid, and so I'm not
sure you're gonna be able to actually put an impeachment through on Obama.
But it will be at least something to keep the nation aware of the fact that this man
is indeed evil, and probably force him to make a move, or force the American people
to just outright reject him, no confidence in him, whether the impeachment goes forward
or not.
So I think the action is a good action.
Absolutely, well, nobody thought the Senate was gonna go after Nixon, but then they got
the votes.
It never even had to go to the Senate, because they had the hearings in the House.
We need real fast and furious hearings.
We need real hearings on the psychotropic drugs.
We need real hearings on all of his insider trading and the Democrats' insider trading.
We need to get on the offensive with these guys.
Well, yeah, you're absolutely right.
And that's the move I think is most important, that we go on the offense.
Right now, we've been defending against the thing, he comes out and does something, and
we react to it.
Well, that needs to stop, it needs to stop immediately.
And we need to move against him confidently, not being afraid of all the stereotypes and
all the things that have protected him over the past three years.
So offense is indeed the defense that we need to employ against Obama at this time.
Why do you think they're in such a hurry to get the guns?
I mean, the Germans are demanding their gold back.
We know that they're raising taxes, the economy's gonna crater.
I mean, what is Obama's endgame?
I think the economy getting ready to crater is perhaps one of the pressing reasons why
Obama wants to take the guns, because we're gonna see ourselves in another year or so
out in the streets begging for bread, or at least the economy being so cratered that people
will be unemployed and people will be ready to take to the streets.
So that's the reason why he needs guns out of the hands of people.
But the other thing, Alex, I told you that when I was on your broadcast, I think three
or four years ago, that Obama does not want to give up this power that he has.
But unlike any other president, he is closer to and employs more power than any other president
in the history of this nation.
And he very possibly sees the opportunity to stay in office as long as he possibly can.
Martial law is one way, and if calling for martial law, he can have guns on the street.
So take them out of the way right away, remove that obstacle, and then deploy the other kinds
of things he wants to do.
You know, a congressman has pointed it out, you pointed it out so eloquently about Obama's
the king, Biden's his queen, the little kids are pawns.
We've got to come up with a 3D graphic of that or something for the nightly news pastor.
But I mean, I think Obama's got a problem overreaching using these little kids like
pawns.
I mean, this was a sickening display.
That's exactly the kind of stuff Saddam Hussein pulled.
Normally, I can stomach a lot of stuff, Alex.
And when Obama has crowds of black people or Hispanic people or whoever behind him,
women or whoever.
I mean, I can deal with it, it's just politics, he's promoting himself, they want an opportunity
to be there.
But this was a terrible misuse, a bastard misuse of these children today.
And calling their names and using them to promote his diabolical plans, I thought was
just off the charts.
Well you're right, again, Pastor Manning, we've only got about a minute left, anything
else you think is important to add for folks?
Well, I want to ask America to pray for you, Alex.
I mean, I don't think people realize just how serious this issue is.
Obama wants our guns, he wants this nation, he wants to trash the Constitution and you
are a powerful voice that have fired up the American people.
And people need to stand with you, they need to pray for you, that God will sustain you
through this battle that's ahead of us.
So my one request before leaving today is that all Americans would bow their knee and
their heads in continual prayer for your safety and your abilities to keep doing what you're
doing.
Wow, thank you, Pastor.
We need to pray for you as well and for everybody fighting against evil.
But I know it's the prayers that are sustaining me.
From the bottom of my heart, I feel that connection with you, Pastor.
Thank you, sir.
God bless you, sir.
God bless you.
Man, we'll be right back with State Rep who's fighting.
We're on the march, the empire's on the run, Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarshop.com.
These are items that I did research on that I personally use.
We've got the LifeStraw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out
in the field.
Strategic Relocation, third edition by Joel Skousen.
When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein.
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Hand crank shortwave AM FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com
and your purchase makes our info war possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you?
Infowarshop.com.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other
harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance.
You are listening to the Alex Jones Show.
Ladies and gentlemen, we're joined for the balance of the hour and I promise everybody
holding, we're gonna get to all your calls for the entire third hour and cover this foggy
legislation but it's not foggy and so I have this huge responsibility.
I'm gonna go back to all our articles we've written the last two weeks, well even before
that the last month where we went back through Handgun Control Incorporated and these different
meetings they've had that have been on C-SPAN with the Attorney General and others and they've
laid out what they're gonna do.
And they're just gonna pull over gun owners and harass you.
They're going to raid people's houses claiming you've got illegal guns.
They're going to just say, we say you're mentally ill, you can't own a gun now.
They're gonna, upwards of $5 billion additional funding to harass gun owners.
They're gonna try to ram through legislation to physically make you turn them in, Dianne
Feinstein has that.
And it's totally, absolutely unconstitutional.
And it's unconstitutional on its face and we have President Obama running four years
ago pledging to never try to take any guns.
And you have the FBI crime statistics of gun crime the last 15, 16 years, we're gonna show
these again in a moment, down 49% nationwide on average and 20 plus percent reduction in
total violent crime.
I mean, the big secret is crime where guns are used is going way down, but I don't wanna
hog the time here.
Representative Steve Toth joins us and he's made national news coming up with a legislative
plan to battle back against this and for the state of Texas to not recognize unconstitutional
federal laws.
Even if they tried to get, just to explain to people cuz I was watching them on both
Blitzer and he'll be able to elaborate on this, Blitzer was interrupting him, acting
like it was just preposterous.
Congress could pass a law saying turn your guns in, it's really unconstitutional and
abhorrent and you'd have to get a constitutional amendment.
And even that is highly debatable because it doesn't give you the right, it points out
the unalienable, unalienable right that's already there.
So he joins us, his career began at a company, a Johnson and Johnson company and led to work
as a regional trainer where he developed in a practice management consulting program called
a residency to retirement.
He served as director of marketing for Apple, it goes on 99.
The point is he is a entrepreneur out there and not one of these sponges.
And he's been involved with the Tea Party and involved in a lot of different community
and church organizations.
And it's just really exciting to have him join us.
State Representative Steve Toth, thank you so much for coming on, sir.
Hey, Alex, thanks so much for having me.
You bet.
I mean, I'm chomping at the bit here because this is so outrageous.
Why do you think Obama's coming for the guns?
And what do you think of him like Saddam Hussein surrounding himself with children, and then
we'll move into your legislation?
Well, I mean, it goes all the way back to Rahm Emanuel.
Don't let any crisis go to waste.
This is part of their agenda.
This has always been part of their agenda to make it difficult for law abiding citizens
to own a gun.
What was your take?
Did you have a chance to watch his speech?
Yeah, I did.
I was actually in the studio here in Austin while he was giving the speech.
And again, it's funny because Wolf Blitzer said, after it was done, he said he gave it
in great detail.
Well, I'm sorry, there are 23 things, and he laid out maybe three or four of them.
And at the end of the day, this is no different than Obamacare.
You deliver a bill that's 4,000 pages that no one has a chance to read, it gets voted
in, and then it goes miraculously, it goes from 4,000 pages to 40,000 pages.
And this is how he does things.
It's just, at some point, we've got to say enough is enough, and stand up and say our
Constitution matters.
We're not a democracy, we're a constitutional republic.
We don't vote on whether or not we have liberty.
We don't vote on whether or not you can or can't do something.
We have this article, it's called the Constitution, our rights come from God and are enumerated
in that document.
And it's very clear about what we can and can't do.
I agree with you, and your call for the Second Amendment Preservation Act here in Texas has
become a big national story.
A lot of other states are saying they're gonna try to introduce similar legislation.
And the Wolf Blitzer was trying to interrupt you so that you couldn't explain the constitutionality
of this and how it works, but I want you to be able to elaborate on it.
But expanding on that, 800 plus cities, 30-something states last time I checked, don't arrest illegal
aliens for even drunk driving because they're just above the law.
They don't arrest them for being illegal, they don't even take them to be deported.
They won't deport most of them most of the time now because Obama signed an order.
Now that's all unconstitutional with the feds and the states ignoring the law.
Well, why can't we ignore federal laws if they're clearly unconstitutional?
Exactly, I mean, you nailed it, you absolutely nailed it.
At some point you've got to draw a line in the sand and say, enough is enough, we're
not sliding anymore towards a king.
I grew up in upstate New York.
I moved my family here because we believed it was the greatest state in the nation, greatest
opportunity to raise our children in freedom and prosperity.
And the thing that gets me about what's going on in New York right now, where they're
limiting lawful people to own a gun, make it more difficult for them to get a gun, it
was just three or four weeks ago that this crazed killer, this is a guy that beat his
mother to death with a hammer, he beat his mother to death with a hammer, bludgeoned
her head with a hammer.
And oh, by the way, more people died from being bludgeoned with a hammer than any kind
of rifle, let alone an assault rifle.
That's right.
He beat his mother to death with a hammer.
And then the libs in New York sent him to jail, where they promptly let him out.
They promptly let him out.
What did he do?
He set his house on fire a few weeks ago, shot two volunteer firefighters, first responders,
people that, you know, give their lives to save others.
He shot them like a coward that he is.
He shot them dead.
And what does New York state legislation do?
Rather than getting on TV and saying, boy, we blew it.
We haven't made it tough enough on criminals.
We should have locked this guy away and thrown away the key.
We should have put legislation in place to ensure that this guy would never see another
sunset again.
Instead, what do they do?
It's this baloney.
They go and create legislation that has nothing to do.
This guy got this gun illegally.
He didn't buy it at a gun show.
He didn't buy it at a shop.
This was a stolen weapon.
And just, we don't want to have a real discussion about what to do.
We just want theatrics.
We just want games.
And it's just, again, it's just another opportunity to erode our rights.
I agree.
State representative hailing from Texas, Steve Toth, is our guest.
And we're going to give you his website as well as you want to get behind him and support
him.
But here's the bottom line.
We either get on the offensive like you're doing or it's over because they are going
to use these dead children.
They are going to wrap themselves around this tragedy.
They are going to bill all gun owners as responsible, calling the NRA mass murder enablers, saying
gun owners are all secretly Ku Klux Klan as Fox Sports, has said, we either get on the
offensive and say, in every case, and it's now come out with a Batman shooter that he
was on a bunch of psychotropic drugs.
They've been on drugs where the inserts say they can cause you to commit mass murder or
kill yourself, a massive increase.
The guy that shot an Austin cop for no reason, no reason at a Walmart, was bombed out of
his brain on Xanax.
He was a Xanax addict, taking more than what you're even supposed to.
I mean, I've known people on Xanax, it destroys their lives.
I mean, I've talked to doctors who will not prescribe it.
And of course, I mean, I heard this guy shot a cop for no reason.
I said, I bet that guy's on psychotropics.
Boom, he was on antipsychotic, basically.
And now the Batman shooter, Harris, Kleibold, in like 99% of the cases, they're trying to
suppress the file on Lanza, who tried to buy a gun, not once, not twice, not three times,
not four times, five times the month before, couldn't.
His mother had gone through some of the strictest gun laws in the country to get these semi-autos,
if you believe the story.
And again, they ignore all that and say, because a guy that murdered his mother with a hammer
went and got an illegal gun and shot people, I've gotta give my guns up.
Because a guy went and killed his mommy and went and killed, it's always devil-worshipping
goths on drugs.
I mean, if anybody needs to be profiled, it's these guys.
Instead, I've gotta lose my rights.
So what about getting on the offensive here?
Yeah, that's it, exactly.
I mean, everyone in every state has gotta take an interest in this thing.
If you think that this is just about guns, you're crazy.
This is about eroding all of your rights.
And I said to Governor Perry last night, and he's behind this as well, and I had such great
discussion with him.
He walked up to me when I was talking to him about the bill and he grabbed me by both arms
and he said, he said, Steve, this isn't about hunting, this isn't about my right to be a
sportsman.
If I want to use an assault-style rifle to kill hogs, that's my right.
And if I don't want to kill hogs and I just want to have that in my gun safe in case I
need it against the federal government or whatever, that's my right.
He is just a liberty-loving.
Absolutely.
And I'm thankful he's my governor, but the deal is y'all need to reach out to your elected
officials.
This is a fight that we all need to be involved in, and it's not just about guns, it's how
we educate our children, it's the kind of food that we eat and drink, it's everything.
We've gotta stop this and we've gotta stop it now.
Well, I mean, I disagree with Rick Perry on quite a few things like the NAFTA highway
and stuff, but the governor has been resisting and really defending the Second Amendment.
And we need to see more of that.
And I've gotta say, I'm proud of Texas, but also Kentucky, Washington State, many other
states that are resisting.
But I have introduced into the public forum articles of impeachment.
And we've got a Texas congressman who has said he will introduce articles of impeachment.
If Obama tries to use executive orders, well, now he's saying 23 executive orders, but like
you said earlier, won't tell us what they are.
Well, I know what they've said they're gonna do, because the anti-gun groups have press
conferences on C-SPAN.
I mean, I know what they're gonna do.
They're just gonna have the federal government put you on a list, no judge, no jury, and
say you can't own a gun.
They're gonna ban importation.
Go ahead.
A couple days ago, he was talking about there's got to be an administrative fix or solution.
That's code for registering our guns.
I'm just here to tell you.
No, that's it.
Yeah.
That's it in a nutshell.
And when that happens, we're done.
We're just done.
And, you know, frankly, there needs to be some outrage for those of you that are listening
in New York, and again, Sheldon Silver and the outrageous leadership that he has demonstrated
in the state of New York, what he's brought that state down to, it's just a shame.
Well, it's so creepy that Bloomberg and Cuomo and all these people, Diane Feinstein is introduced
to Bill, that says you'll have to come re-register your guns and they can, quote, do a forced
buyback if they want, all this vague, really draconian language.
They've all got concealed carry, I've played clips for admitting it, and bodyguards.
I mean, she's worth $100 million in her financial filings.
Most people, I mean, I'm a successful talk show host, but I mean, I don't have the money
to have bodyguards and stuff.
I mean, I know you don't have the money to have bodyguards, I would guess.
I don't either.
My campaign manager two years ago was walking through the, Bruce, if you're listening, love
you buddy, but as he was walking through the parking lot at the Woodlands Mall, two guys
started following him, so he starts taking the circuitous route around cars and everything,
and sure enough, they're still following him.
He walks around a van, drops a package, draws, and as they came around the corner, he looked
at these two guys and said, yes, can I help you?
And they took off running.
He immediately called 911, and like any good concealed handgun licensed owner, he said,
I was in fear of my life.
Two men were coming after me, and I drew, and the police arrived.
He described them, and he said, you know, those two guys, we've been trying to catch
them.
Good thing you didn't shoot them, but we've been trying to catch those guys.
They mugged two people that day, so evidently the president and Nancy Pelosi and Dianne
Feinstein, they're allowed to have protection, but I'm not allowed to protect myself.
It's incredible.
I mean, we have crime maps from local governments compiled then by the FBI, and you can see
where you have increased gun ownership, you have lower home invasions, lower crime rates,
lower muggings, lower carjackings, and the area where people are disarmed is where this
happens.
I mean, I've been in New York myself, and I weigh 260 pounds, and I'm a pretty strong
guy.
I mean, I'm not like He-Man or something, but I can bench press 350 pounds, stuff like
that.
I've had guys come and sit on both sides of me and ask me what's in my bag and stuff and
try to intimidate me.
Yeah.
I mean, this is not the way I want to live, and it's just so despicable that these mob
boss types like Rahm Emanuel and people consciously have this criminal instinct to want to disarm
us.
Right.
That's it in a nutshell.
Anything that they can do, you know, we don't have the Second Amendment for hunting.
We don't have the Second Amendment for putting trophy guns on our wall.
We have the Second Amendment so that we can preserve the First Amendment, which is the
free right to assemble and free speech.
And when people live in fear of the government, we will have tyranny.
And as soon as they take our guns away from us, and again, this is a slow erosion, we
will lose that freedom.
And we've got to get to the point where we say enough is enough and stand up.
Well, sure, if the federal government wasn't buying 1.6 billion hollow point bullets, if
they weren't deploying armored personnel carriers, if they weren't dressing like Darth Vader,
and they weren't trying to gut our borders and calling for world government, if they
didn't have four network TV shows bad mouthing the founding fathers, I mean, these are obvious
usurpers.
They're going down the list of things tyrants do and double checking every box.
So that's all the more reasons, like Jesse Ventura said, when the government disarms
and the government lays down its guns, then I'll think about it.
And obviously, that's tongue in cheek.
The point is, is that they are arming against us.
We need our guns to protect ourselves.
And the media always tries to act like, wow, the state rep just said we need guns to protect
ourselves from the federal government.
Well, that's what the founders said.
And if you don't like that, you're not an American.
No, I mean, that's not like a new thought.
I mean, this is something that our founding fathers knew that just like gravity, you know,
you hold something in there and you drop it, it's going to hit the ground.
Our liberty, our freedom will erode from the gravity of tyranny.
It's the slow erosion.
It's not a quick on off switch.
And we have got to be on guard against it.
It is speeding up at an astronomical rate, exponential rate.
So yeah, I mean, and yes, our founding fathers said, when government lives in fear of the
people, there's liberty.
When people live in fear of the government, there's tyranny.
They understood that.
They understood it well because of what they endured through King George.
We don't want another king.
When we come back, I know listeners already have heard your report on on the WOAI.
It's already made national news.
They have the drugs report dot com and info wars dot com.
But I want to come back and give out your website.
But I also want to talk about what your piece of proposed legislation would do and how we
would implement it.
And it's very, very simple.
I mean, the feds won't even pick up the illegal aliens and police do arrest them.
I've talked to the police has been on the news show if that's illegal and unconstitutional
because that's something you're supposed to do, then how can the states get in trouble
if they don't do something that's unconstitutional?
So we're going to talk about your piece of legislation and how we can get it duplicated
and different ways we can get on the offense against this tyranny with the representative
from Texas.
Hemp USA dot org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine and probiotics.
And we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder absolutely free micro plant powder
only at hemp usa.org call 908-691-2608 that's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder seeds
and oil can do for you only at hemp usa.org only this offer ends January 31st.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson.
Have you ever wondered why banks, stockbrokers, investment advisors won't talk about gold
IRAs?
They've been available since 1986 yet the financial industry won't recognize the value
of gold for your retirement.
Gold is outperformed paper investments yet no word about IRAs.
If you would like to have gold for your retirement call 800-686-2237 don't get left behind by
rising inflation and low returns call 800-686-2237 secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
Hey there, Frank Bates here.
Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out 280 million Americans?
This is really scary stuff.
Vince experts warn that this odd device poses the greatest threat we've ever known.
In fact, just a few weeks ago former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed
piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat.
I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up.
That's why my friend just created a free video at weirddevice.com that exposes this threat
and blows the doors off the conspiracy.
Go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover exactly what it is plus
discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack.
I'm not sure how long this video will be online so go to weirddevice.com before it's gone
forever.
Again, that's weirddevice.com.
We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration.
As an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years and serving thousands of satisfied customers,
the Berkey Guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration systems.
The Berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable black purification
elements that purify water by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria, cysts and parasites to
non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides.
Order the Berkey light system today complete with two black Berkey elements for only $231
and the Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge.
With the purchase of a Berkey light, the Berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride and
arsenic filters for only $39.99.
That's over 30% off the retail price.
Call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653.
That's 1-877-886-3653 or order online at goberky.com.
That's goberky.com today.
Now you noticed Obama just said, I want to give everybody free healthcare, you deserve
it.
And then we finally get the bill, it's death panels, it's written by the insurance companies
to double your rates, doesn't give anybody free healthcare.
Obama says, I'm not gonna raise taxes unless you make a quarter million dollars a year,
I promise.
Raises a bunch of taxes on poor people, massively.
I have a responsibility because they bragged to the Washington Post, I've read their quotes,
I've watched their press conferences.
We know their attack profile, we know what the 23 executive actions are gonna be.
We know, and he hinted at a bunch of them in the speech, but I was talking to state
representative here from Texas who's introduced the Firearms Preservation Act.
And Steve, continuing with what you were breaking down during the break describing what Obama's
doing masterfully.
He's like, hey, I just don't want little kids to get killed.
I'm here, I'm gonna propose something, DHS is gonna run it nationwide, $5 billion, get
ready.
Yeah, I mean, he's masterful at this.
It's smoke and mirrors, you hide behind children, you pull the heartstrings to make an emotional
connection with moms and dads.
And then you introduce this nebulous legislation, and then once the ne'er-do-wells in Washington
pass it, then what he does is he takes his bureaucrats, the only thing worse than a politician
that has been in office too long is a bureaucrat that has been in office too long.
And these bureaucrats are the ones that craft the legislation once it's passed.
Obamacare was only about 4,000 pages only, right?
But once it was the bill that you had to pass before you read it, well, that thing is upwards
of 40,000 pages of regulation today.
And the devil in this thing is really truly in the details, and you won't find out what
the details are, this is the way he does things.
The thing is that they're just too controversial to make it onto the House floor or the well
of the Senate.
That stuff isn't seen, it's not gonna be addressed in this legislation.
And so they're gonna keep it nice and nebulous, warm, fuzzy, children, puppies, and then pass
this.
And then you pass it and you find out that our guns are registered and they're being
taken away.
And by the way, that's what makes me so angry is that Dianne Feinstein, we have the clip
of her saying, if I have my way, all your guns are turned in, Mr. and Mrs. America.
And then I have her new bill where it says, yeah, you gotta come re-register them, we'll
decide if you can keep them, but we need money for a forced buyback.
And then Obama's up there going, it's just reasonable, we just want crazy people not
to have guns.
I mean, it's such a deception.
You'd think once the public learned that they lie so much, then everyone would turn against
them.
But it's almost like people have just gotten used to being lied to.
Well, check this out.
When the liberals say that the war on drugs has been an abject failure, they say it's
because interdiction is impossible.
You can't keep drugs out of the country.
You can't keep drugs out of the hands of someone that wants drugs.
But evidently, they think you can't keep firearms out of the hands of criminals.
I mean, it's just pure- Well, that was my next point.
They're announcing Homeland Security's main duty.
It's not Al-Qaeda anymore.
You've seen the training manuals, gun owners, returning veterans, conservatives.
They're now announcing this is what Homeland Security is, is a new thing to harass and
nickel and dime gun owners, where somebody's got a legal AR-15, not modified, guy has no
criminal record, businessman, what was it in Minnesota.
He pulls the trigger at the shooting range, it goes full auto, they rat on him, and he
goes to jail.
And the ATF says, we know he didn't do it on purpose, but we still wanna put you in
jail.
Do five more minutes with us.
I know you've gotta go, but I wanna talk about your Firearms Preservation Act, how people
find it.
Fire out the best website, sir.
The best way to get ahold of us at this point is just on Facebook.
Steve for House District 15.
All right, stay with us.
You are listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die?
Start purifying your water with ProPure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research, and the best gravity filter out there bar none
is ProPure.
And it's available discounted at infowars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified.
Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%.
Easy to set up and use, doesn't require electricity.
Purify water from lakes, streams, ponds, and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
ProPure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on ProPure.
But if you add the promo code water at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN radio network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
State representative from Texas, Steve Toth, represents District 15.
And he is almost for five more minutes.
I've got some big breaking news after he leaves us in the next segment.
I'm just gonna leave it at that.
Big breaking news.
And this is confirmed.
This is, well, we'll break it down on the other side and go over what this means.
Getting into your State Preservation Act, tell people about that.
I guess they can go to Steve.
Steve Toth for House District 15 on Facebook.
So that's the best place to visit and- Yeah, that's the best place.
How do people find a piece of legislation?
How do they find a copy of it so they can get it to the-
Yeah, we're not out of legislative council yet.
So it's being drafted right now.
And we've been told that alleged counsel will be done Friday and then it's gonna be in the
hands of the Attorney General.
Reason being, we wanna make sure that it's buttoned up as best we can.
We're gonna put it in his hands and let him dot the I's and cross the T's and then we'll
go from there.
We only serve in Texas 140 days every two years.
And we can't introduce legislation in the first couple months.
So the neat thing about this, and you're probably familiar with the TSA bill that Representative
Simpson put through a couple years ago.
Absolutely.
What's the background?
Well, in the local radio station there in Houston said, well, I hope this isn't like
the TSA bill.
It didn't get passed.
Well, the TSA bill didn't catch fire until April or May last year.
It's January.
So the nice thing about where we're at right now is that, and thanks to Texans that have
just shown so much support for this thing that they're calling their elected officials
and saying, we're behind this, they're respectfully calling their officials and saying, we're
behind this and we appreciate it, you'd be behind it.
And that's the best way to talk to one of these people because at the end of the day,
we serve here.
It's really not even, I have a full time job, I own the company, I have employees, and I
do this on the side, I'm paid $600 a month, it barely covers your expense.
No, you're a statesman, you're what we need in there.
And I just appreciate you being on the front lines of this and we've got a good chance
to get this ram through and it will take time and we've got a good chance to get other states
to pick it up because what are, in closing, a few other areas we can get on the offense?
Reach out through social media to people and start the discussion.
I'm amazed when you get under a liberal skin, they're calling my office right now, F bomb
after F bomb after F bomb.
Because they can't have an intellectual discussion around this because their position is just
so weak.
Well, they're authoritarians.
Unbelievable.
So yeah, I mean, we just need to ramp up the discussion and we need to do it with integrity
and honesty.
And I mean, I want to put it back on them too, stop saying we have blood on our hands.
If anybody has blood on their hands, it's the drug manufacturers putting mentally ill
people on stuff that's known to cause psychotic outbreaks and it's making public schools gun
free zones.
I love the NRA's new ad.
It's just a soft target and Wayne LaPierre hit the nail right on the head.
The only way to stop an evil person with a gun is a good person with a gun.
It's the only way it happens.
You look at all of these shootings that have happened as of late and it wasn't until an
armed citizen or a police officer stopped them.
Well said.
Period.
So.
Appreciate you, Representative.
Thank you so much for spending time with us and thank you for being a leader for Texas
and America.
We'll talk to you again soon.
Appreciate it.
Thanks so much.
Thank you.
He'll know more tomorrow, by the way, as as more of Obama's plans leak out.
Let me tell you, that's what makes this so much worse is that they are going with a sneaky
angle.
But that's what they always do.
He writes the NDA, then says he's against it, then says, don't worry if it passes.
I'll veto it.
Then he doesn't veto it.
He signs it.
It turns out he wrote it.
That was all the plan.
So there's no telling what they're going to do and then they're going to get the legislation
written up separately and then have another mass shooting and then just sign a bunch of
executive orders.
But we've got some very important news I'll announce after the break.
Then we'll go to all the callers that are holding eight hundred to five at nine nine
two three one.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are Earth friendly and safe.
See them on the Web at five star soap dot com or call eight hundred three four zero
seven zero nine one for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soap for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the Web at five star soap dot com or call eight hundred three four zero
seven zero nine one for a free catalog.
Tyranny is here.
The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality.
It really says that the state is God.
The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most impressive police states
on Earth.
This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being
expanded nationwide.
This documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all
powerful shadow state.
Police state four chronicles the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen.
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship, body scammers, sound cameras,
citizen spies, stage terror and cameras on every street corner.
It's only the beginning of the New World Order's hellish plan.
The police state isn't coming.
It's here.
Secure your copy today at info wars dot com or see it online in the highest quality at
prison planet dot TV.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver based products.
Our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two
ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well as our all natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100 percent natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and
leave the silver at the surface, but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the
natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the
skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www dot silver lungs dot com and click on our store page to find what silver based
products are best for you.
That's www dot silver lungs dot com.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, we're going to go to your phone calls here to respond
to the president's nebulous announcement.
They have told us 23 orders and executive orders, legislation.
We know the plan.
It's Dianne Feinstein's bill.
It's the other ten bills that are in Congress, taxes on ammo, background checks on ammo,
re-gun registration, can't sell guns to anybody.
When you die, you've got to turn your guns in.
Can't transfer anything semi-auto, can't even sell it to a gun dealer.
Government wants to put you on a no gun buy list, no judge, no jury, you're just on it.
They said last week in a press conference on C-SPAN what they were gonna do.
The attorney general, the Chicago mob boss, Rahm Emanuel, all of them.
And they got up there and they laid it out.
And we've gone over it, but I'm gonna have my writers go back through and just say, here's
the plan.
I mean, if you had the December issue of the magazine, even before Sandy Hook, we tell
you the plan.
It's been the same plan Dianne Feinstein's had for 20 years, where she says, if I ever
get the votes, Mr. and Mrs. America, you're gonna turn your guns in, okay?
And then we're like, hey, folks, Obama's gonna try to take your guns.
He said he'd never take any of my guns, that's a firm pledge.
He also pledged to not raise anybody's payroll taxes, but some of the lowest paid Americans
got them, 77% of tax paying Americans have their payroll tax raised.
He will make them $30,000 a year.
And it's so sad, these gullible people, because they look at you like, you're just mad cuz
you're not on the winning team.
And then meanwhile, Obama is totally chomping these people.
I mean, they really think, their guy got in, everything's great.
I've got the Washington Times here breaking down his point.
And it just goes over, it's basically just track everybody's guns and get them all registered
so they can take your guns and harass gun owners and go after everybody.
Also then we're going to your calls here.
Also we've got DHS to expand formalized coordination on gun efforts, gun control efforts.
So I told you, internally, they're all about getting our guns, it's not about Al-Qaeda,
which they use in Libya and Syria.
Or who they let get on the plane to come over here so they can put naked body scanners in.
Al-Qaeda is used to take your liberties, okay, period.
And DHS does one thing, they train to take on veterans and gun owners, libertarians,
conservatives, and rural communities.
They see you as the undomesticated who don't wanna be a little collectivist with them,
okay?
They want you dumbed down, on welfare, begging for an Obama phone.
And by the way, you want welfare, you gotta take these shots that kill you better than
a hammer down the road.
Here's the Daily Caller reporting.
There is now a second congressman, second GOP congressman suggests impeachment over
executive action for gun control.
And see, Obama blinked.
He said he's gonna have executive orders and said it's for the kids.
That way they can just say, hey, we gotta do something, it's for the kids, aren't I
sweet?
It's for the kids, like Saddam Hussein high-fiving kids.
I high-five the kids, I high-five, we're gonna show you that video coming up.
It's on YouTube, we got it up at infoawards.com.
We are gonna do a great job, we high-fived.
And then meanwhile, well, you gotta get behind the bill, and it's a gun confiscation bill.
But they never even say that, knowing most of the public doesn't go and read legislation.
So there is all of that info, and that is exactly what we expected.
Now here's the announcement, and I'm going to your phone calls.
Something that absolutely, yeah, there it is, totally disgusting if you're a radio listener
and the crowd is clapping, and the kids high-five Obama.
He looks to the kids and he says, I'm gonna get it done for you, because you've written
me letters and this is what you want.
He wants to steal their birthright, so they live in a big mega city being raped and robbed
and taxed into oblivion.
I mean, this is the global government that does medical experiments on little kids, nerve
gases our own troops, injects black people with syphilis, totally ruthless, that's who's
hijacked the country.
And here's Obama, the gangster expression of it.
And if you don't turn your guns in, you're not for these cute little kids.
I mean, this is the worst, most hollow, mindless exploitation meant to manipulate women, to
get women to be anti-gun, cuz they're panicking.
The gun culture's taking over, women are out buying guns, crime rates are dropping.
They've gotta hide that and point out that school shootings are going up, while everything
else is going down, because they've been hyping the daylights out of it.
Now, here is the announcement, I don't just get up here.
Most websites have an IT problem, and they say we got hacked, we got this or that.
Years ago, somebody hacked our website and posted an image of a naked woman on a motorcycle
on the front page.
We've had plenty of denial of service attacks coming out of China, coming out of Japan,
but out of US military bases, they use them to basically zombie the computers to then
attack us.
We've had all sorts of attacks that go on, I don't talk about it.
But I've had senior cyber security people who've been in government and out of government
say, I don't know how you keep your side up.
There's been a lot of hackers out there that have also given us tips and helped us, and
we're eternally thankful for that.
We've got some great IT people.
But in the last two weeks, we've had two different dirty tricks done that are very sophisticated.
I'm not gonna get into what they did or what they exploited, but it's government level
type stuff.
And it's very sophisticated.
And so we've got to basically watch the site 24 hours a day now.
I'm having to hire more IT people just to watch 24 hours a day.
I'm hiring an outside consulting firm to be able to deal with this.
And then they went ahead to hit us with an old fashioned denial of service attack.
It's undoubtedly, we are getting a lot of traffic today.
And traffic's much higher than it's ever been.
But we were thinking early on, this is an all time record traffic, which it pretty much
would be, or almost a record.
But we can see, and they've got graphs in there, like I want them to get shots, that's
a new report, cuz this is newsworthy, showing that it's denial of service from a whole bunch
of zombie computers, government computers, hijacked university computers, you name it.
The minute Obama started speaking today, about five minutes before he did when Joe Biden
was up there is when this started, the site is up right now for now.
And it appears they're very upset about the move to impeach Obama.
And I mean, listen, the globalists kill and assassinate people all over the world.
I am ready for them to kill me, okay?
And I don't think it's gonna happen because I'm so outspoken, and my grandma's praying
real hard for me, and I don't wanna die.
I'll never commit suicide, but I mean, seriously, I've not made a big deal over the years about
some of the other stuff that's going on, because it just sounds like a movie, and people aren't
gonna believe it.
Now, other media people I've talked to, they're like, no, I know that's happened to me or
that's happened to people I know.
A lot of folks get intimidated like this and they just go away.
All I know how to do is fight harder.
I get death threats, I start doing videos at 2 AM, I mean, I start working 18, 20 hours
a day.
I'm like, wow, these people really are criminals, I better do something, I better work harder.
And it's my upbringing, it's my instincts, it's just who I am.
I mean, I'm not bragging about it, I'm proud of my ancestors, though they were all the
same way I am.
I mean, I'm probably like some of the more extreme examples, but the point is, it doesn't
intimidate me.
I mean, I am not afraid.
I'm afraid of being a buffoon, I'm afraid of stumbling over things, I'm afraid of getting
things wrong.
I'm afraid of overworking and getting tired and not doing a good job.
I'm afraid to look at myself in the mirror, I mean, I'm just doing the best I can, and
that resonates with people.
For all my warts, was it Lord Wellington, no, it was Lord Nelson said, you've gotta
take me, warts and all.
I know people are resonating with the fact that I'm real.
And I just want you to know, this is the big thing we're doing, and they are upset.
Look, when they death threat us or they do sophisticated hacks, even against third parties
to try to get into our system, when they call up and tell my wife or myself what we were
just talking about on the phone to freak us out, like a movie, that just confirms everything,
okay?
And these people are criminals, and the reason they are doing denial of service attacks,
the reason they are doing very complex governmental exploits, developed by French companies and
others that openly only sell to governments.
The fact that these are institutional attacks we're having against mfallwars.com, and whenever
that site's having problems, you can go to prisonplanet.com.
But make no mistake, what's happening right now is historical.
And a lot of people joke and say, you're the only one dumb enough to get in this system's
face like this.
No, no, no, let it in, I mean, sometimes when I've been death threaded or messages
are related, it's like, look, do you understand we can kill you?
What you just think, I've been doing all this and I didn't know that?
You think I'm like you, New World Order, most of you guys, go join the evil because you
think it's the winning team.
I cannot join you, okay?
It's not even a question of, not comparing myself to one of the prophets, but things
historically like this.
Ezekiel, they're threatening to kill him cuz he's getting in the corrupt's faces.
And he says to God, he goes, God, they're gonna kill me if I keep getting in their faces,
but it's burning in my bones, I think that was Ezekiel.
And that's what it's like, I am not in control of myself, okay?
I want everybody to understand that I cannot give up, I cannot give in, I cannot stop,
okay?
It is a overriding drive, and it may be ugly sometimes, but it's the best I can do, okay?
And that's it.
But these fools think that dirty tricks, death threats, denial of service attacks, sophisticated
hacks, all sorts of other crud, cognitive infiltration, COINTELPRO stuff's gonna get
to me, saying where I live and saying come kill me.
All this kinda crap on the news saying, I hope his kids don't get killed, I think we
should kill him, yeah, we'll do it in a uniform, ha ha ha ha.
Look, I know you're a bunch of Jerry Sandusky, Jimmy Savelle wannabes, okay?
And look, I'm not ever going to bow to you, you understand that?
I'm never gonna shut up, I'm never gonna back down, I'm never gonna stop.
And all my critics, hey, I know it's ugly sometimes, it is what it is, okay?
I'm in the arena, and I'm in the arena with people like State Representative Koth.
I'm in the arena with people like Ron Paul, I'm in the arena with people like Matt Drudge,
I'm in the arena with people like you that want liberty.
I'm never backing down, I signed my John Hancock on the Declaration of Independence 2012, and
I'm never backing down, never giving in.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but were waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not gonna wanna miss this exciting message.
Here's why.
Solar generators provide life-saving electrical power, and unlike gas generators, solar generators
run quietly, emit no fumes, and produce electricity from the sun.
So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part.
Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse, and we discount them heavily at the end of
each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty, and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait, they go fast.
Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa, where a nicely furnished cabin
with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine, and laundry service awaits.
After a good night's sleep, your adventure begins.
You're on a golden stag safari for big game, but it's not Africa, it's Argentina.
One-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo, huger, bighorn rams, wild boar, and the biggest
stag deer in South America.
All gold medal quality, all the action you can handle.
Land rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages, hunting guides, ground
transportation included, and more, all more affordable than you can imagine.
The adventure of a lifetime starts at goldenstagsafaris.com, the big game hunting ranch, goldenstagsafaris.com.
Making the right decisions is a challenge to investors.
Are we going to see economic growth, slide into a recession, or at worst, depression?
Hi, Ted Anderson from Midas Resources.
We all know when a company acts irresponsibly, divesting ourselves in a move towards safety
is prudent.
When the market becomes volatile, U.S. treasuries are a safe haven.
But what do you do when the U.S. government overextends itself and spends beyond its means?
Many investors are turning toward gold as a common sense alternative to traditional
paper investments.
Midas Resources has put together a powerful book titled Ten Reasons to Own Gold, discussing
costs, benefits, risks, featuring full-color illustrations, weights, and measures.
The book is free and can be yours by calling 800-686-2237.
Paper investments are dwarfed by gold's 6,000-year history.
Discover how gold may be right for you and your IRA by calling 800-686-2237.
Whether buying or it's time for you to sell, the book is free.
Call 800-686-2237.
Feeling like there are too many pressures and demands on you?
Losing sleep, worrying about tests and schoolwork, leaving you on the run because your schedule
is just too busy?
You may be under too much stress, and it may be affecting your mind.
Get your mental edge back with Neutropic Mind Power from mindregard.com.
Neutropic Mind Power is not a drug, but a natural supplement.
Its 12 powerful ingredients are natural and non-GMO, plus it's gluten-free, wheat-free,
and formulated by Americans for Americans by an NSF-certified laboratory.
Neutropic Mind Power is available at mindregard.com, spelled M-I-N-D-R-E-G-A-R-D.com, and comes
with a 100% money-back guarantee.
Free your mind with Neutropic Mind Power, a cognitive supplement from mindregard.com.
Clearly see tomorrow and yesterday today.
Okay, you guys have been holding long enough, I appreciate you holding.
I just can't believe that so many people are fundamentally scared of this criminal government
so then the criminal government wins and takes over.
Because we act like sheep, they then win.
Instead of acting like men, America is in a trance, man.
Even people that know what's going on, you talk to them, you can't get through to them.
It's television watching has turned people into jellyfish.
Let's go to George in Texas.
George, you're on the air, go ahead.
Thank you, Alex, for taking my call.
I know there's been a buzz going around the Internet saying January 19th is going to be
Gun Appreciation Day.
I'm calling on the audience, let's have a Gun Owners of America membership bomb to send
the message that we're not throwing down our weapons.
I agree, I mean, I've said I'm not turning my guns in, I'm done.
That's why I'm so upset.
I've got to sit here as a law abiding person and tell the criminal government, who's exploiting
dead children, you're not getting my semi-automatic rifles, you had incredible draconian gun laws
in Connecticut and this happened.
They probably staged it, they staged Fast and Furious.
That's why I get so angry.
Well, I'm just saying Larry Pratt has been on the fight for a long time, even when public
opinion was against him.
He has held his ground and I think he needs our support.
So I'm saying January 19th, $20 a year membership bomb.
Well, I agree, they've gotten a quarter million new members in the last month with the NRA.
And the NRA got real milquetoast for a while because they were being infiltrated.
We put pressure on them, they've gotten a lot better.
But yeah, Gun Owners of America, I mean, I need to ask Larry, they've gotten a lot of
new members, but they should have gotten a quarter million new members.
And we have NRA board members on and stuff like Bob Barr and stuff, I'm not knocking
them.
I mean, overall, they're getting better.
It's just that they used to, they supported the 68 Gun Control Act that got us into this
mess to begin with.
Thank you so much, George.
Good point.
Bill in North Carolina, you're on the air.
Hey, Alex, thank you for taking my call.
Can you hear me?
Yes, I can.
Alex, first off, I pray for you every day.
I love what you're doing.
You've been incredible.
And the night you went on Piers Morgan, I think that woke a lot of people up.
And I just wanna make a quick point today.
Recently I moved from one town in North Carolina to right outside Camp Lejeune.
And when I got here, I thought the young Marines were gonna be just sheep.
And when I found out, the 19-year-olds, the 20s, the 28-year-olds, they know what's going
on.
They knew about Benghazi, they knew about Fast and Furious, they knew about the discrepancies
in Sandy Hook, and they're gonna stand down.
The ones I'm talking with, if they go in, they get told to confiscate, they're either
gonna stand down, they're gonna pull out of rank, or they're not gonna show up for work.
So I think one of the ways people can get on the offense is talk to your people, call
your local sheriffs like I do, ask their opinion, find out what they're doing.
Call Congressman Stockton, thank him, call Sheriff Merrill, because those guys need the
prayers and they need people to support them because they're going out on a limb.
And we need those guys to be a light out in the open for other representatives and other
people in our legal system and sheriffs to follow.
Absolutely, I wanna get both these sheriffs, one in Kentucky, one in Washington State on,
one of them wrote a letter just saying, look, what you're doing is unconstitutional, I'm
not gonna be part of it.
And it's gotta get to that point, but all this unconstitutional stuff, it's all out
of control.
And again, when I found that the FBI statistics from the locals was 21% reduction in violent
crime generally, 49 in crimes with guns, that is the most powerful statistic.
And again, I've criticized Fox News in the past, but they were showing the statistic
last weekend, or late last week, and I went and looked it up and it was a statistic I
hadn't seen or heard.
And it was compiled from local governments, 49% drop in gun crime, 49%, I mean, and they
want our guns and are parading and high-fying and going, you're beautiful children, the
families here, you lost your beautiful children, like a vampire using the deaths of those kids.
I mean, did it make you nauseated to watch that press conference?
Alex, disgusting, I was sitting here chomping at the bit, I'm listening to and to exploit
those children, it's a psyop, it's disgusting, because we know, those of us who are awake
and those of us who have prior military experience know exactly what he's doing and why he's
doing it, and it's just disgusting to watch.
And one other thing too that I'm seeing too is the hypocrisy, a lot of times when I'm
talking to the liberals out there, it's a matter of their opinion, it's like, look guys,
it's not about your opinion, these are the impeachable offenses, you're Benghazi, you're
Fast and Furious, you're Sandy Hooks, so what you were able to put down in those article
impeachments, I'm able to get out to Facebook and share that with my friends and family
because it's not a matter of opinion, it's a matter of constitutional doctrine.
So keep it up, Alex, I love you, I pray for you and your staff, my brother, keep on keeping
on, brother.
Thank you, my friend as well, and again folks, if they were real dummies that wanted guns
to keep us safe, it wouldn't be as bad, these are mobster gangster crooks that suckered
their own people and said we're not going to raise your taxes and then massively hammered
them, and then almost all the working poor are going down to 29 hours from 40 or 50,
I mean, it's so mean.
We're on the march, the empire's on the run, Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness, get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver, this is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver, Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com, check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Alex Jones here with a very important announcement for truth seekers, we've carried a lot of
amazing films and books over the years on the online video bookstore at Infowars.com
and out of all the titles we've carried, one stands out because it is just so chillingly
convincing and that's Dreams from My Real Father by Joel Gilbert, available at Infowars.com.
This film exposes the fraud that Obama is like nothing I've seen.
If you want to know who Obama's real daddy is, this is the film for you.
Don't forget, your purchase supports our broadcast and our growing media network, you'll also
find at Infowarshop.com, None Dare Call a Conspiracy by Gary Allen, the book that woke
me up.
We're also carrying Behind the Green Mask, UN Agenda 21 by Rosa Corey.
This book is coffin nails to the globalist takeover, The Greater Good, the most professional
and up-to-date film I've ever seen exposing the scourge that is vaccines.
These titles and a lot more are all available at Infowarshop.com.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At E Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my E Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on E Foods Direct.
From the front lines of the information war, it's Alex Jones.
It is really hard to do this radio show because really what I want to be doing is going back
and getting all their statements and video clips and press conferences where they say
what their plan is.
And then I can show you, I say 11 or 12 bills, it's like 20 something now they've introduced
in Congress, but they're all incredibly nasty.
And so no one even knows what the plan is now.
It's just, hey, I'm up here with kids high-fying, any more kids get killed, it's you gun owners,
it's your fault if you don't do what I want, I'm the good guy.
And it's just such a mindless psyop.
It's like saying, turn your cars in or the next time there's a car wreck, it's your fault.
I mean, it is just, yeah, let's get some audio while he's high-fying.
I mean, exploiting those little sweetie pies, man, I tell you, people used to show me photos
of their kids when I was young and I'd be like, why are you showing me photos of your
kids?
Now I've got children, people want to show me their wallet full of pictures, I want to
see it.
You know what I mean?
I just, it makes me sick whenever people use kids for something.
I just love children so much because their little minds ready to be filled with information
and for the adventure of life.
And then I think of people like Sandusky and Saville and these globalist scum and the things
they do to children and it makes me sick.
It makes me sick, it's like people that want to hurt innocent animals like dogs and cats.
I mean, you read about people that it's like some fetish where good looking women beat
animals to death, some kind of snuff porn.
I mean, it's little puppies, kids, but kids, it's like 10 times more angering than puppies.
It's like, who are these people?
And they're always, these perverts and pedophiles and government types are always real fake
and psychopathic and come off like nice guys, but you can see it in their eyes and in their
actions.
And when Obama talks about those beautiful children that got killed, they always call
them beautiful.
I mean, what a pervert, man, okay, I'm going too far what I really think about Obama.
That guy is a demonic pervert.
He wants to pervert our Constitution, he wants to pervert our republic.
He wants to be a Peace Prize winner and launch all these illegal wars.
And the left is just all sick and gets into the death and destruction and all of it.
I mean, I'm just sick of them.
And Joe Biden is such a gangster.
And Rahm Emanuel looks like a cartoon character gangster.
I mean, did you see him in that press conference yesterday, sweating and looking all nuts?
I mean, that guy is crazy.
And you've got all these like San Francisco and New York saying how big your Coca-Cola
can be, how big your apartment can be now.
I mean, just a bunch of control freaks, they just wanna run everybody's lives.
They want everybody living in fear, not need of stuff that statistically isn't a threat.
If my kids went to public school, I'd be worried about them being beat up by bullies, turning
into mindless TV heads, turning into emotional wrecks cuz a bunch of mean kids telling them
they're not cool, instead of their minds being filled with science and sports and discovery.
I'd be scared of the state pushing drugs on them.
I'd be scared of stuff like that.
I wouldn't be scared if my kids went to public school of a mass shooting.
88 people die a year, and last year was a record year.
All the other crimes dropping but those, cuz the media advertises it, of a Sikh temple,
a movie theater, a couple schools, 88 people dead.
I mean, ladies and gentlemen, that doesn't even register in the top 100 causes of death.
But they've got people thinking, I mean, I got news reports pouring out where people
see a kid with a Nerf gun in their front yard that sold at Target and Walmart.
My kids have probably had ten of them over the years cuz they break so easy, and we were
having a Nerf battle this weekend.
I mean, you drive through any suburban neighborhood, it's Nerf war.
Your car gets shot with Nerf darts.
Your car gets hit with footballs.
I mean, people now see orange and yellow and green Nerf guns, and the police are called
and they lock down the area and play along with it.
I mean, it is just sick how they are turning us into a bunch of cowards.
And believe me, everything Obama said in that press conference is a target.
There it is, Nerf gun found after Long Island school lockdown.
I mean, there's a bunch of these happening.
That whole speech was targeting shocker moms about, here's the sweet kids, we don't want
them to get killed.
I got some reasonable stuff I'm gonna be announcing, goodbye, goodbye, high five, high five.
I got an Obamacare, there's no death panels, no, it doesn't increase your premiums.
That's a right wing lie, blah, blah, more like, here it is, here it is.
It's in a bill.
But see, they never say it in press conferences.
So I have to sit here, that's why I'm getting so angry, is this is like Groundhog Day.
You ever seen that great movie, Groundhog Day, with Bill Murray?
And he just, I mean, it's the same day over and over again.
No matter what he does, he has to relive this day over and over again.
And I have to watch people get conned and bamboozled and manipulated and snookered and
conned over and over and over again.
And I know exactly what they're doing, and I'm not even smart.
I mean, that was an incredibly exploitive press conference.
Biden was trying to hold back a smile the entire time, was literally having a you know
what dream up there.
Obama was trying to act somber and look like the devil.
All right, I'm gonna stop.
Andy in Africa, I didn't know somebody was calling from Africa.
Where are you calling us from Africa?
I'm calling from Africa, Alex.
Welcome, you're on the air.
Where are you calling from in Africa?
The good part, the southern part.
South Africa?
That's it, that's right, Alex.
To start out, I just wanna say thanks for making people aware of some of the really
important issues like gun control.
I really like how you've upgraded the show, and hello to all the listeners out there.
May Yahushua bless you all.
Well, thank you.
How do we upgrade the show?
Okay, no, just the new graphics and the TV.
I've watched your show for about, I've seen your show, I wouldn't listen to it for about
five, six, seven years now.
So it's looking good.
We're gonna keep upgrading, but I gotta say, CJ and Chris are just upping their game.
John Bound, the hardest place to work is in here with me, cuz I get in a rampage, and
so I pray for them as well.
They're doing overall a great job.
They really upped their game, so we're thankful for that.
Go ahead, sir, I'll shut up.
No worries, no worries, no worries.
You mentioned your web servers have been going down.
Well, you're not the only one, so to speak.
I am a web developer and researcher, and I'm here to tell you that the Illuminati is back
online.
Breaking news.
Now, what do I mean by that?
You remember the Illuminati card game, right?
Yes.
Okay, interesting thing is this card game started out as an online game, okay?
Running on what we would call an Illuminati server, I guess, which was a DDS system.
So the game started on a server, and then Steve Jackson's games was raided by the Secret
Service, and they confiscated the server and the data that was on that server.
The game was never supposed to get out, according to Stephen Dolan's said to be an ex-Satanist
anti-priest, who exposed the game in the Prophets of God.
By the way, the maker of the Illuminati card game and the video game developer, he has
his offices about two miles from us.
We've called him, no exaggeration, probably 40 times.
I keep saying when we get time, we're gonna go over there.
And also, in the past, I know where he lived, cuz my parents lived close to him in North
Austin, and he'd have these weird Halloween parties where he'd let all the neighborhood
kids in, run through his castle house.
I never went over there, but I read about it in the paper.
Back when I was in high school, actually, we're talking about like in 1992, yeah, his
card game predicts everything.
And I don't know how they did it.
It's bizarre.
Well, that's pretty interesting, cuz possibly Stephen Dolan's had insider knowledge being
a Satanist anti-priest.
So anyhow, Steve Jackson's games, this is where it gets really interesting, Alex.
Steve Jackson games, PrismNet, used to own a domain called io.com, and that's Illuminati
Online.
Now, this domain name actually led to the creation of the Electronic Frontier Foundation,
according to Flashdot.com, and they got their servers back, which they probably weren't
supposed to, and the big part of the hacker movement actually is the EFF, Electronic Frontier
Foundation.
Perhaps they could help you guys out.
In any case, July 1st, 2011, Richards & Richards sold the domain to an unnamed party, okay?
Now io.com is being sold, and it seems perhaps the Illuminati is back online in a big way
cuz io.com now points to io data centers.
Get this, io is Goldman Sachs' worldwide vendor of choice for advanced data storage.
Listen, what you gotta do is you wanna shoot a YouTube video about this, you wanna write
an article about this, because it's complex, I'm not following it all.
Plus, I don't know if this video game maker is a devil high priest, cuz somebody said
so.
I'm a devil high priest, or a ninja warlock, cuz we joked about it once, they actually
think that's real now, that I'm a Vatican assassin ninja warlock, I mean, it's a joke.
But yeah, they have some deep knowledge about things for that card game.
But I mean, then people go too far, there's one card, looks like myself and Ron Paul in
it, and so that's proof that we're part of it.
I mean, but it is bizarre, I mean, cuz I've collected now, well, I haven't collected,
listeners have meld us the entire set, which is pretty rare, I think it's three or four
sets.
And you look at this, and it was made like 20 years ago, and you're like, how did they
do this?
How did they predict all this?
The tower's getting blown up, the Pentagon hit just like it got hit, staging terror,
COINTELPRO, I mean, it's just, wow, this guy really knew what he was talking about, but
he won't come on the show.
And so it's becoming an issue, thank you so much, I gotta move quick here now.
I wanna play some of these clips of Obama that David Knight worked to clip out from
the disgusting press conference.
Chris in Florida, you're on the air, welcome.
Well, Gun Appreciation Day, that'd be January 19th, as the last previous caller mentioned,
that was Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.'s 84th birthday.
And we- By the way, he went and got a concealed carry
permit.
He went and was trying to get a gun permit right before they killed him.
Absolutely, and the deacons of defense who provided security for him from the KKK and
other government-sponsored race-baitors, but we need to demand an apology from our government.
Of course, you know about the 1999 Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. family's court case at the
kingcenter.org, a unanimous jury decision that his assassination was a conspiracy by
state, local, and federal officials, and this was after expert testimony, 70 witnesses,
and a civil trial in Memphis, Tennessee, unanimous decision on December 8th, 1999, after about
an hour of deliberation.
So that's one point I wanna mention, and also the FDA has their adverse event reporting
system on 31 drugs that are disproportionately linked to the reports of violent behavior
towards others.
Now, we have a two-year-old Time magazine article that lists the top 10, it's entitled
Top 10 Illegal Drugs Linked to Violence, and four of which are fluorinated.
That'd be Prozac, Luvox, Effexor, and Paxil.
Next, I would like to also mention that Cheers Morgan is in violation, subject to life sentence
or death penalty, for the death threat against you, Alex, Title 18, Section 241 and 242.
That would also include those co-conspirators on the air, Buzz Buzzinger, sports columnist
for the Daily Beef, and Abby Huntsman of the Huffington Post, they have not redacted their
conspiracy against you, Alex, and that's something that ought to be harped on.
Joyce Riley showed this morning, was also very good on the Hensah-Neewick Elementary
School shooting, she spent two hours with a private investigator, so check out the Power
Hour, and that's a lot of awesome research.
All right, buddy, I really appreciate your call, that's a lot of info, boy, my head wasn't
spinning it is now.
Here's the breaking news, document cam, please, now is the time, the President's plan to protect
our children and our communities by reducing gun violence.
And Aaron Dykes, since this came out about 30 minutes ago, he and David Knight, both
crack researchers, have gone over it and indexed it, it is exactly what they already claimed
they were going to do.
It has created total gun hysteria, tie it to insurance, to get insurance you'll have
to have police brainwashing, active shooter drills, but never wear your arm to protect
yourself to teach you how to go lay in a corner so the executioner can kill you a little bit
more easily.
The BBC has called my phone, no exaggeration, 30, 40 times a day, I'm gonna take this right
now.
Hello, is this the BBC?
ITV, that's out of Canada, right?
Ma'am, ma'am, I lost my phone and I never put the voicemail back on it, just do me a
favor.
I'm gonna be off the air in about 15 minutes or so, why don't you text this?
Yeah, exactly, just text this number, your name and number and I or somebody will get
back with you, okay?
Thank you, this rings nonstop at every TV station you can imagine, I should be doing
all these interviews, but I'm just too burnt out, man.
And another thing is I get on these TV shows, I just wanna blow up at them, cuz I know we
got mafia running things, people are in a trance, and the whole system wants us to just
play along and just be real calm about it.
And then we need to be calm, no, the time for being calm is over, we got into this situation
by being calm.
I've intellectually been calm, I've analyzed the data, these people are criminals, I'm
done with them.
Excuse me, now the irritating thing is I was doing radio interviews driving in this morning
and TV stations would not stop calling it where I couldn't even do the radio interviews.
In fact, I was on our 50,000 watt KMJ and they literally, literally called 15 times
while I was on that 10 minute interview where the interview was worthless.
My wife's like, well, you gotta put the do not disturb on here, which I don't remember
to do, I'm not complaining on air, I didn't answer the phone to act powerful.
I'm just angry about this cuz they've been calling, see I'm angry, I shouldn't have guns,
I'm angry, I'm angry.
You wouldn't have a country if your forebearers weren't angry.
By the way, the reason we've had so much wealth, we haven't been perfect, we've been at our
own problems.
The reason we've had so much wealth is because we didn't let thugs get in control of us and
turn us into the other slaves, okay?
Our ancestors wouldn't put up with anybody's garbage and so there was a lot of private
independent operators and a free market got developed and we all got super rich.
Now we've gotten super decadent, we got taken over, now we're gonna get super poor again.
Because despots make everybody poor on purpose, plus they screw everything up, but they don't
care cuz they got theirs.
Anyways, they have analyzed it and it is used the healthcare law to force everybody to pay
for anti-gun training and anti-gun brainwashing.
So it's gonna be an anti-gun tax in Obamacare, cuz Obamacare is written where they can do
whatever they want.
That's probably the biggest thing here, turn the doctors into spies, have a national demonization
campaign run by Holder, national dialogue, talking about just putting people on lists
without any proof that they can't own guns, banning all private sales, physically banning
semi-autos and handguns if they can get it legislatively.
Arresting anybody that sells a gun to a neighbor, claiming all your guns retroactively to prove
where you got them.
They want you to have to come in and re-register them, active shooter training everywhere to
create more hype about mass shooting.
So all these mentally ill people just get told about mass shooting and shown how to
do it all day.
It's like the DARE program, it proved, made kids use more drugs.
It's like sex ed, I remember sitting there in seventh grader in sex ed, and they're sitting
there talking about sex and I'm looking over at the cheerleader next to me, and she's looking
over at me.
Just like, I think the point is it makes everybody go have sex, folks.
Well, it's the same thing here, you gotta tell the mentally ill people, hey, you wanna
go out with a bang?
Go to a school, shoot some people.
Model emergency response, FEMA involved, they want churches, campuses, everything to be
brainwashed.
They're gonna try to force gun manufacturers to put biometrics on all the guns.
They want high school resource anti-gun brainwashing officers who aren't armed.
But if they are to be armed, they're gonna be federal people in the schools turning into
a prison and a tattletale squad.
And this is how they totally, just like they converted the airports into police state zones
off of some staged events, they're doing the same thing here.
All right, we'll be back with more of your calls, stay with us.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not gonna wanna miss this exciting message.
Here's why.
Our solar generators provide life saving electrical power.
And unlike gas generators, solar generators run quietly, emit no fumes, and produce electricity
from the sun.
So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part, every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't
sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of
each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait, they go fast.
Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
Hi there, my name is Frank Bates.
What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble.
I just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are, incompetent line crooks that
are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high.
Some have called this a conspiracy, others have called it a cover-up and you will be
shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy goes.
My video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them
and how you can beat them too.
Watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patriots have already seen
in the last three months.
Go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect
your home.
Go watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down.
Again, that's 123coverup.com.
Injuries, slow healing, aches and pains, constipation, weakness, fatigue are all common the older
one gets.
The progressive deterioration of the body that occurs almost universally the older one
gets can partly to significantly be prevented with conscientious attention to nutrition.
If the Hanza men can play rugby in their 90s, then it is possible for everyone in North
America to experience a more youthful life as well.
One key ingredient to warding off aging and reversing some of it is the type and quality
of protein consumed.
All protein foods or supplements you currently consume are heat damaged, destroying 50 to
75% of your ability to utilize the bodybuilding amino acids.
One World Way is not heat damaged and allows your body to utilize 100% of the amino acids.
This feat no one else has achieved.
The results to your health can be amazing.
Call 888-988-3325.
That's 888-988-3325.
Or visit OneWorldWay.com.
That's OneWorldWay.com Listen, I've got to go over the Obama speech.
We've got all the clips.
We're going to go into overdrive here today and we've got all these callers that are holding
like Mike in Texas and so many others.
And we will take a ton of your calls in the next hour.
And of course, Infowars Nightly News tonight is going to have my good friend and gun dealer
and New American Magazine researcher and writer Bob Dacy is going to be here analyzing it.
This is all about the UN treaty coming up.
And Aaron Dykes was just showing me more.
It's really bad.
They're going to just have Health and Human Services.
If you're handicapped, you're not going to be able to have a gun.
And what I just read, and it's directly from Health and Human Services, it's why it's hard
to do the show right now because I'm out there reading stuff during the breaks and then it's
just overwhelming.
It looks like they're going to try to take handicapped people's weapons, not even mentally
handicapped.
I mean, it's unbelievable.
It's unbelievable.
And then they're just going to pick and choose gun owners to come harass and SWAT team and
stuff.
And then just have a huge unending brainwashing campaign like the Attorney General said against
Republicans.
All I know is we've got to get aggressive, have national days where we have our guns
out in public.
They hate that because they like to have TV act like guns are already illegal.
We've been fighting back and we've got good sheriffs, good police that are servants that
by the way, I noticed her dressed like police and not army commandos.
You can always see the good cops are dressed like dignified public servants and not like
goons.
But side issue, I was on Porter Stansbury's radio show this morning and he lives in Miami
during the winter.
Not a bad idea, beautiful.
And my allergies are so bad from the cedar during the winter.
I'm thinking about going to Miami or something for three months out of the year and remoting
into the office because of these cedar allergies.
But the point is that he said, yeah, I really like the cops around here.
They dress in just nice conservative outfits, they're real nice.
He goes, I came down now, they're like Darth Vader cars, Darth Vader outfits.
They pull over families and get their shotguns out when they walk up.
And he doesn't even know if he wants to stay there anymore.
I mean, it's just, that's one thing I got to say for R.D.
Cevita.
He's trying to put the police back in old fashioned police uniforms and old fashioned
police cars and have them act like old fashioned cops.
I mean, can't we just have that, do we have to have people playing Rambo all day and then
acting like we're the enemy?
A military fights an enemy.
I don't want my police to look like a military.
I want my military to look like a military, and I don't want my military operating domestically.
But support the broadcast, get the Propure water filters, 10% off the promo code water.
They're the best side by side comparison against the leading competitors, available at Infowarshop.com.
And we've got more of these in now.
We've been selling hundreds of these a day and that helps get the word out and fund the
operation that come and take it, new t-shirts are out with an AK-47 with the Second Amendment
printed inside the AK-47.
The best seller, $19.95, available at Infowarshop.com.
So you support the broadcast and you support the Second Amendment at the same time.
Okay, let's just go to calls next hour cuz I don't wanna go to somebody and cut them
off short.
Mike and Antoine and Craig and Jim and Joseph and everybody else, the toll free number to
join us, 800-25-99231.
And just have your point ready, we'll try to go to the next person as best I can.
Again, my head is spinning right now.
Aaron Dykes and the entire team are in there.
Steve Watson, Paul Watson, Don Salazar, Kurt Nemo, Mike Adams is basically an unofficial
member of the team, hammering through this.
And it's all nebulous, but we got them because with each thing they've called for nebulous,
we have previous policy and bills they've introduced by the very people on this board
in some cases, we know their attack profile.
You already know what it is, register, confiscate, shut down ammo manufacturers, harass gun dealers,
harass gun manufacturers, sue gun manufacturers, ban importation, put you on no buy list with
no proof for no reason, SWAT team and harass gun owners, demonize gun ownership everywhere,
unbelievable.
Thank you for listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution, recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can
be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other
harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Coast to coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Folks, if you go up to infoawards.com, it's been up and down today under a coordinated
denial of service attack, the biggest we've ever seen.
Does it matter?
We'll just start even more backup websites.
Our listeners will just get the impeachment articles out to even more people, get them
out to every member of Congress.
I'll talk about it after we take calls and I got some clips of the president we're going
to analyze coming up here.
But it's the same thing with Obamacare, left it nebulous, and now he's just going to do
whatever he wants.
And they are licking their chops.
I mean, they know there's going to be another mass shooting with all this media hype, guaranteed.
And it's just a matter of time.
And if they're in, they'll stage one.
And like Larry Pratt said, you notice the media won't attack Larry Pratt for that.
They tried and dropped it.
Remember Larry Pratt after Aurora, he said on my show and others, and it made national
news, but then they backed off, Larry Pratt says the government could have staged this.
What he said was if they staged Fast and Furious, they could have staged this.
Ladies and gentlemen, they're the prime suspects.
And then each event has so many earmarks.
It'd be like if you were a cop and you're driving by a bank and you see guys running
out with masks on and bags over their shoulders and guns in their belts.
I mean, that's probable cause, they're bank robbers.
I mean, if they don't stop, you can shoot them.
I mean, it's the same deal.
I mean, they have done this stuff before, they stand to gain from it.
And all the anomalies and the things involved, I don't just say this because I want to think
this, it's overwhelming.
And I haven't even been touching it a lot, people are mad at me.
Because people are like, yeah, this is blaringly staged.
Yeah, of course it's staged, of course it's staged.
There's some real mass school shootings, but these things, you get a mental patient in
there, you shoot them.
You have organized crime, shoot some kids.
They get out.
Even if they get caught, the feds say, let them go, and then you just change the story
around.
And I haven't even gotten into homes.
I mean, that is incredible.
Mike in Texas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Guns and Obama, you're on the air.
Go ahead.
Hey, Alex, my family and I are praying for you, you're doing the yeoman's job there.
I hope that nothing happens.
I hope everything stays peaceful.
Well, listen, I only whine about it and I've gotten my will redone and stuff, because there
is a chance they may set me up or do something.
I'm just letting people know this is real.
I'm not putting it out there, ooh, the show's spooky, and oh man, I mean, these are criminals.
And a lot of people aren't fighting them because they know they're criminals.
And I'm just saying, let's just get this out in the open.
Sorry, go ahead.
Well, you know, we are the cops out in front of the bank, and these guys are the robbers.
They just ran out, they got the masks on, they got the guns, and they're saying, hey,
you know, we'll just go ahead and gaslight these people and say, hey, turn over your
guns.
You can't get us, we just robbed the bank, you can't do anything about it.
But the one thing I called in about is, you know, Obama sounds real reasonable to the
soccer moms and to everybody that wants to obey the law and has empathy for the parents
and the children that were killed and all of that.
Everything he says is real reasonable.
The only problem is, you know, he works for us, and he wants a background check so that
we can have our guns.
What about, he's working for us, we need a background check on him.
He has access to weapons of mass destruction.
He has access to predator drones.
Exactly, he won't release any of his college records, he won't release any of it.
He's got multiple names on record.
He's in college magazines under other names.
We don't know who this guy is.
For all I know, he could be a robot.
I mean, I'm joking when I say that, but I mean, he is Mr. Mystery.
That's why more and more I'm getting freaked out by him.
I mean, I, man, I tell you, we're in trouble, that's all I can tell you.
Yeah, why are we putting up with this?
I mean, you know, this is the thing that should be put out there.
You know, he's never gone through a background check here, you know?
We know he's bad.
No, it's true.
In fact, they've had news articles saying, to work at the post office, you'd have to
have more of a background check than Obama's had.
And that's why they've got him in there, is because who knows who he really is?
Barry Sotero, who knows who his dad really is?
All these other names, he's got at least three different names that have been his name on
record.
We'll be right back.
Hello, I'm Alex Jones, myself, my family, the Infowars.com team want to relay to you
and your families that we are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every
front.
Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats, but we can't do that without
your help by getting the films, bumper stickers and T-shirts at Infowars.com, you will wake
up people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before.
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here.
It's an info war.
The spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
Fight back this cold and flu season with the world's best garlic extract, Ali-C. Why Ali-C?
Because it helps your body fight viruses, bacteria and fungi.
Ali-C has been scientifically proven in double blind studies using low doses to greatly reduce
the number, severity and duration of common colds.
Ali-C contains 300 milligrams of stabilized allicin, the active ingredient in crushed
garlic.
Studies show Ali-C is effective against MRSA, bacterial, fungal and viral infections.
One tablet of Ali-C has the equivalent of 40 cloves of garlic.
Ali-C supports your body's resistance to all types of conditions and can help lower high
blood pressure and high cholesterol.
So boost your body's resistance to infection with nature's best garlic extract, Ali-C.
For more information and to order Ali-C, call 877-888-7126 or go to garlichealthproducts.com.
That's 1-877-888-7126 or go to garlichealthproducts.com for your Ali-C today.
Who wants to be disease free, full of energy and vibrant health?
Two reasons you may feel constantly tired and run down could be that your body's acid
level is high and your pH level is low.
How does acid enter your body?
A cup of coffee, a sandwich, tap water, stress and cell phones, plus your own body produces
acid on a regular basis.
Alkavision plasma pH drops alkalize the water you drink and raise your pH level.
They promote more oxygen in your system, higher energy potential and many other documented
health benefits.
And studies show viruses, bacteria and toxins cannot survive in an alkaline high pH environment.
Alkavision plasma pH drops is the least expensive and the best pH level product you can buy.
Order Alkavision plasma pH drops for just $29.95 at alkavision.com, spelled alkavision.com
or call 800-518-7615, that's 800-518-7615.
Alkalize your body, supercharge your health with pH drops from alkavision.com.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups, you want answers, well so does
he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, it's official, we're trying to get the full text of all of them, we're live
here at 208 Central.
Obama signs 23 executive orders to curb gun violence, urges Congress to act.
And we're gonna be going over all of this and playing some of the clips and then going
back to your phone calls.
The latest is all up at infowars.com and prisonplanet.com, we'll have a lot more tonight, 7 o'clock
Central for the Infowars Nightly News at infowarsnews.com.
Now if you go up to infowars.com, it's scrolled down to the bottom of the featured news area,
it's citizens file articles of impeachment against Obama.
And again, most people get it, some are saying, well, how do you file that?
I'm publicly putting out with links to the lawyers and congressmen and women's statements
and with the text of the Constitution where Obama is clearly violating Article I, Section
9.
And I just go on and on and on, showing all the high crimes and misdemeanors and what
Congress is to do.
And I think I'll go in there and add some statements as well and show some more of the
Constitution at the bottom of the article.
Then I have a video breaking it down there, but citizens file articles of impeachment
against Obama.
Where you really wanna go is drudgereport.com, that's where I go.
And if you go there, it's got all the latest too, as it's breaking, but the ammo shortages
are so bad cuz of citizens buying ammo.
And now you know Homeland Security bought 1.6 billion bullets, more than they'd use
for target practice in a decade, that's 1.6 billion bullets.
That's enough bullets to shoot every person in America more than four times.
Hollow points, 223, 308, hollow point 40, they did all this because they knew this was
coming.
And Obama's on record, that's the thing I get so mad about.
They all admit they've always wanted total abolition of our guns, the UN treaty pushes
that.
The abolition of civilian ownership of firearms, because civilian ownership of firearms threatens
the legitimate power monopoly of the state.
That's a quote from Unideer and the treaty in July 7th, 2001.
And it's the same treaty today, they just added to it.
This is their goal, don't say it's about the dead kids, it's about domination.
Because every country where they take the guns, the cops are running around in black
masks with machine guns and torturing people and arresting everybody in giant prisons,
okay?
We know what this is about.
Let's start going to some of these clips, and we'll have more of these on the nightly
news tonight.
Jacari Jax is doing it, but undoubtedly I'll do some special reports as well.
Cuz as soon as the broadcast is over, I'm gonna put my head in all this and come up
with some statements.
It's exactly what we thought, but even bigger, they're gonna swarm us with our own tax money
to take our guns at every level.
They're gonna make the entire homeland security hysteria and fear about guns.
They're trying to kill the gun culture, and I got news for you, it's gonna backfire.
Currently, there's gonna be more mass shootings, though.
That's why they're so confident, they've got something really nasty planned.
Like Fast and Furious was when the Second Amendment, thousands of dead Mexicans conservatively,
hundreds of dead Americans conservatively, five dead law enforcement conservatively on
our side, hundreds on their side.
Thousands of citizens, civilians, as we're called, these are cold-blooded mafia dons.
I mean, Obama admits he signs death orders, what is it, every Tuesday for hundreds of
drone strikes, because it's okay when he does, even though it violates international law.
In all these countries we're not even at war with, that Congress hasn't authorized, and
they'll blow up an entire apartment building to get one bad guy, they say.
And it's like, well, that's collateral damage, yeah, dead kids.
Go out and play golf, smoke cigarettes, drink whiskey, you know what Obama does.
I mean, this is disgusting exploitation, and the high-fying makes me wanna throw up.
Drudge has a photo of that up on his site, we can play it here for viewers.
But radio listeners, we've got it linked up at info-wars.com as well.
Yeah, there's the clapping and all of it.
Here's the first clip, universal background checks, okay?
Obama, we're gonna go to the clip, 11 minutes into his speech, he says 40% not checked,
yeah, when you sell it to your neighbor, or they sell it to you.
I mean, criminals are always gonna get guns, they bust cops all the time selling guns they've
gotten in buybacks.
So here's the universal background check comment by Obama.
First, it's time for Congress to require a universal background check for anyone trying
to buy a gun.
The law already requires licensed gun dealers to run background checks, and over the last
14 years, that's kept 1.5 million of the wrong people from getting their hands on a gun.
All right, that's enough.
But it's hard to enforce that, though.
Yeah, but Adam Lanza, your patsy- When as many as 40% of all gun purchases are
conducted- That's good, I'm gonna go back to the air.
Adam Lanza, your patsy, I guess they're so used to me in the first hour talking over
him, I'm doing it again.
Yes, you're right.
Adam Lanza, the patsy, or whoever he is, the whacked out of his mind, the cover of a Hollywood
movie about mind control, same look in all these guys' eyes.
On psychotropics, under psychiatric care, they fought like a devil to keep that from
coming out, but his family's on record now.
He tried to buy a gun five times and couldn't get one.
I mean, obviously, going to gun shop, plus his mental illness was in the health record.
They got filed, and he looked like he was whacked out of his brain.
I've been at gun shows with private dealers, somebody selling off their collection.
They don't sell to people that look like they're illegal aliens, they don't sell to people
that don't.
They'll talk to you before they sell you a gun.
And so what if you're a felon?
Most felons were innocent.
Or who's to say if somebody did a white collar crime 20 years ago, they can't have a gun
to protect themselves?
Look, here's the deal, you try to take somebody's guns, they're gonna try to take your guns,
it's real simple.
In the old days, when you got let out of prison, if you were arrested with a gun that you legally
owned, your gun until the 50s in most states was given back to you.
Here's your shotgun you were arrested with, you bought down at Sears and Roebuck.
Don't try to use that illegally, because people got it, a criminal's gonna get a gun anyways.
And I understand it's a way to put criminals back in jail if you catch them with guns again.
Look, all that should be in prison is violent offenders and white collar criminals, and
you shouldn't be getting out.
It was a lot less crime in this country back in the 30s and 40s and things.
When if you did a robbery or something, you're gonna be in jail for ten years, busting rocks.
Now it's like a college of criminal activity.
Let's go ahead and go to a Second Amendment right of individuals to own for sport, hunting,
protection, and collection.
Notice he had to stick protection in there.
But how am I gonna protect myself from six or seven gang bangers if I don't have a semi-auto?
And we've seen those countless videos of store owners and others.
So this is Obama's version of the Second Amendment, here it is.
Like most Americans, I believe the Second Amendment guarantees an individual right to
bear arms.
I respect our strong tradition of gun ownership and the rights of hunters and sportsmen.
There are millions of responsible, law-abiding gun owners in America who cherish their right
to bear arms for hunting or sport or protection or collection.
Like most Americans, I believe the Second Amendment guarantees an individual right to
bear arms.
Hit pause for a moment.
I respect our strong- The crew was asking me where was the smiling.
There it was right there.
I only watched about half of it cuz I was busy talking over it.
And I turned it off a few times cuz I couldn't listen to it.
Just while I was watching the continued smirking.
It's like when you get caught doing something bad and it's funny, and your dad's going,
I know you did it.
I know, you know, don't lie and you're going, and it's like funny.
I mean, this guy could not get the, you know what, eat and grin off his face.
And the crew was asking me where it's at.
I saw it like five, six times in just half of it I've watched.
But I mean, there it is.
Let's roll that again.
Here it is.
He's an individual right to bear arms.
I respect our strong tradition of gun ownership- Did you see him hold the smile down?
And the rights of hunters and sportsmen.
He is so happy, he had to fight- There are millions of responsible law abiding
gun owners in America who cherish their right to bear arms for hunting, or sport, or protection,
or collection.
There goes another smile.
I mean, this is insane.
And then he goes on to say at the 1554 Club, I wanna play that one.
He says, we can respect the Second Amendment while keeping an irresponsible law breaking
few from inflicting harm on a massive scale.
Yeah, by arming people in the school.
The government has psychological profiles to know who's steadfast, who's always been
to work on time, generally who's got a military style background or an Eagle Scout, people
that are into duty.
I mean, I'll tell you who you are, you are the football coaches.
I mean, this is a no brainer.
You arm honorable people, obviously the weird science teacher, who everybody knows is a
perv or whatever.
And you give them a psychological evaluation, I mean, I'm all for that just cuz you might
end up getting a crazy someday as a teacher that kills people.
Plus the kids are so out of control, who knows what will happen, you're getting assaulted.
My point is to do psychological profiling and arm the teachers, or have retired cops
who wanna work as janitors.
Believe it, they would come and be happy to sweep the floors, be undercover and protect
kids and put a couple of retired cops at every school.
I mean, I bet you get cops that would do it for free, but you don't wanna do that, you
wanna just pay them.
I mean, this is a no brainer, but I don't want the police in there doing the anti-drug
stuff and harassing people and things.
Dealing with bullies, things like that's fine, but I guarantee you, they're saying they're
gonna have federal police in there, we're gonna skip this break coming up.
I guarantee you, they're gonna just turn this into a federal brainwashing, federal spying,
federal anti-gun officers, which is actually what they're proposing.
Instead of arm the teachers, and if the schools are too cowardly to do that, like Texas and
other states are doing.
I had that state superintendent on from that Texas town where they're 30 minutes from the
local police department, but it's a big school out in the country.
And he said, we saw mass shootings in 2007, and we're not gonna wait 30 minutes, and we're
not gonna have our teachers illegally carrying guns in principle.
So we have people that have concealed carry that we do some private training with the
police and some building clearings tile stuff.
But the feds don't want that, they want mass shooting training where you go get in a ball.
And in every mass shooting, a teacher finally knocks the window out and tries to claw out
the burglar bars to go out the window.
I mean, if you hear boom, boom, boom shooting, it should be, if you really wanted to be serious
for something that's still very rare, you would have collapsible stairs, a step ladder
that was right there.
And you'd open it and make sure the windows were openable from the inside to go out the
window.
We're skipping the break.
I mean, it is just amazing, absolutely amazing what's going on here.
I mean, they used to tell people, if you hear a nuclear bomb sirens go off, get under your
desk.
And it was just all about creating fear.
But at least with that, the ceiling might fall on you, that actually might protect you.
There was some reality there, even though it was done for fair mongering, that was later
declassified.
Getting in a ball when someone's coming to kill you is the last thing you wanna do.
You've seen that lawyer where the guy's trying to kill him and the lawyer's dodging and he's
getting shot in the arms, but he still gets all the way up on him and then hides behind
a tree.
I mean, if you're cornered, you're better to fight than just sit there and be a sitting
duck.
I thought that was Remo Williams, remember that movie, Remo Williams, pretty good B movie
where the guy, yeah, Fred Ward, where the Japanese karate master knows how to dodge
bullets.
You've seen that footage of the lawyer, he dodges a bunch of them.
That guy's got a revolver and he's like dodging it.
I mean, if somebody pulls a gun on me and I don't have a gun, that's what's gonna happen,
is that I'm gonna dodge him.
And if somebody came into my house and I couldn't get to a gun or a restaurant, I guarantee
you without thinking I would go throw myself at them, just like Susanna Hupp's dad did
in that Luby saving a bunch of people.
Not because I'm a hero, folks, you couldn't control me.
And I just don't know how we've gotten to the point where a lot of people just kneel
down.
You're shooting people and they just, you're shooting them in a row?
Let me just get ready and put my head down.
Let me put my head down while you shoot me.
I mean, where is the survival instinct?
Every mammal I know.
I remember I was about five, six years old, my grandmother had these mousetraps out for
mice and rats out in the country they were getting in the house.
And I never even told them about this story, cuz it didn't really even break the flesh,
like partially did.
I was like three, four, five, I don't remember how old I was, it was real little.
It was on the back porch and there was a bucket and there was a rat in it.
It had fallen in the bucket, it was trying to get out.
And I wanted to be nice and help him get out.
And I reached in there and that rat bit me.
One time a honeybee was in the baby pool and I wanted to say that it stung me and I really
cried.
My dad said, it was one of my first memories, I was about two and a half, cuz I wanted to
help the bee and it stung me, I didn't know why it was mean to me.
But the point is, is that a rat will bite you, a raccoon will bite you, a dog will bite
you, a seal will bite you, a woodchuck will bite you, a otter will bite you, a wildcat
will bite you, a puma will bite you, a cow will bite you and head bite you.
A bunny rabbit will bite you, a deer will bite and kick you.
Every mammal fights back, it's automatic if you're cornered.
And they're trying to take our basic instinct of defending ourselves away.
And that's why they hate the gun culture because it's helping us redevelop and rediscover that.
Let's go to this bizarre 1647 clip, pundits saying it's all about all out assault by tyrants
on liberty.
Let's go to Obama responding to his critics, here it is.
This will be difficult.
There will be pundits and politicians and special interest lobbyists publicly warning
of a tyrannical all out assault on liberty.
Not because that's true, but because they want to gin up fear or higher ratings or revenue
for themselves.
Oh, I wonder who you're talking about, punk.
And behind the scenes, they'll do everything they can to block any common sense reform
and make sure nothing changes whatsoever.
Yeah.
The only way we will be able to change is if their audience, their constituents, their
members- Let's stop right there.
That is a profound statement.
And he's thinking about Alex Jones.
He's thinking about Matt Drudge.
He's thinking about Glenn Beck.
He's thinking about Larry Pratt, Wayne LaPierre.
I mean, guaranteed, cuz the White House has responded to me before.
And it's come out that Homeland Security's got files on Matt Drudge and Alex Jones and
all this stuff.
And there's been lawsuits over, but they won't release them by InfraGard, that's a board
member of the NRA, Bob Barr, former congressman.
I mean, they're talking about us, cuz that's incredible.
While they're up there, they know we know they're crooks.
I mean, these people shipped 20,000 plus guns into Mexico.
The gun dealers allowing guns to walk under ATF orders, that's just the least of it, so
the media focused on that to divert.
They shipped hand grenades.
They had the US Army get weapons down there, 18 wheelers, rocket launchers, to try to just
wreck Mexico so they could then say there's a bunch of US guns doing it to blame our Second
Amendment.
And again, that all came out.
You know how gangster that is?
That is a false flag.
And they're doing the same thing right now.
And I'm gonna be honest with you, again, I didn't watch that full speech, and I was only
reading these quotes.
That was a stunning quote.
We're gonna do overdrive the whole hour.
Guys, back that back up for me if you can, and I know you've moved to the next clip.
I wanna go back to 1647, that is just stunning.
And you can see him holding back his mafia smirk, hey, that Goodfella business, Biden
might work for you in New York and Chicago and places, okay, nothing against New Yorkers
or Chicagoans.
They're great people, but because they've been such wealthy areas, the criminals all
ran there and they've run your areas for 100 years.
I mean, all that Goodfella crud and your shark skin suits and all that may intimidate people.
And you may think it's funny to sit there with your, I mean, they look like Robert DeNiro
and Goodfellas.
Great Martin Scorsese movie.
I watched it again, it's a true story, with my wife Saturday night.
And that same fake confidence makes my blood literally boil.
And they cannot stand the fact that I got up there and said, you wanna take our guns,
you wanna enslave us.
And that was the number one story in the country for two days.
They were talking about Alex Jones first and foremost.
That's why we need your prayers, because they go, you're discredited, you're yelling at
us, you're calling us criminals.
That's not a real debate.
You're not a real person having a real debate.
You're not like my neighbor coming over and going, hey, we don't have enough land to have
an agriculture exemption.
But if we combine together and get an agriculture exemption, we can get off on our taxes.
If we put honeybees on it or maybe a cow or two, how's that sound?
You wanna do that?
Man, that's a really good idea.
Yeah, that'll lower our taxes massively.
I've been so busy, I really haven't had time to go talk to you, I'm glad you reached out
to do that.
Yeah, let's do that.
I waited so long, the neighbor went ahead and just bought some more properties they
could do it, but they're still nice enough.
I'm gonna talk to them, but let me merge in with them.
But the point is, that's a negotiation, that's a good faith.
I'm talking to my neighbor, hey, how you doing there, Jesse, or whoever the neighbor is,
how are you doing today?
Let's talk about, as regular people, nice calm voices, hey, come on in and have a cup
of coffee.
When somebody is a known liar, telling me they don't want my guns when they're sworn
to get them.
And there are a bunch of crooks that cause mass murder in Mexico and the US Southwest
to blame the Second Amendment and scapegoat gun owners and use a bunch of dead Mexican
kids.
Mexico has press conferences, Calderon did it, we gotta do a piece on that.
He got a bunch of Mexican kids around him and said, America, we ban your guns, it's
your fault.
I mean, it's the most ridiculous script, and the White House did it, and the guy that did
it, killing thousands of people and hundreds of children, is trying to blame you and I
for it.
And then we get angry and they go, you're discredited, and only the sheep go, yeah,
you're discredited when you get angry.
But when they go have rallies with Cuomo and gangsters like the godfather of Chicago, Emanuel,
they start going, we're gonna do it, yeah, yeah, we're gonna get the guns.
But with us, no, don't get excited, hold on, you just sit right there and you take a deep
breath and you calm down and you're discredited, okay?
But you notice the president in his press conference, what did he say?
He said, there are gonna be people saying this is tyranny, there are gonna be people
saying the government's evil.
And he does this little gangster satisfaction, he's not even a good liar now, he goes, and
they're lying, they're wrong, I mean, that is the most incredible thing, the President
of the United States is directly responding to us, there's no doubt, no doubt.
And I've entered this insane vortex where I've got all these pundits on, and they're
saying, yeah, Alex, you're pretty much the most prominent voice now, I didn't even want
that.
I mean, this is creepville on steroids, cuz let me tell you, I'm a macho guy and I don't
like tyrants, but I gotta be honest, it is creepy to have the president responding to
you.
And let me tell you, they're thinking about a group of people there, but right in the
middle is me, I mean, he's thinking about a group of people.
And cuz it's come out that we're in their internal stuff, but I mean, it's just unbelievable,
that criminal now responding to me.
We're on the march, the empire's on the run, Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Hello, I'm Alex Jones, myself, my family, the Infowars.com team want to relay to you
and your families that we are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every
front.
Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats, but we can't do that without
your help.
By getting the films, bumper stickers and t-shirts at Infowars.com, you will wake up
people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before.
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here.
It's an Infowar.
The spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
You've come to expect winter specials from Herbal Healer Academy, and we're not going
to let you down.
Battle through cold and flu season with powerful natural and safe flu fighters, antivirals
like olive leaf extract capsules and elderberry power, vitamin D3, 180 caps, only $9, beta
glucans and an incredible immune system booster, our own four herb tea capsules and Respa 8,
all specially priced during the winter sale at herbalhealer.com.
Also exclusive homeopathic detoxes for lungs, kidneys, liver, whole body and lymph are on
sale.
Herbal Healer Academy offers correspondence courses to teach you how to handle your health
naturally.
And as always, new customers get a free 128-page catalog with your order.
Log on and save big now when you hit the winter specials at herbalhealer.com, healing the
world with nature one person at a time since 1988, celebrating 25 years in service to the
natural healthcare industry.
What would your life be like if you woke up each morning with new vitality, feeling better
than you have in years, and you noticed a difference in your sleeping patterns, blood
sugar levels, and had a sense of well-being overall?
There's something that is changing thousands of people's lives, and you could be one of
them.
It's called heart and body extract.
Sharon Harris, co-creator of Heart and Body Extract, talks about the positive effects
of heart and body extract.
What happens with the formula heart and body extract is it's giving the body the necessary
vitamins, minerals, amino acids, enzymes, and phytonutrients so the body will heal itself.
And yes, the body does have the ability to balance blood pressure, balance cholesterol,
clean and unclog the arteries.
It can also work on balancing the circulation for diabetic stuff.
The body is an amazing thing.
It simply needs some help so it has the tools to heal itself.
Heart and Body Extract gets results.
To order your two-month supply, call now toll-free at 866-295-5305.
Order online at hbextract.com.
What these psycho dungeon keepers really like is putting innocent people in jails.
You know, when freedom fails, the best men rot in filthy jails and those that cried appease
appease are hung by those they tried to please.
I'm not afraid of dying.
I don't want to be locked up in one of their dungeons, man.
If they ever lock me up in one of their dungeons, I'm innocent.
Get me out.
Oh, man.
Again, I hadn't seen the whole speech.
I was reading over the transcripts and now we're playing clips of it and the whole crew
said they were back there having lunch.
Well, part of the crew, the TV crew, they said, no, no, we knew they were talking about
you because obviously I came out saying it's tyranny.
It's a takeover last week.
That was the big story.
The White House responded at the end of Piers Morgan to my petition and denied it as if
they could have ever deported him because I asked anyways.
We were just showing how your whole petition's a fraud anyways.
You're not a dictator.
You're trying to be one.
Any country where you give a petition to the president and they can do whatever they want,
that's not called a president, it's called a dictator.
And by the way, Rand Paul, two congressmen, more congressmen, they're calling him a dictator,
a king.
They're talking about impeachment and they're talking about how they're gonna impeach him.
Let's go.
It's not, hey, if you keep pushing, we're gonna impeach you.
We've got a grandstander up there telling us it's our fault when more kids get killed
when they're the ones trying to block armed guards in the schools.
Remember that?
And he's trying to get the people organized to overthrow their own Bill of Rights and
Constitution.
That is sedition.
He is trying to turn all of our cities into crime-ridden, mafia-dawn areas like he controls,
and we don't want any part of it.
White House now requires we the people petitions to have 100,000 signatures for official response.
Yeah, well, they responded to the states' rights ones that had hundreds of thousands
and he said, no, there are no states.
I am your Supreme Leader.
All right, I wanna go to your phone calls, but let's play this clip again.
Pundits saying it's all about assault by tyrants.
I mean, Obama brought in unconstitutional Obamacare openly.
Hey, guys, will you come, hold on one second, man, will you come, guys, talk to this Canadian
TV thing cuz I'm doing overdrive and just set me up for Skype.
Ma'am, hold on one second.
Here you go.
I mean, they just all have gotten my cell phone number somehow, they're just calling
and calling and BBC's on there too.
And then Good Morning America's on there, I never even told you this morning about it.
So I gotta deal with that, I gotta get more producers, more people, they're working hard
in there.
There's just too much going on.
What was I getting into?
I told, yeah, pundits, we're gonna play pundits.
I know there's gonna be idiots on YouTube in places that aren't listening to the radio
or not watching us on prisonplanet.tv.
Look at this crazy guy, he says the White House is responding to him.
They responded to my petition and said they were watching Piers Morgan, Jay Carney did.
That's the White House press secretary.
Myself, Matt Drudge and others have come out that Homeland Security has files on us just
for our covering the TSA.
Big Sis has responded and talked about Matt Drudge, the White House has.
We have the tens of millions of listeners and viewers and readers.
Piers Morgan has half a million until I went on his show and went up to a million.
And then tens of millions cuz it was aired everywhere else.
I mean, it's an illusion that the president is a nobody punk, he's not our president.
And then they try this just cuz you're racist folks, if there was a black guy that was like
George Washington, I'd wash his feet.
I'm so sick of what color people are, I don't care about their hearts and their minds, the
character of their deeds.
And I'm sick of these racists standing behind a race, they're not even racist though, they
use it to manipulate.
And Obama is a clear and present danger to this republic.
And I'm saying second American Revolution, peaceful secession, boom, people are listening.
I'm saying it's time to impeach his butt, okay?
And he's responding to us and they are hacking our site and doing every dirty trick you can
imagine.
We need people to help us, if they bring infowars.com down, it doesn't matter, we'll just set up
alternate backup sites and we'll get our news out one way or the other.
You're not gonna stop any of us, okay?
But if these are sophisticated, obviously governmental things going on, I'm not gonna
get into the nature of them.
I saw there's one a piggyback on the exploitations, but it is not fun.
And we have people up 24 hours a day, we're gonna put more on the job and it'll just make
us stronger by the grace of God.
But they're mad, because no one will call them what they are, low down gangster thug
criminals and waging war against our Bill of Rights and Constitution.
Putting us under UN command, passing Obamacare, raising taxes on poor people.
Man, I tell you, that makes me these helpless, sad, a lot of people laugh at these Obama
noise and I've done it to myself cuz it's funny.
It's funny cuz they sound funny.
I told the Obama lady, I said, you sound like a Muppet.
I said, I have laughed at you, but I care about you as a human.
I don't know if I should laugh or cry.
And then I showed her how he lied and said he wouldn't raise taxes and how he lied and
said he wouldn't come after the gun.
She goes, wow, I never saw that, he is a liar.
And my whole point is I want her to have a future, I want her to have a country, I want
her to be free, I care about her soul, her mind.
And the media just says, no, you're racist if you don't vote for Obama.
I mean, it's just such a dumbed down, how obvious does it have to get?
Here's the kids, I'm high-fiving, I'm gonna get the guns for you kids.
The kids said, you're against the little five-year-old if you don't give me my guns.
But I'm not, I'm not a tyrant.
There's no tyranny, there's nothing wrong going on anywhere.
I mean, this is insane.
They are attacking me and others because we're aggressive.
And they wanna just normalize all this tyranny.
Let's go to this clip one more time, here it is.
This will be difficult.
There will be pundits and politicians and special interest lobbyists publicly warning
of a tyrannical all-out assault on liberty.
Not because that's true, but because they wanna gin up fear or higher ratings or revenue
for themselves.
And behind the scenes, they'll do everything they can to block any common sense reform
and make sure nothing changes whatsoever.
No, that's not true.
The only way we will be able to change is if their audience, their constituents, their
membership says this time must be different.
And that's what they call it, now is the time and his executive orders that are now out.
Up there with those dead kids trying to blame gun owners for it.
And we've said, don't make schools victim disarmament zones.
We've said, get people off these Prozac type drugs that 20% of the country's on roughly.
Don't have the federal government demand that foster kids be put on psychotropics, 67% of
them.
I mean, they know the vaccines are killing people, it's on the inserts, they can kill
you.
And they get on the news and go, there are no side effects, that's a conspiracy theory.
I've shown you news clips, I've shown you news articles.
These people do not care about you.
And he represents Goldman Sachs and JP Morgan.
We've got to start a protest, those guys start pulling money out of them.
I guess that's the answer is just go after the banks.
The foreign banks, I mean, I guess that's it, he's just their agent.
And they've taken the country over by fraud and now they don't want us armed to ever be
able to get our country back because they're planning real tyranny.
They want those guns so bad because they're in a race before everything collapses.
Because if it all collapses, they'll use it to be able to take over and get control.
But if we have guns and fight off the roving hordes of welfare people burning things, that
won't play into their hands, will it?
So they've got to get guns demonized so they can have cover to wage their homeland security
war on gun owners, and that's the plan.
The NSA, the whole homeland security system and giant anti-gun checkpoints, and that's
what these federally funded quote gang checkpoints are all over the country.
Texas is heading it up, totally unconstitutional.
But see, Texas thinks conservative means police state, no, it means the opposite.
So they're like, well, yeah, we have crimes, we're gonna have checkpoints to look for gang
members.
No, it's just a search our cars.
You know where the gang members are, I can take it to them right now selling crack cocaine
five miles from here.
Let's go to a few more clubs than your calls.
Let's just say I can't just be the usual suspects.
Let's play that club, here it is.
That's 18-
We are responsible for each other.
It's okay, go ahead and play that one.
It's all right, guys.
I know we got a bunch of clips here.
We are responsible for each other.
Okay, do you wanna play 18-12 now or, got a whole bunch of clips there in our primitive
computers.
Well, it just says 18-12, I can't just pass the usual suspects, we've got them highlighted
right here.
I was just going off the ones I highlighted.
It doesn't matter, hey, that's great.
Which one can we go to next?
Okay, well, let's just go ahead and play the next clip, yeah, let's go ahead and play it.
Soon as I'm finished speaking here, I will sit at that desk and I will sign a directive
giving law enforcement, schools, mental health professionals, and the public health community
some of the tools they need to help reduce gun violence.
We will make it easier to keep guns out of the hands of criminals by strengthening the
background check system.
We will help schools hire more resource officers if they want them and develop emergency preparedness
plans.
We will make sure mental health professionals know their options for reporting threats of
violence even as we acknowledge that someone with a mental illness is far more likely to
be a victim of violent crime than the perpetrator.
All right, let's stop right there.
Their main mission is to say everybody's mentally ill, or get you on welfare, or get you in
the criminal justice system to say now you don't have your rights and make you a slave
of the state.
This is just modern forms of slavery.
They know exactly what they're doing and they exempt themselves from all their garbage.
They've got get out of jail free cards, literally.
Congress gets caught insider trading, they go, guess what, we'll pass a law to make it
illegal.
It was already illegal.
Then the law they pass legalizes them insider trading if the House or Senate Ethics Committee
run by some of the worst offenders, it's like, well, if the other fox says that I'm allowed
to go eat the hens, it's okay.
It'd be like Stalin saying, well, if the Politburo says I can kill 10 million Ukrainians, I can,
that makes it legal.
Or it'd be like Heinrich Himmler saying, well, we can kill all these people in death camps
if Hitler says it's okay.
Mr Hitler of Der Fuehrer, can you sign this order to make it all legal?
Mr President, can you sign this order for drone attacks to legally bomb countries and
kill innocent people?
You signed the order, you didn't have authority, you say NATO gave it to you, not Congress.
Okay, they're our boss now.
One more clip, one more clip.
This is really creepy collectivism.
You heard, we have rights to be safe in our schools.
We have rights to be safe in our churches.
We have rights to be safe in Chicago, where we've taken all the guns and the mafia runs
things.
I didn't mean to say that.
See, it's this collectivism where you as a group of gun owners, you are responsible for
the dead kids.
And he's had his pundits come out and say that, and that makes me mad.
They're trying to guilt me into giving up my rights when he's nothing but a lowdown
criminal.
And again, I've listed the articles of impeachment.
He is a criminal, and I've listed the proof at infoawards.com.
We are responsible for each other.
Listen to this weirdness now, this stazzy state they're announcing, where everybody's
spying and cuddling, and it's collective.
We're all in socialist healthcare now, so you're not allowed to eat that steak cuz I
gotta pay for your healthcare.
You're not allowed to drink that Coca-Cola or that beer now, because I say it's bad for
you.
And it's a nanny state, and we're the collective.
And we're gonna get the gun manufacturers, NRA here, not the Second Amendment, but stakeholders
to decide if we're gonna ban the guns.
All this UN talk, let's go to that clip.
We are responsible for each other.
Again, we are responsible for each other, and it ties into all the rest of the garbage.
We're gonna be playing more of these clips tonight on the transmission.
Let's just go to more calls here.
Antoine in Florida, you're on the air, go ahead.
Hey, buddy.
I just wanna get a couple points for us, just I think we need to get on the offensive.
I think I was talking to a couple friends, I think we should march on DC with fake guns
cuz I don't want them to put a real person with a gun and say that we shoot people just
to symbolize the guns that we have.
And we should also, I also think you should do a special report cuz your special reports
are very effective.
I was able to wake up a lot of people through your special reports.
If you could somehow, I know you're very busy, and make a really good special report showing
everything that you talked about, how we got here, that'd be really great.
I mean, Facebook or social media, I've woken up a lot of people, just like you woke up
that lady, the Obama phone lady, right there on the air in front of us all.
I've done that to a lot.
I'm African American myself, and personally, every African American that I know that's
under 30 knows that he's a crook.
Now, the ones that are above 30 think he's God.
Well, that's what I've noticed cuz I do get obsessed reading YouTube comments.
And I go to the channels and look, and it's like most of the comments not just on my YouTube
channel, but others are like, this is a crook, we warned you, he's coming.
It's black people criticizing him, but then the media says 95% of blacks support Obama.
I don't think that's true, and I don't think these polls we hear that only 15% don't wanna
turn their guns in.
I mean, that's not what I'm seeing or hearing.
I don't believe these polls.
And trust me, I'm in the black community, I mean, my grandmother cried cuz I wouldn't
vote for Obama.
That's how bad it is to vote for Obama.
Okay, I was playing it to her all, and it was really weird.
They were contradicting themselves while I'm laying out the hardcore facts in their face.
You know, I've talked to folks who told their parents he's coming for the guns, and they
didn't agree.
But now he's coming for them.
You're right, but see, it's kind of too late.
But I mean, look, he said he wouldn't raise taxes on working class folks.
I mean, they're raising taxes on the poorest people in America that are the working poor.
That's pretty cold blooded, isn't it, when you claim you're this big communist that wants
to help everybody.
That's true.
And another thing I noticed too, as I'm an African American, and you get an action card,
he'll tell you the same thing.
The more educated black people have a hard time believing it, cuz they've been in college
and stuff.
But in the same way, look, look, look, these educated idiot yuppies, I don't care what
color they are, are dumb.
They won't listen to facts, cuz they're too busy laughing at you, cuz they're so smart.
I know, it's a joke, I appreciate your call, my friend.
Let's talk to Joseph in Texas, thanks for holding her on the air.
Hey, Alex, I've been listening to you for a while.
The question is, does everybody realize that history is repeating itself?
A lot of people do, that's why I'm freaking out.
We are repeating history, we're in trouble.
You need to actually, the one thing that you need to realize is that he's gonna present
four arguments.
The four arguments are gonna run along the political, which they're already doing.
The social with the children that he parades out.
You watch, next thing he's gonna come out with, and they're gonna cherry pick the data,
is gonna be medical and economic.
No, he's already doing that.
He's gonna turn Obamacare into a funding mechanism for gun grabbing, because Obamacare is written
to where he can do anything he wants.
Yep, but history's repeating itself, and it seems whenever there's a new bad thing, right
now guns with a new smoking, they're bad, according to the government.
They break out these four arguments, and the only way to fight them is basically say, quit
cherry picking the data, let me see the entire report.
Well, it's more than that, I got a right to defend myself.
I don't care what you say, you're not getting my gun, cuz I'm not guilty for what somebody
else did.
That, and do they honestly think, do the people in New York, these legislators in New York
who passed all these gun control laws, do they honestly think criminals are so stupid
that they're going to be stuck in getting guns from the street?
No, they're gonna go across state lines.
The criminals are gonna rejoice.
I mean, the criminals are on the run right now, because they're getting their butt shot
off by the police and the citizens.
We'll be right back, stay with us.
You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa, where a nicely furnished cabin
with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine, and laundry service awaits.
After a good night's sleep, your adventure begins.
We're on a golden stag safari for big game, but it's not Africa, it's Argentina.
One-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo, huger, bighorn rams, wild boar, and the biggest
stag deer in South America.
All gold metal quality, all the action you can handle.
Land rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages, hunting guides, ground
transportation included, and more, all more affordable than you can imagine.
The adventure of a lifetime starts at goldenstagsafaris.com.
The big game hunting ranch, goldenstagsafaris.com.
American gardeners and fellow patriots, make the right choice with your money, time, and
your family food supply.
Choose 100% pure heirloom seeds in the Survival Seed Vault from mypatriotsupply.com.
Why spend more?
The Survival Seed Vault from mypatriotsupply.com is only $37.95 and includes 20 varieties of
pure, hardy, easy-to-grow heirloom seeds.
Yes, only $37.95, that's 70% less than our competitors.
You could buy three Survival Seed Vaults for less than one of theirs.
The Survival Seed Vault from mypatriotsupply.com includes detailed planting and seed-saving
instructions and ships same day.
Plus, all orders over $49 ship free.
Mypatriotsupply.com is American-owned by patriots like you, passionate about freedom and preparedness.
Call now, 866-229-0927, that's 866-229-0927, or discover more emergency preparedness items
when you order at mypatriotsupply.com.
Choose the original, choose the Survival Seed Vault at mypatriotsupply.com.
My name is Steven Heuer.
After 22 years of nutritional counseling, I've observed that most brain malfunctions
have at their roots some form of toxicity and brain damage.
So whether it is poor memory, poor focus, lack of creative thinking, or more serious
matters like inability to focus, speak normally, or remember things, the emphasis to getting
one's brain working optimally needs to be on detoxification.
One World Way supports your body's number one means of detoxification, which is glutathione
production.
My name is Angie, and my son has suffered from borderline autism and constipation.
I got him on One World Way, and in two months, his constipation is gone.
He has become friendlier, he can carry on a normal conversation with me, and he has
made his first friend.
He's doing great, and he looks forward to taking One World Way every day.
You could offer him a present or a cake, and he would prefer the One World Way.
Go to oneworldway.com, that's oneworldway.com, or call 888-988-3325, that's 888-988-3325.
We're gonna have a big info wars nightly news tonight, 7 o'clock central.
You can get 11 memberships for the price of one.
Just go create the username passcode and share it with people, that's how we get the word
out more.
Yeah, no more Mr. Nice Guy, the globalists are dropping the hammer because they're behind
schedule and they've got to kill our gun culture.
It's very positive that they're being this nasty, and it really shows we're hurting them.
And so they're gonna try to get their legislation through without ever really admitting, here's
a little kid, I don't want your guns, well, the bill says it.
Here's a little kid, hey, your Obamacare has death panels, no, it doesn't, yeah, it's right
here in subsections.
Shut up, racist.
I remember actually watching Chris Matthews call people racist, and they'd be like, I
see you are, you're racist.
How does not wanting death panels mean I'm racist?
Well, of course a racist wouldn't say they were racist, I mean, it's, look, little kids
turn on your guns.
The little kids want them turned in, don't worry, Jimmy, I'll get the guns.
I mean, it's so transparent, Obama takes our tax money and wages war against us and gives
it to foreign banks.
And then I try to sell t-shirts like the new come and take it one to fund my media operation.
And yeah, there's evil pro gun people that make money.
And him and Biden are like, that's really terrible.
Yeah, we didn't make it out of insider trading like you and Dianne Feinstein.
Yeah, Biden, gosh, she's incredible.
Jim in California, you're on the air, go ahead.
Hey, mega dittos, Alex, if you're not fan of me before the end of this, ask me about
the Paris Morgan thing, I have some constructive criticism.
But the reason I called, I think regarding the Second Amendment, we could clear up all
the confusion of terms, intent, and reason if everybody would just go get a copy of Unintended
Consequences and read it cover to cover.
Yeah, it's an excellent book.
It's an excellent book.
And I think later I'm gonna mail my copy to Barry Hussein, highlight it, might get me
killed but might be worth it.
But this whole discussion about 1776 and we're all gonna go have a gun battle in the street
and stuff, before we get to that point, it seems to me that it would be smart by trying
the intelligent approach first.
But if everybody that went out and bought guns and bought ammo and had background checks
and did all that stuff, would just stop paying their taxes, most of these problems would
go away.
Hey, brother, let's get something straight.
I'm trying to stop the Civil War.
Believe me, I'm gonna be the first person killed or locked up.
I don't want this, okay?
I'm saying they want to get it started while having kids around them going, we just wanna
be reasonable.
I'm telling you, we're in danger.
What's your constructive criticism?
Okay, I'll skip there at some point.
But constructive criticism, I'm Paris Morgan.
You were great.
I love you.
You're preaching to the choir.
But I'm not the guy when you go on Paris Morgan, you should be talking to, you should be talking
to my mom and dad and my neighbors and whoever.
I tried to share with other people and they couldn't get past the tone and the indignation,
which I totally get this.
Totally justified.
But I think you need to put on a little bit of a dog and pony show to get a few more people
over on your side.
You've already won the Over a Marty list and I'm already calling your show.
I'm not the target audience when you go on Paris Morgan.
It's the little old lady who sits and drinks the Kool-Aid all day that you need to be kind
of that-
Let me get to a certain point, but I found if you slap them upside the head, down the
road they wake up.
It's like a delayed action.
And I didn't even do that on purpose.
I just got mad at the sniveling lying.
Christ overturned the tables and beat the money changers.
Paul Revere rode around saying get your weapons and shoot people.
I'm not doing any of that.
I didn't overturn the table.
I'm not saying shoot people.
I'm saying look, look, you want my guns, you little tyrant, okay?
And I'm sick of you.
And I'm sick of your propaganda, all right?
Now, if you'd like to learn more, we'll be covering all this tonight, seven o'clock central.
We take you now to Klandathu, where our forces are winning an incredible battle against the
Obamanoids.
Alex Jones signing off.
That's a Starship Troopers plug there.
And I'm not going crazy before the New York Times talks about Klandathu.