From the front lines of the information war, it's Alex Jones.
It's Sunday, the 20th day of January 2013.
Here's an important report filed by Melissa Melton.
Melissa Melton reporting for Info Wars Nightly News.
Last week, Alex Jones appeared on the Piers Morgan show on CNN
to discuss his views on gun control.
The following night, Piers decided to host a panel regarding Alex's appearance,
and he had on Daily Beast sports columnist Buzz Bissinger,
Huffington Post's Abby Huntsman, and lawyer Gloria Allred.
And Mr. Bissinger made what can only be described as a threat against Alex's life.
Let's take a look at this clip.
It is pathetic. It is ridiculous that you are allowed,
I don't care what the justification is,
that you are allowed in this country to own a semi-automatic weapon,
much less a handgun, but what do you need a semi-automatic weapon for?
The only reason I think you need it is, Piers, challenge Alex Jones to a boxing match,
show up with a semi-automatic that you got legally, and pop him.
I'd love to see that. In uniform.
I'll borrow my brother's uniform.
Now, as you saw in that clip, Bissinger tells Morgan
the only reason he would need a semi-automatic gun is to, quote,
pop Alex Jones, to which they all laugh, and Abby Huntsman actually says,
I'd love to see that, and Morgan even says he would borrow his brother's uniform.
And this isn't the only time during that television show that a threat was made on Alex.
Earlier in the show, one of Piers' guests also made the comment
that he hoped Alex's children would not be killed.
I don't want Alex Jones to get the phone call at 3 o'clock in the morning
that one of his children have been shot and killed by somebody who shouldn't have
a handgun or a rifle.
This kind of talk from supposedly anti-gun activists is abhorrent.
They're making a threat on national television to shoot and possibly murder someone,
and it's no joke either.
As you'll see in this next clip, private investigator Doug Hagman
came on the Alex Jones show just a few weeks ago
and talked about how he has an inside source in the Department of Homeland Security
and that the DHS is actually keeping a list of pro-gun activists
and political activists who will be taken out.
Anyone reporting on journalism speaking out against government policies,
anyone who protests, anything that is antithetical to this regime
will be shut up and censored, if you will.
And not only that, but according to my source, put on a list
because when the money supply or when the economy collapsed,
when we can no longer buy anything and the riots break out,
the very first people to go, according to my source,
the very first people to be rounded up,
the very first targets, if you will, on the radar of this regime
are the people that are speaking the truth about what's taking place.
On Hagman's site, he relayed in detail that there are lists of political dissidents
maintained by DHS and vocal opponents of the politics of the global elite,
the bankers, and the opponents of anything standing in their way
while they are on the top of the list to be, quote, handled.
In the days following that broadcast, news broke that Keith Ratliff,
a man behind FPS Russia, a gun show on YouTube that made the channel
one of the top ten most popular on the entire site,
was tied to a chair and shot execution style in the back of the head.
Then John Noveske of Noveske Rifle Works, a gun manufacturer known for his AR-15s,
was mysteriously killed in a car crash just days after he posted a list on Facebook
linking mass shootings and horrible acts of murder and suicide
to antipsychotic medications.
In the wake of these threats against Alex on the Piers Morgan show,
it would seem Twitter fans picked up Piers' sentiment and also threatened to shoot Alex.
One Twitterer wrote,
I hope Alex Jones gets taken by terrorists who shoot his arms and legs off
starting at the fingers and toes and work their way up.
Another, for the first time I see a good reason for guns in the USA.
Alex Jones, someone please shoot this Muppet.
I wish somebody would shoot this Alex Jones guy in the face.
And then another responded, please and thank you.
As the system ratchets up this war on our Second Amendment rights,
we are seeing some unprecedented attacks against pro-gun activists
and political activists who are just trying to fight for our freedom.
Are we going to see another false flag next?
Are we going to see another mass shooting, another Oklahoma City,
another systematic takeout of a group like we did in Waco?
Well, Doug Hagman left us with this chilling warning.
By the way, Alex, according to my DHS source, expect more.
Expect at least one more.
One more incident to really solidify in the minds of people that these big, bad assault rifles,
that misnomer to be sure, are not to be in the hands of the American people.
For InfoWars Nightly News, I'm Melissa Mountain.
We'll see you next time.
Well, it's our first visit with Ron Paul of 2013.
He is now the former congressman.
The first time I interviewed him, he was running for Congress again, I guess back in 95, 96.
And he'd been in Congress once before as a libertarian and, of course, went back as a Republican.
And he has been our greatest defender of liberty, worldwide loved and admired.
He's got big announcements coming up soon.
I've heard the rumors and I'll see if he'll give us any hint.
But he joins us, obviously, to talk about the fiscal cliff that he said we've already gone over a long time ago.
What's happening with that?
The Sandy Hook shooting, the announcements of the NSA openly spying on us.
Something Ron Paul talked about 15 years ago and got called a conspiracy theorist is now just out in the open.
And former congressman and really omni-budsman of liberty worldwide, thank you so much for spending time with us.
Good, good to be with you.
Did you have a good Christmas?
Yep, very good. Family got here.
We had a lot of fun and didn't solve any world problems.
I wish I need to learn how to unplug as well.
Wow, you heard what I threw out there, sir.
Where would you like to start first?
Well, the things that I've talked about is mostly, well, the general, you know, deterioration of our individual freedoms and our liberties and our arkets.
But I think the big thing, as I wound down my career, dealt with, you know, financial and the economy.
And I think both major parties and most members of Congress are in total denial as to what the real problem is because they think it's just a budget.
You know, well, if we change this number, raise taxes, cut spending, you know, pretend to cut spending, we solve the problem.
And I think it's much bigger than that.
I think, first off, the country is bankrupt.
We're insolvent.
We can't pay the bills.
And they won't admit it.
I mean, we have these obligations of $220 trillion in national debt of $16 trillion.
We're the biggest born debtor nation ever.
And that is ignored, and they talk about, you know, what they're going to do with tinkering with the tax code.
And they talk about cuts, which aren't cuts.
It's just all deceit and trying to fool the people into believing that they can tinker with a budget.
But I think the problem is, is government is too big.
They don't follow the Constitution.
They don't know what the rule of government ought to be in a free society.
And they don't admit we're bankrupt.
And oftentimes I've used this saying that, are we going to go over the cliff?
Well, in many ways, we're over the cliff in that we're not going to retrace ourselves.
If you're over a cliff, you just don't have a chance to climb back up.
And we really don't.
We're not going to have enough people in Congress in the next go around, or do we have them now?
We have better people now, and we're going to have some people speaking for us.
But we can't go back and all of a sudden balance our budget, remove the regulations, and protect our liberties.
All we have to do is listen to our president, what his plans are.
But the Republicans aren't doing a whole lot more because we're facing a situation where it took 100 years
for our governments and our schools to indoctrinate our people to accepting the idea that the rule of government
ought to be to take care of us and provide perfect safety and make sure nobody falls through the net
and take care of people and the whole world.
And I think we have to address the subject, what should the rule of government be?
The founders made an attempt at it.
They wrote a constitution.
We don't obey it.
And to me, if we would accept the notion that the rule of government is to protect our freedoms,
provide some national defense for us, provide a sound currency, and protect our liberties,
there would be no warfare state and there would be no welfare state.
And nobody wants to address that.
You know, in all this talk, neither Republicans or Democrats would even suggest about cutting the militarism.
The only talk was, should we increase the military expenditures by 18 percent or 20?
The people who wanted 18 percent were castigated for slashing national defense.
Instead, they were, you know, unpatriotic.
So that is where the mess is.
I see the mess that we're in, a problem of education, a consequence of 100 years of control
of many generations indoctrinating them into bad economic policy and bad foreign policy.
Congressman, you've talked about globalism, the Bilderberg Group, people like that,
but it's now in the Financial Times of London.
It's in hundreds of papers that we can probably pull some up and put them on screen
where they announce global government by the six mega banks.
And I listen to Bloomberg Financial on XM and they brag that they've conquered Europe with debt,
they've signed the Europeans onto derivatives, they've got them dependent on socialism,
but most of the debt is actually the central bank's debt that are really private.
And now I see them wrecking us, Congressman, on purpose to make us debt slaves while also making us dependent.
I mean, surely they know the facts, even the Congressional Budget Office, as you know,
three or four years ago said we were bankrupt.
All these other government economists have admitted this.
So you're not just somebody who studied economics, you're also a medical doctor.
It's kind of like a patient that's got cancer all over their body.
This is already a done deal.
So what's your take on my statement that we've been maneuvered into rack and ruin by loan sharks?
I mean, I think it's important to not just say there are a bunch of buffoons in D.C.
Goldman Sachs, J.P. Morgan and others in my research are just mafia organizations
that want us as basically debt slaves on a sharecropping plantation.
I think it's partially true, but it's also involved indoctrination through education.
It's just not 10 or 15 people who get together and all of a sudden they can change people's minds.
People endorse Keynesianism.
They endorse the Federal Reserve.
They endorse us being the policemen of the world and we should have these wars in the Middle East.
So they have been indoctrinated.
And yes, there are a few who are going to benefit.
You know, I can't read into their minds.
They sit back and say, you know what, we're going to bankrupt the country and cause us chaos.
I think they try to get away with manipulating and maneuvering
and benefiting themselves both with power and money.
And philosophically it doesn't work out, so they have to react.
So they take advantage of it.
It's sort of like taking advantage, don't let a major crisis go to waste.
I mean, they create the problems.
They think they're going to get away with it.
And then when the crisis hits, they make use of it and they say, well, we have to do.
They're motivated by money and power and they have to have control of politics.
Sure, sure. I'm talking about...
I don't think they're smart enough to on a daily basis say, well, we're going to do A and B is going to be results.
I think there are mostly unintended consequences that occur and they react.
I'd like to get people to react differently.
I agree with you that at the mid-level and even the upper levels, obviously,
it's just a corrupt system people have been born into now.
But I'm talking about the 112-point plan that got leaked out of the World Bank
when Joseph Stichlitz resigned the Nobel Prize winner in economics in 2002.
It talked about how they manipulated third-world countries into bankruptcy to take control
and it discussed doing it to the West.
So at Bilderberg, from our sources, but also at Davos, I've got Herman von Ruppe, head of the E.U.,
saying we're going to use the financial crisis to bring in the new world order.
That may be, and I don't know every individual who makes these plans,
but I do know that I meet a lot of people who believe...
I mean, you take a guy like Bernanke.
I think Bernanke actually believes that chunk.
You know, I think he really believes that he's been sent here by the Creator
to make sure we never have a Great Depression before
because they didn't print the money fast enough.
I don't think he sits and says, and goes much further than this,
because he has invested a lifetime into proving this ideology.
I think he's wrong. He's determined to prove he's right.
He creates truth.
And then these people that you're talking about,
they know what's going on, and they line up, and they get involved,
and they learn how to manipulate the system for political reasons.
So we know that our president has an agenda, and it's very, very clear,
so he works his agenda with the system that exists.
I agree with you.
There's different factions who only care about themselves,
and together they're the perfect storm.
But you're saying he thinks he's right, you think you're right.
Sir, I watch a speech that's in our film Matrix of Evil you gave in 2003 at McKinney-Ruffs
right outside Austin, here in South Austin,
and you laid out everything that was going to happen,
how they'd use the drones here, how they'd have the NSA spy on us,
how they would use the Patriot Act on the citizens,
how, when they collapsed things, they would use that to take full control,
how the derivatives bubble would work.
I mean, it's like you're a prophet, but you're not.
You were in there in the committees, you've studied history,
you knew what was going to happen.
You said the stimulus would work.
You said all these things wouldn't work.
You said that the Republicans would vote to raise taxes.
One dollar of cuts for every 41 in spending increases.
Seventy-seven percent of Americans with tax increases on payroll.
I mean, it's like the lying.
What's happened is we've been eased into this tyranny,
and so now you're here saying, well, we'll see who's going to be proven right.
You've been proven right, Congressman.
Toot your own horn.
We'll be right back with a conclusion of our important interview with Congressman Ron Paul.
As well as our all-natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents,
which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface.
But rather, we have formulated our silver gel
using the natural skin-nourishing chemistry of aloe vera
to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.SilverLongs.com
and click on our store page to find what silver-based products are best for you.
That's www.SilverLongs.com.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive
from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought
to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At eFoods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough
to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote,
Almost all the grocery stores are closed,
but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece.
It is better to be prepared ten years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex
and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies
and starve patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items
at InfoWarsShop.com.
These are items that I did research on, that I personally use.
We've got the LifeStraw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Kator Hand Crank Generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out in the field.
Strategic Relocation Third Edition by Joel Skousen.
When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein.
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Hand Crank Shortwave AM-FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at InfoWarsShop.com
and your purchase makes our InfoWar possible.
We're getting prepared. Are you? InfoWarsShop.com.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver,
a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution
that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning
and help improve wound healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day,
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases
such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria
at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Coast to Coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
And I'm not taking this moment to bash Glenn Beck.
I've tried to be nice to him, but he says he's now the leader of the libertarian movement.
Yes, I saw that. I'll have to check him out. I wonder what he believes in.
Yeah, because he told me that your supporters four years ago were going to blow us up with bombs
and that we did Oklahoma City.
And then he keeps saying that we shouldn't get in the government's face.
I mean, my only deal with Glenn Beck is he says I'm dangerous and basically shouldn't be on the air.
Piers Morgan basically says that as well.
And then now he tells me that he's my leader
and that he's now going to become Ron Paul and Alex Jones, I guess, mixed.
Do you have any comments on that?
Not too much because I don't know exactly what he's talking about.
All I can do is speak for myself on what I believe in and what I'm trying to do.
And I've been pretty much up front on what the principles are and which direction we should go and effort.
I think I do one thing differently than others, and that is I try to stick to ideas rather than personalities.
Of course, we've already mentioned the president and I mentioned George Bush.
But over the years, I basically don't attack the individuals.
I don't generally attack Bernanke.
Sure, but you did call him a demagogue when he said that your supporters wanted to blow up buildings.
Yeah, that's for sure.
But generally speaking, I don't do the personality thing.
That doesn't mean that, as a matter of fact, if you do the personality thing, you get a lot more attention.
But I don't want it to distract.
If people want, they'll try to entice me to say, what should we do with Bernanke?
How should we punish him?
Remember what our governor said that we should do with him.
I might agree with it.
I might even say things along that way.
But most of the time I'll go and say, it's the system, it's the system of the federal reserve.
No, no, no, I agree, I agree, I agree.
And that is what I want to concentrate.
Some people will concentrate on different things.
They'll have different tactics and different viewpoints.
And I think that's fine.
No, no, listen, I think Glenn Beck does a lot of great work and has gotten better and better.
He is just systematically, I don't infight.
You'll never hear my show talking about other people that are in the liberty movement.
He just routinely says, he said, I made up the 1.6 billion bullets, even though that's AP Reuters direct federal purchases.
I'm making up the police state.
I'm making up NSA spying.
Your supporters want to blow buildings up.
I mean, he is trying to gate keep, and I'm just warning you that unless you join with Sauron, Dr. Paul, he's going to stab you in the back.
And I'm only saying that kind of like a chart when you're coming into a bay in a boat.
I'm just marking the chart, Dr. Paul.
But you're a smart guy, you know that.
We've only got about six, seven minutes left in closing.
Sandy Hook and now the Feinstein bill and others to make us physically turn them in, not just go back and re-register with the ATF at their pleasure.
Now they want to just open where they decide law-abiding citizens turning their guns in.
What is your take on that?
And are you concerned about a purge or persecution of gun owners?
Well, I'm concerned about their inconsistency.
They want to get rid of guns because somebody used a gun and did some violence.
But we all know that more people are getting killed with hammers and fists and knives.
So they're not very consistent.
They see an opportunity.
They want to get rid of the guns.
Some people believe they're dangerous and want to get rid of them.
And other people want to get rid of them because they know that guns can resist a government tyranny.
And some people like the idea that governments become tyrants and they should run things.
As long as the government kills children, it's okay.
So they want to protect that.
You know, all that scandal and outcry, which much of it was justified seeing kids getting killed is a horror.
But at the same time, how about those people who are saying, okay, this is an excuse to take away the rights of people who use guns to defend their family.
How many of them are shouting and screaming about the children that our drones are killing on a daily basis?
Because they're Muslim kids in different color and they're overseas and nobody has to line them up and shoot them.
We can do it by directing drones from this country.
That doesn't even count.
So that's what their whole goal is, is to distract us from some of the horrors that governments perpetuate and the way they destroy our liberties.
And they perpetuate the violence.
I mean, compared to the violence that governments have perpetuated on the people versus what the people do to each other, there's no contest.
Historically, government's the number one killer, as you know.
University studies out of Hawaii and others, 292 million people killed in the 20th century, non-military combatants.
We have a red alert, sir, that just came out while you were on with us.
DrudgeReport.com, Weekly Standard, AP, you name it.
Obama White House threatens executive action to physically confiscate the firearms.
Biden has now given a speech, sir.
They've got a bunch of state reps and federal reps.
I've literally got over ten articles.
They're all calling for executive orders.
And Obama is saying now that he'll do everything in his power, including executive orders.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is what we feared.
Congressman, constitutionally, that's beyond a constitutional crisis.
As a constitutional expert, sir, if he signs an order ordering we turn in our guns, what does that mean?
Well, it should go without saying that he's gone way too far.
It also should go without saying that he's acting with the use of illegal violence.
And he becomes the violent person to say that if you don't – and this is not new.
He's been doing this.
You know, an environmental – if Congress moves too slowly, well, I'll write an executive order.
But he didn't invent the executive order and the signing orders.
You know, I'll ignore this.
It's a bipartisan thing.
But it's accelerating and getting dictatorial.
They now sell our militaries.
Yeah, it's been going on.
What do we do if Obama orders us to turn our guns in?
Doesn't that make him a dictator if he just says I'll do whatever I want?
There's certainly a dictatorial move on that.
If the American people had been a little bit better versed, maybe they wouldn't have reelected him.
So I do not say that he is a dictator like some of the 20th century dictators that killed 290 million people.
But these are dictatorial moves.
They're very, very dangerous.
And people say to me, well, how are you worried about, you know, the military arresting American citizens,
National Defense Authorization Act?
Because only one or two people were involved.
Yeah, but the principle is 100 percent when you establish a principle.
So what he's doing is perpetuating a principle of putting more power into the presidency.
And it's very, very dangerous.
Setting the precedent under NDAA?
We're almost out of time.
Sir, will you turn in your semi-autos?
Well, I might not even have anything to turn in for that purpose.
But I don't think the American people will.
I've always assumed that the line in the sand may well be drawn.
If the federal agent marches in unannounced and they say, well, give me your gun and give me your gold,
I don't think that we'll do that, you know, in a calm way.
I think the American people will highly resent it and resist.
So you think I was right, then, telling Piers Morgan if they try to confiscate the guns, it will start 1776, Part 2?
Well, I don't know whether I put them in the same words, but I think I said something very similar to what you're saying.
Well, God bless you, sir.
I hope we can get you back again in a month.
What are any other websites that are important to plug?
Just campaignforliberty.org?
Do that, and then we'll be listing some new things there because we're making some other web pages.
I'm going to have a home page.
Unfortunately, I didn't have ronpaul.com, so I'm going to have to have ronpaulshomepage.com.
That'll be coming up, but it's not ready yet.
All right, big announcements coming soon. We'll talk to you and say hi to the family. God bless you, sir.
Thank you.
Great to talk to that man during this dark time.
I told you executive orders were coming. They're getting us ready to see if we'll take it.
Ladies and gentlemen, this could be it.
Well, that concludes my interview with Congressman Ron Paul last week.
Just incredibly important information where he agrees with me that most Americans' line in the sand is the Second Amendment.
That's how our country was founded, and this is nothing but pure tyranny we're witnessing right now.
So I pray we can fix this peacefully through the courts, through the states, and through the Congress,
and a lot of people are standing up against this tyranny, including our next interview,
former state rep and, of course, Luby's Massacre survivor and mother and all-around just amazing patriot, Susanna Hupp.
I talked to her and here are some excerpts of this incredibly important interview.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support,
and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action.
Tyranny is here.
The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality.
It really says that the state is God.
The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most impressive police states on earth.
This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being expanded nationwide.
This documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all powerful shadow state.
Police state four chronicles the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen.
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship, body scammers, sound cameras, citizen spies, stage terror and cameras on every street corner.
It's only the beginning of the New World Order's hellish plan.
The police state isn't coming.
It's here.
Secure your copy today at Infowars.com or see it online in the highest quality at PrisonPlanet.tv.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy.
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At E Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my E Foods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece.
It is better to be prepared ten years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on E Foods Direct.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal-Bend Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now.
Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Coast to coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers? Well so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Representative Susanna Grasha Hupp, former representative.
She's a survivor of the Luby's massacre. Some of her family was killed.
She famously testified before Congress to Chuck Schumer that, hey, our guns aren't for duck hunting.
The full testimony is up at infoawards.com right now.
We just reposted it up there.
She said it's to protect us from you guys up there.
And I wanted to get her on the air because she was instrumental nationwide testifying before legislatures everywhere,
not just the Texas legislature that she later chaired committees on, to get concealed carry-in.
And we've seen 25, 30% or more reductions in every state that's done it.
So she'll be joining us to the bottom of the hour here in just a moment.
Here is just a short excerpt of her testimony before Congress.
The Second Amendment is not about duck hunting.
And I know I'm not going to make very many friends saying this.
But it's about all right, all of our right to be able to protect ourselves from all of you guys up there.
Man, and boy, that was what back in the mid 1990s.
And here we are in 2013. Great way to kick off the new year with a champion of liberty.
Who, I've got to say, if any one person got concealed carry-in, you can say what you want about it turning a right into a privilege.
The point is, is that it put guns on the street in law abiding citizens' hands and the criminals are keeping their heads down.
Violent crime down over 20% nationwide on average since then.
We've shown the new FBI statistics, except in areas where they've taken the guns, crime is up.
Former representative, talk show host on 590 AM, you name it, best selling author.
Mrs. Hupp, good to have you on with us.
Hey, happy new year to you, Alex.
Wow, I am excited.
What's your take on everything that's happening and the open calls now and the Feinstein bill to physically make you turn guns in?
It's a scary thing, isn't it?
You know, I've talked to a lot of friends of mine who, we all kind of talk big, you know, you hear the from my cold, dead fingers comments.
But the truth of the matter is, if a bunch of jackbooted thugs show up at my door and put a gun to my child's head and says,
turn over all your guns or else, I'm probably going to turn over my guns.
You know, so I think it's really important and I think this is why so often revolutions are mostly about young people and young people without extended families.
You know what I mean?
It's a scary world right now.
It certainly is.
But there's one hundred and sixty plus million gun owners.
If one percent fight back, that's one point five million soldiers.
I agree.
Most people are going to turn them in, at least in the first wave.
But the tyranny that follows is going to result in a civil war.
And if you notice all the branding of Obama as the new Lincoln and how he's going to kick the butt of the states is pretty creepy.
It is.
It's very frightening.
And, you know, when I talk about people turning in their guns, I think there are an awful lot of people that are going out of their way to purchase guns that don't have a track record.
You know, that are that can't be traced to them.
And those guns are going to be hidden and buried all over the place.
And, you know, we might be we might be some of those people.
Alex, you and I are going to be the first doors that they knock on.
You're right.
They're going to try to make examples of people.
Why do you think for listeners to just join us?
We have the club.
Diane Feinstein and others are saying Mr.
And Mrs. America, get ready to turn your guns in.
Why do I think she's doing that?
I think because she's she's absolutely clear that she has the backing of the president and she now has, I would say, 70 percent of the media firmly behind her.
I was I was actually sitting, getting a manicure a few days ago.
And it was a lady kind of across from me, somebody I didn't know at all.
And she got to talk about the guns and the shooting in Connecticut.
And she turned to me and said, well, I just think we should get rid of all the guns.
What do you think?
Of course, that was a mistake, right?
No, I took it very easy on her and I didn't tell her any of my background or anything.
I said, well, you know, I've thought about it.
And it seems to me that not one single one of these mass shootings has ever occurred where guns were allowed.
And she stopped and she kind of blinked and she got up and she went and washed her hands and then came back and sat down and looked at me.
She said, you know, I never thought about that, but you're right.
So I think I think there are an awful lot of people out there that you can't grab with statistics.
You can't grab with with logic.
I think there are a lot of people out there that you have to put them in a position of being, you know, as close as you can,
put them mentally in the position of being completely helpless and then ask them if they would rather have somebody with them,
even if they choose not to have a gun, if they would rather have somebody with them that knows how to use one or not.
You know, even if they won't defend themselves, most people are willing to defend their child.
So I do my best to talk about that sort of thing.
I know it's hard for you to talk about it, but you do to save other lives.
And I've got to commend you again.
As you know, people can pull up the uniform crime statistics since concealed carry became ubiquitous in most states.
Crime rates on average around 24 to 25 percent national.
It's only about 20 because of some of the gun free zones like Chicago and New York.
But the Luby's massacre was a mass murder that took place October 16th, 1991 in Killeen, Texas, United States,
when George Hennard crashed his pickup truck through the front window, got a band pickup trucks on a Luby's cafeteria and shot 50 people,
killing 23, exchanged shots with responding officers and then hid in a bathroom and fatally shot himself.
You were there. You lost your parents.
I know it's tough to talk about, but we've now seen fathers that lost children in the last few shootings come out and say,
don't use this to take people's guns. But the media tries to ignore them.
You as a survivor, I mean, you more than anybody have a right to lay out the record.
Can you, for people that don't know, describe what happened and what would have happened if you would have had a firearm?
Well, to try to keep it brief for you folks, my parents and I, I was about 31 I think at the time, or I just dated myself.
My parents and I had gone to a local cafeteria and we were actually eating with the manager of the cafeteria.
The place was packed. It was Boss's Day. It was the day after payday, middle of the day, beautiful day.
And this guy drove his truck through the window.
It was a floor-to-ceiling window and crashed into a number of tables and came to a jerking halt pretty much in the middle of the restaurant.
And, of course, you think it's an accident.
And we began to rise up to go help people he had knocked over and we heard gunshots.
I was on the passenger side of the vehicle and it was maybe 15 feet away from me.
My father and I immediately got down on the floor and put the table, turned the table up on its side in front of us.
My mom was down behind us.
And the shooting continued.
I realized this was 1991 and these mass shootings weren't occurring back then, so it wasn't the first thing that comes to your mind.
We were waiting for him to say something like, all right, everybody put your wallets up on the table, or something like that.
But that didn't happen. He just kept shooting.
And when he worked his way around the front of the truck and he was working toward us, a full, I'm going to say 45 seconds had passed.
And I realized he was just executing people.
And it took 45 seconds.
Alex, 45 seconds is an eternity.
When I did realize that I reached for my purse that had fallen on the floor next to me, I thought, I've got him.
I've got this guy.
I used to carry a gun in my purse illegally because an assistant VA out of Houston that was a patient of mine convinced me to carry it illegally.
But I did like most people.
You know, you think, eh, what are the odds?
If I need a gun, it's going to be if I break down on a back road somewhere.
It sure as heck is not going to be in a crowded restaurant in the middle of the day.
But my gun was 100 yards away in my car where I had begun dutifully leaving it.
So long story short, at that point, my dad started to break free from my grip and said, I've got to do something.
I've got to do something. He's going to kill everybody in here.
And he made a run at the guy and the guy just turned and shot my father in the chest.
Again, I apologize. I'm trying to make it a short story.
No, it's important. Thank you for sharing it.
We'll be right back with more of this powerful testimony from Susanna Hupp.
I'm Alex Jones.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal-Bend Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now.
Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
You prepare by purchasing gold, food and firearms.
But if you don't have a home security system, then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection.
When you're sleeping or away from home, who's watching out for intruders?
Check out SimpliSafe. It's a new do it yourself home security system that is completely wireless.
Go to getsimplisafe.com.
SimpliSafe is independent and off the grid. It runs on battery power so even if the grid goes down, you're protected.
It's completely customizable so you can use it in your home, business, boat, trailer, storage unit or shed.
Getsimplisafe.com.
SimpliSafe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes.
So there's no need to let a stranger into your home.
If you move or need to relocate, you can take the system with you wherever you go.
You aren't always at home, but SimpliSafe will stand guard, protecting your property 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
Again, that's getsimplisafe.com.
Coast to coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
The Alex Jones Show.
Because there is a war on for your mind.
Again, thanks for tuning in on the Sunday transmission.
We're also here weekdays, 12 noon to 3 p.m. Eastern.
And of course, the website is infowars.com.
Let's go back to this amazing testimony by Luby's Massacre survivor, Susanna Hupp.
The good news with that, my dad was mortally wounded.
I mean, he had covered maybe half the distance, he was seven, eight feet from me.
But he was still alive.
The good thing about that was it made the gunman change directions and he had to go off to my left instead of continuing directly toward me.
Somebody way at the back of the restaurant broke out one of the windows back there and began to escape through that window.
People were able to escape that way.
We were kind of up in the front corner and couldn't get out.
When I saw what I thought was the chance, the gunman had his back turned toward me.
I stood up, I grabbed my mother by the shirt collar and said, come on, come on, we've got to run, we've got to get out of here.
And my feet grew wings.
So, circle it back around, my mom did not follow me out and I didn't know that.
Until after, literally, I was outside of the restaurant.
She was staying with your dad, wasn't she?
The police officers later told me what happened to her.
They said that, and a number of them were patients of mine, and they took me and my family to lunch about a week later and told us.
They said that when they got into the front, they saw a woman on her knees cradling a mortally wounded man.
And they didn't know who the gunman was.
And they saw this 30-something-year-old man walk up to her, they said, he put a gun to her head, she looked up at him, put her head down, and he pulled the trigger.
And they said all they had to do was fire a shot into the ceiling and this guy rabbited to a back bathroom alcove area.
As he said, exchanged a little gunfire with him and then put a bullet in his own head.
My parents had just had their 47th wedding anniversary a couple of weeks prior to this, and it just didn't occur to me while I was running.
Mom, mom wasn't going anywhere without dad.
So I was really angry, Alex. I was really, I was really angry. I felt very guilty.
I was very angry, and I know people think I made this up later, but you can check that the newspapers from the second day, I said I was angry at my legislators,
because they have legislated me out of the right to protect myself and my family.
And you can say, well, Susanna, you could have missed.
Yeah, I could have. Your gun could have jammed.
Well, okay, it's possible. It was a revolver, not likely, but it's possible.
But the one thing you can't argue with is it would have changed the odds.
I can't begin to tell you how frustrating it is to sit there and wait for it to be your turn and having no way, no means of defending yourself.
I can't imagine being in that position again and having my children or my grandchildren with me and having no way of defending them.
Makes me physically ill.
Well, we now have countless cases since you went public back in 91, 92, 93, where people have at churches and everywhere else stopped gunmen.
Just happened down in San Antonio. It's just happened to other places just since the Sandy Hook shooting, and the media will not cover it nationally.
And we see these countless local news videos of gunmen coming in trying to shoot people for no reason at shops and concealed carry folks that know how to use them take them out.
And I see the gun grabbers rushing in to try to ban guns right now because they know the gun culture and the self-defense culture is taking over society.
All the top rated TV shows, women out buying guns, liberal women's magazines show women with guns now.
Not because they want guns, the liberal owners, but because they realize women have woken up.
They're losing. That's why they're launching this offensive against the Second Amendment.
Can you elaborate on that statement? Do you agree or disagree?
I agree with you, but I do think that they see an opportunity here because of the Connecticut shooting.
You know, it's so hard for any of us to imagine that all those little children being just executed like that.
It's just, you want a way-
And they put the guilt onto us.
Have you ever seen such demonization of gun owners where they say we're Klan, we're Nazis.
We helped kill those children when it was a gun-free zone and the media advertising crazies go to schools and kill people.
If anybody has blood on their hands, it's them.
Isn't that the truth? That's something that I've advocated for for years is for teachers to be able to carry.
And of course, here in Texas, individual schools can make that decision.
My school does not allow the teachers to carry, but I can tell you that I know a few that carry anyway.
They just keep their mouth shut and do it, thank God.
You know, the bad guys, I don't know why people don't get this.
Bad guys like that want a high body bag count.
They're going to go where they think they can shoot as many people as possible without anybody shooting back at them.
Nobody knows these cowards like you. No doubt your father saved your life.
Nobody knows these evil people like you, Susanna Hupp, a survivor of the Libby's Massacre, are with us.
And really, you know, the grandmother of the concealed carry movement, no doubt, not to use the term grandmother like she's old,
but she's the person that really started it, thank God, and saved countless lives.
Why do these cowards always commit suicide as soon as the cops show up?
I mean, it just shows they really are ghoulish demons, that they all act exactly the same.
You know, I'm trying to teach my children. I have two boys, 16 and 14.
And I think society, in general, tries to teach people that these bad guys are just misunderstood,
or they've had a hard life, or, you know, all the various sundry excuses that you can come up with for them.
I mean, I've actually literally had people asking me, why didn't you try to talk the guy down?
Like, really? I mean, I can't even argue with that. It's such a stupid statement.
Yeah, just shot your dad in the chest, and then you're going to go talk to him.
Let me go talk to this guy about his childhood.
What I'm trying to teach my children is that, you know, there certainly are criminals.
I would say the vast majority of criminals in the world that were created.
You know, they did have bad childhoods and whatnot.
But there's also evil. I honestly believe there is absolute evil that exists in the world.
That's my next point.
Have you noticed that with Son of Sam, Ramirez, the Night Stalker, Harrison Kleibold, Lanza,
and the guy that just shot the firefighters, they were all admitted devil worshippers.
Shouldn't we be profiling them?
I did not know that, but I'm not even slightly surprised.
Okay, maybe mildly surprised, but not shocked.
How about that?
It's incredible.
Evil exists, and I believe that you must do your best to stand between evil and innocent evil.
And it doesn't mean, again, I want to make this clear because, you know,
I'll tell you what one of my biggest fears is, Alex.
One of my biggest fears is that I'm going to be in some position that I get shot and killed by a bad guy,
and I'm not able to get a round off for some reason.
And I'm so afraid that the other side is going to say, see, her gun didn't help her.
And I've said it a million times, it's not a guarantee.
It changes the odds.
It means you're not a helpless prey animal to be fed upon by devil worshippers and psychopaths.
At least I'm not going to be an easy target.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to do my best to bloody them.
You know, they might take me out, but I'm going to do my best to put them in the hospital at the very least.
Everybody's going to know who the bad guy is.
You know, in the time we have here, because I know you've got to go, Shane,
maybe you can do five more minutes with us after the break to talk about your book,
which I need to carry at the Infowars online bookstore, because I know it's so important.
We all need to reach out to the dumbed-down people that really think turning their guns in is going to protect them.
Looking at Dianne Feinstein, have you seen the testimony in Congress where she admits she has a concealed carry
but doesn't want you to be able to?
I have seen written quotes from it, but I have not actually seen it, no.
It's amazing, though.
How can they all have bodyguards and she can be worth $100 billion, but then we're not supposed to have guns?
I remember being on CNN or one of those shows when Rosie O'Donnell,
there had been some incident with one of her adopted children, a bodyguard protected the child.
You know, and I went on the air and said she must be horribly, horribly, feel awfully silly at the moment,
because she's telling all of us to disarm, and most of us don't have the kind of money
that we can hire personal bodyguards for our kids, and she must be terribly embarrassed.
But I feel that way pretty much about Feinstein and most of them.
It's just an elitist attitude. It's okay for me, but it's not for you, because I don't trust you.
Well, if you notice, I've even got Christian Science Monitor admitting,
I have an article that our government's trying to restrict free speech online and going the way of China.
I've got an article after you leave us we're going to go over where top Georgetown professors saying,
yeah, go ahead and kill old people, death panels.
I mean, they're not just going after the Second Amendment.
Do you see it as a big canary in the coal mine that they are this open and brazen right now?
Here's what I really think, Alex.
I don't think Obama is the problem. I don't think Feinstein is the problem.
I honestly believe that our public education system is the problem,
because those are the people that are growing up to run for office that think socialism and Marxism is a good thing.
They're the ones that grow up and vote for the Obamas and the Feinstein's.
So I truly believe, you know, you and I tend to attack this and a lot of partisans tend to attack this at the top.
You know, we have to get so-and-so out of office or into office.
And I really hope that the problem is down in the school system.
All right, folks, that's all we've got time for with Susanna Hupp.
We're going to go to break and start the second hour with special reports.
Larry Pratt of Gun Owners of America.
And, yes, ladies and gentlemen, we discovered her.
We found her identity, the Obama phone lady.
Obama got us a phone. He's going to do more.
That's right. I had her in studio last week.
That's coming up as well.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at InfoWarsShop.com.
These are items that I did research on that I personally use.
We've got the LifeStraw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor Hand Crank Generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out in the field.
Strategic Relocation Third Edition by Joel Skousen.
When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein.
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Hand Crank Shortwave AM-FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at InfoWarsShop.com.
And your purchase makes our InfoWar possible.
We're getting prepared. Are you? InfoWarsShop.com.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy
and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At eFoods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote,
Almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece.
It is better to be prepared ten years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Coast to coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
Live from Austin, Texas, broadcasting worldwide, it's Alex Jones.
Our reporters went out on the streets of Austin to get people's take on the attempted gun ban.
I'm here to not only talk about voting no on some of the legislation that is loosening up registration and re-registration of gun owners,
but more importantly to ban assault weapons.
An assault weapon is a weapon full automatic.
It's allowed only the military and the police.
It's only for the military and police and for a special trust where you can buy a class-free weapon.
I don't think that taking away a person's right to bear arms is the answer, but I do believe that there should be restrictions.
I have a clean record, so technically I could go to a gun show and purchase as many guns as I want to, have them in my house.
I have a four-year-old daughter. Why should I have an assault rifle?
A gun show, a shooting range, you never see mass shootings there.
There's all kinds of ammo and guns and people walking all around them.
Yeah, I don't support the assault weapon ban.
What I do believe is a good alternative would be like my colleague here mentioned,
is strong restrictions when it comes to evaluating the people's mental health, psychiatrist's exam or something.
Now what about in China where a gentleman I believe is around the same time slash 20 children with a knife,
what do you say to people who may bring that up?
Well, I can tell you that I'm a citizen of America, and in America we're a civilized people,
and as civilized people we need to set our own rules in place to govern our country.
What do you say to people who say, well, maybe the Sandy Hook guy had a gun but this guy had a knife?
A person with a knife is a lot easier to subdue.
What do you think about gun-free zones at schools?
Oh, free massacre zone.
Say the principal had a gun in her office, would she have had time to even pull it out, take off the safety and use it?
And to that extent, so I don't think that's a good argument.
How long do they have to wait until someone got there to stop this guy?
Because no one in this quote-unquote safe school zone or no gun zone was there to defend the children.
Obama's kids, they go to a school with 11 guards.
Now besides assault weapons, are you for any other type of legislation such as banning high-capacity magazines
or certain types of ammunition, anything like that?
Yes, but I think the core of it is to get rid of the weapons.
People say they don't want you to have more than 10 rounds in your magazine.
You know, it's just another incremental step.
I mean, okay, is it 10 rounds a day? Is it five rounds next week?
One of the alternatives I really, really would push for would be raising the price on bullets,
raising the price on bullets, raising the taxes on bullets.
Okay, you realize that a deer rifle or an AR-15 are basically the same thing, just one looks spookier than the other?
Well, it should be a weapon that shoots one bullet at a time.
The federal government recently just spent, you know, just purchased 1.6 billion.
I believe it was in the past calendar year.
Well, if it's the federal government purchasing it, then it's probably going to go to our law enforcement.
I think that's something that our law enforcement people need.
Not too long ago, the Empire State Building, where the police opened fire on one guy
and hit eight or nine other people who were not their intended target.
So what do you say to that?
Well, I mean, we can have no comment on that.
Don't you want to defend yourself against tyranny?
Yes, sir, I do.
Somebody that wants you put down like this, wants to make you a slave,
isn't that the freedom of the Second Amendment?
No, as far as the Second Amendment, it has the right to a well-regulated militia.
Do you think a well-regulated militia could use something like assault weapons?
And the Second Amendment is the right to bear arms.
And it also has for a well-regulated militia, that's also in there as well, miss.
Well, it's our military is our militia, not our common everyday citizens.
Now, sir, there are people out there that say,
why do you need a semiautomatic rifle such as the one allegedly used in the Sandy Hook shooting?
Well, just once again, it's not about my need, it's about my right.
If I can ask you a question talking about the blood of children on our hands,
the Obama administration, and it went back to Bush as well,
had something called Operation Fast and Furious
where they gave fully automatic weapons to Mexican drug cartels.
Now, they said it was a sting operation,
but it was used to kill a Border Patrol agent, policemen, as well as other children.
Do you think anybody should be held accountable for that?
Okay, I'm not going to comment on that.
When seconds count, police are only minutes away.
And I carry a 1911 because the police was too heavy.
Now that we have moved into the winter season,
there is an increased need to support our immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs
by providing a full selection of silver-based products.
Our most popular silver-based products are the 32-ounce nano silver solutions,
our 2-ounce nano silver nasal applicators,
as well as our all-natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents,
which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface.
But rather, we have formulated our silver gel
using the natural skin-nourishing chemistry of aloe vera
to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin
while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.silverlungs.com
and click on our store page
to find what silver-based products are best for you.
That's www.silverlungs.com.
From the front lines of the Information Ward,
it's Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is now the top story
at mfullwars.com and drudgereport.com.
With the video, we played it earlier,
White House threatens executive orders on guns.
I told you that was coming.
Larry Pratt, executive director of Gunners of America, told you that.
There have been a lot of tweets sent out
calling for my death, calling for Larry Pratt's death,
calling for Wayne LaPierre's death at the NRA.
They say we killed the children.
They say it's our fault.
I guess we killed the people that died
or been injured in that big ferry crash.
We've got to ban ferries now.
Bad things happen.
There's 7.5 billion people in the world or close to it.
315 million here.
They wave the bloody shirt of 20 poor dead children
who we pray for and their families
and then tell us we did it.
When they're the ones that made them victim disarmament zones.
And I told you, they're going to use an executive order.
The ATF last year started telling gun shops what to do outside law
and they told them, hey, don't argue.
When he's reelected, we'll do whatever we want.
I talked to multiple gun show people
in Tennessee, in Arizona, in California, and Austin.
We broke that they were being given memos
and they said, well, there's no law.
This law didn't pass.
They said, well, you do what we say or we're going to shut you down.
We found an eye that wasn't dotted, literally.
And now when you go in to do your background,
it's all put in a computer.
When you call the feds, it's all computerized.
You're already registered.
They're now saying they're going to physically take the semi-autos.
Like Dianne Feinstein said,
Mr. and Mrs. America, get ready to turn your guns in.
That's a quote.
And then Piers Morgan says, I don't want your guns.
I just want you to turn all these in.
And then I get angry at him.
And then he says, I'm dangerous and shouldn't have guns
when I have no criminal record.
And then the next night, last night,
and the man we're about to talk to is scheduled to be under tonight,
Larry Pratt.
Piers Morgan doesn't have a big audience,
but when it's a gun debate, it goes in all the other news
and tens of millions, probably a hundred million.
I mean, this is the biggest story in the last two days
is what I did with Piers Morgan.
And that wasn't my full plan.
It was part of it.
If he pulled bull, I was going to get in his face
because all he ever does is bully people.
So I gave him his own medicine back
and put him on notice because I realized what Ron Paul said last hour.
He said, the line in the sand is the guns.
There will be a revolution.
He agreed with me.
If they come to take the guns, it will happen.
Folks, I don't want this to happen.
I'm not planning to physically resist.
I'm a media person.
I'm a general.
Okay.
They're going to use this to purge and persecute gun owners.
And it is going to be an unmitigated nightmare for police and military
who even if you try to carry it out, I mean, it's a death sentence.
And that's the globalist plan.
They've been preparing for this and police are like, you're right.
If this happens, it's going to be horrible, but they wouldn't dare.
Yes, they will.
And they're getting it ready for another executive order
where the next mass shooting, you know, will happen with all their hyping.
And now we have them saying, Larry, I called you this morning to get you on
when you were driving into work.
Have you had a chance to see the CNN clip now
where the host and his two guests talk about shooting me
and agree it's okay as long as they wear a uniform?
Alec, I haven't had a chance to even look at a clock.
I've been so nonstop.
But I'll tell you what, you were just discussing this executive order.
That is something that I believe I might have even talked about on your show
because you've been nice enough to have me on so many times.
But sometime well into last year, it occurred to me,
these guys don't have the votes in Congress.
And after the election, it was clear they didn't have the votes in Congress
for the next Congress either.
But Obama has shown by what he's done in other areas, such as immigration,
he'll just bloody well do what he wants
and issue an executive order against the law, against the Constitution.
Hey, when you're socializing the country,
what's a few broken laws here and there?
They were only put on the books by a bunch of dead people
that aren't here anymore.
It's our country now, and I want it because I got elected.
And so I think he believes he might have been elected king,
although even the British king has far less power than what he's presuming.
But I saw what they would do.
If you assume the guy is lawless, then you don't have to be a prophet,
and I'm not a prophet, but I could see that that would be, for him,
the course of least resistance.
That's where his water would flow, if you will.
And he's doing it.
Well, I had Ron Paul on, and you just heard me basically paraphrase what he said.
He agreed that they want a civil war.
They know what they're doing.
If they think they're going to get 160 million gun owners to turn their guns in,
there will be a percentage that's not going to go along with it.
Well, it's very, very, very critical that if anything bad comes down,
that it be very clear that it was the government initiating violence.
Remember Lexington and Concord.
That day's battle was started by the British
because I think his name was Preston or Prescott.
The captain on Lexington Green said,
Hold your fire until fired upon.
And if I recall correctly, there were a couple of guys that died almost immediately
following that order because the British did fire first.
Yeah, quite a few of them, but that gave them the moral high ground.
And I think it's absolutely essential that we hold our fire,
that we even be willing to perhaps be the first one down
because we are in a war of ideas, a monster culture clash,
and it's absolutely essential that we be perceived as the law-abiding ones,
as the lawful ones.
We need to make it understandable that there are two kinds of rebels.
There's the rebel who goes out in the mountains on his own
and is out there kind of like Robin Hood shooting people.
And then there's the rebel that comes with a badge.
If either one of them are acting outside the law, that makes them a rebel.
And I know the statists of our time can't get it through their head
that they could be the rebels.
But the Constitution was put up to strictly limit what the federal government can do.
Well, that's profound what you said.
When Lenin took over and then Stalin, they were rebels,
and they even call us counterrevolutionaries.
That's what Bill Ayers and Obama in his training, they know they're the rebels.
That's why they operate like this and are buying 1.6 billion bullets
and armored vehicles and demonizing real Americans,
because they are an occupying rebel enemy force against the Republic.
And you're absolutely right.
So we need to remember the Battle of Lexington.
It ultimately went very poorly for the British that day
because our guys insisted that the moral high ground be theirs.
And that may take a lot more courage than would be needed to go
and hide behind a rock and shoot, which they did later in the day.
But to stand there at first naked against the British ball
that was coming down at them out of those muskets, that was real courage.
But they knew why they were there.
In fact, their preacher had preached on that the Sunday before,
and he was there with them because he believed as much as they did
what he'd been preaching about.
I believe he died.
I don't remember that, but that's entirely possible
because it was not a fun day for either side.
The British ultimately lost about a quarter to a third
of their entire regiment that they sent out, some 800 guys.
Not that many made it back.
And more importantly, we were able to get to London
ahead of the British couriers and point out what had happened
and who had fired first, and that it was this oppressive government
that we'd been hollering about for four and six years in formal petitions,
petitions of right, bills of right, all those kinds of things
were going over to the British mainland, being published in their newspapers,
and then it finally came to that.
And so I think we have to remember that history,
the history that's not being taught in our government schools,
but our forefathers did it right, and God willing, we'll do it right.
Yes, sir.
We'll do it right.
We'll be right back with the conclusion of our important interview
with the head of gun owners of America, Larry Pratt.
The New Year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology
that is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day
to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care
and is highly effective for water purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support,
and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today
and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water
and laughing as you get sick and die?
Start purifying your water with ProPure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research,
and the best gravity filter out there bar none is ProPure,
and it's available discounted at Infowars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified.
Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%.
Easy to set up and use.
Doesn't require electricity.
Filter from lakes, streams, ponds, and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water
and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
ProPure is the best gravity-fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on ProPure,
but if you add the promo code WATER at checkout,
you get an additional 10% off at Infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter
from colds, flu, and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver,
a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution.
Recent advances in silver technology
have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily
to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold, and food poisoning,
and help improve wound healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day,
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases,
such as stress, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus, and other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies
of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness
of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today
and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package
and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now.
Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars
and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at FiveStarSoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Coast to Coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
I can't believe we're to the point that we're having to talk about 1775, 1776.
I mean, this is not a joke.
I had you on a few weeks ago and I said,
from all I've seen, this will be the greatest assault ever.
And you said it's shaping up to be that.
Undoubtedly now, Larry Pratt, of gunowners.org,
this is clearly the greatest assault ever.
Certainly in my lifetime.
For a while I've been comparing it to Columbine,
but I'm beginning to think that they are much bolder than they were even back in Columbine.
And one of the guys here made a suggestion which I still think could well be the case
and that is they've overreached what Dianne Feinstein has proposed in her legislation
is so far beyond what she, excuse me, got enacted in 94.
That they're essentially, with a few exceptions, coming for it all.
Her much-vaunted statement after she'd enacted her quote-unquote limited gun ban of 1994
was, well, I just didn't have the votes, otherwise I'd have said, Mr. and Mrs. America, turn them all in.
Well, we know what her objectives are, so we shouldn't be fooled.
She's told us.
And she's now indicating that she wants more.
Now, I think she's getting greedy and I think we can use that against her.
Without money, guarantee you, Alex, none of these jaspers here inside the Beltway are volunteers.
They're extremely well paid.
I'm sure that 99% of your listeners would love to have what this 1% that works here in the government class is being paid.
So, this is definitely something that can be solved partially by money.
If we can get around the Speaker of the House who is like a downed tank blocking a bridge
and if somehow we can build another bridge or get him off the bridge in some way,
then I think we could actually enact a spending measure that had a proviso in it.
None of these funds may be used for the implementation of executive order, whatever it might be.
Well, sure, go ahead.
They're out of gas at that point.
You have always, again, been a very measured, calm person, and I'm like that in private.
When I get wound up, I get very, very upset and did that with Piers Morgan because he's always been a bully.
I was not going to let him bully me, so I just basically dominated him.
But I want to play you a clip here because this is what was said last night amongst other things.
They said they hope my children don't end up dead, and then there was this.
So, I'm going to play it for you now.
Piers Morgan and guests discuss shooting.
Alex Jones, Daily Beast writer Buzz Bissinger says Piers Morgan should pop Alex Jones with a semi-automatic weapon.
Then Huntsman's daughter, Abby Huntsman of the Huffington Post, says I'd love to see that laughter in a uniform.
Piers Morgan, I'd borrow my brother's uniform, who reportedly is an Army officer.
So, I guess if it's a uniform, it's okay.
I want to play this clip and get your take on it.
Here it is.
But what do you need a semi-automatic weapon for?
The only reason I think you need it is, Piers, challenge Alex Jones to a boxing match.
Show up with a semi-automatic that you got legally and pop him.
I'd love to see that.
In uniform.
I'll borrow my brother's uniform.
That's enough.
And then there was talk of, I hope my children don't get killed.
I mean, this is entering a whole other level of Creekville.
What they did there is reveal the heart of the leftist.
The leftist is about force.
They're about imposing their righteousness on us slubs that don't know what's good for
us.
And it's such a delightful topic to talk about offing some loudmouth like Alex Jones.
That'll teach those pumpkins a thing or two, won't it?
I guess it will.
My children were there watching when their deaths were being discussed.
I mean, they're clearly trying to terrorize the entire American people with these shootings.
While they're horrible, statistically it's one of the rarest forms of death.
Right.
Along with our general murder rate, which is declining.
And I was just looking at something happily.
My son Eric pulled something up that's quite good.
There's an under-reporting of murder data in England, which is always held up as the
country that's so wonderful compared to ours.
British crime, I'm quoting from the finding.
Reporting tactics keep murder rates artificially low.
And then this is a quote from a report from the Inspectorate of Constabulary.
Suppose that three men kill a woman during an argument outside a bar.
They are arrested for murder, but because of problems with identification, quote, the
main witness is dead.
Charges are eventually dropped.
In American crime statistics, the event counts as a three person homicide.
But in British statistics, it counts as nothing at all.
And then the report is quoted directly here.
With such differences, this is British, 2000.
With such differences in reporting criteria, comparisons of US homicide rates with British
homicide rates is a sham.
That's the British cop group, the Inspectorate of Constabulary.
Well, can I have that headline?
Because I've got the Telegraph and others admitting that they're the crime capital of
Europe.
Portland has the lowest crime rate in the world because, of course, they have more guns.
But you can just type in Britain or England, the crime capital of Europe.
People are beat, stabbed, you name it.
But yeah, I read all the time where if you fist fight someone raping your wife at busting
your house, they throw the book at you.
You know, the farmer who'd been robbed three times defending himself and they threw him
in prison.
I mean-
They probably give some condoms to the guy that was raping your wife and tell him to
clean up his act.
Amazing.
I know.
I mean, but see, that's on purpose.
They want-
That's a criminal government trying to team up with the criminals.
Why do they love crime-ridden cities run by mafias?
Well, because we're then terrorized and we must depend all the more for our, quote, protection
on the very authorities that have put us into that predicament to begin with.
And I don't know whether they're accepting it in England, although it is, as the Telegraph
said two days after that Piers Morgan interview, it is the fourth most violent country in the
world.
Violent crime, which would include murder, but also rape and everything else that's-
And that's with watered down numbers, because I've seen those numbers before that they just
let murder- I mean, they don't even investigate when they come to your house and you and your
wife are chopped up.
I mean, it's just like you could have the neighbor running around with a hand in their
hand of a chopped off person.
They just say, oh, no big deal.
Right.
They do not believe in self-defense.
That farmer who was infamous up in the little town of Norfolk in England had, after like
the third home invasion by the same Gypsy gang members that had been terrorizing the
whole area, he shot one of them in the dark of night who was coming up the stairs, actually
shot both of them and killed one of them.
And for that, they gave him a life sentence, which now he's out of jail because happily
British public opinion finally focused on that outrage.
And see, that's what scares me is that I'm still a young man, 38, but I've got aches
and pains and things and problems now from a life of action.
I can't imagine once I get old and all I can depend on is the gun.
I mean, if two guys are coming up my stairs, I'm going to get so angry, even if they're
pretty tough, I can probably deal with them.
But not when I'm 65, 70, I need that firearm.
And more and more now, I mean, as I get older, more and more, I try to avoid physical stuff.
It's just natural.
We need to equalize things for the infirm, the old, the women, handicap.
I mean, the real liberal thing to do is to arm women.
Exactly.
And to make it so that unarmed children can be protected by their teachers, the janitors,
whatever, in schools rather than insist for now 20 years that if we just say no guns at
schools, everything will be fine.
Well, everything is not fine.
That's where most of our, in fact, that's where all of our mass murders have occurred
in whatever kind of gun-
I hope you can get that out tonight with Piers Morgan.
Five more minutes with our guest on the other side, gunowners.org.
It's Larry Pratt.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support, and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
We'll be right back.