big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
all right welcome to the Alex Jones show it is Monday January 21st 2013
inauguration day of our well the second coming of our Lord and Savior according
to the mainstream media yes all hail Obama all praise Obama and you made you
may know something about history and by the way I'll give you a rundown of the
guests we have coming up today is a hard-hitting show we've got a lot of
breaking news a lot of hard-hitting guests as well but just this
inauguration thing if you probably notice it throughout history the less
legitimate a government is the more pompous and over-the-top the ceremonies
are for its illegitimate leader and that's what we saw here today just a few
minutes ago with the Obama inauguration a band playing all these people I'm
surprised I didn't have stiff-legged soldiers marching around with the Heil
Hitler type of sign going out there you know I'm surprised they didn't have 57
Air Force jets and nuclear missiles on on vehicles rolling down the road and I
mean anything you know people holding up the Emperor's fake invisible clothes I
mean I'm surprised they didn't just go all out because it's so ridiculous that
the complete illegitimacy of this government now and this Obama
administration think about it if Ron Paul had been elected president do you
think Ron Paul would have wanted all this this just pompous celebration of
him no Ron Paul would say we don't need a party we don't need it just just
all this show what we need is to have a quiet dignified confirmation that the
Bill of Rights is alive in America today all we need is to not have a man in
charge but principles of liberty in charge and there we go for those
watching on prison planet TV a picture of the inauguration oh my gosh the
draping of the flags this looks like something pulled right out of Nazi
Germany I mean it is all put that back up on the screen guys and show me some
more photos because I was actually driving in during some of this I didn't
see it all this looks like a Hitler inauguration it it looks exactly like it
you just change the flags to a different you know German Nazi Germany flag and
that's it and the the postures of the people are the same the pompousness the
arrogance is the same this is sick it is sick where this country is going folks
and just to remind us Obama has been tweeting out now this morning saying I'm
honored and grateful that we have a chance to finish what we started our
work begins today he says that's a quote from Obama that he tweeted out our work
begins today oh what what work let's uh let's talk about that the work of
dismantling the US economy the work of destroying our jobs the work of
essentially revoking the Bill of Rights the First Amendment the Second Amendment
the Fourth Amendment the Fifth Amendment and of course completely ignoring the
Tenth Amendment the work of turning our airports into Nazi police state security
zones with naked body scanners yeah I know they say they pulled those but
they're they're replacing them with all millimeter wave machines so the
announcement that the TSA is pulling those scanners is a bit of a hoax
they're just replacing them with other machines so what is Obama's work really
in this country what has he done in the last four years that he's going to
continue look at it take an honest look at what he has done without even
thinking about political affiliation unemployment is up we've got 128 million
Americans now living on the government dependent on the government and for some
reason those people are still even allowed to vote why should people who
are living on the government be allowed to vote to control the revenues of the
taxpayers who are actually contributing to society why should the takers be able
to control the outcomes of elections in a free nation it doesn't even make any
sense anyway all that much more straight ahead plus some hard-hitting guests like
I said and all the breaking news from today right here on the Alex Jones show
stay ahead we'll be right back Alex Jones here with a message to fellow
freedom lovers the prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs
from bad to worse the globalist model is to shut down societies and starve
Patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover that's why we've
assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at info wars shop
calm these are items that I did research on that I personally use you've got the
life straw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go the K
tour hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages are
out in the field strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen when
disaster strikes by Matthew Stein thorough safe used by Homeland Security
to protect yourself during any radiological event and crank shortwave
am-fm radios everything that we've researched and found to be the best is
available at info war shop calm and your purchase makes our info war possible
we're getting prepared are you info wars shop calm millions of people are going
to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them
protect yourself with supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum
antibacterial solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a
silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and
food poisoning and help improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe
enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of
many serious diseases such as stress staff pneumonia coals flus and other
harmful pathogens this new technology has the ability to terminate entire
colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of
colloidal or ionic silver solutions the Science Digest Journal says silver is
our mightiest germ fighter it is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a
wonder of modern medicine go to supernatural silver calm today and use
the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off that's supernatural silver calm and like
us on Facebook sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison
to your water and laughing as you get sick and die start purifying your water
with pro pure my friends I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter
out there bar none is pro pure and it's available discounted at info wars calm
its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth there's no
priming required it's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce
fluoride up to 95% easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity purify
water from lakes streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial
minerals which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that
leaches from the plastic probe here is the best gravity fed filter out there
it's what my family uses info wars calm already has the lowest price on pro
pier but if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10%
off and in full wars calm you can also call to order 8 8 8 2 5 3 3 1 3 9
we are on the march
on the run Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network
all right it is the Alex Jones show on Monday January 21st 2013 Inauguration
Day and also Martin Luther King Day we've got comments on the inauguration
as well as Martin Luther King and his desire to carry concealed and his
support for the right of self-defense and I think by the way oh by the way
this is Mike Adams filling in for Alex Alex will be back tomorrow I'm just the
fill-in host here and thanks for continuing to have me on everybody I
appreciate your support I'm just here fighting for liberty that's it that's
why I'm here so we've got a bunch of news coming up on gun control on the
economy on issues like this one and the MIT I'm sorry a Harvard Medical School
professor is seeking a quote adventurous woman to give birth to a Neanderthal man
that they're going to implant in her body by reconstructing the DNA of
Neanderthals how much more evidence do you need yet that we're violating the
will of the Creator hmm it's not just GMOs with plants and corn I mean now
they're gonna they're gonna actually try to have a woman give birth to a
Neanderthal and then what what are they gonna do then what are you gonna what
are you gonna do with the Neanderthal you're gonna make it president I mean
what do you do with a live Neanderthal it's it's insane this is this is this is
a violation of nature and it's going on from every angle but let me give you a
quick rundown before I get too far into this coming up at the bottom of this
hour we have as a guest author max velocity yes max velocity that is his
call sign he's the author of this book contact a tactical manual for post
collapse survival and the reason I'm having max velocity on is because he
served in the British Army as well as the United States Army and he is now a
US citizen but he's one of those rare individuals who has perspective from
both the UK and the US as well as being well-informed on survival and the
Patriot movement in the United States so that should be a fascinating interview
don't miss that from max velocity in the next hour we've got Sheriff Denny
Paimon he was on last week with Alex Jones he is that sheriff I believe he's
from Kentucky if memory serves me correctly he's the sheriff that posted
that famous now famous YouTube video where he was almost brought to tears
talking about the founding fathers and the sacrifice that they made in order to
bring us the liberty and the freedom that we are desperately trying to
protect today and then in the third hour we're going to be joined by John
Rapoport for a few minutes with some additional comments and updates on the
psychiatric police state that has now been implemented in the United States
but getting back to what is actually happening today and real quickly Lance
Armstrong books are being moved to the fiction section of a library in
Australia they've now decided that Lance's entire history is complete
fiction yeah so they're moving them to the fiction section which seems
appropriate but the real reason that I bring that up is because Barack Obama is
the Lance Armstrong of politics think about that for a second why is Barack
Obama the Lance Armstrong of politics well Barack Obama is a highly charismatic
person he's a good-looking person like Lance Armstrong I know some of you might
argue with me but I'm saying across the board a lot of people look at Obama at
the way he speaks at the way he carries himself he has charisma so does Lance
Armstrong they both got charisma but what else do they have in common they're
both lying to you that's all they know how to do is lie and deceive in order to
climb their way to the top of positions of power and influence they use the
media to manipulate the public and they are indignant against their accusers and
whistleblowers and they they say things like how dare they even suggest that that
I was doping or that that or in Obama's case how dare anyone suggest that he was
going to sign the NDAA the NDAA the National Defense Authorization Act which
of course he helped write or his attorneys did his administration did and
then he signed we have been infested infected with a culture of charismatic
liars psychopaths sociopaths who all they know how to do is lie in order to
get to the top they do not honor ethics they do not honor spirituality they
typically don't believe in a creator they don't believe in the human soul
they don't believe in an afterlife they don't believe in in judgment that any of
us are ever going to be judged for actions all they know how to do is live
as charismatic parasites living off the goodwill of people who are easily
manipulated into supporting them that is Lance Armstrong in my opinion and that
is Barack Obama in my opinion and I think I the one reason Obama is so
dangerous is because he's so charismatic is far more charismatic than Bush ever
was and she can't look at Bush and and say charisma no the the last person who
had this kind of widespread charisma was probably Bill Clinton and also another
highly accomplished liar these people are all liars and but they're
believable liars they know how to lie with such apparent credibility that they
sucker people into it even we had the the obama phone lady here sitting right
there in this in this office what was the last week with Alex or the week
before and she was not aware that Obama lied about raising your taxes she was
not aware that Obama lied about not taking away your guns but once she
became informed about that her position changed very quickly once she became
aware of the truth she actually began to start questioning some of her own
support for Obama so that's just one example of what happens when people
actually collide with the truth you know the truth that Alex Jones says to them
and by the way I think I'm going to try to approach this topic with with all
seriousness I think it is time and this is my opinion this is not Alex Jones
opinion this is not info wars opinion but I think it is time that we began to
make a list of all those who are enemies of the Bill of Rights who are enemies of
America anyone who has publicly advocated the stripping away of your
Second Amendment rights or your First Amendment rights or who calls for the
end the abolishment of the Constitution or who calls for destroying the Bill of
Rights or forfeiting all of the rights that are granted to you under the Bill
of Rights I'm talking about people on the news I'm talking about news anchors
I'm talking about writers it's time we made a list now you might say what's the
purpose of this list the purpose in my opinion should be eventually as the
Patriots restore the Republic in America because I believe that's what's coming
we must arrest these people on the list and strip them of their citizenship and
here's why if they do not believe in the Bill of Rights and they would want to
strip you of your Second Amendment rights then what right do they have to
even call themselves Americans if they do not believe in your rights they
forfeit their own so anyone who is out there speaking out against the
Constitution speaking out against the Bill of Rights is technically an enemy
of America if they do not believe in the founding fathers they do not believe in
the very principles the philosophies the ideas that great that gave us the great
abundance the innovation the freedom and the liberty to become the greatest
nation on our planet if they do not believe in those things they are not
Americans they are not Americans and they are trying to destroy America by
turning it into a nation where none of us have those rights anymore where we
don't even have the separation of powers anymore where the executive orders from
one president whether it's Obama or some future president can override Congress
and override representation and override public debate on issues that really
matter to our day-to-day lives I say because I'm an advocate of non-violence
I say we make a list now and we put these people on this list with the
intention of having them arrested and stripped of their citizenship take their
passports take their IDs put them on a list do not ever enter this land of the
free again you are barred for life from the Republic of America have two ships
waiting one on East Coast the ship on the East Coast sails to Havana you can
get on that ship or the ship on the West Coast sails to North Korea you can get
on that ship it's your choice because it's it's the land of the free so you're
free to choose which ship you want to leave on and then we kick these people
out of America we send a message that says if you're going to be an American
if you're going to be on the media in America if you are going to have any
position of power in America if you're going to be a member of Congress and
vote on bills a member of the Senate then you must support the philosophies
of freedom and liberty and justice upon which this great republic was originally
founded and I want to put that idea out there with all necessary and justified
force I don't mean violent force I mean dedication is what I mean because again
this is this is the nonviolent way to do this there are some people out there
that are maybe more radical that would say they should shoot those people I say
no no we must operate with dignity we must operate with honor we must adhere
to the principles because of being philosophically correct and of non
violence because we are in the right we are in the right we have history on our
side we have God on our side we have the Bill of Rights on our side and anyone
who is an enemy of those of those fundamental philosophies rest assured
they are an enemy of this nation and they must be they must be shown the door
get out of America you traitors get out of America now today is Martin Luther
King Day and I believe that Martin Luther King would agree with much of
what I'm saying here maybe not all of it but I know that Martin Luther King was a
man who espoused nonviolent solutions that he believed in the Second Amendment
the right to self-defense he applied for a concealed carry he knew that his life
was being threatened and he was correct that there are dangerous people that
were trying to silence him so he wanted a firearm to carry for his own
self-protection and he was right to seek that out if Martin Luther King were
alive today I believe he would condemn the actions of Barack Obama he would say
Obama you are wrong to take these rights and freedoms away from the American
people including all the African Americans out there who have the right
to self-defense to defend themselves against tyranny or threats of violence
or anything that might threaten their own safety or the safety of their
families or communities that's what Martin Luther King would say today I
believe stay with us we'll be right back on the Alex Jones show looking back on
2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters like
Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships
brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost
everything at e foods direct we hear from customers every day that are
fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand after
Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all of the grocery stores
are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my
sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too early than one
day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what
Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or
go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best
tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet
your life on e foods direct is this the year you finally get serious about your
family's drinking water if so keep listening for a special offer from Big
Berkey water filters did you know that over 60% of municipal water is
fluoridated Berkey water filters distinguish themselves from many other
filtration systems with a capability to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine
fluoride arsenic and disinfection byproducts from municipal water via the
black Berkey and PF line of filters then there's affordability it only 1.7 cents
per gallon Berkey water filters purified treated and untreated water even stagnant
pond water stop and think how much money you could save by simply reducing buying
bottled water and using water filtered by your Berkey water filter no need to
be constantly replacing expensive filters with a Berkey a single set of
filters can last for five to ten years choose the best size Berkey for your
needs at Big Berkey water filters calm and right now all GCM listeners get 5%
off all ceramic filter systems just call one eight seven seven ninety nine
Berkey that's eight seven seven ninety nine BER ke y or visit Big Berkey water
filters calm free shipping on every order over $50 Big Berkey water filters
for the love of clean water stop the pain from broken chipped and damaged
nails and eliminate toenail fungus with a revolutionary new nail hardener nails
of steel just apply one drop of nails of steel over natural or polished nails and
go with nails of steel there's virtually no drying time and it's guaranteed try
this all-natural antifungal and herbal formula for women and men call eight one
six eight nine six eight three zero seven or get free shipping at nails of
steel calm nails of steel calm it's like a salon in a bottle we the people grow
cotton we fabric engraving embed strips and fibers to protect from counterfeit
then carting to a private bank having it led back at interest forcing taxes to
service debt this capitalism or was Jefferson correct when stating a central
bank issuing the public currency is a greater menace to the liberties of the
people than a standing army hi Ted Anderson I'm placing a silver dollar in
a book explains our monetary system call for your copy eight hundred six eight
six two two three seven it's time to understand the system call eight hundred
six eight six two two three seven that's eight hundred six eight six two two
three seven big business has discovered the preparedness market and
that makes it difficult to know where to go and who to trust my patriot supply
comm is owned and operated by Patriots just like you has the best prices on
storable food non-gmo seeds water filtration devices home canning
equipment survival and self-reliance books and more my patriot supply comm
has old-fashioned values and the absolute best customer service in the
industry look for the deal of the day unique affordable survival supplies that
fit anyone's budget get same-day shipping on all orders and free shipping
on orders over forty nine dollars call eight six six two two nine zero nine
two seven eight six six two two nine zero nine two seven or visit my
patriotsupply.com for emergency preparedness self-reliance and food
independence shop with a name you know and a name you can trust before it's
time to survive it's time to prepare my patriotsupply.com from his Central
Texas command center deep behind enemy lines the information war continues it's
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
welcome back this is Mike Adams the health Ranger filling in for Alex Jones
today I'm the editor of naturalnews.com a frequent contributor to infowars.com
and check out infowars.com right now and every day during the broadcast here
as more news is being posted it seems like every hour there's a Kurt Nemo and
Don Salazar are working very hard as well as other writers Paul Joseph Watson and
other contributors to get to bring you the news that really matters now just to
clarify during the last segment yes I did advocate creating a list of all of
those people in America who are calling for the abolition of the Constitution or
the Bill of Rights and then having those people arrested and stripped of their
citizenship and deported from the country yes that's it that is exactly
what I'm going for let there be no mistake and it makes perfect sense
because they are traitors from within in fact think about it Obama today in the
inauguration he swore an oath to defend the Constitution I mean how could that
not be comedy hour Obama swearing an oath to defend the Constitution but the
entire crowd should have broken out in bouts of mad laughter when when he swore
that because he is the one destroying the Constitution but that that oath
means you must swear to defend the Constitution against enemies foreign and
domestic why is that even in the Constitution because the founding
fathers knew that there would be many enemies of America from within the most
insidious kind enemies from within enemies of the Constitution enemies of
the Bill of Rights enemies of the founding principles upon which this
great nation was originally created which which gave rise to the abundance
and the innovation and the freedom that made this the greatest nation in the
world so why should we tolerate these enemies from within to run around our
country and continue to try to destroy it why should we tolerate that we should
arrest them we should kick them out again I'm an advocate of non-violence so
I don't I don't think we should commit any violence to that I'm not saying we
should throw them in secret prisons like Obama does I'm not saying we should put
them on a kill list like Obama does I'm not saying that we should do what Obama
does and launch unmanned drone missiles to kill innocent children that's what he
does I'm not saying that at all I mean Obama is the king of violence he talks
about protecting children from violence he's the one killing children with
violence I mean it's it's such hypocrisy but why should we let these people run
around and try to destroy our country from within we shouldn't we should make
a list have them arrested give them a fair trial show the evidence of what
they said on television what they said on CNN those people that said Alice
Jones should be popped and shot with an ar-15 they should be arrested stripped
of their citizenship and shown the exit shown the door you're out of the country
buddy don't come back go to North Korea that probably have a place for you there
I'm sure you could clean toilets in the gulag for Kim Jong-un yeah they might
love that they might love that job that's what we should do with them now
I've got a video all across the country over this weekend there were gun rights
protests our Second Amendment advocation protests at state capitals everywhere
and I've got a video here from this this is a short speech by Roger Saucier the
one of the co-founders of the Connecticut Minutemen group and here's
what he had to say on the on the Capitol steps of the state of Connecticut over
the weekend fellow patriots I am here to support our second amendment right to
bear arms which is provided to us by our Constitution but not just these rights
only but for all the god-given rights that our government has no business
interfering with who the hell are they to tell us that we can't have solved or
20-hour soda or an ar-15 I only have one comment I will not comply
yes I will not comply those are the words of Roger Saucier the founder or
co-founder of the Connecticut Minutemen group and his words were reflected all
across the country in dozens of other protests at state capitals by people who
are fed up and who have had enough of the tyranny who've had enough of enemies
of America operating from within trying to destroy the Constitution and the Bill
of Rights they're trying to bring us to a civil war okay that's what they're
doing they're trying to turn America into a war zone so that they can then
launch their drones on Americans and they can then activate their kill lists
on Americans American patriots returning veterans they're trying to take over
because they're losing they're so desperate they're so desperate that look
everything out there is a hoax the the media CNN will have 13 anti-gun guests
on with only two defenders of the Second Amendment the polls that they show that
the mainstream media shows are completely fabricated they'll delete the
poll if the gun rights are winning or they'll change the numbers to make it
look like people want guns banned the inauguration total theater everything is
a hoax out there to try to make you think that the public supports taking
away your Bill of Rights but it's not the case freedom is winning liberty is
popular infowars.com is leading the way so stay tuned right here on infowars
at Alex Jones show we'll be right back after this break with much more we're on
the march the Empire's on the run Alex Jones and the GCN radio network if you
want an American company with American products made by Americans here is the
Cal Ben soap company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for
years these all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and
coconut oils that are earth-friendly and safe see them on the web at 5 star soap
calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog buy the one to two months sample
package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now or save
big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs this
is an amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and you will love
the way real soap makes you feel see them on the web at five star soap calm
or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog
tyranny is here the grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality it really
says that the state is God the United States is now recognized globally as one
of the most impressive police states on earth this film conclusively proves the
existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being expanded nationwide this
documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an
old powerful shadow state police state for chronicles the sickening depth which
our Republic has fallen prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency
dictatorship body scammers sound cameras citizen spies stage terror and cameras
on every street corner it's only the beginning of the New World Order's hellish
plan the police state isn't coming it's here secure your copy today at info wars
calm or see it online in the highest quality at prison planet TV now that we
have moved into the winter season there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health at silver lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by
providing a full selection of silver based products our most popular silver
based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our 2 ounce nano silver
nasal applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps just released
is our 100% natural silver gel our new silver gel is not based on synthetic
gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface but
rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while
delivering the silver more effectively visit www.silverlungs.com and click on
our store page to find what silver based products are best for you
that's www.silverlungs.com from the front lines of the information war it's
Alex Jones
all right we're back on the Alex Jones show welcome back on this Monday this
inauguration day January 21st 2013 this is Mike Adams the editor of natural news
dot-com filling in for Alex today it's also Martin Luther King Day and we had a
few comments about Martin Luther King and his advocation of gun rights for
private citizens you know it's funny we got banned by Facebook a few weeks ago
for posting a graphic where Gandhi was speaking out in support of self-defense
because you know all human beings have a sacred divine right to defend themselves
against aggressors and Gandhi understood that and we put that on a graphic and we
put that out on Facebook and Facebook suspended our account yep and in fact
Drudge linked to that story and it became quite quite a quite a bit of a
story across the internet well Martin Luther King was also an advocate of gun
rights so you've got these two people who history shows or at least mainstream
history says these are the champions of non-violence of pacifism that they say
you're supposed to just lay down and be obedient that is not what they said at
all Gandhi only resorted to non-violence because his countrymen were disarmed if
Gandhi had an ar-15 and his countrymen had an ar-15 they would have kicked the
British out of that colony a long time many years earlier Gandhi had to resort
to non-violence because that was the only thing left and even in his own
writings the doctrine of the sword in particular the doctrine of the sword you
can search that online he spoke of using self-defense to protect yourself or your
brother or your family from aggressors who were intent on violence so don't be
fooled into thinking that Gandhi or Martin Luther King only espouse
non-violence no they knew that we have a sacred divine right to self-defense and
they both understood the role that firearms play in protecting innocence
from aggressors and that's why Martin Luther King's own house was described as
an arsenal of weapons he had all kinds of guns in there because people were
trying to kill him as actually happened he was right to be armed as are you
because you never know what kind of bad person out there might be trying to take
you out or take what you own or just commit random acts of violence that's
why we need responsible upstanding citizens to be armed when they're showing
that graphic there with Gandhi that we did post if you're watching a prison
plant TV in any case changing the subject now we are joined by our first
guest today his name is max velocity or his his call sign I should say and he's
the author of this book contact a tactical manual for post-collapse
survival now max velocity was born in the UK and he served in the British
Army first before serving in the United States military and he has a very unique
perspective therefore I'm serving in the militaries of both nations and a unique
perspective on a nation that has strict gun control versus America which has gun
rights and gun freedoms so you can find his books on amazon.com and everywhere
else and we'll give out its website soon but max velocity joins us now welcome to
the show max hi thanks very much for having me on it's a my pleasure to have
you have you on you've just released a new book called Patriot Dawn that lays
out a rather frightening scenario of what could happen in America can you
give us a just a brief synopsis of what that book is all about and what you're
trying to explore narratively through that work of fiction yes yeah sure
really that book is a result of my personal journey as I came through the
whole prepping thing to writing my own books and my own manuals trying to give
people the tools to to be able to defend themselves initially you know when I was
writing contact it was more of a collapse kind of situation and as I
learned more it kind of also gave gives you the tools for you know perhaps a
civil war resistance against the tyrannical government all the tools are
in there and then I the reason I wrote Patriot Dawn was because it really came
to my attention that the fiction is a good way of getting things across to
people some people might not want to buy a manual it might have you know too
technical that kind of thing tactics but so what I've tried to do with with
Patriot Dawn is to prevent is to is to write about what I think is a very
realistic scenario not that I expect it to happen exactly the same way that I go
through in the prologue to Patriots Patriot Dawn it's just setting a scenario
there's something I think you know may well be coming soon and by telling a
story try and sort of probably tell it an interesting story but also to educate
people in a little bit of tactics a little bit about what they might face
what things they might be against and just to try and use that medium to get
the point across well on the on the philosophical side let me ask you this
you were born and raised in the UK you became an American citizen many years
later what are your beliefs and philosophies on the Second Amendment the
Bill of Rights the right to self-defense versus living in a disarmed society I'm
I mean it's not a canned question I'm actually curious about what kind of
contrast you see what are your thoughts on all that yeah well I mean I am a
despite the accent I am a US citizen I consider myself a patriot I have sworn
the oath on joining the US military and when I became a citizen I take it very
seriously I joke a little bit I'm now here living in the United States I have
an American wife and children and I I should almost be suing for breach of
contract because I came to America before I came on so many years with and
before and you know US military forces that kind of thing in place like the
Middle East and it wasn't that much of a of a of a change to me to actually come
and I mean associated with Americans for a long time before that so it wasn't a
great culture shock to me I've taken it very seriously and I fully support the
Second Amendment I fully support the Constitution although because of things
like the UCMJ I have to be careful what I would say because for instance you
know the commander-in-chief is the president and so therefore I have to be
careful what I say but I will point out that that the when you swear your oath
of allegiance you swear your oath of allegiance to the Constitution exactly
not to a person but to the Constitution so what if what if someone violates the
Constitution what is your allegiance to them well we see that all the time you
see that people seem to be violating the Constitution and there doesn't seem to
be anything any repercussions or consequences for that right it just
happens all the time and you've got these instances like Benghazi you've got
the you know the I forget the name of it you know the Mexican gun running thing
yeah the the Sinaloa cartel are all kinds of different cartels a drug fast
and furious operation that you know you see you know thuggery across the United
States with police officers doing things unconstitutionally the TSA you've got
lots of things going on unconstitutional and really something needs to be done
about that and you originally asked me the question you know how you know how
do I feel about how do I feel about it well having come from the UK and now
being a US citizen I feel privileged to be in the United States and given that I
started on this path planning for like a prepper planning for a collapse before I
really got to the political side of it and started to wake up and see the
dangers inherent in our own country the importance to me of having firearms
whatever you want to call them weapons is one of them that you call it you have
your personal weapon that's what it's called so I mean people use the language
but you need those to be able to defend yourself against whatever may happen I
feel privileged that should a collapse happen if I'm living in the United
States I'll have the ability to defend my family if I'm living in the UK I have
nothing well that's a good point so we are on the verge many people believe of
an economic collapse a global cascading debt collapse of the trillions or more
than a quadrillion dollars in derivatives which are of course you know
fake fake constructs of mathematically inclined greed mongers or something yeah
the point is the system it looks ripe for collapse what will happen in the UK
if there is chaos and the citizens have no real way to protect themselves
because they've all been disarmed well I dread to think about my family is still
still living back there and I you know I I really don't know what they can do I
mean I have family who's actually in the British military I would hope that they
would get themselves onto the translation which at least has firearms
to benefit you know and somewhere to actually you know protect themselves
there is nothing most people can do and and this is one of the things you know
you see these I have to mention the name Piers Morgan but you see these
interviews and you know this British guy coming over and telling people they
don't need a Second Amendment anymore but my experience is that the UK is a
very violent society well yeah now that you bring it up let me bring up Piers
Mordor and he joked about shooting rivals this is an article out of Daily
Caller it says in England Piers Mordor joked about shooting I'm obviously
invoking Lord of the Rings there Piers Morgan slash the Dark Lord Sauron
Mordor joked about shooting rivals said homeowners who killed and said said
homeowners who kill burglars should not be prosecuted so Piers Morgan was saying
that he first he joked about shooting professional enemies and he wrote that
he was a rabid fascist who wanted burglars tortured and quote after a
decent period of cattle prodding testicle electrode treatment and slow
gentle skewering over hot coals these are the words of Piers Morgan as
published by Daily Caller what do you think about that well I mean the man's
outrageous he basically got kicked out of the UK and now you know people trying
to pull him from the United States and people in the UK don't want him back I
mean he it's not really for him it's not really about banning a certain type of
firearm or gun it's really about his real agenda is banning them all because
he's a you know he's one of these these progressives you know these
collectivists these statists and you know he's a he's a front man for all
that so really you know his point I thought I'd forget who it was with I
saw an interview on the internet someone was being interviewed by him and it made
some very good points and he referenced it back to what the real meaning of the
Second Amendment is which is you know to defend against tyranny you know it's not
about being a hunter all those things are things that come out of the fact
that you might have run firearms target on what it's really about and all he
could do was just keep the region on this guy so you know it it just it's all
on your site I mean it all comes in from so many different angles the kind of the
demonization you know the full crime it's really just about pushing this
agenda and to disarm you know the American population so that anything can
be done to them well that's exactly it you got it you got to ask the question
what kind of a nation or let's say this what is a government planning if it must
first disarm the citizens so in fact there's a quote from the author of this
book called the resistance to tyranny by Joseph P Martino and there's a quote in
here that I believe goes any any any government that attempts to disarm its
citizens is either a tyranny or planning to become one so you gotta ask what are
they planning that they got to have everybody disarmed well exactly and I
think you know you guys know a lot more about this I do I'm still on a personal
journey of education with this but you're exactly right because why would
America administration in America want to take away the Second Amendment and
effectively disable the Constitution or you know revoke or get rid of the
Constitution which is the thing that that makes America exceptional and has
made America what it is right if you take away that Constitution then what is
America anymore I mean they got rid of guns in Australia but they didn't have
they weren't protected by Second Amendment right or you know a
constitution so they just basically just they had a similar situation to Sandy
hook and they just said right no more guns but think but think about all the
details of this too we have an illegitimate president who doesn't
qualify whose birth certificate is a total fake an absolute document fraud
you know multiple layers copy and paste font resolutions differ and so on it's
it's an obvious fake that that I I would I would debate that with anybody it's
irrefutable and then we have an administration that runs itself like a
tyranny invoking executive orders bypassing the separation of powers
bypassing Congress which means bypassing representation and the the war of
independence in America was fought in part over the lack of representation of
the American colonies in the decision-making process in the UK so now
we have the same kind of kingship and Obama was crowned king yet again today
in another pompous ceremony that really smacked of you know the Fuhrer this is
the same issue that we once fought a war over to get away from and to establish
liberty that's how crazy it has gotten well my main worry here is that you know
as the United States has progressed through its history from being the
shining light with it with it you know the Declaration of Independence and
Constitution the Bill of Rights now it's becoming basically the federal government
is becoming there for its own sake and for whatever other agendas there might
be and and it becomes you know it's just becoming another socialist state and
it's just starting to do all the things that socialist states do yeah and about
you know back to a previous point why would they want to disarm why would you
possibly if as administration you were interested in what is best for Americans
because we know that all these arguments about you know gun control are just
specious it's ridiculous I mean you me you me can just say that we don't have
to debate it between ourselves it's ridiculous so there is no real reason
apart from agendas and you know thought police type stuff to really want to you
know disarm Americans and and therefore so you disarm all the lawful people and
then basically criminals have the guns and then the worrying probably even more
worrying than the criminals having the guns are if there is therefore no
defense against tyranny should and you know I say this because I have to but
should an administration become a regime as I have it in my book become tyrannical
nobody's got any defense I mean one of the criminals are going to fight it but
I don't see that happening right now the people who got guns I think I think the
the the brain damaged part of this in the minds of the radical left is that
they cannot ever imagine a government becoming a regime because in their minds
their hardcore belief is that government is the Savior government is the answer
government provides solutions it never causes problems it only provides
solutions and therefore how could a government ever murder its own people or
commit genocide and I guess they just they have to you know dismiss all of
human history to hold that contradictory belief but they managed to do that they
can hold that contradiction in their brain little brain damaged you know
minds I don't know how I don't know how I couldn't even fake like being a
radical left you know anti-gun liberal I don't know how they do it I'm not a
psychiatrist but I mean it seems to me that you know you get to that point
where you're trying to push this agenda and so you're the you're the you know
the progressive status who's in power you're the socialist whatever it might
be you know your ideal might be communism whatever the exact agenda is
but you therefore have enemies you may construct those enemies because you need
enemies to push your revolution through but at the end of the day it's easy in
their mind to justify the removal and destruction of those enemies look what
happens in Russia and Nazi Germany or Stalin Russia well that's what it has
become with Obama is is that his entire agenda is really just destroying his
enemies it's not about helping America it's not about boosting the economy even
it why should government even have the role of boosting the economy anyway
government's not going to solve that problem it should be government get out
of the way let innovation rise but but but Obama is focused on destroying his
enemies and not doing anything really for America you didn't build that but
hey Obama's been re-inaugurated and he's gonna do more he's gonna do more he gave
us the phone and he's gonna do more stay with us max velocity we got to go to a
break but we'll be right back after this break with much more straight ahead here
on the Alex Jones show don't go away max velocities straight ahead we'll be right
back if you've ever wanted one of our best-selling generators but we're
waiting for an offer so crazy you couldn't refuse then you are not going
to want to miss this exciting message here's why our solar generators provide
life-saving electrical power and unlike gas generators solar generators run
quietly emit no fumes and produce electricity from the Sun so when the
lights go out you'll always have the power you need now here's the best part
every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as
new we put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily
at the end of each year we call them scratch and dent units but they're
really just like this each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special
bonuses you just won't believe don't wait they go fast go to scratch and dent
solar calm that scratch and dent solar calm for the craziest offer we've ever
made go to scratch and dent solar calm that scratch and dent solar calm feeling
like there are too many pressures and demands on you losing sleep worrying
about tests and schoolwork even on the run because your schedule is just too
busy you may be under too much stress and it may be affecting your mind get
your mental edge back with new tropic mind power from mind regard calm new
tropic mind power is not a drug but a natural supplement it's 12 powerful
ingredients are natural and non GMO plus it's gluten free wheat free and
formulated by Americans for Americans by an NSF certified laboratory new tropic
mind power is available at mind regard calm spelled m-i-n-d-r-e-g-a-r-d.com and
comes with a 100% money-back guarantee free your mind with new tropic mind
power cognitive supplement from mind regard calm mind regard clearly see
tomorrow and yesterday today weekend by GMO stressed out about money and blasted
by the electric environment hi I'm pastor Jenny and that was the state I
was in back in 2010 then I learned about RNA drops I learned that 97% of my DNA
that scientists have called junk is actually packed with millions of gene
switches that play a critical role in controlling how my cells organs and
other tissues behave I learned I don't have to put up with disease decay or
decline like I've been conditioned to believe I began taking RNA drops a 100%
natural formula designed to turn on those switches and provide me with
amazing health and joy learn more about RNA drops and order a free sample today
visit RNA free sample calm that's RNA free sample calm or call toll-free 888
five seven seven three seven oh three pay only shipping and handling for a
free 30-day supply of RNA drops get the information you need and the health you
want at RNA free sample calm
with Max velocity and author and patriot and individual who served in the British
Army as well as United States military and by the way this shirt is continuing
to sell like crazy at the infowars store infowarsstore.com it is the come and take
it shirt showing the outline of an ak-47 that is formed by the words of the Second
Amendment and for example it has shall not be infringed coming out the barrel
what part of shall not be infringed do you not understand I guess it's all
about parsing words now isn't it Bill Clinton is is not is and Obama we're
gonna do more we're gonna do more to erode the Bill of Rights and destroy the
Constitution and we've given them four more years and I guess I guess enough of
popular support to where they think they can try to get away with it but they're
gonna find that real Americans aren't gonna put up with that so good luck good
luck with that good luck with your little commie agenda all right now
continuing with Max velocity the author of contact the author of Patriot Dawn a
very interesting individual who has served in militaries of two nations the
UK and the United States and also served as a contractor working alongside US
military men in the Middle East Max you still you still with us there yeah I'm
still here all right great so I wanted to ask you your thoughts since you've
been you know in trenches so to speak with so many individuals in the military
if an order comes down from Washington to say martial laws declared well here's
how it would happen first the false flag attack is set off somewhere in a major
u.s. city they blame it on gun owners they then declare martial law bring in
the military violating posse comment a comment atis and have the military start
kicking indoors and confiscating guns to disarm the American citizens do you
think max that American military servicemen would engage in that behavior
how or what percent would follow orders or what do you think might happen well
Mike I'm not really sure about percentages but I did basically cover
this topic in my book Patriot Dawn because I actually have you know
resistance elements fighting against what I call regime forces and the way
I've described it is I think it would be a split because some people are awake
and some people aren't and some people come from different backgrounds so among
the great variety of people in the United States military some of them come
from strong kind of patriot families depending on what part of the country
they come from other people don't you don't remember a lot of people are
recruited to the military through the inner cities for instance yes so there's
two parts this is really what the background is of of the people in the
military the military reflects the society it comes from and so many people
in today's society are not aware of and really understand things like the
Constitution and the Bill of Rights we've got the whole push now you know
for safety and security which is infringing upon people's rights and so
you've got many people in the military who are similar to a lot of the people
or even the entitlement class as we call them you know who are out there in
America today the other side of it is is if you've got an active duty unit for
instance that's sitting on a base if it's chain of command doesn't flinch
and it just you know the orders come down and if there is you know an
intelligence briefing that says you know this false flag attack is happening
we're going to say it's a false flag attack but such-and-such has happened
and there are terrorists and we have been ordered to deploy and do operations
against these terrorists in the domestic United States a lot of people aren't
going to question that well yeah that's how the manipulation will be done they
would call gun owners terrorists can you stay with us for one more segment max
we got to take a quick break yeah sure all right we'll be back in just a little
over one minute with the final segment with max velocity author of Patriot Dawn
and I'd like to give out your website as well and we've got other breaking news
on gun control including a quote from Bill Clinton who says don't trivialize
the gun culture all that straight ahead here on the Alex Jones show infowars.com
we'll be right back
this is GCN the Genesis communications radio network the new year is a great
time to take charge of your health and wellness get serious and make a stand
with supernatural silver this is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver
supernatural silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses
infections yeast and molds supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound
care and is highly effective for water purification it is the number one choice
for thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect
choice for your emergency preparedness go to supernatural silver calm today and
give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance that's supernatural
silver calm check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook waging war on
corruption Alex Jones on the GCM radio network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones and we're back into the second hour on the Alex Jones show this
is Mike Adams filling in for Alex today Alex returns tomorrow and you know one
of the great things about what's happening right now is we really have to
thank Obama and we've got to thank senator Feinstein from California we got
to thank all of these gun grabbers were overreaching vastly overreaching they
have made a tactical error they have awakened tens of millions of people to
the reality that we are under siege by an illegitimate unconstitutional and
perhaps even a criminal government and this is going to work in our favor and by
us I mean Patriots I mean people who actually believe in America believe in
the founding fathers and the principles upon which we were founded so they've
overreached and Bill Clinton warned about that and just recently this is an
article of Politico January 19 Bill Clinton says the Democrats don't trivial
don't trivialize the gun culture a lot of these people he's talking about people
who advocate gun firearms ownership private firearms ownership a lot of
these people live in a world very different from the world lived in by the
people proposing these things he means gun control measures I know because I
come from this world yeah Arkansas there is a big gun culture in Arkansas there
is in fact gun culture isn't even the right word it's a culture of liberty and
self-reliance that's really what it is so max velocity continues with us in
this segment he's our guest the author of Patriot Dawn and Max and like your
comments on Bill Clinton's quote there about not trivializing the gun culture
and but first please give out your website address so people can find you
yeah sure it's it's max velocity tactical calm max velocity tactical okay
max velocity tactical calm and I see that forwards to a blog spot page so
very good link to the blog on there as well all right and not a lot not a lot
of info on there yeah but I'm sure you'll continue to post but there are
some pictures of you in action what is that a is that a saw a pull auto rifle
there I think yeah much what you're going to but there's yet picture me with
store yeah that was like that's pretty heavy-duty firepower you got there dude
that's right is that is that what you have in your house now yeah those full
auto kind of kind of pricey to get those these days yeah not too many private
citizens with a saw all right no hammers that's a totally different story but not
saws okay only gun owners will get that joke but go ahead sir with your comments
on the on the bill Clinton thing about making the gun yes what do you think
what do you think about that because multiple thoughts because yes I think
maybe in their arrogance people at Feinstein have overreached but what
worries me is I mean we were just talking before about how how military
could be kind of persuaded to be used domestically against so-called domestic
terrorists who might just be preppers or gun owners or whatever it is you know
you have those those those pronouncements that people having
waterproofed ammunition and more than seven days of food could be like
domestic terrorists and ridiculous things like that what worries me is is
at one point people are going to kind of stand up by which mean I actually may
not do anything violent that's one of the dangers is that it might be some
kind of false flag thing which is put onto you know this could be how it
begins they've blown up somewhere or they've shot someone and these are the
right-wing extremist terrorists right now we've got to calm down yeah well
that's where we're fully expecting that to happen in fact I put I'd put money on
that happening I'm sure they're working on it yeah and what I really mean is you
know when people really gonna just stand up in a like civil protest because what
worries me you see enough already of these these kind of these squat no not
raid supposedly against the wrong addresses that kind of thing yeah and you
know if they just start to take people down isolated people in different houses
or little compounds or whatever whoever they decide to see is the new threat you
know you get any kind of Waco chair Ruby Ridge sorry I forget the name yeah
Ruby Ridge you know you get those kind of situations which which are appalling
well max we got it we got to let you go we got to go to break but thanks for
joining us today the website is max velocity tactical calm if you want to
learn more the book is Patriot dawn available everywhere now thanks for
joining us max all right we'll be right back after this break stay with us here
on the Alex Jones show you prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms but if
you don't have a home security system then you're missing a critical weapon in
your arsenal for home protection when you're sleeping or away from home who's
watching out for intruders check out simply safe it's a new do-it-yourself
home security system that is completely wireless go to get simply safe calm
simply safe is independent and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if
the grid goes down you are protected it's completely customizable so you can
use it in your home business boat trailer storage unit or shed get simply
safe calm simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in
under 20 minutes so there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you
move or need to relocate you can take the system with you wherever you go you
aren't always at home but simply safe will stand guard protecting your property
24 hours a day seven days a week again that's get simply safe calm looking back
on 2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters like
Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships
brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost
everything at e foods direct we hear from customers every day that are
fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand after
Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all of the grocery stores
are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my
sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too early than one
day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what
Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or
go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best
tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet
your life on e foods direct millions of people are going to get sick this winter
from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with
supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution
recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that
can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help
improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every
day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as
strep staph pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new
technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at
several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions
the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
thank you for joining us today on Monday and January 21st 2013 this is the Alex
Jones show and I'm Mike Adams the health Ranger editor of natural news calm
filling in for Alex today Alex will be back in this chair tomorrow to continue
with his comments I can only imagine what he's gonna have to say about
today's pompous inauguration of the king Obama and everything else that's going
on these days but we're gonna go through more news and then at the bottom of this
hour we've got Sheriff Denny Paimon from Kentucky who is going to be joining us
as a guest with an update on his thoughts on the Second Amendment the
founding fathers and what's really happening to America in the meantime
we're gonna we're gonna go over some news and I'd like to take some calls in
the the second half of this hour so if you if you're interested in calling it's
1-800-259-9231 yeah just making sure that's it 1-800-259-9231 all any time in
the next 30 minutes or so and then we will start taking your calls about the
Second Amendment or especially if you ever call for Sheriff Denny Paimon now I
was just thinking during the break there how is it that these operatives in the
Obama administration and in Congress how do they think that they're not gonna
face their own sort of Nuremberg trial at some point I mean really do they
because look all they've done is they've activated the Bill of Rights resistance
to tyranny that was part of the DNA of America they've activated the DNA of
America they've activated the culture of independence and freedom and liberty and
they've grossly miscalculated Bill Clinton just pointed that out read that
in the last break Bill Clinton says the Democrats don't trivialize gun culture
basically he says you're not gonna make any headway by just dismissing the the
pro-gun arguments he says the issue of guns has special emotional resonance in
many rural states it's not just emotional residence it's survival people
you live on a farm you live on a ranch if you don't have a rifle if you don't
have a hunting gun if you don't have a shotgun you you can't succeed in farming
believe me I know that because I live on a ranch and that many times that I grab
a shotgun and rush outside and have to take care of something to protect our
our animals or to investigate a strange noise from a wild animal or a strange
sound or whatever many times you do that and if you're a farmer you need a
varmint rifle you might need a hunting rifle a high-powered hunting rifle with
like one-half MOA accuracy something like that to really reach out and you
know long-range accuracy but how do these people in the Obama administration
actually think and all these people on CNN that are advocating the destruction
of the Constitution the destruction of the Bill of Rights do they not realize
that they are admitting their guilt as traitors to America do they not realize
that do they they they have no view of history they have no understanding that
they've just admitted total guilt and I tell you what it's on and if if if the
communists don't win if they don't take over the entire nation they're all gonna
face trial all right I'm just I'm just putting that out there they're gonna
face trial and may God have mercy on their souls because I'm not so sure that
the citizenry will have mercy on them I'm always an advocate of non-violence I
think people should have a fair trial I think we stick to the Bill of Rights we
stick to due process we would give them what they would deny us which is a jury
of their peers and and and due process see they would deny us the very things
that we would grant them because we are the ones who occupy the moral high
ground we are the we are in the right we have the philosophy the ideals upon
which this nation was founded we would grant them a jury trial we would grant
them the right to remain silent we would not try to take away their rights even
though they try to take away ours and that's why we will be victorious because
they will alienate the population if they try to conduct gun confiscation
raids even by calling gun owners terrorists it won't take very long
before those military bases find out that all their supplies are cut off
because they depend on the goodwill of the citizenry to give them food and
water and safe passage to and from the base to their homes as Paul Howe said in
a in a recent piece that we talked about here last week or week and a half ago it
wouldn't take long before any military personnel based in America who engage in
gun confiscation and the murder of American citizens it wouldn't take long
before their homes and their families were identified by resistance groups and
they would start taking casualties so you're either with the Republic or your
toast I mean to put it in simple slang you're either with the Republic or your
toast that's that's the bottom line and let me tell you something I'm with the
Republic all right no matter what I'm with the Republic you can count on that
and I want you to know all of you listening out there I very much
appreciate you I feel a closeness to you and to your passion and to your mission
right now and I am I will I will do whatever it takes to speak up or freedom
for justice for this Republic to publish stories to help out here at
infowars.com when I can you know I'm here as a volunteer you know I'm never
paid to be here you know so much for Obama's excuse that people are ginning
up fear to try to make revenues for themselves you know I'm getting paid
zero to be here I'm here because I'm a patriot I'm a patriot and I believe in
this Republic and I believe we're gonna win back this Republic and I hope we can
do it through through the Constitution I hope we can do it without violence I
hope we can do it with no suffering that's my that's my prayer out there
let America be saved let the Republic be restored with no loss of life with no
bloodshed with no suffering of innocent people that's what it's going to take
and I'm going to be here to help make that happen it no matter what all right
I just want you to know that I know a lot of you don't know me I grew up I
played football one year in high school I ran track four years competitive
athlete very high academic scores went into engineering school ended up with a
degree in technical writing wrote software documentation found that a
software company became a business innovator and ended up creating a
multi-million dollar software firm that sold software to 20 20% 25% of the
fortune 500 and found Liberty and the the need for Liberty in the 1990s on the
tail end of the Clinton administration I began to see a beginner my eyes began to
be opened to the reality of what was happening in our world and I gotta say I
was in in in college I actually believed a lot of the liberal stuff I was
indoctrinated by the public education system I was I was suckered into the
Clinton charisma and I think a lot of people are suckered into the into the
Obama charisma with the same thinking today I had to find Liberty myself I had
to read and study and learn and become a defender of Liberty and teach myself
history that the public schools wouldn't teach me so I didn't have the benefit of
homeschooling I didn't have the benefit of private schooling I was a public
school educated you know typical Midwest
student and had to come out of that anyway enough about me I just wanted to
give you a little background so you know where I'm coming from I come from the
Midwest and I had to find Liberty on my own let's get to the other news the
kindergartner has been suspended for bubble gum terrorism so that this
kindergartner pointed a five-year-old girl pointed a bubble gum gun at a
fellow student a Hello Kitty bubble blower and was then suspended there you
go I also wrote a piece last night about
nerf guns apparently oh my god you can buy on amazon.com a full auto nerf
assault rifle that has 18 round magazines I mean high-capacity clips it
comes with three of them 18 round magazines and it's full auto man I mean
full auto nerf guns and they don't even have background checks required how
dare Amazon sell full auto nerf assault rifles to children it's advertised to
children the eight-year-olds no background checks no fingerprinting I
can't believe it I so I I propose I propose that we have a new federal law
that is called the nerf control act of 2013 and what we have to do is limit all
full auto nerf guns to no more than seven rounds of ammo per magazine to be
in compliance with New York and even if you have an 18 round nerf magazine you
can only load seven nerf bullets into it otherwise you're a terrorist and you'll
be suspended from your school or they'll make you wear an RFID chip like they do
in San Antonio how wonderful is that nerf assault rifles yep soon soon our
little kids will be arrested as terrorists or toting nerf guns alright
Time Warner has banned gun ads continues to produce movies full of gun violence
this is a story by Paul Joseph Watson up on infowars.com right now Time Warner
bans gun ads any ad that shows a gun pointed at another person they're
banning it but of course they're going to keep producing movies that show the
total hypocrisy of all the Hollywood celebrities who've been calling for gun
control who meanwhile star in all of these roles of pure blood and gore
shooting people blowing their bodies apart on screen with massive splotches
of blood striking the camera and dripping down the lens they love that
but they want to ban ads now that depict guns pointed at people all right we've
got this from prison planet.com actually it's from Lou Rockwell blog we've got a
cartoon a weapon guide for the uninformed it's called guns guns and
Obama for dummies and it shows how many people are killed each year by these
various objects shows an ar-15 rifle mass shootings 18 and then it shows
remote a remote a car remote with a key on it auto accidents 32,885 deaths it
shows a rifle 453 deaths and then it shows a bottle of whiskey drunk driving
10,839 deaths it shows a blunt object hammer 674 deaths knives 1,817 deaths
hands feet and fists 859 deaths oh my goodness it looks like we should ban
Jack Daniels automobiles hammers knives and fists yes you must all be amputated
to conform with the new weapons control legislation in Washington which is also
great because you won't be able to post on Facebook all right stay with us we'll
be back with a lot more straight ahead this is the Alex Jones show we'll be
right back looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves how did we ever survive from
natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to
the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to
those that have lost everything at e foods direct we hear from customers
every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm by having a supply of
food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the
grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be
able to help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too
early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the
warnings and do what Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six
three three today or go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your
food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the
planet call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three or e foods direct
comm slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct
hey there Frank Bates here have you heard about the weird device that could
wipe out two hundred and eighty million Americans this is really scary stuff
defense experts warn that this odd device poses the greatest threat we've
ever known in fact just a few weeks ago former Speaker of the House Newt
Gingrich wrote an op-ed piece for the Washington Post warning about this
deadly threat I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this it may
be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up
that's why my friend just created a free video at weird device calm that exposes
this threat and blows the doors off a conspiracy go watch the shocking video
at weird device calm right now to discover exactly what it is plus
discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack
I'm not sure how long this video be online so go to weird device calm before
it's gone forever again that's weird device calm
plan a healthy garden easy and fast with organic a seed calm easy because
organic a seed calm offers one of the largest online selections of organic
heirloom non-hybrid and untreated seeds as well as tobacco and cotton seeds at
low prices go to organic a seed calm spelled o-r-g-a-n-i-c-a-seed.com organic
a seed calm remember organic a seed is healthy see hi this is Ted Anderson have
you ever wondered why banks stockbrokers investment advisors won't talk about
gold IRAs they've been available since 1986 yet the financial industry won't
recognize the value of gold for your retirement gold is outperform paper
investments yet no word about IRAs if you would like to have gold for your
retirement call 800-686-2237 don't get left behind by rising
inflation and low returns call 800-686-2237 secure your future and call
1-800-686-2237
in the u.s. one in every 50 homes will have a break in this year burglars call
it smash and grab police call it robbery we call it avoidable we are fake TV a
simple electronic device that can fool even professional burglars fake TV
easily plugs into any outlet and simulates the changing colors of a
television to a burglar it looks like someone must be home watching TV so
they'll likely move on to an easier target at only 34 95 fake TV costs less
than a month of most alarm monitoring plants and it's perfect if you're
traveling or away from home order your fake TV by calling 8 7 7 5 fake TV or go
to fake TV comm that's 8 7 7 5 3 2 5 3 8 8 or fake TV comm fake TV the burglar
deterrent waging war on corruption Alex Jones on the GCM radio network
yeah we're back it's the Alex Jones show in four wars
calm Mike Adams here filling in for Alex today we've just become aware of a new
law being debated in the Senate SB 124 it turns parents into criminals if they
fail to report to the school that they own a firearm so let me let me just run
this down for you a parent has a child that goes to the school if the parent
owns a firearm that parent must notify the school district that the parent owns
a firearm within 30 days of enrolling the child in the school otherwise they
become a criminal the written notification needs to include the names
of the parent and any child attending the school and the fact that the parent
owns a firearm so of course they're trying to create another database and
they're going to discriminate against her child in the school so you're bad
you're your mommy or your daddy owns a gun you're bad you're evil and they're
probably going to then force that child into psychiatric care and then use the
psychiatric diagnosis as a justification to take away your right to own a firearm
so you see how this works it's all a catch-22 little scam now how is this
gonna stop a kid like Adam Lanza from killing his parent and stealing her guns
think about that I guess they're gonna have to charge the dead mother of Adam
Lanza with a felony because it's her fault it's her fault that her son
allegedly killed her and took her guns it's her fault I mean if if if your
child kills you and steals your guns it's your fault they're gonna dig up
your grave they're gonna dig up your body they're gonna throw you in handcuffs
and charge you with another felony crime and probably have you as a guest with
Piers Morgan just have a corpse right there talking to Piers Morgan just a
corpse Piers Morgan would say to the corpse how dare you be a corpse I think
it's just like zombie time total zombification of America but that law
SB 124 is a I don't think it's on the floor of the Senate yet but it was
sponsored by Chappelle and Nadal Nadal I don't know how you pronounce that those
are the co-sponsors there you go SB 124 now you have to alert the school if you
own a firearm and if you have a child in school so one more reason to home school
folks as if we needed more we got a guest coming up here in just a few
minutes we've got Sheriff Denny Paimon he is the outspoken sheriff who is now
famous for his YouTube video talking about the importance of the founding
fathers and what they would want to to see happen in America today which is the
restoration of the Republic and the rights of the people uninfringed so we'll
have we'll have that sheriff on the show here in just a few minutes here's a
quote from Bill Clinton this was mentioned last week by Aaron Dykes in a
video Bill Clinton said and I'm not sure what year this is quote when we got
organized as a country and we wrote a fairly radical Constitution with a
radical Bill of Rights giving a radical amount of individual freedom to
Americans this is Bill Clinton again it was assumed that the Americans who had
that freedom would use it responsibly there's a lot of irresponsibility now
and so a lot of people say there's too much freedom Wow well wait a minute
mr. Clinton when we the people granted power to the government to have limited
powers to run a few small things in the nation we assume that the limited
government would use those limited powers responsibly but it didn't it
became irresponsible it became oppressive it became a regime it
bypassed the will of the people and has become a monster that is on the verge of
committing genocide so to quote Bill Clinton that's a lot of irresponsibility
and so a lot of people say there's too much government and when government is
abusing our freedoms you have to move to limit it that's so that's the flip side
of Bill Clinton's quote you see Bill Clinton was saying that oh my god there's
too much freedom there's too much there's freedom everywhere freedom is
flowing around it's it's out of control there's so much liberty it's just
totally out of control what are we gonna do we're gonna have to limit the freedom
he says but wait a minute the answer is government's out of control it's too
much government in invading every little area of our lives how much water you
could flush in your toilet how big your soda can be in New York and now you got
to register your your guns if you if you have a kid in school if this bill passes
I mean that government is intruding in every area of our lives I wouldn't be
surprised if New York mayor of Governor Cuomo passed a law that said you can
only use 2.5 square sheets of toilet paper every time you use the restroom in
New York two and a half sheets and they would require toilet paper manufacturers
to put extra perforations at the half sheet mark so that you can tear off
exactly two and a half sheets without leaving a frayed edge which is not
acceptable to the Mafia running the New York State Government two and a half
sheets of toilet paper is actually that's what the Cuomo administration is
probably worth after they're used we'll be right back straight ahead this is the
Alex Jones show don't go anywhere we're on the march the Empire's on the run
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network if you want an American company with
American products made by Americans here is the cow bed soap company Alex and his
staff have used these pure soap products for years these all-natural soaps are
made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth friendly
and safe see them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for
a free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are
twice as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year
supply of soaps or all your cleaning needs this is an amazing deal you can
save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
see them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free
catalog the new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness
get serious and make a stand with supernatural silver this is a
breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver can be taken orally
every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds
supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective
for water purification it is the number one choice for thousands of people for
immune system support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency
preparedness go to supernatural silver calm today and give yourself and your
loved ones a fighting chance that's supernatural silver calm check out our
new low prices and like us on Facebook now that we have moved into the winter
season there is an increased need to support our immunity and health at silver
lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver based products our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce
nano silver solutions our 2 ounce nano silver nasal applicators as well as our
all-natural silver soaps just released is our 100% natural silver gel our new
silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate
and leave the silver at the surface but rather we have formulated our silver gel
using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly
penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively
visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver
based products are best for you that's www.silverlungs.com
you can run on for a long time we've got Sheriff Denny Pymond joining us now in this segment and taking
some of your calls so thank you for calling in Joe, Rick, Pat, Austin and
others and the sheriff Denny Pymond of course is the sheriff of Jackson County
Kentucky who made an emotional speech to his constituents that was posted on
YouTube talking about the importance of honoring what our founding fathers
fought for and the liberty they gave us and the moral responsibility that we
have to protect those freedoms for future generations and Sheriff Pymond I
want to welcome you back to the Alex Jones show thank you very much just my
pleasure to be here well it's it's great to have you back on sir
things are moving rapidly but I first want to ask you what has been the
reaction so far to your appearance last week on the Alex Jones show as well as
your YouTube video what are you hearing from people well it's been it's all it's
all been very you know pro what we're trying to keep here it's been you know
there's been no negative calls whatsoever what I'm getting from people
mostly is that they're ready to dig in they're ready to stand their ground and
that's been that's been really exciting to see that there's still people that
are willing to step up and to stand in the gap even for the people that choose
not to the people that choose to are still staying in a gap running for their
freedoms but for the freedoms of the people that that obviously don't
understand what's happening right now so have you had a meeting with your
deputies then where where it's very clear to everybody that you're standing
your ground you're not going to disarm constituents in your county and so on is
it is it clear to everybody now where you and your office stands yes it's very
clear and the support that's come back from the community has just been been
great sometimes when you make a stance like that you step out I mean I didn't
ask anybody about it I didn't ask for a pole I didn't ask for the favor if it's
gonna be good or bad I just went by my heart and the commitment that I made
when I took an oath and the way I was raised and the things that I was taught
in my home by my parents there was just no other response to have us but no it's
just not gonna happen here well yeah yeah I mean you're exactly right this
isn't up to a pole that's the whole point of the Bill of Rights is that this
is the these things in the Bill of Rights are not subject to debate they're
not subject to popular movements you you always have a First Amendment you always
have a Second Amendment and so on they cannot be taken away from you no matter
how unpopular they may become in any particular moment in history so you did
the right thing you followed your oath exactly and that's what I think people
are looking for I think a lot of people are still you know what's politically
correct and what's you know gonna get me reelected or you know they have their
own little hidden agendas as to their safe being but with me it was just the
commitment that I had made in the the issues that I count to be important to
me and to my family and the people around me and that's a that's a very big
commitment is to you know uphold what has been given and handed down to us the
price that others have paid that we might just even you know have these
opportunities absolutely and also just from a a practical and perhaps even a
tactical viewpoint if your population there your constituents if they were
forcibly disarmed from some other method or if they turn in all their guns for
some reason which I know they wouldn't do but wouldn't that put you and your
deputies in grave danger responding to 911 calls because now you are you're
going into situations where you don't have any help of firepower from the
citizens exactly what I talk with citizens every day and we talk with
those today one that had just come in and I've known this man to carry a gun
for the last 15 years every day that I've been around him I've never seen it
I've never seen his gun but I know every day that he has when I asked him if he
had his his weapon with him easy as he did and you know if I'm out in a remote
area and my closest backup is maybe 30 minutes away and I'm in a bad situation
I should would like to see a citizen like that show up absolutely yeah and I
should be hanging myself out to disarming you know yeah that would be
crazy have you ever or has have any of your discussions gone into the area of
let's say a possible financial collapse followed by civil unrest and then how
your county might protect your community with the help of armed citizens has that
ever entered your discussions at all not so much like an open discussions in a
meeting or anything like that but just in coffee room talk yeah what people are
saying what they're gonna do and you know you have a lot of people that you
know do the home storage they get the food they get the water and they've been
real good too but they're pacifist type people yeah and you know I understand
that I respect their beliefs but I also know that that's the first place that
they're gonna hit because they're they know there's no resistance there right
it's so is that really fair to their family who they have you know proof you
know said they're gonna provide for for the next year while we go through these
situations these problems and to have somebody else marching to take this
stuff out of their home that leaves them with nothing well there was there was a
comedian I think it was I think it was Gaffigan who said this he said if if you
store up a bunch of food and you don't have a gun all you've done is stored
supplies for the biggest bully on the block exactly not not such a good
strategy are you open to taking a few a few calls sure cuz I I would like to
take some calls live calls here and we've got one guest Rick from New Mexico
I'd like to go to Rick first please who is says he's got a question for the
sheriff so Rick from New Mexico you're on the air with Sheriff Paimon go ahead
sir hi Mike how you doing doing great sir how about you good I just wanted to
tell you something then I want to ask the sheriff a question all right you
just talked about that homeschooling and we homeschool around about the school
thing you know how corrupt the schools are yeah but we homeschool and we didn't
have our kid vaccinated my dad my wife's never worked a day out of a home you
know and you know there's times when it gets really stressful with the money but
then you know when you hear things like that you're doing the right thing
absolutely what I mean by protected by protecting your kids I'm a big advocate
of homeschooling pardon I said we need more homeschoolers but go ahead with
your question for the sheriff please okay I wanted to know if you're
familiar with the old takers are you part of that or I've learned more about
them no I'm not an oath taker other than a keeper other than you know just from
what I've heard about it but I take any oath that I say it's a promise it's
very important to me well it's sworn go ahead caller sorry I guess I'm an
over-the-road truck driver and you know I get called into the chicken coop or
pulled over by the state patrol and it's very surprising because I you know things
I learned from Alex I'll sit and question them when I'm sitting in the
car and asking questions about the ammunition that the Homeland Security
and these people are very much against Obama I mean for the most part and all
the things that he's doing I mean that's good news I guess well your comments on
that sheriff well for what you know for what I thought of the calls that I've
had I've had from I've had from officers I've had from military people I've had
from everybody that you can imagine but a lot of the officers and military people
are saying when it comes right down to that where them having to come into my
County and do that they said they won't do it yeah I'm very very good well thank
you for your call Rick that was some some good questions sheriff I'm curious
have you had any conversations at all with your senator Rand Paul I mean
because I've talked with him and I've talked with his people we've we've had
quite a few conversations already so it's been there's a lot of support there
anything that you that's okay to share on the air about I mean ran Rand Paul
has been very public about you know Obama being a king and how he's going to
lead a resistance in the Congress against unconstitutional executive
orders for example is there anything in those conversations that is okay to
share with us publicly well just that we have the same beliefs that we have the
same thing at heart that thing is that at heart is the Constitution and by
serving the people that have put us in these positions that's really that's the
only thing we can do in the position that he takes is being supported by
everybody here yeah and I've had no opposition other than just be high
regards for for Rand and all that that he's doing and all the people here to
support him have you spoken with Sheriff Mack yes I have good good it is people
like like you sure Paimon who are the key to victory of restoring the public
in America and I'm sure you realize that but it's a you know it's really kind of
sad in some ways because I've had some people come say oh you know you're
really a hero and what it is it's not being a hero it's a responsibility of
all Americans absolutely and it is something that should have never got to
this point in the first place well that's what I said in the last hour and
I know this is gonna be controversial but I said people who openly attack the
Constitution and the Bill of Rights who are saying we should eliminate it they
are enemies of America and we should deport them and strip them of their
citizenship as far as I'm concerned yeah well you know Kim Jong-un needs some
additional servants in his gulags so I'm sure a lot of those folks will be happy
there let's go to another caller Joe in Pennsylvania with comments on the Second
Amendment Joe you're on the air with Alex Jones show and Sheriff Paimon go
ahead sir how you doing guys doing good um first of all I want to thank you
sheriff what you're doing you know we need more public people people to come
out in public like you are because I'm sure you know a lot of them are you know
thinking the same thing but I think they need to go more public but one thing
I've noticed on YouTube I think they're suppressing accounts on things because
there's like tons of people that are you know they got these comments about the
guns and they systematically do that yes yes and it's disheartening and also like
on Facebook you make comments like this and people they just don't care they
just care about cookies and football but I wanted to share I wanted to share
something with you guys I'm sure you you've seen it before but if not I found
a interesting video on YouTube it was published on December 15th of 2012
Australia bans gun guns crime rate soars and they if you didn't see it it just
shows how they all they're chopping up the guns and and the people they said
the guy said if I the gun I have I have to keep it locked here it can't be
loaded well let's let's direct that to Sheriff Paimon thank you for your call
Joe but what would happen in your County Jackson County Kentucky if everyone were
disarmed what would happen to the crime rate there in your view it would be it
just go out out the roof I mean we'd have people coming from everywhere just
to steal from here yeah well hey why don't but Sheriff why don't you just I
got the solution for you you put a big sign on the road that comes into your
county and the sign says gun free zone then you'd be protected right oh I'm
sure absolutely I'm every good citizen would probably stop there and if they
did have a gun rather than enter they probably turn around and leave and would
not enter that zone if they were you know just a good good citizen that went
by that but of course part of the problem is some of these criminals can't
read because they're illiterate so they came to read gun free zone so that's why
if they can read it it would work then they would just turn their guns in at
the border I'm sure absolutely yeah the biggest problem with this is cold gun
thing is everybody's I don't know what's happened to people's common sense you
know you and me both brother I mean they're talking stuff that I mean it's
just I would be ashamed to even have that come out of my mouth well it's it's
this magical thinking they they think for example this is mostly from people
who are not familiar with firearms they think that a rifle will leap out of the
trunk of a car it will load itself it will turn its own safety off and it will
engage in rapid fire as its own animated metallic object without any human being
operating it that's what they literally believe well we tried to you know so we
have something to back that up that's area we took a gun and we placed it in a
room full of people but we hate it where nobody who knew it was in there but yet
it was in plain view and we had people come and go we did that for several
years and not one of those people ever saw that gun felt that gun that gun
never bothered anybody so really we just we didn't know what to do after that
well I'm pretty sure Obama would say that's an unscientific experiment you
did not have a control group well they also believe I mean at the bottom the
bottom line is all of us want to see less violence against innocence that's
the goal that we can agree on what what we disagree on is how to get to that
point and for some reason the gun grabbers think that if you if if the
law-abiding citizens turn their guns in the somehow fewer criminals would use
guns how I'm not how does that even make sense well you know I mean it's just I'm
looking at the criminal side of it let's just say I'm a criminal and I'm gonna I
picked out a school that I'm gonna go attack so I started doing my homework on
the school and I realized the guy that went ahead of me to go to this school
when he walked into the school guy come out from behind a desk and shot him you
know he didn't get a chance to shoot anybody yeah chances are I'm not gonna
go to that school that's right I have to look for another one well there you go
another argument for arming some of the school personnel let's go to another
call if you're okay Pat in Texas Pat welcome to the show you're on the air
with sheriff Paimon go ahead sir I heard this mention lately but many years ago
in Kennesaw Georgia they passed a law that you had to have a gun in your house
law-abiding citizens didn't the crime rate drop 70% of criminal break-ins
dropped 70% overnight good question are you aware of the stats related to that
sheriff I have heard that but it wasn't here in our area because they didn't
have to pass all like that people had it anyway yeah we're you know that's
something that's just it goes back to the common sense thing you know all
right well do you have a follow-up question Pat yeah I'm worried about that
we you know like taking down the bullets and sail of the bullets away and where
do you hide those I know Tupperware will hold things the waterproof I put
matches and Tupperware and thrown it in the yard and two years later took them
out and struck them now that's the old Tupperware the new Tupperware is
microwave-proof but I was wondering how do you how do you stop them from
detecting that with a metal detector the kind you go to the beach with and
I can answer that living on a ranch in Texas you throw all kinds of scrap metal
all over the yard which is pretty much already there anyway if you live on a
ranch you any any other thoughts on that sheriff that's the way it works though
there's already there's bullets buried that they can dig them up years and
years from now people have thought well enough they had advanced that even if
they pass stuff today they're never gonna get all this stuff so yeah I tell
you if if one of Obama's minions wants to run a metal detector over you know
400 acres go for it that'll that'll distract you while we restore Liberty in
the meantime all right let's go to another caller and thank you for your
call Pat Mariah in Iowa Mariah you're on the air with Sheriff Paimon from
Kentucky go ahead with your call how are you doing great hi Danny are you I'm
doing all right I am in I have a question for you I need some clarity on
it clarification with all this after the president signed these executive orders
and everybody went into panic I know Alex had a few sheriff on don't know
whether it was you or sheriff Matt I was just I'm in central Iowa I have my
county sheriff ran solely the high-profile individual okay calling
we're gonna have to go to break here real quick but please oh we're skipping
it okay I'm sorry we're skipping this break go ahead with your question thank
you thank you I really want to get this out in the open I think a lot of people
are confused at what a share of what what is his duty when he is sworn in my
this this sheriff of my county was like I said a high-profile individual he ran
on his name he was just elected to the second term from his previous job your
question is what were the responsibilities of the sheriff what the
10th amendment I called him I want to know how he stood on the issue of when
if federal officials were to come in does he have the right to say no you
know these are this is my responsibility these are the people is that elected me
well the short answer is yes but let's let let sure if I'm an answer that the
sheriff is the highest elected official for law enforcement in your area it be
if it be the county then that's the area where just like Kentucky we're a
sovereign state they've tried to break that what's happened over the years is
the states have given up rights and things to the federal government if you
go back to the way the Constitution was made that there were all individuals
just like they're trying to make decisions in Washington for the people
in Jackson County all they can make is the decisions for a mass of people I'm
gonna do a better job of or the people here are gonna do a better job of
elected somebody that's going to provide for our needs here rather than something
federal now the sheriff here know or the sheriff there knows your problems of
situation of issues better than the federal people coming in the federal
people can pass those laws but most most shares do not exercise the rights and
authority that they do have because most of them aren't familiar with that's
right that's right so a sheriff can say and if if this is passed by the the
local voters a law that says let's say a federal agent cannot enforce an
unconstitutional gun confiscation in the county a sheriff can legally stand on on
the road with force and arrest those federal agents and that is all 100%
protected under law yes I hope it doesn't come to that I would hope the
feds would back down knowing what would be what they'd be facing but I think
that's what the caller was getting that yeah well I think the way it's gonna go
I don't think it would be the federal people come in to try to get the guns
anyway because most federal people I've talked to believe the same way that we
believe they swore an oath to the Constitution as well yes and I think
it's gonna take outside of this this country bringing people in it that are
actually the ones in the long run when it gets to the out to that point but
this is the key is just don't let it get to that point listen if it in the bud
right now and take control of what is already ours well I I agree with you
hundred percent I know there are many very good men and women in the FBI for
example even in the ATF in the DEA sometimes I criticize the DEA for their
overreaching raids but you know it's there are good people in every branch
just as there are bad apples in every branch but I think you're right there
are enough good people to prevail but are you talking about like a red dawn
type of scenario something really goes wrong and we have foreign troops in the
country is that what you're yeah I think that's where your United Nations is
gonna play in effect yeah if something goes wrong somewhere else they send the
u.s. boys over there something goes wrong here they're just gonna hold the
u.s. boys back because they wouldn't do that they're not gonna go into some
little woman's house that lives her closest neighbors two miles away and
she's just there with her pets and the only thing she has is a ak-47 laying by
her bed to protect herself I don't think they're gonna take it from her no no and
they will have to use foreign troops but I got to tell you every hunter in Texas
can hit a blue helmet at 600 yards so they're gonna they're gonna be in for a
fight if that happens let's go to one more call Austin in Ohio calling in
about the Obama inauguration Austin go ahead you're on the air sir how are you
gentlemen doing today we're fighting for Liberty brother oh yeah I just wanted to
speak my mind on something because this whole Obama inauguration it's just a
complete hoax I'm just saying people around on social media and just
everywhere in general just worship in this puppet kills kids with little
drones and it's just completely ridiculous how they just worship a puppet
who's doing all of this stuff and the sheep out here are just not doing any
type of research out here and they're making all these biased comparisons to
Martin Luther King and all these pictures and stuff and it's just
completely demonizing and Austin let me let me let you in on something here that
I'm convinced and sure if you'll find this interesting as well I'm convinced
that about one-third of all of the Facebook accounts and Twitter accounts
are run by advanced linguistic robots in other words code that's been written to
act like real human beings you don't know that's even a real person so a lot
of that stuff it's a completely like you said it's a complete hoax it's a theater
reaction that's made to appear as if it were real sheriff directing the question
to you and thank you for your call Austin have you seen some of this posts
on Facebook about you that seemed to be sort of maybe there wasn't really a
person behind it auto-generated type of thing yeah well they're out there the
robots are running the online world and that's see that's the thing about local
government when you spoke to your constituents on that YouTube video there
you were in person face-to-face eye-to-eye that's real but this this
stuff on Facebook it's all it could all be a hoax we don't even know yeah very
true that's why I say what you're better off and that's when the sheriff's on the
level of the county level are gonna make a lot better decision for his good his
people his constituents than somebody that's right federal people that's
exactly right that's why they designed it that way are you I'm just curious by
the way we need more people in positions of authority in in America people like
you and I'm sure you've heard that and I know you're a humble person but have you
have you ever thought about I don't know run for Congress and in in the state of
Kentucky or taking on a position of more more influence well I have I've had
people have talked to me a lot about that the last week and I've offered
avenues to do that I I mean what I do is something like that I just have to pray
about it and to see the direction there's nothing worse than to be out of
the will of what God would have you to do I mean if my sole purpose in life is
to be a sheriff in Jackson County and raise up some young men to go on and
fill those positions and guide and direct them the best that's what I would
do absolutely well that's that's the sense I get that you you are you are
already a powerful influential person just by the truth in your voice the
wisdom in your words and without even ever stepping foot in the House of
Congress you are influencing minds right now in a positive direction that can
influence generations to come well you know people came before us the
generations before us were women that took a stand and upon that stand people
reacted and moved with that and that's how we that's why we are we are today I
can still look back into my child and people that helped bold me and its
responsibility of us to hold that next generation I may never be in Congress
but if I can mold a young man or young woman to go into Congress and to make
the right decisions that are going to further benefit Liberty and our area
here then that's what that's what I'm doing words of wisdom from Sheriff
Sheriff Denny Paimon of Jackson County Kentucky thank you Sheriff for joining
us today on the Alex Jones show pleasure to speak with you again thank you sir
and he's right life is fleeting but principle lasts forever
we are back you are listening to GCN visit GCN live calm today looking back
on 2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters like
hurricane sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships
brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost
everything at e foods direct we hear from customers every day that are
fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand after
hurricane sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the grocery stores are
closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my
sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too early than one
day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what
Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or
go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best
tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet
your life on e foods direct
waging war on corruption Alex Jones on the GCN radio network big brother
mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does he he's
Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas Alex Jones
it gives me a great sense of confidence to know that my fellow Americans include
people like Sheriff Denny Pieman who we just interviewed there in that last
segment people like Sheriff Mack people like Rand Paul people like Alex Jones we
are we are blessed to live in a nation where we have the sense of ethics and
morality and sense of history in the context of the bigger picture with which
we can rise up in resistance to tyranny hopefully peacefully and restore the
Republic so that innocent lives can be saved so the bloodshed can be avoided so
that we can move forward as a nation of justice of innovation of progress real
progress for humankind not the the selfish greed progress of an elite few
which is what we're battling against today but I feel proud to be an American
and I've lived all over the world I've lived outside the country I speak a
couple of different languages I've lived in places where guns were illegal for
citizens to own and I've seen what happens there and it's it is a tyranny
it is oppression it's it's a nightmare and do not give up your guns America you
do not want to live as disarmed slaves to a 1984 style Orwellian government that
demands your obedience you do not want to be in that situation all right we're
into the third hour by the way and thank you for continuing with us I know today
has been a pretty heavy day pretty serious a lot going on we have more news
coming up still ahead and John Rappaport will be joining us in a few minutes for
an update on the psychiatric police state and in the few minutes that we
have in this segment I'd like to continue with your calls and then we'll
get into news in the next segment so callers that have been holding let's go
to Stephen in Pennsylvania with comments on the Second Amendment Stephen you're
on the air go ahead sir hi folks I was hoping to talk to the sheriff and ask
him what his definition of is a gun a firearm and that's where I think the
solution lies in that the the laws that were passed were regulating firearms and
if you look back to the original law the definition of a firearm is a I believe a
rifle under 18 inches in length barrel or a 16 inches barrel length or a
shotgun smooth more that will fire a smooth bore rifle that will fire
shotgun type ammunition under 18 inches in length and they were able to pass
that law according to my understanding was back in 1934 when these gangsters
were going into banks and robbing banks and they could hide a short shotgun under
their trench coat or whatever a long shotgun over 18 inches was very
difficult sure so you're thinking they might be playing word games with us here
and you know doing like a hoax ban on firearms but it doesn't technically
apply is that what you're saying I'm saying explicitly a firearm is only a
smooth bore rifle under 18 inches in length anything 18 inches or over as
long as it has micro grooving in it rifle all pistols are not firearms not
one single pistol that has a has rifling in it is not a firearm not one single
rifle over 16 inches barrel length is not considered a firearm none of them
are well that's that's a very interesting angle there Stephen I'm glad
you brought that up I guess we'd have to get to some attorneys to help parse the
language to see if there's any legitimacy to that but you know I'll
take my one and eight twist barrel any day over a smooth smooth barrel right so
I'm glad we have rifling otherwise we would not have range right we would not
have some stable ballistics in flight so thank you for your call that's a good
point we got to go to a quick break and straight ahead as we return here on the
Alex Jones show will continue with your calls and additional news and one more
guests coming up also at the bottom of this hour so stay with us we'll be right
back and don't forget to visit infowars.com for today's breaking news stay
with us
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers the prognosis for the
entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse the globalist model is
to shut down societies and starve Patriots out until they acquiesce to the
global takeover that's why we've assembled the most vital and important
preparedness items at infowarsshop.com these are items that I did research on
that I personally use we've got the life straw so you can turn fetid water into
safe water anywhere you go the Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key
equipment during power outages are out in the field strategic relocation third
edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein they're a safe
used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event
and crank shortwave AM FM radios everything that we've researched and
found to be the best is available at info war shop calm and your purchase
makes our info war possible we're getting prepared are you info wars shop
calm millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and
other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural
silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution
recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that
can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help
improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every
day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as
stress staff pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new
technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at
several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions
the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook the new year is a great
time to take charge of your health and wellness get serious and make a stand
with supernatural silver this is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver
supernatural silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses
infections yeast and molds supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound
care and is highly effective for water purification it is the number one choice
for thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect
choice for your emergency preparedness go to supernatural silver calm today and
give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance that's supernatural
silver calm check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook
Texas command center deep behind enemy lines the information war continues it's
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
welcome back to the Alex Jones show this is Mike Adams filling in for Alex
today I'm the editor of naturalnews.com and a frequent contributor to Infowars I
guess I'm the unofficial crew member here is the way my role has been described
I'm gonna blow through a bunch of news here for you give you some headlines just
as quickly as possible and then we're gonna go to John Rapaport who has an
update with us on the psychiatric police state and also what I'm calling the era
of thought crimes now being a reality as psychiatrists are given judge dread type
of authority to strip citizens of the constitutional right so that's coming up
but here we go here are the stories for today rapper Lupe Fiasco thrown off
stage during pre inauguration event after anti Obama rant you see you can't
have an opinion anymore if it's against the state Obama averages 49% approval
rating in the first term some of the lowest approval ratings that we've seen
in history except for perhaps Jimmy Carter CBS News political director Obama
must destroy the Republican Party you see it's all about destroying the
opposition not about helping America it's not about doing what's right it's
not about making America a great nation it's about destroying the Republican
Party and disarming your guns at the same time because of course that's that's
one of the big goals out there remember he gave us a phone and he's gonna do
more alright Condoleezza Rice joins CBS News as a contributor well there we go
go from government you know gun-grabbing government right into the media you'll
fit right in Condoleezza the weekly standard in our inaugural ball ticket
prices slashed by 50% they just couldn't fill the chairs at the Nazi style Fhrer
inauguration kinging of the Emperor with no clothes event that we saw
earlier this morning significantly smaller inaugural crowd expected that's
old news now since that already happened Biden says he's proud to be president
yeah and we're proud to have a person with his level of sanity in the White
House yes we are public inauguration just for show cost taxpayers a hundred
million dollars check it out is this a record guys or what we're just blowing
through this news this has got to be a record I tell you keep score we'll have
a scoreboard back here how much news can we get through establishment media
announces the second coming of Obama oh the Christ the king the Obama heil
heil Obama Barack Obama the Lance Armstrong of politics the federal
government now requires that we ask you the following personal questions this is
from zero hedge and this is whoa whoa what is this if you if we fail to ask
these questions we are subject to I'm sorry I don't understand the context of
this is Obamacare prying into our personal lives even more this is the
danger of getting into the news stack you never know what's in there it's kind
of like Forrest Gump life is like a box of chocolates news is like a box of
randomness Obama I did it as he was sworn in his daughter says good job
daddy the president responded I did it because it's all about him yes no
dignity no philosophy no history no principle no ethics all about Obama he
gave us a phone he's gonna do more Tony Carlucci on prison planet calm the
greatest way to dishonor Martin Luther King is to compare him with US President
Barack Obama I couldn't agree more Martin Luther King a man a man of
substance excuse me a man of substance a man of principle a man who actually stood
for the people versus Barack Obama a deceiver a lying person someone who
knowingly fabricates things and says he won't pass the NDAA and then does says
he's trying to help Americans and then he destroys the American economy destroys
jobs come on there's no comparison and by the way I hope you know that that's
that's proof that it's never about skin color around here it's about principle
as Alex Jones says if there was a black president who protected the Bill of
Rights we would love that guy we would all love that guy where is that guy we
got to find that guy wouldn't that be great
the quote Jamie Foxx how great is that to find a black president that that
supports the Bill of Rights how great is that that's what we need but we haven't
found one yet and we haven't found a white president that supports the Bill
of Rights what am I talking about that would be great too that's Ron Paul you
know how great would that be to have Ron Paul in all right continuing and by the
way John Rappaport will be joining us here in just a couple of minutes I think
I'm finally starting to have fun here today I was I was kind of down in the
first couple of hours not down but but serious you know I usually come in here
more jovial joking around more flippant sorry to use those big words for those
of you who are public school educated like I only the homeschoolers will
understand that I don't have to look it up all right I'm just joking don't take
it all too seriously folks Americans not in labor force has increased eight point
three million eight point three million more Americans jobless under Obama thank
you and he's gonna do more flu season fuels debate over paid sick time laws in
New York they're trying to pass laws that would mandate companies to pay for
for employees to stay home sick that way they're saying well they wouldn't come
to work sick and spread the flu hey once you just give out vitamin D at work it's
like a couple cents a day why don't you just give them some vitamin D and then
they won't miss work and they won't get the flu and they don't even need the
vaccine shot but no that just makes too much sense for America today another
battle over taxes in the Washington Post the economic collapse says the sovereign
debt bubble will continue to expand bang until the system explodes that's the big
that's the big elephant in the room that people aren't talking about it doesn't
matter who's in the White House this system is coming down coming down real
soon and global debt collapse domino effect system leading to I mean isn't
this probably why they're trying to take our guns because they know they're gonna
have to declare martial law in the economic collapse that's what's going on
I mean that's at least a reasonable assessment of what's going a couple more
headlines here Nevada legislator Brooks arrested accused of threatening assembly
leader why okay whatever California's Hispanic population to outnumber whites
by the end of 2013 hey why don't we have a Hispanic president that supports the
Bill of Rights that would be awesome too that would be great I don't care what
skin color you are if you support the Constitution and the Bill of Rights
you're my hero that's all there is to it you could be you could be Asian you can
be Hispanic you can be Norwegian as far as I'm concerned you come here you
become a citizen you qualify correctly not with faked documents now can't have
all those layers in your birth certificate you become president you
support the Constitution you're my hero that's it that's all there is to it
CIA drone strikes will get passed in the counterterrorism playbook officials say
yeah because the rules don't apply to the unmanned drone strikes that are
blowing up little children hmm you want to end violence against children stop
shooting them with missiles just a little bit of logic for those who don't
yet get it fanfight outside Georgia Dome leaves one injured I think he got stabbed
in the neck guess you got a band next there's no end there's no end to it it
gets punched in the face you got a band fist right there band knives TSA toys
with the surfs at Lou Rockwell blog saying it's retiring some of its porno
scanners naked body scanners from the airports but as we talked about earlier
that is a hoax because of being replaced by a millimeter wave scanners just
another way to irradiate your body so that is the blow-through news cycle I
hope we covered some territory for you there now joining us by Skype is John
Rappaport with an update on the psychiatric police state in America let
me give you a bit a bit of background on that the article that I wrote on this is
that psychiatrists are now given judge dread authority to strip citizens of
their constitutional rights just because they say so so John Rappaport wrote one
of the first articles on this about the psychiatric police state in New York and
now joining us is mr. Rappaport from no more fake news calm John any new
developments in this realm of thought crimes in America well the thought crime
aspect is the big one like that you pointed out in your article to me it's
all an extension of all of the surveillance that's been building up
over the last 10-15 years you know we've got the drones we can spy on you you've
got smart appliances in the home that can tell where you are what you're
doing we've got intercepts on all emails phone calls purchases we've got
everybody under surveillance in America the only thing that was missing was what
are you thinking that was the last piece of the puzzle well yeah that piece is
being put into place because the psychiatrists are now the new high-priced
predator drones of thought it's like psychiatric drones but the you know the
real thing about this so if you think about it is that now they can set up a
catch-22 where if you believe in the Constitution you're mentally ill if you
think you need to own a gun there's something wrong with you so now just the
mere expression of wanting to exercise the rights and freedoms that you should
have under a republic gets you diagnosed with a mental illness classic
catch-22 totally you're totally trapped as a patient although why you would want
to see a psychiatrist in the first place is beyond me but yeah but John they're
gonna mandate it that's the thing I mean right now we can say no but soon they're
gonna mandate it well they're definitely gonna try and it's gonna be part of
Obamacare and that they're gonna be many more occasions let's put it this way
where they will be able to order you to a court-ordered psychiatrist for any
reason they want to and then once you're there according to the New York State
law has just been passed if the psychiatrist feels that you represent a
potential harm to yourself or to others he has to report you to law enforcement
at this point if you have a gun they come to your house and they take it
whatever things they take and of course you can't buy another weapon but the
point is who hasn't ever had some kind of thought not an action but a thought a
moment a fleeting moment of anger the ideation of violence against some other
person or some organization you know your boss at work whatever getting to
because the psychiatrist is in charge of making that assessment yeah but I mean
everybody's had some kind of fleeting thought that doesn't make you criminal
saying he just does all right we're gonna go to break we're gonna break it
we'll be right back after this continuing with John Rappaport and the
psychiatric police state in America this is the Alex Jones show infowars.com
stay with us we'll be right back with all that and more calls straight ahead
you land in Buenos Aires then a shuttle to Santa Rosa where a nicely furnished
cabin with all amenities Wi-Fi executive food and wine and laundry service
awaits after a good night's sleep your adventure begins you're on a golden stag
safari for big game but it's not Africa it's Argentina one-on-one guided hunts
for water buffalo, huger, bighorn rams, wild boar and the biggest stag deer in
South America all gold medal quality all the action you can handle land rovers
top rental guns with scopes all food beverages hunting guides ground
transportation included and more all more affordable than you can imagine the
adventure of a lifetime starts at golden stag safaris.com the big game hunting
ranch golden stag safaris.com digestive health is the key to wellness and
elimination of toxins that bears repeating digestive health is the key to
wellness and elimination of toxins and pro em one daily probiotic cleanse is
the key to digestive health pro em one is a powerful liquid probiotic strong
enough to cleanse gentle enough to use every day pro em one is dairy wheat and
soy free contains all-natural and certified organic ingredients contains
no preservatives or animal products supports a healthy digestive and immune
system supports weight loss improves absorption of food nutrients aids in
controlling yeast infections is never freeze-dried and uses three groups of
live viable beneficial microbes to cleanse and remove toxins order pro em
one daily probiotic cleanse at tereganics.com spelled t-e-r-a-g-a-n-i-x.com
tereganics.com or call toll free eight six six three six nine three six seven
eight that's eight six six three six nine three six seven eight pro em one
the raw probiotic hempusa.org has a newly designed website and a new and
improved detoxification product order our new micro plant powder gold loaded
with vitamins minerals iodine and probiotics and we'll send you our travel
size micro plant powder absolutely free micro plant powder only at hempusa.org
call 908 691 2608 that's 908 691 2608 and see what our
powder seeds and oil can do for you only at hempusa.org only this offer ends
January 31st hi this is Ted Anderson have you ever wondered why banks stock
workers investment advisors won't talk about gold IRAs they've been available
since 1986 yet the financial industry won't recognize the value of gold for
your retirement gold is outperform paper investments yet no word about IRAs if
you would like to have gold for your retirement call 800 686 2 2 3 7 don't
get left behind by rising inflation and low returns call 800 686 2 2 3 7 secure
your future and call 1 800 686 2 2 3 7 hello this is Ty Bolinger author of the
best-selling book cancer step outside the box I want you to know some very
important information in 1985 president Ronald Reagan requested that carnivora
be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the president could
obtain this world-class healer now 27 years later carnivore capsules are used
around the world to keep people healthy now you can protect yourself and your
loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that
instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single normal
cell if you want to stay healthy now's your chance to literally wake up your
critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body
call 1 866 Venus fly or order from carnivore calm that's car ni vor a.com
that's 1 866 836 8 7 3 5 1 8 6 6 Venus fly or visit carnivore a.com protect
your immune system it's the only one you've got okay yeah we're back on the
Alex Jones show thank you for continuing with us it's been an interesting show
already and there's more yet yet ahead for us here broadcasting from Austin
Texas this is Mike Adams sitting in for Alex Jones today Alex comes back
sometime today and he'll be here running the show and run his show tomorrow so
I'll be listening in that's the one thing that I don't like about hosting
the show is I don't get to hear Alex do the show I mean I actually like to hear
other people's thoughts on these things and and Alex is great at understanding
the historical context and the angles that you don't normally think of right
away so I was like his analysis I'm sure he's got it I'm surprised he hasn't
called in guys he must be he must be out of cell phone range because he often
calls in with some additional comments in any case we've got John Rapaport
with us right now from no more fake news.com with comments on the
psychiatric police state in America so John it looks like psychiatrists who
were actually part of the problem and their drugs the drugging of children
they're they're perhaps the largest contributing source to the problem now
they're going to be put in control and given more power in reaction to the very
problem they caused the school shootings yeah they're totally off the hook now
nobody is going to take up the question in the official media of all these drugs
that cause people to kill other people like Prozac and Zoloft and so forth
that's all going to go by the wayside completely but let me run down what was
going to happen in the office you see psychiatrists are sitting there the
patient comes in psychiatrist says so what's the problem the patient begins to
talk and the psychiatrist is going to inject at some point and say well what
about your fantasies have you ever had thoughts of say getting revenge well
yeah sure against whom I said well what thoughts did you have well I wanted to
destroy you know well I had a dream what's about destroying the school
where I went you know when I was nine years old I see now at this point you
see you're done because the psychiatrist can now file a report saying potentially
a harm to others is talking about blowing up things and so we need to see
if this guy has a gun and all of a sudden this guy gets a visit at his
house and says what are you talking about I was talking about a dream I had
when I was nine years old we don't care about that get out of the way when it
starts the house and you're on the list and bah bah bah bah bah it's now as you
wrote a thought crime and this is how the psychiatrist brings it out of a
person you could do it I could do it anybody on the street could do it you
just engage in a little chitchat and say have you ever had any you know thoughts
about violence I mean we all have certainly well sure I once wanted to
blow up the planet I remember we were drunk at a party we're talking to all of
a sudden you're done you're a thought criminal huh no more rights yeah that's
it that's that is exactly what it is coming to John Rappaport and you know
the problem with this is that I mean these kids most of the school shooters
right they have been bullied as children I mean many in many of the cases they
were bullied and they go back to the school to take revenge on those who
bullied them powered by the psychiatric drugs that the psychiatrist has given
them so in their minds they do have an anger they do have a revenge but that
alone is not enough to trigger the trigger it's got to be the drugs that
separate them from reality that really makes it go over that takes it beyond
the realm of ideation or imagination into the realm of taking action and at
that point the shooters feel like they're in a in a dream state or a video
game they don't feel like it's real so that's what the drugs do but you know
now go ahead this has been pointed out a conversation that I had some years ago
with dr. Peter Bragan who is the conscience of psychiatry that not only
do these drugs like the SSRI antidepressants and other psychiatric
drugs even like Ritalin or Adderall push kids over the edge into actual homicide
but they can also stimulate as he told me grandiose plans for destruction so
it's just immediate impulse this is let's get to the blueprint blueprint the
drawing board let's paint the scenario here let's work up the whole scene on
how we're going to do this these drugs also promote that kind of behavior in
kids that yeah they feel angry but ordinarily would do nothing absolutely
maybe Eric Holder is on these drugs you know maybe maybe the people in
Washington who are plotting conspiring to overthrow the Bill of Rights and
disarm the American people maybe they're on these drugs I think a lot of them
must be you bet and why don't we know let's have a list what drugs god forbid
the list is going to be incredibly long is Joe Biden on what lists are all what
drug is Joe Biden not on are you kidding me dude that is so far gone
you know president Biden all the people in the House of Representatives in the
Senate what drugs are they on what prescription drugs what drugs everybody
we gotta we gotta go to break John sorry to cut you off we gotta go to break but
good questions what drugs are our politically our elected political
leaders on there there cuz a lot of them are smoking crack I think we'll be right
back on the Alex Jones shows stay with us we're on the march the Empire's on
the run Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
is here the grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality it really says that
the state is God the United States is now recognized globally as one of the
most impressive police states on earth this film conclusively proves the
existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being expanded nationwide this
documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an
all-powerful shadow state police state for chronicles the sickening depth to
which our Republic has fallen prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency
dictatorship body scammers sound can citizens spies stage terror and cameras
on every street corner it's only the beginning of the New World Order's hellish
plan the police state isn't coming it's here secure your copy today info wars
com or see it online in the highest quality at prison planet TV looking back
on 2012 we asked ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters like
Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships
brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost
everything at e foods direct we hear from customers every day that are
fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand after
Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all of the grocery stores
are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my
sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too early than one
day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what
Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or
go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best
tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet
your life on e foods direct if you want an American company with American
products made by Americans here is the cow bend soap company Alex and his staff
have used these pure soap products for years these all-natural soaps are made
from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and
safe see them on the web at five star soap comm or call eight hundred three
four zero seven zero nine one for a free catalog buy the one to two months sample
package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now or say
big with a one to two year supply of soaps or all your cleaning needs this is
an amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way
real soap makes you feel see them on the web at five star soap calm or call
eight hundred three four zero seven zero nine one for a free catalog the Alex
Jones show some people say a man is made out of mud a poor man's made out of
muscle and blood you gotta wonder when has the government ever proposed that a
solution to any problem could be solved by having less government never never
the solution is never less government the solution is never more individual
freedom less intrusion in your lives and now in the wake of the sandy hook
shooting about which there are many many questions including questions about
possible multiple shooters we have the government proposing new new solutions
always involving taking more power away from you and putting it into the hands
of the very people who are causing the very problems under which we are all
suffering and in this case is the psychiatrist and John Rappaport joins
us continuing he's the creator of no more fake news dot-com and to lead off
this section and we will take some calls to this section in the segment John
here's here's what I want to hit you with right now it used to be that
psychiatrists and psychologists were at least they were advocates of the patient
or at least they pretended to be you know they were in your corner they're on
your team trying to help you solve your problems with confidentiality you know
you can tell me anything tell me what's wrong you tell me your greatest fears
your fantasies your challenges will help you solve it that's been that's been the
marketing line of psychiatry and psychology now it's different where
snitches for Obama or stitches for the government whatever you tell us and in
private conversations we're going to fill out a report and send it to the
feds and they're going to use that to take away your rights now they are the
secret police the psychiatrists are secret police snitches for the
unconstitutionally operated federal government is am i am i wrong about that
or is that what it's come to it's absolutely right and the American
Psychiatric Association has just issued a statement applauding the whole move
toward greater gun control so they're patting themselves on the back because
they're saying yeah we like this niche role that we're in now we think it's a
good idea and even the psychiatrists who are less insane than the other
psychiatrists think about what they're going to go through they're sitting
there with a patient who says to them you know I'm very angry at my father I
mean that's a statement that a psychiatrist heard you know maybe
100,000 times in his career but all of a sudden this guy is going to stop and
think hmm what happens if I don't report this patient exactly and then later he
goes out and he kills his father that's exactly it they're going to report every
little thing then to start cover themselves I'm done so I'm going to
report everybody and everything that I possibly can so essentially the only
thing you can say to a psychiatrist now is oh life is great everything's
wonderful everything's fine peachy no problem when and if you're going to say
that why go to a psychiatrist I just want one of those that you've got I mean
I feel great but I think I could feel a little better and I've ripped out Prozac
maybe you could you know write me a script that's all they want to say and
the psychiatrist actually thinks that's great well of course yeah they're good
they're getting the kickbacks and everything dispensing drugs and if they
can shrink an appointment down from a half hour to ten minutes are they going
to run more people through every day yeah you're right nobody's going to want
to say anything but now sure fine no problem but the bigger point here is
that we have ignored we I mean the nation has ignored the problem what
causes the outbursts of violence that result in fatalities of innocent
children psychiatric drugs a culture of violent movies and video games perhaps
plays a role but definitely psychiatric drugs so Obama didn't mention
psychiatric drugs in any of his 23 executive orders psychiatrists are given
more power by any account we're going to have more school shootings because we're
going to have more psychiatrists giving out more drugs to people who refuse to
address the real issues they're having because they don't want to tell the
truth now because the psychiatrist is going to snitch on them no question
about it they're going to be more of these killings and murders because more
of the drugs that cause the killings and murders are going to be dispensed but
here's another factor that shows you where Obama's head is really at if he
really wanted to end gun violence in America he would stand up at the podium
and he'd say look at this map folks this shows you where the gun violence is
taking place in America where the people are being killed in greatest numbers and
who's committing the crimes gangs for example cities these are the facts we
have to face them because my motivation as your president is to end gun violence
and therefore this becomes our new mission did he do anything faintly
vaguely resembling that of course not because it's not gun violence that he
wants to end it's gun ownership that he wants to have a good point yeah and also
your approach is logical you know you you want to look at the causes of the
thing you're trying to stop but you got to understand I know you understand this
but I'm speaking to the listeners Washington doesn't want logic they want
an emotional and invocation of an irrational emotional knee-jerk response
that doesn't stand up in any kind of actual critical thinking they just want
you to react and the reaction is blame an inanimate object blame a gun refuse to
look at the psych drugs that altered the mind that pulled the trigger that shot
the child you know you it's like you're asking you're asking people to think and
in America today that's too much apparently at least on the on the
radical left you can't ask them to think they're not supposed to think they're
supposed to react they're supposed to leap to conclusions and they're supposed
to worship their king Obama who's gonna do more and it's all for the children
keep that of course yeah high-fiving the kids even though these drugs that are
going to be dispensed in greater numbers than ever the psychiatric drugs that
cause violence and murder are going to result in more children being murdered
that's not part of the argument that's not something we think about that's too
logical we can't approach that what we just have to keep saying is it's all for
the Sandy Hook children that's why we're taking everybody's guns it's totally
irrelevant doesn't make any sense but that's the emotion of the moment yeah
and look at Obama's logic he said if we can save one child's life then I think
he said something like we owe it to ourselves to try what he means is any
any cost in society is worth reducing one death well by that logic we should
ban all swimming pools ban all trampolines ban all automobiles in fact
you should ban being born yes I guess they do with all their abortions but
they should ban childbirth because that can result in a child dying so therefore
ban childbirth that's Obama's logic ban thought ban all thought because
obviously thought precedes action and some actions result in harm so let's
have a drug that the psychiatrist can give us that will stop people from
thinking all together and then that will be the final solution we just have
zombies around the landscape and everything is wonderful yeah what is
something's drugs called guys throughout a sci-fi movies there have been lots of
different names and and and fiction also different names for these drugs that
that quote normalize the range of human emotions and thought I like the movie
the island with Ewan McGregor that's a great film to review right now because
of the medical police state that were under and I believe they were all on
drugs there and that in that movie as well and give it a false reality to tell
them a fairy tale so that they wouldn't resist and that's what we're seeing
right now with sandy hook also speaking of that John I want to take a call from
Robert in Georgia who apparently has comments on sandy hook of the Second
Amendment so Robert in Georgia you're on the air go ahead sir awesome thank you
very much for taking the call and I've got a lot of my heart the floppiness I
mean I thought I was living about 9-eleven and here you have sandy hook
and not one person down there not one child died I've been researching it it
is anybody died down there if you continue looking at the research and how
they've done all that they don't nobody's died they're actors I'm not
kidding you they are actors down there and this is the worst one I've seen it's
just let me stop you for a second so I just want to make sure understand your
position so you're saying that there were no children died at all in sandy
hook no sir I've been honest for hours on the end and then people were actors
and you can go down there we need to get a phone number going down there to
Connecticut and Sandy Hook and start calling them police officers well no I
look look I I want to say I agree that there are a lot of questions about
sandy hook and John I want your comments on this as well they haven't shown the
video footage for example I'm convinced that there was no ar-15 used in the
shooting whatsoever I I haven't perhaps investigated as much as you have caller
but I'm very skeptical of the idea that nobody died there but I but it's a good
question to raise we should always ask questions so John what are your thoughts
on that on that scenario that the caller is explaining well I just wrote an
article about this this morning but you know these people have unearthed
tremendously interesting video clips of interviews with survivors at Sandy Hook
and they look like actors some of them I've seen right yeah you place on it
yeah is is a that's under question but there's no question that what we're
looking at here are people who have been in one way or another programmed out of
being able to feel genuine human emotion in the midst of a horrendous tragedy
let me go back to the caller because I Robert what what in your mind is the
best evidence that exists today that that as you say no one was killed there
okay Robbie Parker and for one when the news channel does it they use your
proper name Robert my name's Robert my family used to call me Robbie for him
to call this fellow Robbie Parker and not use his real name and he's laughing
and cutting up and then you know if you haven't seen it yet I've seen it yeah
it's said in all of the interviews there is no remorse and one thing here I want
to really stress is that truth is not threatened by a lie but a lie is
threatened by the truth and I hope that they're just getting so sloppy on this
it's gonna be exposed people if I was living about 9-11 this is literally sick
and I was in surgery that day that morning on the 14th I was going to
surgery and it started all happening and I could tell it right from there things
were really bad I wish I lived in that area so I could ask people I know I mean
I mean caller in one sense you're right that we can never really know what is
theater could they stage something like that with all actors theoretically
possibly but there it seems like there must be real people out there who lost
real children or maybe I don't know maybe I'm still being suckered in I John
your thoughts I mean how do you know what's true that's the bottom line well
this is the point because everything comes through television right how do we
know there are only certain people that are going to be interviewed for example
anybody any parent who is outraged angry about the investigation who wants to get
to the bottom of it who is close to being actually catatonic because they
have lost a child who was really killed who is incredibly angry at the press for
trying to approach them for an interview in the wake of the death of their
children none of these people are going to be interviewed on television you're
not going to see that and so right but we see is this section of people that
appropriate for the scenario that's being created by the major media that
is independent of what actually happened there in Sandy Hook and so we get this
entirely insane picture of who these people in Sandy Hook are and plus we've
got all the tie-ins with actual fiction theater you know the Batman movie the
Sandy Hook on the map with the strike zone circled right around it it actually
looks like the school on the map in Batman and you know I'm not saying okay
maybe it could be coincidence but you get enough of these and it starts to
become very suspicious and that's that's where I am on this folks is asking
questions I haven't reached all the conclusions or anything but asking
intelligent questions is what we're supposed to do members of the press are
supposed to ask questions but we've got CNN and others just actually just shoving
ideas down your mind without asking any questions that's what I'm that's what I
have trouble with there's a difference between a staged event that actually
happens you know people are killed but the perpetrator is not the person that
is blamed by law enforcement in the media that's a whole scenario that I've
explored in depth that Lanza was not actually the shooter he was a patsy then
you have the idea that nothing happened at all that the whole thing was a
gigantic hoax and nobody died for which I would see personally no real motive if
people would go that far in staging an event they would have no compunction
about actually killing people right adults whatever well it's like the I
think Larry Pratt said this if they would stage Fast and Furious they would
stage anything but for example in the the Gabrielle Giffords shooting in in
Arizona I was able to actually make a phone call to a close personal friend of
of Gabby and to verify sort of what went on I actually was a distant friend of
Gabby she was a wonderful woman by the way just just a wonderful representative
for the people there even though she was in the Democratic Party she was just a
very wonderful person and so I you know I'm convinced that you know that
shooting took place there's no question about it the question is what what
caused that shooting but in Sandy Hook we don't have one well-known person that
we can call and confirm I mean it there are way too many questions that we can't
confirm it and I personally don't know anybody in that area to confirm it maybe
I don't know maybe somebody can call in and and phone lines are open 1-800-259-9231
if you've got proof one way or another or the other on Sandy Hook how about
that let's put that out there and we'll jump to your calls first fair enough
sound good John sure all right cuz I know you want to get to the bottom of
this too but yeah absolutely I mean look I've looked into Robbie Parker to the
degree that there are articles about him in Utah newspapers like the Deseret News
that he wants his family is from there that he had a family that this guy is
not just some actor that they brought in from you know the sky to portray
somebody that doesn't exist at all right so you know got to think about this
if you had a group of 15 or 20 or 50 or 75 actors that were brought in to stage
a complete hoax don't you think that somebody out there in the world who
actually knows one of these people and said hey you see that guy who's supposed
to be a fireman or a cop or a parent that's Marty don't you remember Marty we
went to school together I gotta put up a YouTube about Marty this is ridiculous
don't you think that would have proliferated by now unless somebody's
going to say no these hundred people were you know kidnapped 50 years ago or
20 years ago and they were raised you know they're raising a psych ward no I
look I I suspect I suspect the real story here is kids were killed but they
were killed by multiple shooters who were put up to this and that's why they
they killed Adam Lanza at the end so he couldn't talk that's what I suspect very
similar to Aurora because I know you know a lot about guns I mean for a while
there and I still think they're saying that Lanza killed himself with a
rifle well yeah you can do that yeah is that an easy thing to do is to turn a
rifle around on yourself well I mean the other kids did it in the what the zero
day shooting they did that right on camera in a school they put the rifles
on the you know the butt stocks of the rifles on the ground vertically and then
they just put their chins over the rifles and and or a shotgun in one case
I think and pulled the trigger so yeah they kids know how to do that I mean if
they're violent like that psychotic kids then they can do that well I agree with
you I think so far from everything that I've seen this kid was a patsy and there
were professionals who did the job and that opens the issue up completely to
the whole aftermath which is grab the guns yeah yeah clearly that it whether
it was real or or or staged the issue is that it was a justification to take the
guns and that makes no sense now I want to go to some more callers after this
break that's coming up here so William and Cindy and can stay on the line there
we'll get to you right after this break that is coming up shortly and John
Rappaport of course continues to join us from no more fake news.com what are we
doing here we're asking questions about Sandy Hook and if asking questions is
bad then America is lost okay this is the job of the media CNN should be
asking questions instead of towing the party line all right the mainstream
media should be asking questions instead of leaping to wrong conclusions let's
ask questions and find out what really happened a lot more straight ahead stay
with us food stores check survival tools check weapons and water filters check
but what about a permanent source of cooking power that can run forever
without buying fuel or paying for maintenance introducing afterburner
stoves home of the original patented rocket stove the Kelly kettle and the
solo stove afterburner stoves has what you need and now offers all GCN
listeners our complete preparedness package with the means to cook meals and
sanitize water whether you dig in or bug out cook almost any meal with just a
handful of sticks we already have the lowest online prices guaranteed but if
you enter coupon code GCN at checkout we'll knock off an additional 15% and
send you our amazing six hours solar rechargeable light bulb absolutely free
all for only two hundred and forty nine dollars visit afterburner stoves calm or
call eight six six seven one six five two one four eight six six seven one six
five two one four afterburner stoves calm cook hot meals with just a handful
of sticks hi there my name is Frank Bates what I'm about to tell you in the
next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble I just created a free video
presentation at one two three cover-up calm that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are incompetent line
crooks that are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power
bills criminally high some have called this a conspiracy others have called it
a cover-up and you will be shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy goes my
video at one two three cover-up calm exposes the truth and shows you the
secret of how I beat them and how you can beat them to watch the controversial
video that thousands of other smart Patriots have already seen in the last
three months go to one two three cover-up calm and discover one weird
trick to slash your power bill and protect your home go watch my video now
at one two three cover-up calm before they force me to shut it down again
that's one two three cover-up calm we all know that Berkey water purification
systems are the most trusted name in water filtration as an authorized Berkey
dealer for over six years in serving thousands of satisfied customers the
Berkey guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration systems the
Berkey light systems include a set of self sterilizing and re cleanable black
purification elements that purify water by removing chlorine pathogenic bacteria
cysts and parasites to non detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such
as herbicides and pesticides order the Berkey light system today complete with
two black Berkey elements for only two hundred and thirty one dollars and the
Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge with the purchase of a Berkey
light the Berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride and arsenic filters for
only $39.99 that's over 30% off the retail price call the Berkey guy at one
eight seven seven eight eight six three six five three that's one eight seven
seven eight eight six three six five three or order online at go Berkey calm
that's go Berkey calm today he's the t-rex of political talk Alex Jones on the
GCN radio network
in regards to that last call I think we have to be very cautious if we are to
have any credibility whatsoever in questioning the official story of events
like Sandy Hook we've got to be careful and I am that caller probably have good
intention and maybe he knows more about it than I do I'm not sure but we have to
be careful not to leap one bridge too far so to speak otherwise we all get
painted as as as complete loons we have to ask good questions look for what we
can actually substantiate where is their video evidence for example with the ar-15
rifle not being used in the shooting there's they haven't released any video
footage why wouldn't they release video footage if the kid was carrying an ar-15
around shooting kids they would love to release that footage so we can say
logically and rationally as skeptical journalists the fact that they haven't
released that footage probably means they don't have it that's a rational
thing but we got to be careful not to go too far and there's there are also
agents of disinfo out there that try to get us to go one step too far to make us
look stupid I'm not saying that was that caller that caller sounds like he was he
was informed in his research and was putting forth what he believes but we
just have to be cautious is all I'm saying let's go with what we actually
have evidence for and not allow anyone to pull us one step too far down the
road of of things that didn't really necessarily happen so so John what are
your thoughts on that I mean can't we there's a lot that we could actually
like on 9-eleven there's so much evidence that building 7 was taken down
intentionally not hit by an airplane and so on on all these issues there's a lot
of evidence for us to stand with right huge amount of evidence and to go back
to something you said before the break these the reason people think oh these
are crazy questions is because they can condition to the media that never asks
these questions should be asking the questions I mean what we're talking
about here is what CNN and Fox and NBC ABC CBS should be doing all the time
yeah they should be saying how did the kid get in the school okay which we want
to know we don't want just some little brush off here I mean you have a fairly
heavy door there did you what kind of glass was there did he talk over video
they have a video system he's not supposed to get in unless he identifies
himself he's wearing all these weapons and so forth somebody let him in let's
dig into this let's not stop let's be relentless until we get the answers all
right let's dig into this the way the media used to dig into Nixon during
Nixon administration Washington Post you bet absolutely you see so now people say
well the people that ask these kinds of questions are crazy because people are
hypnotized into believing everything the police says is true oh I know that's the
danger that's the danger of where we are is that you're considered crazy if you
even behave like a responsible intelligent journalist I mean journalism
has become a joke in this nation because the people working for CNN for example
refuse to ask real questions I heard a press conference three minutes outside
chief of police at Sandy Hook and the reporters started asking questions about
the guns what was the gun found in the trunk again was it the bushmaster was
it the thing was that and was it two handguns that he had and so forth and
the police chief danced around that the reporters were starting to zero in and
on the fact that there were contradictory stories and then they all
backed away like it was a time for a picnic let's go to a picnic whatever the
chief says okay forget about it there was nothing left it was all a travesty
crazy go where and then they stopped all right well look we're gonna go into
overdrive here today on the broadcast on the Alex Jones show and the callers
please stay on the line I promise I'm gonna go to you right after this roughly
one minute break William Stephen and others we are going to go to your calls
after we come back and we'll go into overdrive and John please stay with us
but for those of you who who joined us today I thank you for joining us thank
you for your support keep asking intelligent questions okay right is on
our side we have the ethics we have the morals we have the Constitution we will
not be defeated take care thank you for listening to GCN visit GCN live calm
today millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and
other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural
silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution
recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that
can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help
improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every
day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as
strep staph pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens this new
technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at
several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions
the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook
coast to coast direct from Austin you're listening to the Alex Jones broadcasting
network network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones all right we're gonna take as many calls as we can in the next five
minutes during this overdrive segment let's go to Greg in Utah Greg welcome to
the show what's on your mind yeah I'm your only Utah affiliate here by the way
all right anyway I had a conversation with Richard Max on a Richard Mack on
another program here and it was a good conversation and people are always
wondering you know we got all this talk radio we got all you know all the news
and it just keeps getting hash and rehash there's got to be some solutions
well he talked about a solution a solution that everybody can do I don't
just mean going around buying guns like that has been going on I mean what
people need to do is they need to contact their sheriff and say hey look
we're gonna put something together this is going to be made public how do you
stand on a Second Amendment are you going to keep these people from you know
are you gonna protect our rights we elected you for this it's gonna be made
public let them know it's gonna be made public I mean I've fortunately I've got
the use of the radio station here but others have like yourself have the
opportunity to put it out on on their web page you know there's a site well
that's good to hold them accountable right now see where they stand absolutely
because these are elected officials yes and if they don't if people don't like
what they're hearing they're out of there so but in my conversation for
instance here in Millard County Utah the sheriff made the cost of the comment
that he wasn't a constitutional sheriff I want clarification but he was not a
constitutional sheriff yeah what does that mean exactly are you not willing to
uphold a Second Amendment or any of the Constitution I want clarification I know
there's sheriff's out there calling themselves constitutional sheriff's
they're involved in and they're in keeping their else I we want to know you
know all right and that's gonna make it public yeah well well said Greg a good
luck to you out there in Utah great great suggestion let's do that let's do
that all across the nation call your local sheriff find out where they stand
on the Constitution if they're not constitutional sheriff's then they then
they're in violation of their own oaths of office they should be kicked out
immediately but let's let's take some more calls I want to get John's comment
on this as well William in Connecticut William thank you for holding in and
welcome to the show thank you very much well there's a lot of information that
is not made public and that lead us to speculate in foreign theories I'm calling
because I have information that I believe is legit Adam Lancer he told his
mom that if he she put him in a special school his he was going to kill her in
her sleep and he did he there's also suppose there's supposed to be a video
about Adam Lancer going to the high school first but because he saw a
patrol car outside he moved into the little school to the other school so I
don't know why they are not saying that
well wasn't John go ahead that said that Lancer had threatened his mother or he
was very angry at her because she was going to have him institutionalized and
that was at one point given as a motive for the killing but then later on
questions were raised whether or not that actually ever happened that turned
out to be as I recall somebody's opinion rather than a direct observation of what
the mother was threatening to do and Adams reaction to that so all right good
I don't know about that good good call though thank you call let's go to one
more call can in Texas you're on the air you got about 30 seconds go ahead sir
I lost it are you there Ken all right Ken let's go to Cindy in Oregon Cindy
real quick just a few seconds my hi hi Mike thanks for taking my call I'm gonna
make this quick it's not specifically about Sandy Hook but I did want to make
a comment on the second amendment I want to bring something to you in Alex's
listeners attention that I and many others know is very important is
actually many people feel it's actually grossly underreported right hurry up
it's not the best by Alex okay it is an article January 21st 2013 and
godfather politics by Ted Krahn called the Vatican Vatican wrongly supports
Obama's gun glass all right that's all we have time for you have to search that
folks thanks for joining us this is Mike Adams here on the Alex Jones show Alex
is back tomorrow