We've got it
Waging war on corruption
It's Alex Jones coming to you live from the front lines of the info war
It's the day of the big game
And during the big game Super Bowl 2013
From the season of 2012
technically Super Bowl 2012
We are going to be brainwashed by ads against the Second Amendment
Financed by the globalists and other collaborators against our liberty and the
exploited
children of Sandy Hook survivors with their choir
to tear-jerk and demonize the Second Amendment
Unbelievably
opportunistic and disgusting but
Don't ever expect the criminals that run this system to not be opportunistic and over-the-top. They think you are stupid
They think you are utterly
And totally mindless they think there's nothing you won't buy
We're gonna be going over the latest on the Second Amendment today
but there is an article out of Forbes that's excellent that we have linked up at infowars.com and
prisonplanet.com
It's also I found it at drudgereport.com on the left-hand side
NRA winning the influence battle over gun control
And I don't just believe polls when I hear them or see them. I've studied polls. I've studied statistics
I've studied how they work and I'm able to gauge polls over a long period of time from what I read in quasi
internal government white papers
plus what I see on the streets and
This told me what I already knew they went to one of the biggest and most respected data mining companies
And that's really the polling agency of the future and found that it is a total route of
the anti-gunners the victim disarmament
a kleptocratic crowd that wants to disarm their quarry
In fact, they find with military precision
organically
individual gun owners
supported through the
NRA that we've taken control of it was under globalist control about 20 years ago
There's there's no doubt and Larry Pratt agrees with me that that with laser
Military laser like focus is the quote that we are
Annihilating the enemy now that that that's a big plush
And it's because we realize they're an enemy a deceptive group who don't want to take guns to keep kids safe
Don't want to register guns to actually stop criminals. They want to target the American people
We've seen them take the guns in any city the global is during control of we've seen them
Disarmed people in more than 30-something nations the last 50 years or so. We know their game plan. We know their program
we know how it works and
Because we're one of the last countries to hold out like Switzerland
We've we've gotten to have front-row seats to all the tricks and the globalist are global
They run the same program the same plays they switch them up a little bit
But it's basically the same playbook in country after country
They try to take over and not just on guns when they go for the guns
it means they're insecure and they're afraid and politically that they're not going to get away what they've done and
And it means they want to use authoritarianism on the public now that said we're gonna be getting into that
We're gonna be getting into an amazing report up at infowars.com
That ties into like seven other links just to the article that Kurt Nemo did
And I was even able to find some more we're gonna play some of these clips coming up
Reverend Jesse Jackson
To rip off Rush Limbaugh's
He says it but well, that's how Reverend Jackson always says it the Reverend Jesse Jackson
says gun supporters are
Domestic terrorist. I shouldn't laugh
There was a video saying on the on the comments at info wars calm right for Showtime like 10 minutes for air
I laugh so hard. I could hardly go on air
You ever laugh so hard it makes you start coughing and you can't quit
It said Jesse Jackson responds to infowars.com and I thought well
Let me put that we put that YouTube URL in and it was chunk from the goonies
And then I realized that actually
There is a resemblance to Jesse Jackson. I couldn't believe that. Oh
Oh my gosh, he's the black chunk. Sorry. We're gonna be right back. Stay with us.
You prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms
But if you don't have a home security system
Then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when you're sleeping or away from home
Who's watching out for intruders? Check out simply safe
It's a new do-it-yourself home security system that is completely wireless go to get simply safe calm
Simply safe is independent and off the grid. It runs on battery power. So even if the grid goes down you are protected
It's completely customizable so you can use it in your home business boat trailer storage unit or shed get simply safe calm
Simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes
So there's no need to let a stranger into your home
If you move or need to relocate you can take the system with you wherever you go
You aren't always at home, but simply safe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days a week
Again, that's get simply safe calm
Crashing through the lies and disinformation, it's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network
Nobody rides for free
The globalists are not going to make our servicemen women mainly men
Serve two three four five six seven eight nine tours in the last 12 years and not have massive
suicides
massive
Mental problems massive health problems as well
Did you know that they make US military personnel?
You can look this up go into combat and force them back into combat when they've had legs blown off
Oh, you didn't know that. Thank you for joining us. Ladies and gentlemen, it is
Sunday Sunday the third day of February
2013 I am Alex Jones your syndicated radio talk show host and I am very very thankful that you have joined us today
Wow where to begin number one, there's new numbers out new numbers out 22
Servicemen and women commit suicide every single day
That is more than seven times the previous record from the end of the Vietnam War in
1973 74 75 when they had bad suicides that is
22 military veterans commit suicide
Every day and I want you to know they're gonna talk about the veterans and talk about how great they are and talk about how
They love them and and try to connect the veterans and their valor and their their heroism in many cases
to the
Establishment and the criminals that run our government from both political parties and the whole police state
They're setting up and even though a lot of these wars have been fraudulent and wrong and have been done for globalist interest
Still the men and women of the military that I've met that I know that I've talked to that I've researched
they are the most focused awake people out there and
They joined because they wanted to defend this republic and I am sick of all the fake
Patriotism of oh, thank you for your service to the you know to the country and then okay. Well, can I have a job?
Oh, I gotta go. I gotta go. There is a demonization program going on behind the scenes against veterans
that's now busting out into the surface and
There is a public cover that all the government and the media and the system loves veterans
There's a lot of charities out there that have been caught raising money for veterans. It really doesn't go to the veterans
And so I just wanted to mention up front today that we're gonna see lots of stuff tonight at the Super Bowl
Connecting football and mom and apple pie, you know to the veterans and in and trying to make the political system look good
They want you to have the memory of America and the Republic and the Bill of Rights and Constitution that our troops reportedly
protect
While they dismantle the entire thing in the background
While they go to combat ground robots, not just drones in the air
Humans, the globalists believe the ruling technocratic class are obsolete
We are not obsolete. The tyrants are obsolete the old
oligarchical systems of control that have pledged humanity in every civilization and every culture for more than 6,000 years are
obsolete we either end this this system of dumbing down the public and
Of playing grips off against each other and balkanization in divide and conquer or humanity isn't going to make it
All right. We've got a big broadcast lined up for you again
I'm live here on the all-holy day of Super Bowl Super Bowl Sunday, and I'm here because
Football is not America football is not freedom football is a game that has been turned into nothing
But a giant propaganda arm of the globalist and you're going to see ads paid for by the billionaire Bloomberg
Who got his money from insider operations on the stock exchange?
The gangsters got armed guards and helicopters and the rest of it who flies above us
He is sponsoring. He's the main guy giving money to mayors against gun violence like the guns did it themselves
And we're gonna play this ad coming up. He's running an ad there's other ads and they're and they're trying to get donations
Out there to create an anti-gun anti-second amendment move across the country. They're gonna have
The little children of Sandy Hook from the choir are being exploited by the globalist mafia
They're gonna be singing during the halftime
This is this is something I personally
personally and boycotting our country's in deep trouble folks and
I hear all these other talk show hosts about man the good thing about being America's Super Bowl
I'm gonna savor this big game. I'm gonna I want my Bill of Rights and Constitution. I want my factories back
I want my jobs back. I don't want the government shutting down our power plants while China builds three new ones a week
I think going into depression is a bad thing. I'm not watching games. I'm defending my
Constitutional Republic on this Sunday broadcast and I'm not I don't need to be thanked for coming in on a Sunday
It's an honor to be here
It's an honor to be on the radio six days a week broadcasting all over the world warning not just the United States
But the planet about the global private crime syndicate known as the New World Order
Okay
Let me stop right there and tell you what's coming up on the Second Amendment front today
Not just the Super Bowl being turned into a giant anti-gun extravaganza anti-liberty extravaganza
So Reverend Jesse Jackson says gun supporters are domestic terrorists. The video is up there
He told the Wall Street Journal this
Four days ago and it made it into two newspapers
about Jesse Jackson on gun violence and economic summit
And the big bombshell is he says we're gonna have to have reconstruction we're gonna have to have the North take over the South
Gun owners are racist. They're the new they're the new
What do you call it a confederacy and gay and again, that's a talking point
I got a bunch of clips
We're gonna play right now and then coming into the next segment where on all these different shows you've seen it
You've read it race has nothing to do with it
And they're just injecting this to create division it is
unprecedented and
You've got Bob Schaeffer on CBS saying we defeated Hitler and the Nazis we can defeat gun owners
We can take their guns on CBS
He said the president defeated Hitler or the Nazis know our grandparents and great-grandparents did
Just amazing. We've got other clips of Fox Sports saying look, you know, the NRA gun owners of the Ku Klux Klan
We've got Jesse Jackson saying
And then meanwhile, I see this every few days now. This is just from a few days ago
MSNBC has host on mainly white house saying oh the racist crackers need to give their guns up
Yeah, the Republicans are all just racist crackers
I'd be like using the n-word talk about black people and it's meant to fire up racial division
In this country and then politically correct groups can slam
Anybody that says hey, I don't like you, you know trying to put me down and everybody else will just through guilt
Basically submit to that so that's coming up
also, Chris Kyle
the
Sniper the Navy SEAL sniper was gunned down yesterday up outside, Dallas
With with the head of his foundation and a PTSD marine they reportedly taken out there. He's been arrested there
They've charged him today
And they're saying that this individual and I'll give you his name
This individual who had PTSD and was under psychiatric care Eddie Ray Roth
Is the main suspect in the killing as a three million dollar bond?
Now again, you have 22 service people killing themselves a day
And that's why I brought that up and then every couple of weeks
You'll hear about a service person killing their wife or their boss or something
statistically out of
300 and it's now 20 million people. I mean statistically we've shown the statistics FBI gov
Mass shootings are 88 a year
88 people about half those gang related
Veterans killing people is not even a thousand a year sounds like a big number
But it's not even the top hundred causes of death in this country
But the media creates this illusion and I remember seeing these Homeland Security reports four years ago
When Obama got in suddenly saying veterans gun owners conservatives libertarians, they're the terrorists
They're gonna attack veterans will use IEDs at every city to bomb police departments
Remember that they were given the cops the training and I thought well that doesn't make sense
Sure, you've got troops committing suicide. You've got them putting them on psychotropics that say on the insert
They can make you commit suicide or go on a psychotic rampage
that's there but still those numbers won't be high enough to
The point is they're going to initiate and stage events. I've been saying that I'm not saying this is staged, but it fits the mo
with the psych
Psychotropically hopped up mind control subjects to start this stuff and look who it is. It's Chris Kyle
We're gonna break that down as well all this and more coming up today. I'm Alex Jones info Wars dot-coms the new site
Introducing pro one all of your filtration in one system portable on the go no more
Do you have two or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride?
You have a system that cuts out the sodium fluoride and up to 95% of hydrofluorosolic acid advanced
manufacturing technology combines silver impregnated white ceramic with new
Aquametics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals all in one filter element
It is the only one that does it and out of the gates
We have a discounted at 10% off with promo code water
This is the only system that in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides
herbicides
chloramines ammonia and chlorine
Hydrofluorosolic acid the most common form of fluoride not covered by other fluoride filter brands and sodium hexafluorosilicate
Get your pro pure with the new pro 1 filters today at info war store comm or by calling 888
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans here is the cow Ben soap company
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and safe
See them on the web at five star soap comm or call 800
340 7091 for a free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as
What you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs
This is an amazing deal
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
See them on the web at five star soap comm or call 800 340
7091 for a free catalog
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers the prognosis for the entire
Planetary economic system runs from bad to worse the globalist model is to shut down
Societies and starve Patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at info wars shop calm
These are items that I did research on but I personally use you've got the life straw
So you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go the K tour hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power
Outages are out in the field strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein
They're a safe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event and crank shortwave AM FM radios
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at info war shop calm and your purchase makes our info war
Possible we're getting prepared. Are you info wars shop calm?
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses
Don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial solution
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria
Bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing
Supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep staph
Pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful
bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or
Ionic silver solutions the science digest journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off that's
supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook
You coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network
Crashing through the lies and
Disinformation it's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network
All right, we are back live here. I'm gonna race through the key developments in the battle
that's happening right now for the Second Amendment, and we're winning the
War right now, but that doesn't mean we'll continue to win unless we continue to fight and Forbes is a big article
Where they contracted a large data mining firm?
It's actually tracking what you're saying not just what fake polls are putting out and they find that we are routing them on the Second
Amendment, but we were routing them on Obamacare and
The fact that it was written by the insurance companies as a forced corporate tax to rip people off and would double premiums the first
Year, that's this year. It's now happening
and have the average family yearly premium be
$20,000 a year by
2016 that's now official, but it doesn't matter they got it in place
They're gonna ram it down your throat just because we're winning the fight for hearts and minds doesn't mean we're winning
We have to go a step further night
I'm going to get to that Forbes article coming up in our a winning the influence battle over gun control
I'm gonna explain how most of these big polls are fake now. You can tell them a poll is accurate or not
Okay, let's just stop right there
Again up at info wars calm and our other sister site prison planet calm
Reverend Jesse Jackson says gun supporters are
domestic terrorists and the full interview and video
Is up there, but first I wanted to play some other clips
Here is Jason Whitlock of Fox Sports
Elaborating on how he believes the NRA that means gun owners. It's never the Second Amendment
Does it have to talk about that? It's the NRA
It's never we the people that's the NRA speaks for us, and they're the new KKK
Nothing racially involved the NRA shut up to train at the end of the Civil War
Northern recruits and soldiers how to shoot
Including blacks has nothing to do with the KKK never has the KKK in the south
Got the first gun control laws passed in
1868 because they didn't want blacks who were newly freed to get guns the truth is the anti-gunners have the KKK history, but
It's just amazing
It's just it's just so incredible. Let's go to that Club
I did not go as far as I would like to go because my thoughts on the NRA
And America's gun culture. I believe the NRA is the new KKK and that the the arming of so many black youth
and
Blowing up our communities with drugs, and then just having an open shooting gallery is the work of people that you know
Obviously don't have our best interests. You know what's funny, and you know what's funny
It drugs in this country when they started crimped
Making me legal in the 30s the first places it was kind of left alone was the lower income areas
So in a way what this guy's actually saying is true
That the drugs were allowed in the minority communities and because it was a pretext to you know basically get control of those communities
But that's corrupt mafias
Knowing they could operate somewhere because others would say not in my backyard
They always try to build the chemical plant in the poor neighborhood
They always try to I mean it didn't matter if it's India and all it is is Indians living there
They go put the chemical plant in the poor neighborhood
Thought about race so much as it is about not in my backyard of the rich people
But just injecting the NRA is the new
KKK
No, sir the people in New York and Chicago in the last 55 60 years that took all the guns out of your cities
So that only criminals have them so you have the highest crime rates in the world in places like Chicago and New York
Chicago's number one
That's what allowed this culture and MTV promoting gangster rap and cop killer rap
Where I just saw some other famous rappers just shot each other last week. I mean I mean, it's crazy
That's that's that's black rappers putting that out and then the media and Sumner Redstone putting it out via Viacom and
MTV
That's not my fault. I don't want you to die. I'm sick and tired of hearing because I'm white
I inherently don't like you now a lot of whites who weren't racist hear all this and go well
you know what I don't like you either, but you know what I'm not gonna stoop to the level of Jesse Jackson and
People like the individual Jason Whitlock
I mean these people are a joke and they're they're the racist it's clear
And it's how they sit there and are in our in our identity politic people
And notice they always tell whites and conservatives don't be identity politic. You know why they say that because that's effective
It's effective, but see I don't want to just be some gang
I want people to identify with the Bill of Rights and Constitution and
Declaration of Independence and freedom and all men are created equal endowed by their Creator an
idea our founders had that didn't even get expressed to the last few decades I
Have a dream that will judge people by the character of their deeds
The content of what they stand for not off what color they are
but let me tell you something the Democratic Party is now the party of institutional racism and aggression and
It's disgusting. Let's go ahead and go to another clip. Here's Jesse Jackson bumbling around, but if you listen to it. He implies that
States rights movement, it's inherently racist
It's the new Confederacy
Well, what do you call it when the federal government's run by foreign banks?
Overturning the entire Bill of Rights Constitution the states are supposed to step in with a check and a balance. That's the
Three branches of government and then those two are splitting the two again
Just like the legislative split in two. It's meant so you don't get a dictator, but oh no. It's just racist
You're Jesse Jackson these weapons. We're not talking about guns for your house and guns for hunting these military pause
It's always the same script back it up, please
I'm not about guns for your house guns for hunting
Chicago New York and a bunch of other cities where these people run things with a globalist liberal socialist collectivist authoritarians
they're not really liberals where they run things they take all the guns and then people like
Jesse Jackson has bodyguards and a concealed carry and Diane Feinstein does and Bloomberg does and and and Michael Moore has guns and bodyguards
Charlie Sheen who I know well for seven years you'll probably stay at this house 20 times
You know he's like well. I got bodyguards, so nobody needs guns
Hey, Charlie, and I told him this not everybody makes three million dollars a week like you, bro
It's all about oh we feel sorry for the kids
Let's turn the guns in just as a sign
We're sad for him the globalist we should be mad at the globalist the PR
propaganda is using the dead kids to go after our guns
Again here is Jesse Jackson. Oh, we don't want your guns
Which is not for hunting the Second Amendment in for that you know it's a script folks. He knows that
He's following a script. They want the government to be able to totally take over while it arms of the teeth against us
Let's go back to that clip here it is
I'm not the hot guy's house who killed the people at Aurora. He was right near the airport
Runway he could blow up airplanes with that stuff
Well, we're waiting for that. That's like the next step these anti-american people. We're really arming
To stop the government from taking our taken they're fighting the government. This is a confederate ideology. This is like serious
So with power to do something about how they feel
And it's places like Chicago. We need Homeland Security not just the local police
Local police if this is Chicago
And this is Chuck's gun shop right here have all guns are killed put the last five years come from this gun shop
Thinking to them and look at it
They know they know what if this is Iraq. You know the guns are made
We're gonna go to break come back with the rest of it
I got a bunch of other clips where MSNBC's Finney says you know it's the crackers everything's their fault white people
Evil flows from white people I mean the ultimate bigotry unit just like the Nazis saying evil flows from the Jews
But it's okay because it's the Democratic Party run by foreign banks who want to get a race war going in this country
That's their goal. There ain't no doubt. We'll be right back these people are terrorists
Prison planet TV
Tyranny is here the grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality
It really says that the state is God the United States is now recognized
Globally is one of the most impressive police states on earth this film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps
Now being expanded nationwide this documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all-powerful shadow state
Police state for chronicles the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship body scanners sound cameras citizen spies
And stage terror and cameras on every street corner
It's only the beginning of the New World Order's hellish plan the police state isn't coming
It's here secure your copy today at info wars calm or see it online in the highest quality at prison planet TV
Introducing pro one all of your filtration in one system portable on the go no more
Do you have two or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride?
Do you have a system that cuts out the sodium fluoride and up to 95% of hydrofluorosolic acid advanced manufacturing?
Technology combines silver impregnated white ceramic with new
Aquametics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals all in one filter element
It is the only one that does it and out of the gates
We have a discounted at 10% off with promo code water
This is the only system that in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides
herbicides
chloramines ammonia and chlorine
Hydrofluorosolic acid the most common form of fluoride not covered by other fluoride filter brands and sodium hexafluoro
silicate get your pro pure with the new pro 1 filters today at info war store comm or by calling 888
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans here is the cow Ben soap company
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth friendly and safe
See them on the web at five star soap comm or call 800
340 7091 for a free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as
What you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs
This is an amazing deal
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
See them on the web at five star soap comm or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog
You prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms
But if you don't have a home security system
And you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when you're sleeping or away from home who's watching out for intruders
Check out simply safe. It's a new do-it-yourself home security system
That is completely wireless go to get simply safe comm
Simply safe is independent and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if the grid goes down you're protected
It's completely customizable so you can use it in your home business boat trailer storage unit or shed get simply safe comm
Simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes
So there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you move or need to relocate you can take the system with you
Wherever you go you aren't always at home, but simply safe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days a week
Again, that's get simply safe comm
Coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance
You're listening to the Alex Jones show
I will give the number out coming up here in the next segment. We'll have open phones in the second hour
We are into the first hour
Early three minutes into it right now. Okay. We just joined us. I played a clip of
Fox Sports
Caster Jason Whitlock is also syndicated columnist saying the NRA is the new KKK and I have
similar clips here by well we had Al Sharpton and
Say quote, but I forgot to get that clip queued up. We'll play that
After these clips if you can find it say that we've got to overcome the south and whites and the Constitution
He even said the Constitution you saw that a few weeks ago on the niche and it's every couple days
I see prominently the talking point by white black Hispanic commentators you name it
That that gun ownership is right there
And they know how politically correct Americans are if they said put your child
In ongoing traffic or throw your child into the oven or the microwave or you're racist
I think most Americans would probably go stick their child in the microwave and turn it on and I'm not even being sarcastic
I think we've gotten the politically correct point that if they came to your house and said
Slit your rest or your racist the average white American would slit their rest
They would they would absolutely do that
All right, let's go ahead and go back to the Jesse Jackson clip. Here it is. I mean you break it you break up the trail
We used to guns made in Barrington
Rock Island
So the chucks and put us up they make them to sit in they kill we stand around feeling helpless
And so you've got some combination in this drug thing and so you've got some combination in this drug thing
And this gun thing of of territorial fights the gun fights over that
Maybe the four percent would kill assault weapons
They kill these other these locks in these magazines where the killing is taking place there
Some others is just shoot out because just because the culture is into
Guns as a remedy my point is probably focused on fiscal clever and debt ceiling over here is this stuff
Is not on the table and it matters it's metastasizing and it's festering
So we're trying to put some focus on this issue of reconstruction
Not just and we need target job for these zones of heavy unemployment
With black males in chicago and new york member around 50 percent employer around 50 big number here in new york
But so beyond just the job some plan for reconstruction and we know how to do it. We've done it and we do it around the world
All right, let's go ahead and go to msnbc just a few days ago talking about the real problem in america here it is
Those, you know crazy crackers on the right like if they start with their very hateful language that is going to kill them in the same
06 the death now for republicans is the tone of this conversation
They absolutely we had evangelical latinos wanting to meet with howard dean at the dnc
I mean i'm just saying like that's a shift right?
Now this is part of the hoax that the republican party's gone conservatism's dead
Everybody really wants total socialism. Wow. This is a mandate
I'm going to talk about that at the end of the segment when I want to go back to some of these clips
here first
Let's go to this next
Clip, this is bob shafer on cbs saying presidents could defeat
racism
The presidents could defeat the nazis. They can defeat the nra i.e
The nazis they can defeat the nra i.e gun owners
They don't want to say gun owners or the second amendment or the bill of rights. They say the nra
First they demonize the nra. They're nazis. They're scum
They're kkk and then by extension you and then now homeland security met on monday with the
Top mayors and sheriffs and police chiefs as you know
And i've got those reports coming up and said no the new terror threat is not al-qaeda
It's gun owners conservatives libertarians what they call domestic extremists
They're returning veterans
And they're just hyping that of tens of millions of veterans
They'll use every week a veteran robs a bank a veteran shoots somebody. Well all veterans did that
Oh, somebody does a mass shooting gets the guns illegally on a bunch of psychotropic drugs doesn't matter
Doesn't matter. It's gun owners killed the children
The veteran kills his wife veterans did that doesn't matter statistically and you can look this up at fbi.gov. We've done reports on it
Uh, they've got it broken down in racial groups demographics everything
You know that uh veterans are one of the most law-abiding groups out there. Does it matter what reality is you are bad?
You are bad. Let's go ahead and go to this next clip with bob shafer
What happened in newtown was probably the worst day in this country's history since 9 11
We found osama bin laden. We tracked him down. We changed the way
Uh that we dealt with that problem
Surely finding osama bin laden surely passing civil rights legislation as linden johnson was able to do and before that
Surely defeating the nazis, uh was a much more formidable task than taking on the gun lobby
Uh, this is a turning point, uh in this country and uh, the president is going to have to do more than just make
A speech about it. This is one of the best features i've ever heard him deliver
But it's going to take more than that from the white house. He's going to have to get his hands dirty
He's going to have to get in there and and work this problem until he gets it done
but uh
Unless we figure out a way to make sure that something like newtown never happens again
Uh, we're not the country that we once were I think we still are I think there's hope I think something's going to happen
Well, there you go the president, you know, he overcame the nazis so
So he can overcome the gun owners. See we are now the nazis. We they take you are kkk you are nazis
Uh, every time i'm see a clip of of msnbc they're saying whites are inherently bad
In fact, i've been hearing it's it's over for conservatives white women support obama
White women support obama black support obama hispanics asians and then the media does this victory dance. Oh, it's over
It's all over for the unknown soldier
And this big victory dance that oh man
It's over and again foreign banks are raping you financially. They're robbing you they've raised the different taxes across the board
They've raised the payroll taxes on people making thirty thousand dollars a year
They've raised all these other investment taxes
The obamacare plan sets it up where the companies cut their full-time employees back to 25 hours. They don't have to get the uh insurance
And the gdp is already shrinking massively. That's the plan get you on welfare, but it matters as long as you feel like you're winning
now the truth is
The fix was in as I clearly broke down and it's done hard to break down
Mitt romney's a globalist mitt romney was for gun control. He helped write the assault weapons ban that passed in his state
semi-auto ban
The truth is he supported carbon taxes. He supported open borders
He supported abortion. Do you want to keep going?
But they they put out the two guys who were almost identical in reality
But they have a political fight with each other romney then becomes a conservative says some good things
But it's all for show like a don king boxing match and then obama wins and there's evidence of massive election fraud
I don't just say that there was evidence of fraud against al gore in 2000
I hate al gore, but i'm on record saying there was evidence of fraud against him
There is overwhelming evidence that mitt romney really won bev harris a black box voting. He's been a big democrat
It would help make the hbo documentary hacking democracy said she saw a lot more fraud towards romney than towards obama
The fix was in so the republican leadership gendel
And and even rand who's a good guy
Could be told to come out by their consultants and say we've got to get with the times
And then we'll start winning I guess get with the times become left of mal say tongue on the false paradigm
Because that's what's going on in this country. That's what's happening. That's the bill of goods that we've been sold as a society
And it makes me physically
Physically nauseous to see this unfolding the truth is congress for about six years. You can look this up
Just type it in congress has a nine percent approval rating and some numbers in data mining companies have put out
I'm going to go over some of that in the next hour show or maybe the next segment show that it might be as low as
three percent
So ninety something percent of people conservatively
Ninety-one percent conservatively probably more don't like the government
Don't like the government
but if they can get it in a
Coke pepsi ford chevy red skin cowboy seattle seahawks versus the eagles, you know, whatever if they can get a fight going
Between two groups then they can get you to join a bandwagon and kind of join one side
total con game oldest trick in the book
false choice
And that's what they've sold
So there are a lot of weak-minded kind of bandwagon folks that have gotten away from obama the last four years
When he didn't deliver all the free goods
They kind of got back on the bandwagon because they want to be winners. Well by saying you like obama. You're a winner
Alex jones here with a very important announcement for truth seekers
We've carried a lot of amazing films and books over the years on the online video bookstore at info wars.com
And out of all the titles we've carried one stands out because it is just so
Chillingly convincing and that's dreams from my real father by joel gilbert available at info wars.com
This film exposes the fraud that obama is like nothing i've seen if you want to know who obama's real daddy is
This is the film for you. Don't forget your purchase supports our broadcast and our growing media network
You'll also find at info war shop.com none dare call a conspiracy by gary allen the book that woke me up
We're also carrying behind the green mask un agenda 21 by rosa cory
This book is coffin nails to the globalist takeover the greater good the most professional and up-to-date film i've ever seen
Exposing the scourge that is vaccines these titles and a lot more are all available at info war shop.com
Now that we have moved into the winter season there is an increased need to support our immunity and health
At silver lungs. We are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of silver-based products
Our most popular silver-based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our 2 ounce nano silver
Nasal applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps
Just released is our 100 percent natural silver gel
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface
But rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera
To quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively
visit
www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver-based products are best for you
That's www.silverlungs.com
Looking back on 2012
I know personally i'm thanking god that my family and I made it through the year from natural disasters like hurricane sandy and the devastating
Summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything
My friends at e-foods direct hear from customers every day that are fortunate to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand
Danny from new york city wrote in following hurricane sandy and said almost all the grocery stores are closed
But I managed to get my e-foods just in time to be able to help my sister and my niece bottom line
It's better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late heed common sense's warning and do what i've done call
800-409-5633 today or go to efoods direct.com forward slash alex
They have the best tasting long-term storable food on the planet call 800-409-5633
And ask about the alex jones special or go to efoods direct.com forward slash alex get self-sufficient today
Call 800-409-5633 or efoods direct.com forward slash alex
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with
Supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution
That can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing
Supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as stress
Staph pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria
At several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions the science digest journal says silver is our mightiest
Germ fighter it is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code
Silver 2012 for 20% off that's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on facebook
Coast to coast direct from austin you're listening to the alex jones broadcasting network
Defending the republic from enemies foreign and domestic it's alex jones
Is
Second hour is only about 13 14 minutes away and after the news
We'll be back and be taking your phone calls on the second amendment, but also the overarching police state
And more i'll also be getting into the navy seal
And his uh compatriot who were killed up by dallas yesterday very suspicious story
We're going to be breaking that down as well. The toll-free number to join us is
eight seven seven seven eight nine alex is a different number than the weekday show eight seven seven seven eight nine two five three nine
Eight seven seven seven eight nine two five three nine and the first time callers give first-time callers a chance
Please only call if you're a first-time caller on this sunday edition to give us your breakdown on what's happening and unfolding
Okay, let's continue getting into the second amendment attack
Um in the article up at infowars.com linkedin read in the featured news area
reverend jesse jackson says gun supporters are
domestic terrorist and and basically that the you know
The new radicalism the new extremism is this new confederacy and that the gun thing's being used to try to again
It's it's just more of what you've heard of well
fox sports commentators saying the nra is the new kkk
And and that's what said if you don't like obamacare, you're a racist if you don't like globalism
You're a racist if you don't want to give it up your liberty. You're a racist. It's racial politics
because this country now
If in the under 20s is way more quote minority than it is white, but if there's uh again under this system now
That's fine. They don't want whites having racial politics
Okay, regardless of which side of that thing you're on
There's a lot of different sides, but they certainly are going to create racial politics and notice
It's a bunch of white limousine liberals who are leading it because they represent these foreign mega banks
That have signed us on to debt slavery. That's the real civil rights violation that we're going under agenda 21
Where globalist corporations are exempt from all these regulations and taxes designed to shut down their competition
That china could have three new coal power plants a week
We can't have any and hundreds have already been shut down the last four years and our power prices are going up and our economy's
Shutting down. So the whole gun thing is also about scripting obama
There should never be another child shot again. And if there is it's gun owners fault. He puts out that false idea
And then diverts everyone from his drone killings arming al-qaeda and libya and syria
Uh, the police state the secret arrest the ndaa the continuing torture the banker bailouts
All of this tyranny. They don't want us getting in a populist movement
Unified by the bill of rights and constitution and freedom together. They want to unify
Disparate racial groups under a socialist ideology where their chief
Is government versus the middle class which the establishment sees as predominantly white
and so it is a racial ideology and a racial system for the
Globalist in what they're doing. They are they are welding together a racial coalition and i've known
so-called progressives that are really smart people and know what's going on, uh, and
They they now will people I used to have on as guests they will sit there and say it is racist to not turn your guns
in it is it is racist to not support obamacare
even though it's a rip-off written by insurance companies it is and and it's like a cult they are just
absorbing into the hive borg
These are authoritarians and they get a wild reflected glory a lot of humans are designed
To get wild reflected group think group power out of tribalism and the government is the big overarching tribe
Welding in all these different groups and it doesn't matter if the government's screwing them
It doesn't matter if the government's destroying their future doesn't matter if the government's injecting them with deadly vaccines
full of cancer viruses and aspartame and thousands of foods
It doesn't matter because they feel like winners and that's what matters to them
They feel
Like hey the government's my government
In fact, we have an al sharp and clip coming up that we will play that one
They're finding the one where he says we've got to get you know, defeat the Constitution
He says we've got a we've got to defeat the Constitution. We've got to defeat the South
Played that last week
We have a clip of sharp and coming up after I play this mayor clip of this new mayor's against gun violence ad
Where he says hey forget the Second Amendment. Yeah, it was there to protect you from the government
But we got drones now the government's got drones and that's what they say when I'm on these different so-called liberal shows
He's authoritarian shows in in in liberal clothing
Thomas Jefferson was a liberal these aren't liberals. I know I say that every day is so true
You got to get that through your head folks, and I'm sitting there
Even before I went on CNN, they're like, oh we don't want to hear it's for guns
the producer was saying to protect you from government the government has drones and
I've been on countless shows you hear it everywhere where they say well the government has drones
Yeah, and humans pilot those and they're under quote the Bill of Rights and Constitution
They're not they're not under the declaration of war by Congress. They are illegal
They're attacking countries illegally, but the point is we could get back control of them
Our government couldn't take over Vietnam our government running our military couldn't couldn't hold Baghdad
So I don't want to hear that because there's drones that you know forget it the hive Borg you will be assimilated
Nothing can defeat the New World Order. It's our tax money our energy that built this giant military now
They're getting rid of posse commentatis. They've they announced last week. They're gonna use the military
for domestic operations to fight terrorists and
Now any gun crime any crime where a gun is used is considered terrorism. That's the big announcement in the news
I told you years ago. It was coming
So you're now the terrorists the spying the data mining the checkpoints they've announced they're gonna use the NSA to target quote gun crime
They've announced they're gonna use it to target domestic extremists remember
They weren't spying on us five years ago, and then well we're doing it to fight al-qaeda and now forget about al-qaeda
I've never seen an article. I'm gonna get to where they say al-qaeda is on an issue now
Well yeah, cuz it works for the globalist publicly even general boykins come out and expose that now
Former head of special forces no no no it's you you're the terrorist well no kidding the thing was always set up for us
It was always set up for the federal government to absorb the states and now they're saying
Obama is the new Lincoln anyone that opposes what he does is a confederate and now you're seeing it on CNN
Fox Wall Street Journal all these different pundits saying the new confederacy is any state that resists
Obama is here. He is coming. He knows best
You know they're gonna shut down the plants shut down the factories raise the taxes till they bankrupt everything except insiders that are exempt
And then you'll go on food stamps. You'll go on government assistance, and they're gonna have national compulsory service
They're already announcing it and the Conservatives will say hey
don't let those liberals not work since you know a hundred million two hundred million will be on welfare by the time they're done and
Then you're in forced labor
They did it under Roosevelt. They're already calling to bring it back, but ten times worse. They're not going to be building national park
Lodges this time they're going to absolutely have gun control
Checkpoints that's in the FEMA Corps documents from nine years ago in the Baltimore Sun in the Philadelphia Inquirer
How they were training the small units of FEMA Corps college students to assist the police in
Finding illegal guns and radioing them in and they have these weird red uniforms black trousers and red uniforms
Completely fascist you've seen the videos Obama says we need a national you know a defense force a
Domestic force just as big and just as strong as our military and then the videos of the training course
Sitting there worshipping Obama like it's North Korea doing chants about Obama and doing military drills. I mean it's our typally
authoritarian and
Bloomberg who made two billion dollars off of insider deals the evidence is clear in the stock market
who wants to tell you what you can drink and what you can eat and what you can do as illegal checkpoints and now body
Scanners all over New York City a goon
With his own private security force that that roughs people up in DC the talk radio network reporter who politely asked him a question
Last week this goon wants your guns
To ensure that his quarry his property is defanged
To make sure you're gelded and now today during the Super Bowl coming up
They're gonna air this ad like we're children. Please take the guns
Please have a background check when they have background checks in 97% of the sales
They want it for when you sell to your neighbor or give a gun to somebody where you can't ever transfer a gun again
That's what her bill says and every time they register they then confiscate
Criminals aren't gonna follow the law anyways, but the children, please take the guns for us. This is how sick it is
Here's that clip from the upcoming ad today?
Shows cute little children
Once supported background and they play patriotic music in the background when they're globalist
We think it's reasonable to provide mandatory instant criminal background checks for every sale at every gun show
No loopholes anywhere for anyone
Oh America can do this for us America can do it, please
And and folks 20 years ago
20 years ago lop here said that lop ears now said it doesn't work criminals still get guns and he went further
He said the people don't trust the system anymore. That's right
They don't want background checks because they're angels and really want to save kids the globalist could care less
The government shipped guns into Mexico to blame the Second Amendment and killed tens of thousands of people
Several thousand confirmed almost 60,000 dead the last six years in Mexico where they've taken all the guns already
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans
Here is the cow Ben Soap company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth friendly and safe
See them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800
340 7091 for a free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as
What you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs
This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
See them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers the prognosis for the entire planetary
Economic system runs from bad to worse the globalist model is to shut down societies and starve
Patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at info wars shop calm
These are items that I did research on but I personally use you've got the life straw
So you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go the Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power
Outages are out in the field strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein
They're a safe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event and crank shortwave AM FM radios
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at info war shop calm and your purchase makes our info war
Possible we're getting prepared. Are you info wars shop calm?
Coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the alex jones broadcasting network
From his Central Texas command center deep behind enemy lines the information war continues
It's alex jones and the GCN radio network
All right, I haven't even scratched the tip of the iceberg, but I'm not gonna make callers wait
I'm gonna get to the strange death the very suspicious death of Chris Kyle
Who Jesse Ventura has been suing and winning in court Kyle has had no witnesses
Jesse had I think like six eyewitnesses that he came he went he spoke at the commencement he left
Why would he come to a thing full of seals and say I'm glad seals are dying
He never talks like that and then no witnesses to him being beat up
Kyle
Really was gonna probably expose some big wigs in the lawsuit
And then he took a lot of vets out who would contact him say they had problems
They probably sent a wind-up toy out on him, which has been declassified. They've got these people Sirhan Sirhan you name it
I'm gonna give you my to and I don't just say that okay. It's got a lot of telltale signs
But a real PTSD crazy would have those sides to we know he's under psychiatric care so the drugs alone do it
We're gonna look at that. Also the good news out of Forbes
Where it breaks down from data mining not polling real data mining the gun grabbers are getting their head handed to them
Politically though they could still go forward. They don't care
But this is the big fight. This is the big issue as I said before Obama got reelected
Well, I'll tell you doesn't Wayne LaPierre and others
You get a lot of credibility, you know what remind me tomorrow with the nightly news John go get the clips where?
Bob
Chapman before he died talked about this too, but the head of the head of gun owners of
America and the head of the NRA
Who by the way the head of gun owners of America's back on tomorrow on the nightly news?
They all said that we have our Intel
There'll be a huge attack on the Second Amendment once Obama gets back in and Obama and the media said that's a conspiracy theory
And then now look what's happened
So pretty pretty darn
pretty darn
Amazing that Larry Pratt and so many others said that and it indeed happened, and then we're going to get into
This whole skeet shooting thing and I haven't talked too much about the last few shows because I had
So many other things on the front burner
But Obama says I've been out skeet shooting I've never seen a shotgun like that
He's shooting really weird
Looks like a smoke gun or something like a pop gun and the White House put it out and said you're not authorized to use
This photo it's only for press and media
You can't put something out and vaguely say press and media can use it and then nobody else can
Plus it was taken
I actually checked into the law and the regulations and precedent on this with fair use if
Taxpayer money pays for a film production on a percent taxpayer funded
or if a tax
funded operation
Put something out there in public domain
They can't selectively say who can't use it and the claim that no one has a right to use or alter the photo
Knowing people would photoshop it and people thought it was almost a joke like they were baiting people
To create a new meme of Obama shooting the gun. No the White House photos
I've been on there now say copyright, and you can't use these well of course we use them
I mean just because these criminals say we can't use our property now there
It is Obama mocked for releasing skeet shooting photo during gun control debate and people have got him shooting at the Constitution and
Like Looney Tunes where the flag comes out of the comes out of the shotgun look at that weird-looking shotgun
I got to say that looks like fake smoke
That looks I've never seen I've videoed a lot of guns firing
I've never seen a shotgun with that weird white thing on the end
It looks like a rubber stopper, and then there's that smoke looks fake, and then the porting
I know they've got ports on the side, but
And something's weird
Something and it's almost like they put this fake stuff out to create the debate
I mean like that it wasn't just that they put that out in layers with a computer program problem
It had different type fonts within the same typeset, and it was a fake font
That's meant to look like old-fashioned typewriter
But the C's the D's all the letters had the same splats around them with a real typewriter each splat is different even with the
Same letter because it's like a fingerprint or a snowflake. I mean it's just it's a hundred percent fake
I mean you understand
There's no debating fake fake fake fake fake fake fake and and I've got a good eye anybody's got a good eye
That's work for Photoshop that photo looks fake that photo looks fake
Okay, that I've shot more skeet than I'd care to even remember that looks fake
What kind of gun is that we'll be right back with your calls?
You prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms
But if you don't have a home security system
And you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when you're sleeping or away from home
Who's watching out for intruders check out simply safe?
It's a new do-it-yourself home security system that is completely wireless go to get simply safe calm
Simply safe is independent and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if the grid goes down you're protected
It's completely customizable, so you can use it in your home business boat trailer storage unit or shed get simply safe calm
Simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes
So there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you move or need to relocate you can take the system with you
Wherever you go you aren't always at home, but simply safe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days a week
Again, that's get simply safe calm
We are on the march the Empire is on the run
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
All right, we're into the second hour here of the Sunday transmission
I'm back weekdays 12 noon to 3 p.m. Eastern time
We're going to be right back with a look at what's going on in the world. We're going to be right back with a look at what's going on in the world
I'm back weekdays 12 noon to 3 p.m. Eastern that's 11 a.m.. To 2 p.m.. Central
Thank you so much again for joining us on this Sunday broadcast
I'm gonna go to your calls for the next two segments or so
Then I'm gonna get back into Second Amendment news, and then I've also got some Postal Service news
They say they're now immune from local traffic laws and when I saw this
Yahoo
Headline I thought a cop must have given them a ticket
for
Being stopped in a no stopping zone, but they're able to stop as they're putting mail out
and then I read the article and it was about them running red lights and
speeding through school zones with kids almost being run over and
The judges ruled they're immune that is again the new royalty I
Mean and again on average post men and women are really good people
I I'm not a big fan of government institutions, but this is one of the first American institutions
It's pioneering our postal system invented by Benjamin Franklin
And I like the competition that there's a bunch of companies out there
Like FedEx and and UPS and then a government one you know where they can all compete against each other
I don't like the fact that it's subsidized now
I think it kind of subsidizes the other guys in a way
But the point is is that the fact that a judge has ruled there above the law
Katie bar the door it's the same with the cops
They don't get in trouble when they're speeding and it's not an emergency
I mean
This is the new governing class where they're above the law and the UN has diplomatic immunity all the rest of it
I guess I already got to that didn't I there it is postal services. It's immune from local traffic laws
Running red lights and
speeding in
school zones
You know I was never a big speeder in neighborhoods, but now that I have children
I mean, I just drive like five miles an hour
When I'm going through neighborhoods, and I still almost have run over people on bikes little kids run out in front of you
Just this week. I was cutting through a neighbor going about ten miles an hour and little kids
Came shooting out in front of me on their scooters a little kick scooters
And I was one like six miles an hour and thank God. I was right. I almost hit one of them
I was going six miles an hour
And it makes your heart stop it certainly does CJ. Yeah, there it is Postal Service
We're immune from local traffic laws my favorite example is the UPS truck driver delivering mail while naked
Or USPS excuse me for I did not mean to defame
UPS is a USPS
Okay, yeah, I guess the the USPS is immune, but not FedEx and
Not UPS okay. I'm gonna go to your calls
Then I'm gonna get to NRA winning the influence battle over gun control. I don't just believe an op-ed
I don't just believe a poll unless I've done my own back research
Because you have internal market studies you can get out that are pretty accurate see corporations want internal market research
That's where you find the really accurate stuff
Now I'm gonna be getting to some of that a big data mining company. We are routing them on the gun issue, but for one reason
We are sustained and they admit in their algorithms
we're gonna lose the Second Amendment if we don't keep pushing, so they're telling the the
Anti-gun groups just just you know it's a war of stamina
And so that's coming up as well and the Chris Kyle Navy SEAL that Ventura suing
He got shot and killed yesterday very suspicious. We're gonna be looking at that some but right now
Let's go to some of your calls Kim Michael Darryl Zane Jose John Frank Zach Glenn Dan
Scott and others we're going to go to you
Let's start at the bottom of the calls this time set at the top. Let's go to Scott in Colorado. You're on the air welcome Scott
Are you doing Alex? I'm doing all right, but I tell you it's getting crazy
Absolutely is Obama's taking over. I
Gotta say that I've never
Thought it would move this quick, but but yeah, he says the UN's over our military
He can secretly arrest us if he wants. He's arresting good whistleblowers that expose any government criminal activities
It's unprecedented. I
Have a question for you Alex. Yes
Who's Mallory Mahoney?
Mallory Mahoney is one of our graphics people that works here at the office
Wasn't she formerly with Stratford? Yeah, you guys are mentally ill and I appreciate your call
you know whenever we hired six graphics people for the magazine and for working in here and the University of Texas is here in
Austin Stratford is like a
Private intelligence gathering firm that in my opinion puts out propaganda
It's like a feedback loop to like agree with the Pentagon's they can say look this private group said it somebody worked there for a month
And a half is a unpaid intern and helped write a paper on China
And and I mean what am I gonna do if somebody was ever in the military or somebody ever?
In come you how many people you know about a third of the UT?
Journalism people that we bring in here for interviews because we heard a couple from UT actually three of them from UT
Did you know about half of them or more at war had an internship there?
There's not many places to get a media internship the Austin American Statesman
The Austin Chronicle, this is for print the Houston
Or the Texas Observer or whatever it's called that's small and then Stratford because it's mainly writing thousands of things a day that is
Mental illness you see we're not worried about the New World Order
We're not worried about everything else listen people say I work for the government
Okay, I wouldn't get up here and say don't take the vaccines the government's pushing that I wouldn't get up here and say criminal elements
Of our government were involved in 9-11 because they were or they're running al-qaeda and libya and syria
I mean just use your brain
You know what if I work for the government then I'm the worst government agent the planets ever seen
Total mental illness and people always say you need to answer this or you need to answer that and no matter how many times I?
Answer something I will still be asked the same mentally ill question over and over again people are looking
See what's happened is the public has lost faith in the mainstream media and the government which?
Overall is a healthy thing the founding father stated that history shows that but they had judgment
It doesn't mean that then everything is fake
It doesn't mean that I'm I'm Bill Hicks or that I'm I'm really an actor and the professor in
Florida who says that Sandy Hook may have been staged with crisis actors, which they really have that I'm him. I mean mental illness
mental illness
But I understand in a society in crisis
you
Know just doesn't believe anything anymore mental illness
Let's go ahead and talk to
Another caller Glenn in New Jersey you're on the air go ahead
Hey Alex Jones, can you hear me? Yes?
Thank you, sir
I'm a caller and I got a serious story here a fellow member of we are change
New Jersey has just been arrested here in Jersey City
and they're also trying to link this for gun possession and they're trying to link this to the info wars Obama dictator poster contest that
We participated in saying that it's extreme to print out print posters of Obama with dictator scum posted at the bottom of this
So they're saying in the Jersey Journal. It says right here
MJ comm Jersey City police say man had illegal rifle handguns as well as prohibited bullets
And so they're getting him for the muzzle
Modification the flash suppressor making it an illegal weapon in New Jersey. Yeah for those who don't know there now
They're no magazine. Sure. Sure. I'm glad you called in about this and listen
I've told everybody I didn't just say that last hour to have fun
They've officially announced gun owners are the number one new terror group along with returning veterans
libertarians and conservatives the government is so authoritarian so of so
Absolutely Marxist at the grassroots of the government. It's foreign banks at the top, but they'll use whoever they've got
They are so out of control
They're openly saying and I've already seen this not the article you're talking about that anyone
Criticizing Obama's a terrorist anybody who owns the guns are racist and that we're the new terrorists not al-qaeda and Homeland Security's main job
I'm gonna say that again
Homeland Security's main job is going after the American people now
I'm gonna get that headline again from you so I can search engine it during the break and
Get it up there for me
But you guys can probably just search Alex Jones. What is my name in the in the article?
But they're trying to implicate me because I participated in the video, okay, so they're saying Obama dictator poster contest
The name is Keith Pantaleon
33 of Jersey City was set to appear at
$75,000 bail he currently is in carny prison and my name is Glenn Zarmenov. I'm a long time
Let's just stop right there brother. Let's just stop right there
So they do talk about my contest to to put up signs saying Obama's becoming a dictator that I did three years ago
The media said should be illegal. We are by the way, we brought the t-shirt back the tyrant scum t-shirt
Limited edition a new design is out available at info war store comm we should all wear these proudly
Yeah, they said on more than 20 TV stations. It should be banned
I should be arrested for saying he's a tyrant of course. He's proving me right, but yeah, there's a purge against gun owners
We'll be right back stay with us
Introducing pro wine all of your filtration in one system portable on the go no more
Do you have two or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride you have a system that cuts out the sodium fluoride and up to?
95% of hydrofluorosolic acid advanced manufacturing technology combines silver impregnated white ceramic with new
Aquametics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals all in one filter element
It is the only one that does it and out of the gates
We have a discounted at 10% off with promo code water
This is the only system that in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides
herbicides chloramines ammonia and chlorine hydrofluorosolic acid the most common form of fluoride not covered by other fluoride filter brands and
sodium hexafluorosilicate
Get your pro pure with a new pro one filters today at info war store comm or by calling eight eight eight two five three
three one three nine
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action. Tyranny is here the grim future foretold in
1984 has become reality it really says that the state is God the United States is now recognized
Globally as one of the most impressive police states on earth this film
Conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being expanded nationwide
This documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all-powerful shadow state
At least eight four chronicles the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen
Prepare to enter the secret of world of emergency dictatorship body scanners sound cameras citizen spies
Stage terror and cameras on every street corner. It's only the beginning of the new world orders
Hellish plan the police state isn't coming. It's here
Secure your copy today at info wars comm or see it online in the highest quality at prison planet TV
Looking back on 2012
I know personally I'm thinking God that my family and I made it through the year from natural disasters like hurricane Sandy and the
Devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything
My friends at e foods direct hear from customers every day
But are fortunate to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand Danny from New York City wrote in following hurricane
Sandy and said almost all the grocery stores are closed
But I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my sister and my niece bottom line
It's better to be prepared 10 years too early and one day too late
He'd common sense is warning and do what I've done call eight hundred four oh nine five six three three today or go to e foods
direct comm
Alex they have the best tasting long-term storable food on the planet call eight hundred four
Oh nine five six three three and ask about the Alex Jones special or go to e foods direct comm
Alex get self-sufficient today call eight hundred four oh nine five six three three or e foods direct comm for slash Alex
Now that we have moved into the winter season
There is an increased need to support our immunity and health at silver lungs
We are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of silver based products
Our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our 2 ounce nano silver nasal
Applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface
But rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera
They quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively
visit
www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver based products are best for you
That's www.silverlungs.com
Coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network
Crashing through the lies and disinformation
It's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network
We have to politically get good members of the House and Senate federally
But also state legislatures to come out authoritatively and say look these purges are wrong in Connecticut, New Jersey
California New York and other states
What's happening is and I see these articles all the time now. We're gonna go over a few of them here in just a moment
where
Not even the the ban of over 10 capacity magazines where you can't physically possess them
Hadn't even fully gone into effect yet and a army veteran no criminal record
Who actually ran a charity for other veterans? They they have a license plate reading software now
most police cars in in in major cities have them and
They admit because it's on the Southern Poverty Law Center watch list and ADL watch list that whoever they say
Is a group you now are a terrorist you now have no rights returning veterans
gun owners we are change is a group that spun off from one of my listeners Luke Rudowski that just goes out and asks
journalists you know citizen questions
I'm in there
People that don't like the Federal Reserve are in there and and these foreign globalist organizations like the Southern Poverty Law Center and ADL
They're there saying if you believe in a new world order you're a terrorist and they brainwash the cops
They tell them the founding fathers are bad. I'm not joking
I have the training videos in my film road to tyranny they tell them all this
They have four shows now airing on TV. We're set to air this year
Demonizing the founders
Whole sitcoms dramas like I hate Paul Revere
This is the new cool thing as Al Sharpton said we quote must is the quote
Overcome the founding fathers
Overcome the Constitution was his exact quote
And you're like, but it doesn't make sense we're racist cuz we own guns well a lot of people that aren't white-owned guns
What it's about individualism. It doesn't matter. They're just gonna demonize you so in the news
They say an extremist was arrested now
He brought this up and I actually have the article we can punch it up on screen or go to the document cam shot here
for people
Jersey City police say man had illegal rifle
prohibited bullets at home, and they're saying he had over a 10-round mag and
they're saying that he had a
Flash depressor on it, which does nothing so this is it. They're gonna come after the gun owners
And they're now even in the places that don't have a lot of gun laws
SWAT teaming people because the neighbors said they saw a gun and going you'll never get your hundred guns back because you shouldn't add a
Hundred or just like New Orleans where they went to the high and dry areas and took the guns
So so here it is out of Forbes
NRA winning the influence battle over gun control yes, we're winning in the scientific polls
We're winning in the inner research. We're winning on the internet scans, but they don't care
They're just gonna say we're terrorists and turn homeland security loose on us
the government shipped
20,000 guns and hand grenades into Mexico the memos came out to blame the Second Amendment. They're ruthless
they want our guns while they buy 1.6 billion bullets and armored vehicles and build emergency centers and
federalize the police and set up warrantless checkpoints now like they have in Austin with the the TSA
Totally illegal totally unconstitutional. They're just doing it huge military drills every day in major cities
Terrorizing the public getting us ready for military occupation Army Times admits. They're preparing to have troops on the streets
It's already happening everything. I warned you about 15 16 17 years ago is happening
Because they announced it today government to take control of private pension funds to protect them
That's the headline at info wars comm
big government announcement Friday and there will be a special tax on top of the
3.8% tax already there on top of pension funds in Obamacare and the 3.8% increase in
Payroll tax and all the new taxes because they love you
No, it's the governing class is going to take everything. We've got it's happened hundreds of times in other nations
It's getting ready to happen here now. I got to get to all the callers, but Glenn in, New Jersey
I'll put you on hold after you go. You can give me all the names and facts
I did find where the other blog where they're talking about yeah, this guy who had the 30-round mag
He he had he was part of a poster contest where they put up posters saying Obama was bad
It should be illegal these are extremists. Oh my gosh. You don't say somebody the government's bad in America
You don't have freedom of speech, so yes. Thank you for giving us a heads up about that
As you were saying during the break when I talked to you. They are going to try a purge of gun owners
They're testing it right now
We've got to get back in their face and go you're the terrorist coming in and taking over our country
Saying our military is under foreign control. That's official and saying our guns are illegal go ahead
absolutely
Thank you Alex Jones for having me. Don't thank me. I won't have time to get all the other callers
Yeah, no more. I'm gonna put you on hold. I'm gonna put you on hold Rush Limbaugh did this 20 years ago
I got to do it. You just got to say dittos folks all we do is say how great I am
I am not great. Okay. I'm angry. I want to keep my liberties
I don't like a bunch of crooks taking over and running my life. Okay. I'm sorry go ahead caller
Yeah, they basically look. He's in jail right now. He is a friend of mine
We did the poster contest his other blog the Pope post is one of us question mark
And it says part of his legal troubles might be linked to this video
That he and a friend made in Jersey City and a link to the Facebook post of the Obama poster contest that we entered in
So yeah, they're kind of smear us
They're trying to do a purge right now
Anyone who listens to Alex Jones info wars anyone who supports liberty and I don't even own any firearms
And that's the whole problem here is that I'm just putting up posters out there
On behalf of your poster contest or any other posters. I've done posters on my own exactly look we have an authoritarian government
Obviously authoritarians don't like their slaves being armed the last thing they've taken is our guns
That's the last they've already taken the bank accounts the dollar. They're gonna take everything they need those guns first though
They're gonna go ahead with it and have a civil war they want to get as many
Voluntarily as they can we've got a Stalin or a Hitler in control, but it's bigger than Obama
The Republican leadership's been told you better go along with it. That's why they're saying. Oh, we got a broken wing
We've got to do whatever big government says it's a mandate socialism turn your guns in because they're controlled
I'm gonna put you on hold I want to get all the info if you write a blurb about it
We can link to it. You're gonna be okay. Don't let them scare you
This is going on where the crime bosses run everything, New York, Chicago areas of Jersey
This is what it's turned into let's jam in another call here. I gotta get to more of these
Let's talk to Zach in Tennessee. You're on the air Zach
Yeah, if you need to I don't know if you call the thing today
It says three well-known Second Amendment supporters young business owners
And I know you've covered them all on your show Chris Kyle Keith Ratliff the FPS rusher guy
And then also the John the Vinsky and they said they all died under mysterious circumstances within one month
But that's not even that important
Listen it's really starting to emerge that they've got killings
I mean SPS Russian producer was tied up and killed execution style there are more and more pro-gun people getting killed
There's this video out right now called Yolo it was all over YouTube last weekend
Basically, it's demonizing preppers and saying that anyone who you know doesn't live life on the edge
It's basically a call to a young generation to do whatever they want and live recklessly
And then I know you covered the Milwaukee Sheriff on Piers Morgan
I was going to comment on that but more importantly than that
Bill Maher was demonizing conspiracy theorists about a week or two ago
And you know they were basically he had all these left and rightists on there
And they were saying you know 9-11 shooters are from the left and whoever thinks the birthday thing is fake
Then you know they're from the right, so they're just playing no
They're saying you're a bad guy if you don't believe the known liars
But being a conspiracy theorist means I don't believe a government and a mainstream media system caught lying
Thousands of times to me that's what it is today if you question if you don't just on the surface believe whatever they say look
How do you know if media is good you judge the tree by its fruits look at the fruits of the political system?
Absolute tyranny more calls straight ahead
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with
Supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution
That can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing
Super natural silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious
Diseases such as stress death pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology has the ability to terminate entire
colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or
Ionic silver solutions the science digest journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
Supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off that's
supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook
You prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms
But if you don't have a home security system
And you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when you're sleeping or away from home
Who's watching out for intruders check out simply safe?
It's a new do-it-yourself home security system that is completely wireless go to get simply safe calm
Simply safe is independent and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if the grid goes down you are protected
It's completely customizable
So you can use it in your home business boat trailer storage unit or shed get simply safe calm
Simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes
So there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you move or need to relocate you can take the system with you
Wherever you go you aren't always at home, but simply safe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days a week
Again, that's get simply safe calm looking back on 2012
I know personally I'm thanking God that my family
And I made it through the year from natural disasters like hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by
Disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything my friends at e foods direct hear from customers every day
But are fortunate to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand Danny from New York City wrote in following hurricane
Sandy and said almost all the grocery stores are closed
But I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my sister and my niece bottom line
It's better to be prepared 10 years too early and one day too late
He'd common sense is warning and do what I've done call eight hundred four o nine five six three three today or go to e foods
Direct.com forward slash Alex. They have the best tasting long-term storable food on the planet call eight hundred four
Oh nine five six three three and ask about the Alex Jones special or go to e foods direct.com forward slash Alex
Get self-sufficient today call eight hundred four. Oh nine five six three three or e foods direct.com forward slash Alex
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans here is the
Cal-ben soap company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years
These all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth friendly and safe
See them on the web at five star soap calm or call eight hundred three four zero seven zero nine one for a free catalog
by the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now or
Save big with a one to two year supply of soaps or all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
See them on the web at five star soap calm or call eight hundred three four zero seven zero nine one for a free catalog
Coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network Network
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance
rallying patriots worldwide
You're listening to the Alex Jones Show
Alright we're back here and you can hear the frantic voices of the people calling in
The power structure doesn't want to go after criminals they are criminals
The power structure and it's really bad on the East Coast and other crime syndicate controlled areas obviously
They want to target the little guys and teach us that they're basically our owners
That's what all of this is about
Now up on screen if you are a TV viewer I have an article out of the Smithsonian magazine
For forty years the Russian family was cut off from all human contact unaware of World War II
In the 1930s they came to their Christian village the Soviet atheist and they mowed down their families mercilessly
This has been declassified by the archives
And in 1978 geologists were flying around looking for outcroppings a hundred and fifty miles from even the smallest town
And the helicopter picked up what tended to look like tilled fields I want to do a whole report on this
And this family of five lived there the mother had starved to death when her children were small one winter
Refusing to eat so they'd have the only food and they were dressed like cavemen everything
They had walked more than five hundred miles total from their original village because the Soviets were always hunting
They wanted to kill every Christian they could get to didn't matter how much money needed to be spent
And you can go read the full annals of this it was so important to kill Christians
And these were just poor villagers and it describes how they ran into the woods with just a bag of seeds
And then a blight killed their rye crops the mother starved to death but a year later
They live in different camps over the decades that it took them to get a hundred and fifty miles out in the middle of nowhere
And the Soviets killed conservatively off and on around 50 million people from 1917 through the 1980s
And before the Soviets could basically get to most of them they caught pneumonia probably because their immune systems were so debilitated
Once other humans came around with new strains of viruses most of them died one of them is living today one of the daughters
But you read about you know the things they've said and what they went through and there were tens of thousands they ended up finding decades later in the woods
And exterminated because even though you're living out in the middle of nowhere 50 miles 100 miles it doesn't matter
You need to die because the all-powerful atheist state says so and of course the atheists come and they're gonna have guns
Piers Morgan said he'd like to shoot me and a lot of Buzz Bissinger said he'd like to shoot me
And a lot of others they talk about how they want to kill us these are horrible people very very horrible people
But America is that's why they demonize preppers that's why if you don't trust the system and you want to be self-sufficient they don't like you
They want you under their control like Bob Dylan wrote in 1983
Yeah I can see someday when even having your own garden they'll be against the law
Yeah it's sundown on the union what was made in the USA sure sounded like a good idea until things got in the way
Yeah we used to grow corn in Kansas now we grow it on the moon and eat it raw
Talk about somebody that saw the future and that's what's going on here that's what's happening
That's why they want you shut down when you punch it back up on screen for folks I want to show the viewers out there people watching at Infowarsnews.com
The 40 years the Russian family was cut off from all human contact unaware and just amazing helicopter photos of their little shack they built
No hammers no nails little daughters that were tiny girls when they ran and I was looking at some of the other photos on the deeper in the Smithsonian site
Showing the aerial shots there it is of the terraces they put up on the side of the gorge to grow the few plants that they had they could also keep the seeds from
In the future you run to the hills with your seeds they'll only grow once then they don't grow the next year
It's all about patenting life all about centralized control that's the name of the game
And that's why they don't want you self-sufficient that's why all over the country now they're saying you can't have a backyard garden you might grow marijuana
You might see you're guilty until proven innocent you can't trust a prisoner we're all prisoners now that try to grow a garden in your backyard
Don't trust that in America government's got to come look government it's all secret building bunkers and buying billions around ammo but you
Well they're now saying to see something say something main program is do you see guns in people's houses
And the average anti-gunner is such a dumb mindless domesticated creature that they come in your house they see a gun case they call the police
And the police come and take it even though it's not illegal and they go well there was just a report you may sue us try to get your guns back you see that in the news
Well we've decided you might be a danger the government is here to break us and I'm telling you folks if you don't wake up and realize how much trouble we're in it's all over
This transcends liberal conservative garbage it's down to freedom versus slavery let's talk to Kim in Florida Kim you're on the air
Hello Alex I just want to say the same exact thing that people better wake up because it's unbelievable I just had a very recent visit from ATF
They I wasn't home at the time but they knew exactly where I was even the name of the company that I work at
Oh it's incredible I had the ATF like a decade ago say that a gun I had didn't have a right serial number randomly they wanted me to come down there
And it's just a way to harass you if you're not a Mexican drug cartel ship the narcotics and you're a bad guy
And now it is a purge we are the new criminals they want to fill all their new private presence it's us the gun owners
And we're in trouble the cops want to keep their jobs they'll put us in jail all day long
Oh yeah and you know we were led to believe like ATF works with the police and when we did some inquiring they said well we don't know what ATF is doing
They could be doing whatever they want to do
What was their claim we need to check a serial number or something?
No I guess because we had purchased several guns in a short period of time
Oh yeah that's the new thing if you buy even a hundred rounds of ammo they come and visit you like you're dirty and create a bad it's all harassment
I mean I see the reports all over the news where a veteran visited after he bought two new rifles
And again it's all about you're bad you're the perp you're a criminal you did something wrong it's this new psychology that we're now going to learn how to do the perp walk
That's what TSA is all about learning about lining up learn about them putting their hands on you
Where I live now has TSA checkpoints totally illegal violates the tenth amendment the fourth amendment they don't care
Yeah and my whole reason for calling today is what would be your advice on how to deal with this situation because at the time I wasn't home and they spoke to my husband
Which I was the one that purchased the firearms and as far as I'm concerned they got all the information they needed to know
That's exactly it you say this isn't a straw purchase I bought the guns for us but I bought them legal and lawfully
You're here to try to create a criminal account a criminal file on us you know full well so just get on out of here
And again these are the ones that ship the guns to Mexico and outside of law they tell it was the gun shop that did it to you
When you buy two or more and they wanted a law two years ago they couldn't get it passed so they just did it extra legislatively
This is a big issue now they're saying they may just ban guns without a law just with a rule making and that's what they do
And then they think you're ignorant most of these gun arrests I'm seeing for a flash suppressor or something they're not even illegal
But the juries are so stupid they'll put you in jail for a wrong statute and the lawyers are also corrupt
They'll put you in jail and make you think you got a deal they want to give gun owners a record I'm telling you folks it's a criminal purge
And listen you could turn your guns in they're not gonna stop they're gonna take look listen
The heirs and others that were Obama's mentors this came out in trials we played the video clip of it being broken down
They said we're gonna put 50 million Americans in forced labor and we're gonna kill 25 million of them
Their goal is to put us in camps and blow our heads off I mean they want to do what they did in the Soviet Union and they will do it
And the neo cons are all a bunch of Trotskyites who helped Trotsky do what he did and they all ran over here
As Stalin kicked them out they're gonna try the same thing these are authoritarians folks this isn't rhetoric
We're in deep trouble the government is run by evil people they want a civil war against gun owners
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial solution
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria
Viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume everyday while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases
Such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria
At several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook
The documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all powerful shadow state
Police state 4 chronicles the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship
Body scammers, sound cameras, citizen spies, stage terror and cameras on every street corner
It's only the beginning of the new world order's hellish plan
The police state isn't coming, it's here
Secure your copy today at Infowars.com or see it online in the highest quality at PrisonPlanet.tv
New Aquamedics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals all in one filter element
It is the only one that does it and out of the gates
We have it discounted at 10% off with promo code water
This is the only system that in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides, herbicides, chloramines, ammonia and chlorine
Hydrofluorosilicic acid, the most common form of fluoride not covered by other fluoride filter brands
Sodium hexafluorosilicate
Get your Pro Pure with the new Pro 1 filters today at Infowarsstore.com or by calling 888-253-3139
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at Infowarsshop.com
These are items that I did research on, that I personally use
You've got the LifeStraw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go
The Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out in the field
Strategic Relocation 3rd Edition by Joel Skousen
When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein
Aerosafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event
Hand Crank Shortwave AM-FM radios
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at Infowarsshop.com
And your purchase makes our Infowar possible
We're getting prepared, are you? Infowarsshop.com
Coast to Coast, direct from Austin
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center
In the heart of the resistance, you're listening to the Alex Jones Show
Thomas Jefferson said the level of tyranny that you will live under is the exact amount you put up with
The government is run by real live authoritarians
Who have robbed countless third world countries, the IMF and World Bank
They want to re-educate America
They want to start a civil war, Homeland Security was set up for the American people
It's a lot bigger than Obama
This is a long term strategic plan
The reason the Republican leadership is going along with all this globalism
Is because they're bought and paid for by Goldman Sachs, JP Morgan and others
Now I'm not saying this year they're going to come arrest all the gun owners
Though they're harassing them and arresting veterans
In fact, here's one of the articles right here
It was just up on Infowars.com, I actually was doing a search on it
Where army veteran arrested for 30-pound mag in New York State
Faces five felonies, had no criminal record
Those mags are illegal now
And people are saying, well we're going to defy it
And gun shops are saying, we're going to protest
They're like, good, we'll fill the prisons
And they will, they don't care
It's up to juries to nullify unconstitutional laws
And it's time for these politicians to start getting arrested
They're setting themselves up as God
It happens everywhere else
Look how decadent America is
But we're not all individually decadent
And they think America's dumb
They think we're done
They think they can take over
And I'm telling you, they're saying gun owners are responsible for all crime
We're Nazis, we're scum, we're trash
The government needs to defeat us
This is the nomenclature
Hitler didn't even say things about Jews like that
Until he'd been in office two or three years
He didn't even write things that radical
They're saying things publicly
That Stalin didn't even say about groups he was wiping out
So we're being demonized
I mean, can you imagine if they got up on the TV
And called black people the n-word
When they're calling whites crackers
Whites are on there to create division
And they're calling gun owners Nazis
You're being demonized
But you have American hospitality
You're like, oh shucks, go ahead now
And I mean, it's flooding in
People buying ammo are getting ATF visits
And they go to people with no criminal records
Upstanding members of the society
I even saw an article where they visited a cop's house
Who bought 500 rounds of ammo
It's the idea that we're all bad, government's good
And the small federal family, as they call it
Janet calls it the federal family
What are they, Sicilian?
I mean, it's just amazing
Michael, Ian, Genesee, you're on the air
Thanks for holding
Yes, I had a really quick idea
I think you ought to put a news sticker
At the bottom of your new screen there
That has the Bill of Rights
Or you could also put the Constitution
Because I'm an avid reader
I know a lot of people read
And you have a lot of information
And this way it would just kind of
Nail it into these people's heads
I agree, you're talking about on the TV show
Start having a scroll?
Yes
That makes sense
What do you think about the accelerating gun purge?
Change and all that
I'm sorry, caller?
I said yes, you know, like they do
A news sticker for the New York Stock Exchange
And they do updates and all that
On the Bill of Rights or the Constitution
Is that what you called in about?
Yes, that was one of the things
And the other thing is
You know, I remembered watching a movie
Where it was called Kingdom of Heaven or something
And the knight had everyone kneel
And he said, as of this day, I'm knighting
You all just get out on one knee and make this vote
I think deputies ought to just deputize
Their public like Barney Fife
And Andy Griffith used to do
The problem is they've taken over most of the police departments
We've got a lot of good sheriff's departments
Because they at least know about the Constitution
And they're elected, that's the difference
They want to represent the people more and more
It's time for all of us to deputize ourselves
Before God and country
To understand real authoritarianism
Has come to our shores
And the globalists think they can totally take over
God bless you Michael
Let's go to Dan in Pennsylvania
Dan, you're on the air, welcome
Hey, how are you doing Alex
Good sir, thanks
You and your crew
Thank you for holding
Yeah, I just was wondering if
If you've seen House Resolution that was introduced 437
It's the assault weapons ban of 2013
And also 449
It helps, it provides amnesty for the veterans
To turn in their guns
And register them and for other purposes
It's really draconian
I know, I know, it talks about
There's a bunch of gun confiscation and assault weapons bans in there
It was in Feinstein's first version
And it's got language in it
People understand, they're like
We just want to have reasonable background checks
And they've got gun bans
Where you've got to turn them in like New York just passed
Their goal is take our guns
While they sit there going, we don't want to take your guns
We don't want to take your guns, they've done that everywhere
You know, they're now taking the single shots and bolt actions in Australia
See, first they take the semi-auto
Then they take everything
What was the particular bill number on that one?
That was 437
It's the assault weapons ban of 2013
And it has the text up online
But there was also one other one
It's the House Resolution 40, I believe
I was trying to find it online again
And my computer froze
Yeah, we found it, punch it up
No, I've seen that one, punch it back up for TV viewers
For radio listeners, just go to the Library of Congress
It's HR 437
I armed the military in DC
There's a bill in there that says
You know, to arm the military in the District of Columbia
No, I know
And that's like Caesar bringing his troops into Rome
Look, in the NDAA bill that passed last year
To supposedly reform it
It continues the secret arrest provision
And just gets rid of posse commentatis
That's what I'm telling people, folks
They are going whole hog
Republicans have gotten real scared
Yes sir, we'll do whatever we're told
You're right, we're bad
You're right, you've got a mandate
It's because it is hammer down
I mean, I've never been this concerned
This is not a game
This is a revolution by foreign banks
This is espionage
God bless you
Yes, thank you for bringing that up
Yes, I'm aware of it
That's what I'm telling people
This isn't a game
By the way, you can buy the February issue of Infowars Magazine
On the cover it says
Why the tyrants want your guns
About 80% of the 60 page glossy magazine is on that subject
It explains how they're going to take your guns
Why they want to take your guns
Their strategy to do it
Their strategy to beat them
It is available at InfowarsStore.com
That's InfowarsStore.com
Or InfowarsShop.com
Also gets you there
And it's at cost
You can buy them in groups of 10
Up to 100
In fact, John Bowne was at the public library
Getting books for his daughter yesterday
And said he saw a stack of them
Somebody put in there
So good job folks
You can also get subscriptions at cost
And you can give subscriptions
Give subscriptions to people you want to wake up
Imagine 12 issues
Good chance of waking them up
InfowarsStore.com
Or call 888-253-3139
We've brought back the Obama Joker Tyrant shirt
Redesigned
Because the first one was a limited edition
Show is this one
Your purchase supports the broadcast
Let's talk to Zach in Tennessee
Zach in Tennessee
You are on the air
Zach, what is on your mind today?
Yes sir
I was just holding from earlier
But I was going to tell you
Did you see the Bill Gates article
That he doesn't care about money
And he goes on to say
He's spiritual but doesn't believe in religion
Did you see that one?
Yes I did
They're bringing in an entire system
We'll look more into that
I'm telling you
It's a total global revolution
Ladies and gentlemen
Designing high tech to enslave us
Not to empower us
It's a total blueprint
It's called a technocracy
In their own words
Let's talk to Zane in FEMA Region 3
Formerly Virginia
Now globalist occupied territory
Go ahead Zane
You're welcome to the airwaves
Hey Alex
How's it going?
Pretty good
I read an article
I work in one of the few factories
Left here in Virginia
And someone had posted this article
It was out of a magazine
And it was saying that
The way they're going to get the gun grab
Is they're going to make it
Where you can't afford to have a gun
They're going to make you get insurance
On your guns
Have you heard anything about that?
Yes, no
They've got state and federal bills
Insurance is a power to tax
The power to tax is the power to destroy
They're hitting us with a thousand torpedoes right now
They're hitting us from every single angle
And we've got to take their attack
And show how they're authoritarians
With bodyguards
And how they've taken guns everywhere else
And how this is a plan to enslave us
And turn it back on them
We have to go on the offense
Or we're going to lose everything
Well that's for sure
I am sick and I am tired
And everybody that hears this
Needs to be sick and tired
Exactly
I mean we are being enslaved
Being upset is what got us our liberty
We need to get upset and awake again
God bless you
And I meant to get to this
And I didn't
I'll cover it tomorrow on the weekday show
NRA winning the influence battle
Over gun control
Appinions
Is one of the biggest data mining
Public groups
And the company breaks down
Off a variety of data mining
What they found
And they have found that second amendment advocates
Are absolutely trouncing the gun grabbers
And this is a
Again non-partisan
Non-political analysis of it
And it says gun rights advocates
Have more stamina than gun control advocates
Gun rights advocates show military coordination
With laser focus
Well yeah because we're people that actually work
And live in the real world
Any mainline person that supports gun control
Who isn't a tyrant
Is just a jellyfish
They think the government loves them
And wants to help them
Government wants to inject you with cancer viruses
And put you six feet under
After you're done working
Alright I'll see you back tomorrow
11am central info wars dot com
Great job crew