Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are so busy, I literally just slid into the chair here. I was busy
in there in the other office watching a two-minute excerpt of the Obama phone lady from the show
yesterday. You can't go to mfullwars.com. We're rebooting the site right now, but it
is linked on drugsreport.com, halfway down the right-hand side.
Nice little excerpt of the Obama phone lady here in town with us yesterday. We need to
go through all the interviews that she did and kind of boil it down, because the average
person can't watch an hour and a half of it. I'm glad somebody on YouTube got a clip out.
We need to get the clips from her on the TV show last night, cuz she was so nervous in
here in studio with us yesterday. She was so incredibly nervous that she, it was kind
of subdued. But when she got on the TV show, she really talked about a lot of important
issues and we played the clips of Obama lying to folks.
So that certainly woke her up as an example of what we can do for others. Okay, here's
the deal. The news that we've got is so incredible that words really can't even describe how
serious our situation is right now. But I will do the best job I can when we come back
from break and I'm kind of officially kick off the broadcast today to go over all of
this.
This is so amazing when I'm looking at Joe Biden, White House eyeing 19 executive actions
on guns. Politico, CBS News, New York Assembly Speaker Silver, we are going to ban assault
weapons, period. And the governor said, first they make you come in and register them, then
they'll order them, hand it in.
And that is what the bill says. It's now passed the Senate in the New York legislature and
it's going to the full house. So we are in deep trouble, ladies and gentlemen. By decree
of the king, there are some steps that we can take that don't require legislation. That's
a video clip of Obama in his press conference yesterday.
Rahm Emanuel, we played this clip yesterday, says take American people out of the Second
Amendment debate. We have that that's gonna be coming up. I'm gonna play all these clips
coming up in the next segment.
And New York's also preparing to put gun owners in mental hospitals. I mean, you just can't
make up the magnitude of this takeover. All over the country, governors, legislatures,
they're all declaring war on the Second Amendment. New York Senate passes draconian gun bill.
We've got some good news though, sheriffs all over the US are going public and we have
one particular video we're gonna play coming up. Sheriff says teachers should be armed,
Second Amendment shall not be infringed.
And Aaron Dykes' video report is up on our YouTube channel and at prisonplanet.tv. That's
why we have those auxiliary sites so that when in full war is down, people are able
to get there. Rand Paul slams King Obama over executive order. And there's also talk in
the Congress of impeachment against Obama. In fact, guys, will you go to the search engine
and type in impeachment?
Cuz I saw several articles this morning that I forgot to print out or send to you. And
I wanna be able to show those news articles that there's multiple people in Congress now
talking about impeachment. And that is the only way. I mean, that should have happened
when Obama's get fast and furious or when they said that our military was under NATO
command and Congress should sit down and shut up.
GOP congressman threatens impeachment if Obama uses executive action for gun control. That
is a report there that we're gonna be going over as well today. That is just some of what
we're going to be breaking down. But this is it. This is the big enchilada. And I hope
that everybody realizes that this is the time to put up or shut up beside which side of
the republic that we are on.
We'll be right back. Stay with us.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad
spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver
solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning
and help improve wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph,
pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the ability to terminate
entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal
or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ
fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go
to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off. That's
SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance.
Ladies and gentlemen, these are the times that try men's souls. It's times that we all
have to have a gut check and get right with God. Everything that we have unfortunately
predicted these globalists would do is now unfolding and soon the gun confiscation will
be in the present.
It's in the near future right now and then soon we will be in the aftermath of whatever
comes out of this. Now, ladies and gentlemen, the corporate media in collusion with the
politicians and their globalist owners are openly saying in the news, the president is
allowed to take guns by executive order.
The president is allowed to shut down gun shows by executive order. The president is
allowed to order you to turn your semi-autos in. And they are passing or are in the process
of passing outright gun confiscation in multiple states right now. We're going to be going
over all of it. Now, if you go to DrudgeReport.com, you see the big headline up there, Congressman
threatens Obama with impeachment if he tries to use executive action to restrict the Second
Amendment. And if you click on that report, it's from the Daily Caller.
We have our own reports obviously predicting this the last few months because the gun control
group said, don't worry, once he gets reelected, we're going to use executive action. People
are like, Alex, don't fear monger, that's unconstitutional, he won't do that. Texas
Republican Representative Steve Stockman, who you notice Larry Pratt has pointed out
would be our champion and had told him privately he would do this, threatened Monday afternoon
that he would file articles of impeachment.
Let's get it going, let's go, against President Barack Obama if he institutes gun control
measures with an executive order. Stockman warned that such executive orders will be
unconstitutional and infringe on our constitutionally protected right to keep and bear arms. And
he went on to say that I will seek to thwart this action by any means necessary, including
but not limited to, eliminating funding for implementation, defunding the White House
and even filing articles of impeachment.
Stockman said in a statement, boy, he didn't wanna get on the airplanes anytime soon, we
need more people to come out and support him now, like Rand Paul, now, not later. That
this is late they're doing this, this should have been done a long time ago. At his press
conference Monday, Obama floated the possibility of using executive action to enact policies
aimed at reducing gun violence.
He didn't float it, look, look, you see this magazine, this was published in late November.
And it says this man wants your guns, December issue of Enforce Magazine. And in the article,
go read it, we sent out an e-version of it to everybody. We have 10 predictions for 2013
and it's they would be coming for our guns by Mike Adams. In fact, the prediction in
here is that they would use executive action to do it, boom, that happened.
You've got the article, Obama wants your guns and the rest of your freedoms. And we go on
to say they will use executive action to get our guns. Why? Because they said they would
do that, okay? Now, here we are, and some of the more timid mainline conservatives are
like, how dare you get in a red coat's face and say, look, it's gonna cause a civil war
if you do this.
It's not that we want one of these civil wars, it's that they have set up Homeland Security
and put it in a posture where they say gun owners, conservatives, libertarians, returning
veterans are the enemy. And they've got the state police all over the United States training
for gun confiscation.
The new army manuals that we've listed and shown over 100 times here, they talk about
gun confiscation in US cities. This is now happening, this is now unfolding, this isn't
a game, this isn't a joke, this isn't a drill, this is the real deal. In fact, as soon as
infoawards.com is back up, we're rebooting it and doing some scans of the site.
As soon as it's back up, I'm gonna have Kurt Nemo, Paul Watson, I'm gonna have all of them.
Cuz I called Paul Watson about 7 this morning, even before I saw the Daily Caller. And I
said, we need to do a report on this congressman saying impeachment. And I said, impeachment
is the way to go.
And I said, now we've got to get on the offensive and we've got them on Fast and Furious, lying.
The Republicans could gut the Democratic Party right now for all the stuff they've done.
They don't want to cuz they're bought and paid for at the top by the same people, Boehner
and all the rest of them. They're traitors, they're Benedict Arnold's.
Three hearings last year where they told Congress NATO is now over the military and tells the
president what to do. We don't come to Congress, boom, instant impeachment. Obama ordering
the Department of Energy to shut down coal power plants outside of law, massively increasing
our power prices outside of congressional law, boom, impeachable right there.
And so I want Paul Watson, and I want Kurt Nemo, and I want Adan Salazar, and I want
Steve Watson. And I want all the rest of our riders, everybody else out there should be
beating the drum, beating the drum for all out impeachment. And we're gonna impeach Obama
publicly.
Hold on, Watson, listen, remember this morning I called you and I said the way to go is to
go after him and call for impeachment for all the stuff they've done. We need to put
out our own articles of impeachment. And I'm gonna talk about the articles of impeachment
on air in the next hour.
Okay, and you can go check everything I say historically and pull it up. There's at least
ten reasons, people always like the number ten, ten reasons to impeach Obama, that we
must impeach Obama now. Okay, we've gotta get on the offense. And we've gotta get behind
this Texas congressman and others, okay?
Because it's just all out. And by the way, while Infowars is down, you can go to prisonplanet.com.
And again, we're trying to upgrade and revamp the site so they can handle the increased
traffic. We're getting like three times the traffic we used to the last week and a half.
And it's just sustained. And the ad servers just can't handle it, so I'm suspending outside
ads.
So let's have our own house ads up there just to get the info out. So they're busy reloading
the site right now and everything else. And I'm just telling the listeners that right
now, prisonplanet.com is the backup auxiliary, be sure and go there. And Paul, we just need
to go through also, you and Steve are always good at ferreting out old articles.
How many articles did we write the last year saying he would become a dictator, he would
use executive orders and we have to impeach now. We need to also flashback so people understand
not hey, look, we're smart. Hey, look, we know what we're talking about, better listen
to us, okay?
So have somebody do a report on that, okay? All right, God bless you, my friend. Thank
you. All right, by the way, ladies and gentlemen, I guess Infowars is back up now. That was
Prison Planet, okay, Infowars should be back up soon.
New York State Senator, gun bill passed in the middle of the night turns law abiding
citizens into criminals. That's how mafia does it. New York Senate passes tough gun
control law. Paul, most Americans support new gun control measures after Newtown massacre.
By the way, this is how they play it. The Washington Post puts out some fraudulent poll.
Post polls show the majority of people are pro second amendment all the way. And it doesn't
matter if 51% say they wanna put me in chains and make me pull a plow, I don't have to do
it under natural law.
If 51% say I gotta turn my guns and I don't have to. If 51% say they support Obama becoming
a dictator, it's not just my right, it's my duty to resist. Do you understand the globalist
have installed dictators over multiple European countries? Do you understand we're going head
long into tyranny?
Look at this, Politico, Joe Biden, White House eyeing 19 executive actions on guns. Iowa
lawmaker calls for retroactive gun ban, confiscation of semi-automatic weapons. New York Assembly
Speaker Silver, we are going to ban assault weapons. Boom, gonna ban them, make you turn
them in. And see, that's what the bill that's passed the Senate in New York says.
That's what Cuomo said two weeks ago in the New York Times. People are like, this can't
be true. I mean, he's on the radio saying it. The New York Times wrote about it. We
wrote a story about it and people couldn't believe it. They wouldn't even follow the
links to find out it was true.
Because you can't believe it's actually coming to this. Yes, they're coming, they're coming,
they're coming for us. They want to get a shooting war started. That's why I went on
CNN and said don't start this. Because people need to know where this is going. People need
a heads up, ladies and gentlemen.
Let's play Rand Paul on gun control. And again, it's not gun control, folks. It's victim disarmament.
It's enslavement. We need to stop using their terms. Here's Rand Paul saying King Obama.
And Rand Paul-
I think it's having a king. I think having a monarch is what we fought the American Revolution
over. And someone who wants to bypass the Constitution, bypass Congress, that's someone
who wants to act like a king or a monarch. I've been opposed to executive orders, even
with Republican president. But one that wants to infringe on the Second Amendment, we will
fight tooth and nail. And I promise you there'll be no rock left unturned as far as trying
to stop him from usurping the Constitution, running roughshod over Congress. And you will
see one heck of a debate if he decides to try to do this.
Senator Paul spoke to us in our Jerusalem bureau. Look for more of his comments on the
Middle East and Israel in the days ahead.
That's not strong enough, Rand. Okay, you need to do what the Texas Congressman Steve
Stockman has done. Okay, you need to get aggressive right now. And we need to start, not threatening
impeachment. The president is saying he's gonna sign 19 executive orders taking our
guns, okay?
Now this is not a game. We've gotta come out and say this is illegal. The dictator word,
not the king word, the dictator, it's here, it's happening. Let's go out to break with
Rand Paul, here it is, one more time.
I'm against having a king. I think having a monarch is what we fought the American Revolution
over. And someone who wants to bypass the Constitution, bypass Congress, that's someone
who wants to act like a king or a monarch.
I've been opposed to executive orders even with Republicans.
That's good, we're gonna go to break, but listen to me and listen good. Dictator, we
are segueing into a dictatorship. People are like, well, wait, he got elected, Hitler got
elected. If you get elected and then overthrow the checks and balances, it's called a dictator.
The office is becoming a dictatorship. The executive run by the globalist, we're under
occupation. Okay, those aren't words, that's the truth, we're occupied.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just
in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Is this the year you finally get serious about your family's drinking water? If so, keep
listening for a special offer from Big Berkey Water Filters. Did you know that over 60%
of municipal water is fluoridated? Berkey Water Filters distinguish themselves from
many other filtration systems with the capability to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine,
fluoride, arsenic, and disinfection byproducts from municipal water via the black Berkey
and PF line of filters. Then there's affordability. At only 1.7 cents per gallon, Berkey Water
Filters purify treated and untreated water, even stagnant pond water. Stop and think how
much money you could save by simply reducing buying bottled water and using water filtered
by your Berkey Water Filter. No need to be constantly replacing expensive filters with
a Berkey. A single set of filters can last for 5 to 10 years. Choose the best size Berkey
for your needs at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com. And right now, all GCN listeners get 5% off
all ceramic filter systems. Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY. That's 877-99-BER-KEY or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
Free shipping on every order over $50. Big Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean
water.
Plan a healthy garden easy and fast with OrganicaSeed.com. Easy because OrganicaSeed.com offers one of
the largest online selections of organic, heirloom, non-hybrid, and untreated seeds,
as well as tobacco and cotton seeds at low prices. Go to OrganicaSeed.com. Spelled O-R-G-A-N-I-C-A
Seed.com. OrganicaSeed.com. Remember, Organica Seed is healthy seed.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson. Have you ever wondered why banks, stockbrokers, investment advisors
won't talk about gold IRAs? They've been available since 1986, yet the financial industry won't
recognize the value of gold for your retirement. Gold has outperformed paper investments, yet
no word about IRAs. If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns, call 800-686-2237. Secure
your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
Big business has discovered the preparedness market, and that makes it difficult to know
where to go and who to trust. MyPatriotSupply.com is owned and operated by patriots just like
you, has the best prices on storable food, non-GMO seeds, water filtration devices, home
canning equipment, survival and self-reliance books, and more. MyPatriotSupply.com has old
fashioned values and the absolute best customer service in the industry. Look for the deal
of the day, unique affordable survival supplies that fit anyone's budget. Get same-day shipping
on all orders and free shipping on orders over $49. Call 866-229-0927, 866-229-0927,
or visit MyPatriotSupply.com for emergency preparedness, self-reliance, and food independence.
Shop with a name you know and a name you can trust. Before it's time to survive, it's time
to prepare. MyPatriotSupply.com.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are back live here. Yesterday, I was on air talking about what
would Paul Revere do during this entire period of history. Mainline conservatives would call
him a traitor, and if he rode down the street saying to arms to arms, the redcoats are coming
to confiscate our guns, the average neocon would step out with pleasure and shoot him
from the horse, guaranteed, and then salute the redcoats.
And that's what some conservatives said about me. They said, you shouldn't yell, you shouldn't
get upset. Really, our forebears killed people. When someone comes to usurp and enslave you,
that's the response or you become a slave. I'm just trying to peacefully fix things.
I'm a wimp compared to Paul Revere. But then the super wimps call me bad. And here is Boston
Magazine, AMC is developing a show called We Hate Paul Revere.
Isn't that just cute? And it's all over TV and the culture bad mouthing the founders.
And they've got three or four different TV shows now that have just come out airing.
One's called Founding Fathers, where anybody who's a patriot's evil. And guess who they
waged war against? Gun owners during gun confiscation, and the gun owners are all horrible scum.
And the army infiltrates them and takes them down in Texas. They've actuated this out.
They knew it'd be Texas congressmen that resisted them like Steve Stockman. They knew, and so
they've got all these TV shows on ABC, NBC, all airing, where the bad guys are the gun
owning libertarians. They were all being developed last year.
That's why I said they're coming for the guns next year, because of that and hundreds of
other data points. They pre-program us, they get us ready. This is brainwashing. AMC is
not satisfied with Mad Men's foray in the 1960s is setting a new comedy in colonial
Boston and titling it We Hate Paul Revere.
And it's basically about two brothers who are not fans of industrialist and activist
Paul Revere. And then the show reportedly from Deadline Hollywood just makes the founders
look bad. I mean, whoa, a bunch of TV shows demonizing the founders. This is what a foreign
occupation force does. That isn't rhetoric, okay? And Obama's not becoming a king, he's
becoming a dictator.
And that's why the Republicans are going, you know what, we'll legalize the illegals.
You know what, we will go for some gun control. You know what, we will raise taxes. You know
what, we are gonna go for Obamacare. Because they've been told, you sit down and you shut
up and you get in line.
We know about your insider trading, we know about your girlfriend, we know about your
boyfriend. A mafia takeover is taking place and I'm here going, hey man, we're in trouble.
I'm here having to do this, which is not fun, but it's my duty, and I will not be a slave.
And then I get to watch all these armchair quarterbacks going, man, you're going a little
far, don't raise your voice. Okay, fine, folks, they're gonna take everything, okay? You got
that?
They're gonna gut the country, open North American Union, toll roads on all the roads,
doubling, tripling water prices, energy prices. They are going to rape us. They've said they're
going to rape us. And as things get worse and worse, I was on Current TV with The Young
Turks last night.
And he's like, come on, all right, they secretly arrest us. They've got more wireless wiretapping.
They're setting up highway checkpoints. You're right, but still, do you need mental health?
You shouldn't get upset about this. And I'm like, you know what, you're mentally ill.
If I was in Nazi Germany in 1941 saying this is wrong, I would have been called insane.
If I was in the Aztec Kingdom 500 years ago, I would have been called insane for saying
don't have human sacrifices. That's what I said to him. He just laughed at me, man. It's
funny to these people.
All this is happening. It's all happening. It's all gonna get worse and worse. There's
army manuals on FEMA camps. There's army manuals on gun confiscation. And people are so cowardly
they flip it around and go, it's not that bad. Real cowards lie to themselves and say
something isn't happening or it's okay.
Yeah, all this is happening, but it's not that bad. And then I am mentally ill. Because
I see straight, I know history, I'm concerned, and I've got enough courage to get up here
and put my name, my honor, everything on the line. Folks, they're testing us right now.
If we bend over, ladies and gentlemen, if we lay down, they are gonna run right over
the top of us. Again, a lot of people hear this show and they go, man, you're scaring
me.
Why are you trying to scare us? I don't think you're cowards. I mean, look, if you're in
a parking lot and a guy comes up to you, and another guy behind you, and they go, we're
gonna beat the daylights out of you, might as well go ahead and fight. There's nowhere
to run, we're cornered in an alley.
I'm not gonna lay down while they can kick me in the teeth. I mean, it just isn't happening.
It's not an issue of courage. These are authoritarians who wanna gut this country. They're not liberals,
they're authoritarian monsters. And their minions will soon be saying, so they're arresting
right wingers, big deal, cuz they're now talking about that, just getting rid of us all.
Here on the march, the empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health. At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver-based products. Our most popular silver-based products are
the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our 2 ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well
as our all natural silver soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver
gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver
at the surface. But rather, we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera, to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin, while delivering the
silver more effectively. Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver-based
products are best for you. That's www.silverlungs.com.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought, to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just
in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today, or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers. The prognosis for the entire planetary
economic system runs from bad to worse. The globalist model is to shut down societies
and starve patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover. That's why we've assembled
the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarsshop.com. These are items
that I did research on, that I personally use. We've got the LifeStraw, so you can turn
fetid water into safe water anywhere you go. The Ktor hand crank generator to charge up
key equipment during power outages or out in the field. Strategic Relocation, third
edition by Joel Skousen. When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein. TheraSafe used by Homeland
Security to protect yourself during any radiological event. Hand crank shortwave AM-FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com
and your purchase makes our info war possible. We're getting prepared. Are you? Infowarsshop.com.
There's an old saying in Tennessee, I know it's in Texas probably in Tennessee that says
fool me once, shame on me, shame on you. Fool me, we can't get fooled again. He aligns himself
with the truth and it's time for you to choose a side. You're listening to Alex Jones. Again,
there are four different TV shows airing or about to air on broadcast TV and cable bad
mouthing the founding fathers.
Situational comedies running them down. I hate Paul Revere. Shows like founding fathers
and others coming out where they admit in the variety write ups that gun owners during
gun confiscation resist and they are dealt with. And the average yuppie will sit there
now and fantasize about being the SWAT teams hunting us down.
And most of these shows are based again in Texas. The globalists know where their resistance
is gonna come from. Because here's the deal, I can't give in to these people. Okay, I've
said I'm not turning my guns in. I am a political information person. I don't plan in the early
stages of this cuz I'm not gonna give them what they want, armed resistance.
You know, I'm not sitting there watching my back. If they pull up and take my guns after
they're banned, that will be something I'll try to fight through the courts and politically.
But they're not gonna stop there. They're all over the news saying lock up gun owners
and mental institutions. We're mentally ill because we don't wanna give up the Bill of
Rights.
When I was on Al Gore's foreign owned TV network owned by the Arabs last night, he sold it.
They were saying, do you need mental help? And I'm like, why? Because we have the NDAA
and secret arrest and army manuals training for gun confiscation and FEMA camps and all
this stuff coming true.
In fact, Bloomberg, here's one of the headlines. Bloomberg urged Obama to take executive action
and to ban guns outside of Congress. He urged him to defy Congress. That's Bloomberg, the
guy that wants to tell you what you can eat, where you can sleep, how big a house you can
live in, how many painkillers hospitals can give out.
He just has orders in New York. I order the hospitals not to distribute painkillers to
people. I mean, it's just, I'm God. I tell you what to eat. I tell doctors what to do.
It's called a dictator pig who swore he wouldn't run for reelection and then got the law changed.
He helped passed on term limits. I mean, it's just a fraud. A guy with armed guards, a gangster.
There have been 50 plus thousand signatures signed in Mexico to the Mexican government
calling for the US citizens to have all our guns taken like the poor Mexican people who've
had total gun bans and the highest crime rate in the world, almost 60,000 dead the last
five years.
Just mercilessly under the control of mafia and mafia government and our government saying,
yes, the Mexicans want us to turn our guns and we better do it. And we've got the British
government and we've got Piers Morgan and the Russian TV and the Chinese TV, all saying
take their guns. And the UN treaty coming up in March. They've got the whole world guns
confiscated and they've got to get us in line with global governance.
And again, the impeachment must start now for Obama three times last year in a letter
and three congressional committees saying NATO is over our military. And Congress said,
no, wait, we fund the military. We direct all that and the president executes it like
the football coach.
But he's given the playbook agreed upon by the general manager. And they said, no, we're
going to be under NATO command. Boom, impeach him for that. Obama needs to be impeached
for Fast and Furious. They've all been caught perjuring themselves and lying. We have them
doing press conferences before they even got caught shipping the guns in, talking about
the Operation Gunwalker and Fast and Furious.
People that said they never knew about it were doing press conferences on it when they
were promoting it, when the public didn't know the full extent of it. Boom, perjury
right there. Obama shutting down power plants so that his buddies in General Electric make
bigger profits and increasing our power prices.
When Congress didn't pass his carbon tax legislation three years ago, he's still just doing it
by executive fiat. We need to start the impeachment of Obama for directing the auto bailout to
spend $20 plus billion to ship General Motors, Volt, and Cadillac factories to Eastern Europe,
China, and Brazil. Boom, impeach for that economic espionage against this country.
Get impeachment for his environmental departments and people involved in using shadow email
systems throughout his administration. Start the impeachment hearings now and start the
impeachment hearing saying he can use executive orders to restrict our Second Amendment.
And actively promoting that sedition and that treason against our republic. What more evidence
do you need? And the executive power grabs just go on from there. The conflicts of interest.
He needs to be impeached. Of course, Congress is involved in treason as well. But it doesn't
mean you can't have good members that voted against it on the NDAA to secretly arrest
Americans.
Here's a big one. His secret order on cybersecurity, which then the EU and others bragged, that
gives him control of the Internet. He's gonna give the UN control of the Internet. Congress
being told two months ago, you can't see my secret order, my secret cyber order when Congress
has the power of the purse and the power over the agencies as a checks and balance.
He said, I signed a secret order. And the impeachable offenses go on and on and on.
But chief amongst them is Obama saying he's preparing to act with executive orders. Also,
he had the ATF last year with a rule, rulemaking order gun shops when they sold more than two
guns to report it to ATF as a suspicious transaction to order a criminal investigation.
And to open that when it's already on record that you bought firearms through the instant
check, and that's law. What they did is outside of law, extrajudicial. I mean, there's many
other examples, and many a constitutional lawyer has pointed this out. And by the way,
I wanna get Edwin Viera on.
I wanna get Lou Rockwell back on. I wanna get constitutional lawyer Fine back on to
pick their brains and other examples, and we need to codify articles of impeachment.
I want Paul Watson to take the points I just put together. Write the article, I'll approve
it during the broadcast later, slap my name on it, my John Hancock on it, and we'll put
that out there. Just an example to people, because we gotta ride out like Paul Revere
and at least point out the treason that's going on.
I mean, are there any men left in this country? Is there anybody that cares about freedom
left in this country? I got another one for you. Obama last year signed a directive, not
an executive order, not a national security order, not a PDD, presidential decision directive.
Just a directive, just a letter to ICE saying this large swath of illegal aliens, do we
forget this?
This is why he's now saying he'll just take our guns, cuz he's gotten away with it. He
comes out and he says, I'm gonna sign this order saying we're just gonna go ahead and
legalize these illegal aliens kids who weren't born here, but they're under 18. And so we're
just gonna legalize you, we're just gonna say you're legal now.
And now he's talking about an executive order just legalizing all the illegal aliens that
are here and then letting them bring their families here. And then they're all gonna
be on welfare, and then they're all going to be able to go vote illegally. We all know
that goes on all day long.
Cuz they give them driver's licenses everywhere, you got driver's licenses, you vote. And it's,
hey, we already got 56,000 Mexicans being reported, signing a petition. I mean, look
at these headlines, Joe Biden, White House eyeing 19 executive actions on guns. They're
eyeing executive actions and they're saying, we're gonna lean on gun manufacturers, lean
on the retailers.
What did Chuck Schumer say? They've said their plan, they've gone and had public meetings.
We saw Rahm Emanuel say, the police are over, who can have guns now. The public isn't part
of that discussion now. I'm gonna play that clip in a moment. Joe Biden, White House eyeing
19 executive actions on guns, Politico.
Iowa lawmaker calls for retroactive gun ban, confiscation of semi-automatic weapons, door-to-door
confiscation. Daily Times Herald out of Iowa. New York Assembly Speaker, Silver, we are
going to ban assault weapons, CBS News, and make you physically turn them in. Boom, you
hearing this?
I thought I was a fear monger. By decree of the king, there are some steps we can take
that don't require legislation. That's Obama. We're gonna play that clip in a minute. Rahm
Emanuel, quote, take American people out of Second Amendment debate. Let me keep going
here. In New York, preparing to put gun owners in mental hospitals.
New York Senate passes draconian gun bill. Sheriff says teachers should be armed, Second
Amendment shall not be infringed. That's in Kentucky. Folks are standing, that sheriff
starts crying a little bit. He goes, I'm ashamed of the founding fathers were here. But he's
freaking out cuz he realizes he's committed.
He's drawn his line in the sand and he gets sad, not because he's scared. He's realizing
what's happened here. How much trouble we're in. All you people out there need to get your
heads out of the sand, folks. They're going for this cuz they think you're weak. That's
what I told Piers Morgan.
I said, there's gonna be some of us aren't going along. I'm not gonna play into your
hands. They come to me and take me out, folks. I'm not planning to resist. I want that on
record because the minute I said I would resist them, they'll come kill me. And they don't
care about the minions that come. I'm out in the open here. But this is the waters we've
entered.
This is it. We're entering DEFCON 1 for the Second Amendment, ladies and gentlemen. If
you don't know what DEFCON is, DEFCON, you better find out. Rand Paul slams King Obama
over executive order threat. Report, Walmart forbids new ammunition orders.
Mike Adams, war, thou son of hell. As America stands on the verge of domestic war, my heart
sobs for histories. And history harshly learned. And then I've got my articles here in the
stack. In fact, I had that in my stack where it's up on infowars.com, it's now back up.
Here it is, 54,000 Mexicans signed petition, that's out of Fox News, for US gun control
and for us to have our guns taken. Oakland leaders have lost grip on violence. Everything's
disintegrating.
And a lot of people are just like, well, I'll just do what they want. I'll just turn them
around. They're gonna take everything, folks. They are already doubling power prices in
many areas of the country, shutting down the power plants that are city and state owned,
that are totally clean.
So General Electric makes huge profits. They wanna bankrupt you, they want you poor. This
is like Stalin shutting off the food and not letting farmers produce their own food in
Ukraine. Let's start going to these clips. Let's go to Rand Paul one more time, saying
King Obama. And then we'll go to Obama saying, I can accomplish through executive order.
Let's go to that.
I'm against having a king. I think having a monarch is what we fought the American Revolution
over. And someone who wants to bypass the Constitution, bypass Congress, that's someone
who wants to act like a king or a monarch.
All right, that's enough.
I've been opposed to executive order.
And he goes on to say, he'll do whatever he can in the law and Congress will fight him.
No, impeach now. And by the way, people are like, why are they so arrogant? This is so
illegal what they're doing. They're going to stage false flags and blame it on the Patriots.
You can bet your bottom dollar that they're gonna blow stuff up and then play clips of
people like myself saying 1776 will commence.
And we've got to have people on the ground the minute stuff happens videotaping. That's
one thing holding them back is when they did the underwear bombing thing when they staged
that. We had witnesses that were there and saw it and later it came out in Congress that
indeed it was a government operation.
Yeah, that came out. So again, ladies and gentlemen, they're gonna hit more schools.
I have no doubt they were behind Sandy Hook. You can see it all riding on the wall. All
the evidence is there. Look it up for yourself. And this is their season. They're going for
broke. And police and military better understand the plan is for us to kill each other.
Okay, let's go to the next clip here. This is Obama in his press conference yesterday.
And Biden's saying it's 19 orders he's planning. 19 things. This is a purge against gun owners.
They want a war. That's why they're now saying he is Lincoln. I told you four years ago this
was a plan.
He is Lincoln, his face on Lincoln. He is Lincoln. He will crush us. He will show us.
He will show us the federal power. Here is Lincoln right now.
My understanding is the vice president's gonna provide a range of steps that we can take
to reduce gun violence. Some of them will require legislation. Some of them I can accomplish
through executive action. And so I'll be reviewing those today. And as I said, I'll speak in
more detail to what we're gonna go ahead and propose later in the week.
But I'm confident that there's some steps that we can take that don't require legislation
and that are within my authority as president. And where you get a step that has the opportunity
to reduce the possibility of gun violence.
That's enough. It all goes on, the articles up at mfullwars.com and prisonblonded.com
right now. He says he can have warrantless wiretapping without law of you cuz he's God.
He says he can shut down our power plants without law. He's God. He can give waivers
to his friends and not have to get Obamacare for their employees. He's God. He can say
that well, he's not God.
The UN and NATO are God and they say he can launch wars cuz he's a peace prize winner.
The plan is to try to start a civil war and use homeland security that was set up day
one to attack the states, legislatures and the people. And this is pre-Obama. The John
Warren Defense Authorization Act of 2007. Now six years ago, five and a half years ago,
states for insurrection by the states and legislatures.
Obama was scripted for his role of Lincoln from the beginning. And now they admit it.
He's gonna be our Lincoln, but not Lincoln for a north versus south that you can debate.
And Lincoln was a tyrant. You can't debate the fact that he arrested hundreds of newspaper
editors, members of Congress, you name it. It was martial law by a dictator. He overturned
theirs. This is a occupying dictator under a foreign corporate takeover and they've already
got countries like Spain, to a great extent, but the ones that are 100% are Italy and Greece
where they appoint the technocratic leaders, the former Goldman Sachs heads.
And they're gonna do it. And they want war with the American people. Let's go to one
more clip here. This is Obama. I won't take your guns away. I won't take your guns.
When y'all go home and you're talking to your buddies and they say, he wants to take my
gun away. You've heard it here. I'm on television, so everybody knows it. I believe in the Second
Amendment. I believe in people's lawful right to bear arms. I will not take your shotgun
away. I will not take your rifle away. I won't take your handgun away.
But they're now saying that they're going to order everyone under executive order, that's
what they're floating in the Washington Post, you name it, to come and get your lawfully
already bought guns or guns your grandfather gave you when he died, some semi-auto from
the 50s. And you're gonna go in while gangsters, let me tell you, they're gangsters, I've been
around them. They're going to say, all right, hey, you're looking at me wrong. You got a
problem? I'll arrest you right now. Line up. Get the serial number. Now get out, get out
of here, you American trash. That's how they talk to you. Get out of here. They're gangsters.
They know they got to be in your face to keep you down.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not going to want to miss this exciting message.
Here's why. Our solar generators provide life-saving electrical power. And unlike gas generators,
solar generators run quietly, emit no fumes, and produce electricity from the sun. So when
the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need. Now here's the best part.
Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new. We put them
in a special spot in our warehouse, and we discount them heavily at the end of each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new. Each unit comes with
a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe. Don't wait. They go
fast. Go to scratchanddentsolar.com. That's scratchanddentsolar.com. For the craziest
offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com. That's scratchanddentsolar.com.
We can buy GMOs stressed out about money and blasted by the electric environment. Hi, I'm
Pastor Ginny, and that was the state I was in back in 2010. Then I learned about RNA
drops. I learned that 97% of my DNA that scientists have called junk is actually packed with millions
of gene switches that play a critical role in controlling how my cells, organs, and other
tissues behave. I learned I don't have to put up with disease decay or decline like
I'd been conditioned to believe. I began taking RNA drops, a 100% natural formula designed
to turn on those switches and provide me with amazing health and joy. Learn more about RNA
drops and order a free sample today. Visit RNAfreesample.com. That's RNAfreesample.com
or call toll-free 888-577-3703. Pay only shipping and handling for a free 30-day supply
of RNA drops. Get the information you need and the health you want at RNAfreesample.com.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box. I want you to know some very important information. In 1985, President Ronald Reagan
requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the
president could obtain its world-class healer. Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are
used around the world to keep people healthy. Now you can protect yourself and your loved
ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond
to abnormal cells only without harming a single normal cell. If you want to stay healthy,
now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders
that don't belong in your body. Call 1-866-VenusFly or order from Carnivora.com. That's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VenusFly or visit Carnivora.com. Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
So I defended myself. I shot the sheriff.
He's done his self-defense. Let's cue up Obama one more time. We'll play it in a second saying
I won't take your guns because it's now official. They've told the establishment a mouthpiece
Washington Post where they've been announcing all their plans. White House to announce gun
plans Wednesday, which they said they do before New Haven even happened, before Sandy Hook
happened, before Aurora happened. President Obama will unveil a sweeping set of gun control
proposals, victim disarmament, at midday Wednesday, high noon, including an assault weapons ban.
And they're saying it's going to be a physical turn in. Universal background checks and limits
on the number of bullets magazines can hold, according to sources familiar with the plans.
The announcement to be delivered by the White House is also expected to include a slate
of up to 19 executive actions that the Obama administration can take on its own to attempt
to limit gun violence. The White House has invited key lawmakers as well as gun control
advocates to appear at Wednesday's policy rollout, according to two officials who have
been invited to the event.
Obama said at the news conference Monday that he would present his gun proposals later this
week. A White House spokesman said Tuesday morning that he could not confirm the plans.
And ladies and gentlemen, Bloomberg is out, there's video of it, running around saying
just defy Congress, take them. Man, I mean, whoa, the headline should read Bloomberg calls
for Obama to become open dictator.
And I'll say this, and I've said it a million times, I will not bow to this. I am not going
along with this. I may selfishly get my family out of the country. It just continues to degenerate
this fast. But I am gonna stay here and deal with this. And believe me, that's not some
macho thing.
I'm not happy about this. I'm really sad. And folks, you should be freaked out. If your
preachers are telling you go along with this, they're scum, leave that church. If your local
talk show host is going along with this, they're scum. Now's the time to say no, no, no, you
shall not pass.
You shall not pass this gate. You shall not do this. Folks, there are a bunch of lawless
globalists that strip countries down ruthlessly. If they'll do this to us, they'll do anything,
and they are, they're gutting everything. They've already taken 47 trillion from us
offshore.
They're bankrupting us. We're going into bondage. It's world government. They're like, but they
already run everything. Why are they doing this? Because they want war. They want domination.
They want control. They hate you. They hate real Americans. They know you're not gonna
turn your guns in. They want this to happen. They want a civil war.
I just hope that when the history of this is written and these people end up losing
that we have, like they supposedly had Nazi hunters, I hope these people are hunted down
worldwide and brought to justice. No matter what happens to me, do not let them run to
South America.
Do not let them run to other countries. These people need to be held accountable. Nuremberg
trials for all of them. Let's go out to break with Obama's pledge that he wasn't coming
after any of your guns. Here it is.
When y'all go home and you're talking to your buddies and he wants to take my gun away.
You've heard it here. I'm on television. Everybody knows it. I believe in the Second Amendment.
I believe in people's lawful right to bear arms. I will not take your shotgun away. I
will not take your rifle away. I won't take your handgun away.
We'll be back. I have a stack of articles saying they're going to confiscate our guns.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad
spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver
solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning
and help improve wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph,
pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the ability to terminate
entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal
or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ
fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go
to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off. That's
SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook. Waging war on corruption. Alex Jones on the
GCN Radio Network. Big Brother. Mainstream media. Government cover-ups. You want answers?
Well so does he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now live from Austin, Texas,
Alex Jones. America is being completely overthrown. There's been a lot of attacks on us. Our health
freedom, forced inoculations going on outside of law. The open borders, all of it.
But now they're talking about executive orders to restrict our Second Amendment. There's
an all out call for Obama to basically be a dictator. It's very, very sad. I've had
him scheduled for a few weeks. We're gonna talk to him about 30, 40 minutes and then
we'll get back into how we need to move with articles of impeachment.
And I wanted to get him on about what gluten does in the gut. Cuz I'm trying to go gluten
free myself. And my wife's done it and had some amazing results and also wanted to get
his take on the flu. And they admit they never guess which flu vaccine needs to be formulated
to actually give you some protection from the flu, so it's a total hoax.
And so it was such a popular interview we did about six months ago that I have twisted
the arm of Theo Ratliff, the just now retired famous NBA star. Back on, well, this is coming
up in the next segment, and Doc Wallach, to just talk about health news in general, but
also talk about the fact that the establishment knows that we've got mineral and vitamin deficiencies
and trace element deficiencies.
But out of the gates, Dr. Wallach, what is your take on the move to disarm the American
people with executive orders? I mean, if they can take the guns, they're gonna be able to
take the supplements.
Well, exactly right. Basically, I don't think the American people are gonna allow that to
happen. I don't care what the Congress does. I deal a lot with farmers. I deal a lot with
the average person. I'm out there giving 300 free lectures a year, Alex, all across this
planet.
And what we find out is that absolutely the American public is not gonna tolerate their
weapons being taken away for self-defense. It is not gonna happen.
What are folks telling you out there across the country you talk to?
Well, people are digging holes and putting their weapons in. People are buying from each
other as opposed to official areas. They're accumulating guns from, grandmas and grandpas
aren't gonna use them.
And they're actually accumulating weapons from private sales as opposed to sales from
a Walmart or a Costco's or maybe a big sporting store, you know, these big five stores and
things like that that sell weapons. So they're going to private sales.
Well, I tell you, these are the times that tries people's souls. Why do you think the
system is so bold to actually try to go after our guns right now, Dr. Wallach?
Didn't Eric Holder say that crisis is a terrible thing to waste?
Yeah, they've all said things, Rahm Emanuel, you name it.
And so basically what they're doing is they're using this tragic story of this new town,
what is it, Connecticut, where these kids were all shot.
Yeah, Sandy Hook, it's outside there, yeah.
Yeah, okay. And so basically, they missed the whole point. Really, when you look back
and actually in the book, Rare Earths Been Cures, which you have in your bookstore, Rare
Earths Been Cures, there's a whole section on these types of mass murders. And basically,
they are caused by psychologists who don't want to give up their weekly check from talk
therapy. They know, and there's actually laws in the cities and then the counties and in
the states and federal government, where a caregiver who is a psychologist or psychiatrist
can, in fact, have somebody institutionalized that they feel they're of eminent danger to
themselves or the community. But the psychologists and psychiatrists say, you know, if I just
put them on one more drug, I can keep them out of the institution because they give up
their weekly check if they put them in an institution.
And when you look at the records of these people who are managing these individuals
who do the mass murder of serial killers, they've been working with them for a long
time. It's not like it's any mystery that these people are dangerous.
They know exactly, you know what, I want to recap that. And then obviously get Theo's
take on this because it's such big news right now. And then we'll get into, you know, ADHD,
you name it. I mean, they know vitamins and minerals are the answer. They know getting
people off the the dyes of the answer. And I'm gonna talk about some of the incredible
products as well from Young Jevity available at Infowarshealth.com.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support. And it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action.
Tyranny is here. The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality.
It really says that the state is God. The United States is now recognized globally as
one of the most impressive police states on Earth. This film conclusively proves the existence
of a secret network of FEMA camps now being expanded nationwide. This documentary exposes
how the continuity of government program has established an all powerful shadow state.
Police state four chronicles the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen. Prepare
to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship, body scanners, sound cameras,
citizen spies, stage terror and cameras on every street corner. It's only the beginning
of the New World Order's hellish plan. The police state isn't coming. It's here. Secure
your copy today at Infowars.com or see it online in the highest quality at PrisonPlanet.tv.
Coming back on 2012, we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At E Foods
Direct we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my E Foods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared ten years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting non-GMO long term storeable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on E Foods Direct.
You know we're all about solutions on this broadcast. Thank you for joining us. I'm your
host Alex Jones. It is Tuesday the 15th day of January 2013. And if you just tuned in,
the White House is talking about 19 executive orders to restrict the Second Amendment. Joe
Biden headline, White House eyeing 19 executive actions on guns.
Multiple Congress people now are coming out saying that more and more the executive branch
is becoming a dictatorship or a king. New York Assembly Speaker says we are going to
ban assault weapons. That's all semi-autos. Continuing here, just incredible news. Rahm
Emanuel, we haven't played this clip again yet. We're gonna play it later in the hour.
He says hey, the people don't have a right to even debate guns. The police will run things
now. They'll decide. I mean, that's called dictatorship. That's the Chicago mob boss
Emanuel.
Now that is just some of what's coming up. And in about 40 minutes, I'll play a special
report by Aaron showing different sheriffs and police saying they're not gonna be part
of this. So this is a big, big deal. The articles are all up at infowars.com and prisonplanet.com.
But I also wanted to talk about solutions here today. And a few weeks ago, it was one
of the most popular interviews we've done on health.
I wanted to get Theo Ratliff on the broadcast. He just retired. He was able to stay in the
NBA 10 years more than he would have with Dr. Joel Wallach's research. And we promote
all the products that they've developed at infowarshealth.com. When you purchase them
there, it also supports our transmission.
So I've got Theo back on to talk about his experience just with minerals and vitamins
with proprietary systems that have been developed by Dr. Wallach. He's an American former professional
basketball player who played last with the NBA Los Angeles Lakers, primarily a center.
He was an excellent shot blocker who's led the league three times in blocks per game.
As of 2011, he's ranked 18th all time in career blocks and 13th all time for career blocks
per game.
Also a great rebounder. And of course, Ratliff played basketball at Dinopoulos High School
and later graduated from University of Wyoming. And again, he is one of the people that work
with Dr. Wallach and others to develop the product Rebound, the ultimate sports drink
that I know my wife, who's a sports addict, absolutely swears by.
I personally am a big Polymers Plus guy and beyond tangy tangerine. And again, all of
them discounted. Occasionally we do infomercial here amongst the info at infowarshealth.com.
You can sign up there and get free shipping or become a distributor and get discounts
at infowarshealth.com. But the plugging out of the way, there's a cornucopia of things
I wanted to get both these men on the broadcast about, and we'll get Theo to talk about his
experiences and what's happened with him.
But number one, Dr. Wallach, I mean, yesterday we posted an article with Samjay Gupta, how
do you pronounce his name? Gupta, yeah, the brain surgeon on CNN saying almost all these
shooters have been on psychotropics Prozac type drugs. And then the former head of Homeland
Security came out, Governor Ridge, and said we should look at these drugs.
Because in almost every case, these are involved. And of course, for those that don't know who
Dr. Wallach is, I'm not gonna go over his entire giant bio. But he is a doctor of veterinary
medicine that worked for the federal government and did all these autopsies and found out
a lot of stuff because of mineral deficiencies.
He's also got several other doctor's degrees on top of it. Some reason I don't have his
bio here in front of me today, but it's lengthy and it's up at info.warshealth.com. There's
other videos there where that's all introduced. But he joins us now. Dr. Wallach, also a lot
of these behavioral things they admit are the dyes in the processed foods.
And the chemicals that are in the processed foods like McNuggets, they admit have, well,
but basically it is silicone, like you have in breast implants. How do they get away with
this? And as more and more kids drink Cokes all day and eat Snickers bars, and then they're
bound, I mean, if I eat a Snickers bar and then crash an hour later, I wanna beat somebody
up.
I mean, I'm in a horrible mood. If I eat a well-balanced meal, drink some Beyond Tangy
Tangerine, I mean, I feel great. And I can work a lot harder because of Beyond Tangy
Tangerine and the essential fatty acids. The system knows this, but they don't want, they
don't, you were talking in the last segment about what psychiatrists and psychologists
are doing, people that should be locked up.
This woman, she had her guns through background checks, registration, draconian gun laws in
Connecticut. None of these gun laws would have stopped this guy, but they're blaming
gun owners now. What's happening on that front? Then we'll get Theo's take on that and then
give his testimonial.
Sure. Well, certainly gun owners are not default here. Basically, it's the medical system.
You've hit the nail on the head again, Alex, you're just a genius at this kind of stuff.
But it's the medical system that has failed us terribly. There was a wonderful study that
was done in Texas in your state where they looked at two counties, and I get those counties
for you, where they looked at the violent crime, they looked at domestic violence, they
looked at suicides, and two adjoining counties, one of them had an enormous amount of minerals,
particularly natural lithium, which is not a drug, it's really a trace mineral, in the
water compared to the adjacent county that had none in the water. And of course, it was
like night and day. The county that had lots of natural lithium in the drinking water,
the amount of domestic violence, violent crime, rapes, murders, suicides, all that kind of
stuff was nearly like 10% of the neighboring county that didn't have any lithium in the
drinking water.
The nice thing about the Healthy Start Pack, or the Alex Pack, is that the Alex Pack has
a significant amount of natural lithium in there, and that's why you and I are such nice
guys. And if everybody in America would take the 90 essential nutrients, they would avoid
the need for all these terrible psychotropic drugs. The combination of bad food, psychotropic
drugs, and nutritional deficiencies is an explosive mix. And the medical system has
brought all this together for two reasons. Number one, there's insurance, which allows
them to do whatever they want to do for the money. And then they're a protective monopoly.
The medical system is the only monopoly in America. And so they have no competition.
And so this is where I just really applaud you for bringing this stuff to the surface.
Because without you, Alex, this is not going to get out there. It's a combination of bad
food, psychotropic drugs, and nutritional deficiencies. We solve all that. There won't
be any more of our military people coming back home and committing suicide and being
involved in domestic violence. If we do all this, there won't be another mass murder.
And actually, in the book, Rarest Performing Cures, there's several chapters, four, five,
and six, that deal with serial killers and mass murders. And half of them firebomb churches
by throwing Molotov cocktails. They drive cars through malls and run over people. Half
of them don't even use guns. Guns are not the problem. It's a basic trilogy, I would
call it, of bad food, psychotropic drugs, and nutritional deficiencies. And you've hit
the nail on the head once.
Well, you know about the lead conspiracy, which they've proven. I'd love to say guns
is what has made crime drop so much since the 70s and 80s. And that has been part of
it. More guns means less crime in the general population.
That is correct.
But the lead was making people mad as a hatter. And they've got direct correlations of lead,
lower IQ, more violent. So you get the lead out of everything, people start becoming less
violent.
You're exactly right. Of course, toxic metals like lead and mercury, the medical system
actually uses mercury as a treatment. And it's just really sort of backwards. And so
this is where you're educating people on these subjects. It's just genius on your part. Because
if we educate America, the average American is a pretty commonsensical person. And they
will find a way to survive. It's that old song, that old country went through the song,
every boy will survive. And people are going to have their guns. If you depend on the government
taking away guns, they're not going to get all the guns away from the bad guys. I like
the idea. I spent almost 20 years in the military, Alex, and the only way to stop a bad guy with
a gun is have a good guy with a gun. And you point out again, when you have the ability
to carry, you have a permit to carry a concealed weapon, everybody gets real nice. They tip
their hand to the lazies, they open the doors, because you don't know who's carrying a gun.
And so that's a good thing.
Now I want to shift gears into another area. Again, we have Theo Ratliff here, a retired
basketball player, star, just to get people the idea that minerals, vitamins, trace elements
are more powerful than drugs. They're what were actually designed to use. And it's so
much the food we have as adulterated. Shifting gears, Theo, tell folks how you woke up to
this, how you met Dr. Wallach, how it enabled you to stay in the NBA longer, and really
how miraculous.
I mean, this didn't talk, folks, this is true, that the proprietary blends developed by Dr.
Wallach and Young Jebrady were for you, sir.
Well, thanks, Alex, for having me on your show once again. I had a great time last time
we had a chance to speak and, you know, always great to be with the great Dr. Wallach and
all his people over there at Young Jebrady do a great job of just trying to keep people
informed and keep people healthy.
My situation was, you know, I was, I've been playing basketball all my life. And I got
to the point where I had made it to the NBA, doing a great job, taking care of my body,
doing all the necessary things, taking the drugs they give me, the supplement, different
things, and was at a stellar career.
Got to the point where I got all the way to being an All-Star. And as I became an All-Star,
I started breaking things just out of the blue. I broke my hand, had a knee fracture,
had a hip fracture, and all these things was going on. And I tried to condition myself
that bleep, bleep, discipline, no drinking alcohol, taking the right supplements, but
it wasn't the wrong supplements, turned out, and just try to stay focused on my craft as
far as being an NBA player and trying to be the best that I can be.
Then it turns to once I broke my hip, had to go into surgery, felt that my career was
about to be over with because it was hard because I had a labrum tear in my hip and
had congenital arthritis in my knees. So just constantly dealing with that and microfracture
and different things that was just thing after thing after thing.
So I had the honor of once I got here with the Hawks here in Atlanta to meet with the
great Mike Glenn, the Stinger, and the great and late Phil Oliver that introduced me to
Dr. Wylie. And they spoke to me about the mental deficiencies that athletes have and
what I was going through. And the light turned on, the light bulb turned on in my head. It
was like, wow, I've been doing all this stuff and having the best doctors and no one has
ever told me about minerals and how minerals work within your body and athletes and how
we sweat out our memories, not just salt, but all 90 nutrients that we put into our
body, we sweat them out.
And as you deplete them, your body started deteriorating. So you become a lot older as
the more and more you play the game. And that's why you see a lot of people once they retire
not walking with the canes, knees back, hip replacements, blase, blase, go on and on.
So with me being able to get with Phil, Dr. Wylie, and the Stinger, I got on the 90 nutrients,
great program, built my body up, got back to my old self, led the league three years
in a row after I came back and shot blocked, was up for the defensive player of the year.
Two of those years went on to have a stellar career, went on to go in and sign another
$40 million contract. And it was just a blessing, a blessing to basically receive what Dr. Wylie
has prepared within Young's equity in the minerals and also having an opportunity to
formulate an energy drink because I did so well, reformulated the rebound FX energy drink
so I can sustain my energy throughout the game when the guys in the fourth quarter are
dwelling down and their energy is going away.
I'm still at my highest level. And guys, up until this day, until I stopped playing, always
asked, man, you out here 38 years old, how you still running out here with these 20 year
olds? And I tell them every time I take my minerals, I take my supplements, my 90 nutrients
every day, and I'm running on this rebound.
How many of the players have listened to you? Because I've noticed that, and this is real,
this really works. They've done studies with rats decades ago where they know if it's a
super high level, a full spectrum of vitamins, minerals, and trace elements that the rats
live twice as long. In some studies, worms have lived four to five times longer. Anybody
can pull those studies up.
I mean, the system knows this and they know that all these different degenerative diseases
are connected to this. They know that all these new diseases that are happening that
they make up the system. Dr. Wallach, how many doctors out there know this or how many
are just ignorant? Because I was reading about basketball players die so young, doctors die
so young. I guess a lot of them just actually don't know this.
Well they have access to the information Alex, and the problem is they get taught to use
the insurance system. The insurance is probably the worst possible thing for the American
public when it comes to health because there's no law or ethical canon that requires the
medical doctor to cure you if there's a cure available. And so they don't. What they do
is they figure out the best way to get every penny of your insurance money. If they, for
instance, rheumatoid arthritis, if they cure you, they're going to make $300 in office
calls. I can cure rheumatoid arthritis in two weeks. And that sounds bizarre, but it's
an infection with antibiotics. You can kill the bug. It'll take 90 days to rebuild the
damage from rheumatoid arthritis, and it's that simple. But a doctor doesn't have to
do that, even though the cure is available by killing that bug, the mycoplasma bug that
caused the rheumatoid arthritis. They choose to do joint replacements. They use methotrexate,
gold shot injections, and they run up a bill over 25 years of $750,000 versus $300,000.
Well it's well known that, I mean, not just what you develop, but I worked for a large
animal vet off and on in high school. And when winter was coming up, they'd say, now
put them on this mineral mix so you don't lose cattle in the cold weather. You just
give them more of the minerals, I forget which ones they were, and the cows wouldn't freeze
to death. What are those minerals? Well, it'd be selenium is the primary one. And of course
you're looking at calcium is another good one. Magnesium is another good one. And those
would be the three big ones for livestock.
Well see, vets know this because their job is actually to deliver food, beef, and things
to the market and not have it die, not bankrupt the industry. So that's why you get real medicine
there. Theo, I asked you a question and then interrupted going to Dr. Wallach. I mean,
how many people in the NBA around you, where you were about to have to retire, saw you
get what, almost 11 years more because of the minerals? I mean, I would think it would
just sweep the entire industry.
Well that's the problem. I mean, you can tell the story, but you know who control those
guys are the trainers and the doctors. So like I said, I had the best of the doctors
and the best of the trainers, but they have their own way of doing things, their own mechanism
and which how they give supplements and who they listen to.
Some of them do listen, but some of them won't take that leap of faith.
Well what's incredible is Ted Anderson, the owner of the Genesis Network we're on, a couple
of years ago we start promoting the longevity adds good products. It was just a side issue.
Okay, great. You know, vitamins, minerals. I knew it was true. But Ted then went and
he was going to have knee surgery, went to three doctors and he finally got all the products,
the osteo FX, the beyond tangy tangerine, the essential fatty acids, all of it.
And his knees totally better. What happened there, Dr. Wallett?
Well, actually when you look at that, but we can actually regrow cartilage. The medical
system says you cannot regrow cartilage if you have bone to bone arthritis. You're the
perfect candidate for knee replacement, hip replacement, shoulder replacement, when in
fact you can regrow cartilage. It's very simple. You give it the body, the right nutrition,
the body will rebuild itself. We're constructed to do that. And so what I did, I took everything
I learned from the veterinary industry where we don't have insurance. There's no incentive
for a veterinarian to treat you any longer, treat your livestock any longer than he has
to, because you'll figure out a way to do it yourself if, you know, he starts dragging
it out and obviously using it for an ATM machine. Or in the human health industry, there's insurance
either through the government or private. And so the medical doctors try to get every
penny in your insurance policy and they don't feel they're hurting you because insurance
pays is the way they say. This doesn't hurt the patient.
Listen, I know multiple women, I'll just leave it at that, who were not even that old and
had their hair falling out. That's an epidemic now. And one of them even had a thyroid problem
and began taking beyond tangy tangerine, the other products at Infowars Health and their
hair came back. I mean, you know, Wallach, Doc, why are women's hair falling out all
over the place?
Well, their thyroid gland requires all 90 essential nutrients. The medical doctors want
you to believe that all you need is iodine to make your thyroid healthy. And of course,
low thyroid issues can cause loss of hair. But there's a bigger problem with gluten intolerance,
which results oftentimes in low thyroid, because you can't absorb nutrients when you have a
gluten intolerance. And according to Mayo Clinic, a 2009 study, 30%, 100 million Americans
are gluten intolerant. And this is why people are losing their hair, they're getting 14
diseases they didn't have before, because they're all nutritional deficiencies, including
obesity, diabetes, fibromyalgia, which they call it lupus, which they call a autoimmune
disease, it's nonsense. This is all a gluten intolerance. And then you can't absorb your
nutrients and so you wind up with all these nutritional deficiencies diseases.
Absolutely. And folks, I am plugging this and we do fund the Infowar to defend the Second
Amendment and property rights and our sovereignty, promoting things I believe in, whether it's
propure water filters that we have discounted at infowarshop.com, or whether it's come and
take it, pro Second Amendment t-shirts. But you've never heard me promote supplements
like this, because I've never run into anything this incredible. And that's why Dr. Wallach
and Young-Jebedee is one of the biggest companies out there in the last 15, 16 years, because
they know what they're doing.
They've got the researchers, they've got the products. If you wanna call and you're a new
customer and you wanna sign up to get discounts or sign up to get free shipping or just ask
any questions about the products, it's 888-789-9277, 888-789-9277, 888-789-9277. Our customer service,
for any of the folks that are already signed up at infowarshealth.com, 888-636-9277, infowarshealth.com.
And there's great interviews and videos. You see what happened with Aaron Dykes. He actually
followed the whole program and lost 97 pounds. It looks like a new person. I work 18 hours
a day and I've never been a pill person and a vitamin person. I do about 20% of what I
should and I've just had energy increase.
Unfortunately, it's made me get more aggressive. I'm gonna be honest, the side effect is, it's
like I'm 20 again and almost have road rage and stuff. So I'm gonna be honest with people.
And I'm gonna come back and talk to Theo about that. What happened with him once he got on
this stuff? Cuz I feel like I'm 20 again. Problem is when I was 20, I didn't take anything
off anybody. And I don't know how vitamins and minerals make me more aggressive, they
just do.
Dr. Wallach says that doesn't happen with most people, but I'm gonna be honest. Well,
you've seen the difference last year here on air. And then we're gonna get some more
testimony from Theo. But all the products from Polymer's Plus to Rebound and Beyond
Tangy Tangerine to the essential fatty acids. Hundreds and hundreds of products, the best
seaweed, proprietary blends, infowarshealth.com. And all the longevity products are discounted
to the lowest possible price at infowarshealth.com. So take advantage of infowarshealth.com.
We're on the march. The empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now. Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog. Millions of people are going to get sick this winter
from coals, flu and other illnesses. Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Super
Natural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum anti-bacterial solution. Recent advances
in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent
bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing. Super Natural
Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes
of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, coals, flus and other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest
Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is
emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the
promo code silver2012 for 20% off. That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Super Natural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Super Natural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Super Natural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to supernaturalsilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook. We now take you live to the Central
Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance. You're listening to the Alex Jones show. Retired
NBA multi multi multi time all star Theo Ratliff is our guest. He was able to stay in the NBA
10 plus years longer, according to his testimony, and it's on record, then he would have been
able to under traditional vitamins and minerals.
And I wanted to raise this for you, Theo, because I'm throwing in a lot of questions.
So is Doc Wallach. You've got a lot of knowledge. What do you want to impart to people in your
testimony? What what were the sports doctors? And nutritionist giving you versus what you
discovered with Dr Wallach and Young Jeavity.
Well, there are a lot of the synthetic drugs, you know, the you know, the different pain
killers and the different masking agents, basically, you know, it wasn't anything that
was helping you to cure your problem. It was only helping to mask the problem and take
the pain away. So you can go out there, you can play ball, but then you go and sit down.
You can't walk. So that's not good. So we're with the product, with the Gluco gel and the
osteo FX and all these different natural products is actually absorbing into your body and helping
to heal your body.
Like Dr Wallach said, it's healing. It's not just creating a temporary heal. It's creating
a lifetime here. So you don't have, I don't have any issues. I don't have back issues.
I don't have any of that stuff right now. Whereas most guys, when they retire, they
got all kind of different problems going on because they don't have the proper nutrients
more in their bodies.
And now I'm having the opportunity to be in front of a lot of the retired guys because
I'm one of those guys and I'm going to make it my mission to try to explain to guys about
what this product is and what it's about and how it changed my life and give my testimony
to them in order to help them in their future.
Because it's not over with. A lot of people think, okay, just because I got to get this
knee replacement and I'm on bone on bone that I'm going to have to live with this for the
rest of my life. But it don't have to be that way. You just have to use the proper things
in your body to help rebuild that correlation and maintain that bone density and in the
longevity product is the product that does that.
By the way, it's not just Dr. Wallach pioneering this and talking about it. Dr. Blalock, who's
a top retired brain surgeon, he talks about and writes about, and he's got studies that
are published, many of them and a lot of the terms he's developed like excitotoxin are
now mainline terms used in the scientific community.
He says so many problems are just deficiencies and their chronic irritation, inflammation
from the additives. And we think of fancy drugs as something special, but it's almost
like white bread in the 40s and 50s. White bread came out, everybody saw it as fancy.
When it wasn't even bread, it was bleached poison. But it's high tech, it's white bread.
That's almost what these drugs are like. When meanwhile, the real nutrients, it's what we
eat. It's what we're designed for. That's what we really need. And the soils are so
depleted that we're just not getting what we need.
And that was my question for Dr. Wallach. Why did it make me feel, I mean, I was always
naturally kind of an aggressive guy. I'm angry some of the time and stuff, but I mean, not
in a bad way. Why would I take beyond tany tangerine, essential fatty acids, and things
like rebound and stuff?
Why does it make me bounce off the walls and have so much more energy?
Well, because your testicles, Alex, God love them, require all 90 essential nutrients to
make testosterone. So if you're eating four to six eggs a day, you're taking the Alex
pack twice a day because you're a big guy, you're going to produce enough testosterone
to make an elephant happy. And so you don't need to do any doping here. You don't need
to take testosterone patches and all that kind of stuff. You just give your body what
it needs and you'll make enough testosterone that you will be a man's man. And that's what's
happening to you. You've noticed that. And this is why the Olympic athletes, we have
Olympic athletes that have four gold medals. We have one gal, Delicia Jones. She is a woman's
woman, but women like testosterone too, because that's what gives them libido. When a woman
goes for menopause, she stops making not only estrogen and progesterone, but she also stops
making testosterone. And so you get these aggressive women basketball players or football
players or soccer players and they have lots of testosterone because they're eating four
to six eggs a day, they're taking the Alex pack twice a day, and they wind up with gold
medals because they have enough testosterone for muscle strength, for energy, stamina,
and the proper amount of aggression. Women, if you look at who does the killing in the
animal world, it's the female lion. The lioness does the killing. The male just sort of lays
there, looks beautiful. And the female does most of the killing. And so that's the way
it is with humans too. Women should be very aggressive, but then there's times for them
to be very feminine and wear long gowns and put on their makeup. And then there's time
for them to be aggressive, to save their kids. And of course, right now, women aren't supposed
to be feigning and all domesticated. That's a modern affectation of control. Going back
to Theo, what did you notice? Go back in the timeframe of when you were breaking down,
you were gonna have to get out.
It was about 10 years, right, that the products helped you continue. Describe what happened
with your focus. I mean, was it just your body or did you experience getting the old
stamina back?
Yeah, I mean, a lot of the times, before I started taking the product, if I came home
from practice, it was immediately, I gotta go take a nap. And just trying to stay up
and read a book, different things in nature, it was pretty much impossible without me just
falling asleep while reading.
But once I started taking the minerals and the rebound effects, everything just became
clear. It became more clear as far as when I'm reading, understanding, being able to
maintain your focus. And that's what I liked about it a lot because when you're tired,
you lose focus.
And when you're playing in the game, the most critical time in a basketball game is the
last four or five minutes of the game. And if you look at most NBA games, the teams that
have that better focus and that better game plan, usually win those games. And if you're
tired, you're gonna lose that focus, which helps, which attributes to you losing games.
And that's something that it did for me as far as on the basketball court. Like I said,
as far as my personal life and being able to focus and concentrate on doing deals and
being able to sit down, read prospectus and different things of that nature, which people
consider boring.
I was able to do it and really focus in on it and help propel my entrepreneurial side
at the same time.
That's right, you're involved in a whole bunch of stuff and very successful. I mean, how
much money does you total make being able to stay in the NBA 10 more years?
Well, like I said, I signed another $40 million contract, so I hit the lottery again, so to
speak.
Well, that's just amazing. And again, the other stories we see, but I mean, Dr. Wallach
and also Theo, do the sports medicine people not know about this? Or are they so set that
their thing is right, they won't look at it?
Or is there an evil motive? Cuz I can't imagine the average doctor, I mean, they're dying
young too. I mean, I just think they're ignorant most of them.
Well, I mean, you're talking about people that's going to these high level schools,
and they're seeing patients every single day. And they did all these different studies on
what creates, what helps what person that has this disease and that disease.
So when you're speaking of that, when you don't blow, come off the street. They've never
been to medical school or anything to be able to come and tell them something that's better
for their patient. Nine times out of ten, they really not gonna listen.
Incredible, I think that's absolutely what's happening. Dr. Wallach, your take on that.
Okay, well, basically, in 14 years of medical school, Alex, the medical doctors do not get
30 minutes of nutritional training. And so it's not a piece of their language, it's not
something they recognize as being functional. In their brains, they think if you eat variety
and put four different colors on your plate, that you're doing okay. They have no earthly
idea that nutrition can help your body maintain itself. And so when you have a high performance
athlete or somebody who's doing a lot of physical work, they're looking at you down the line
as a knee replacement, a hip replacement, a disc surgery in your back, a shoulder surgery.
And this is what they look at. And so their whole focus is on surgery, surgery, surgery,
surgery.
Every little school kid gets taught, I hope they still get taught, your skin goes away
every 28 days and it replaces itself. But the same thing is true with your cartilage,
your ligaments, your tendons, your bones, your liver, your kidneys, your heart, your
lungs, your muscles, skin, everything goes away. And if you don't have the raw materials
to replace it, then you get disease. And of course, the more high performance you are,
like an athlete, as Theo pointed out, you're sweating out these nutrients. And so you actually
break down faster than a librarian. For instance, there's hundreds of librarians every year
who reach 100 years of age. The average lifespan of a professional athlete in America is 62.
A football player, the average professional football player in America, lives to be 51.
With the exception of a couple of black guys in the old Negro baseball league days, there's
never been a professional athlete ever lived to be 100. The people who you find living
to be 100 are these little old ladies living out in the swamps Louisiana with no utilities,
no education, never see a doctor, and they live to be 114. And librarians, they don't
have knee replacements, and they live to be 100. And they don't exercise. They sit on
a chair and they work on the computer all day in an air conditioned place. They don't
sweat. And it's not because of genetics, it's because they don't need as many nutrients
to maintain themselves as somebody who's a high performance athlete like a guy like Theo.
Just amazing. And again, it's common sense that you need more minerals and vitamins.
And it's common sense that if you don't get vitamin C, you get scurvy and your skin rots
off. I mean, it's common sense, but it's hiding there just in plain view in front of everyone.
And I can say this more than anything about the longevity products, that the more I take
of them, the better I feel. I'm trying to habitualize myself like friends and family
have done to take it all, but I've just never been good at that.
But I can tell you the big thing is just energy. And it's just been amazing. And I hope listeners
will check out infowarshealth.com. They're on the bottom of the site. We also have the
toll free numbers for anybody that wants to call. It's 888-636-9277. Or for new customers
that want to sign up and get discounts, 888-789-9277. Call and sign up and get the free shipping
deal, the auto ship. Or also it's time to be a distributor. It's time for like 10 bucks
and then get other discounts, 888-789-9277.
Gentlemen, thank you so much for spending time with us today. I'm sorry, I rescheduled
last week when I had to fly up to New York to be on CNN. And hopefully we can get Theo
back sometime just to tell some NBA stories. But I'll say this in closing. Theo, a couple
times when I was out in Hollywood, I got taken to parties and saw a lot of retired NBA players,
some of them very famous.
And I noticed that when you see them on ESPN, they're not hobbling with canes. But these
are guys that weren't even that old and all of them were kind of hobbling and you could
tell were in pain. And so what you were saying, I didn't know that. They kind of cover that
up. You're on the inside of this. How many of these guys that are only 45, 50, can't
even walk?
There's a lot. I mean, you wouldn't believe the numbers because a lot of guys end up retiring
early because of an injury. So that injury doesn't rehabilitate themselves just because
they retire. And they end up, like I said, with the knee replacements, the hip replacements
and different joint diseases. So that's why it's my mission to go and make sure I at least
disseminate the information and try to get some of these guys healthy.
All right, well, thank you so much for spending time with us. And I really appreciate it.
We look forward to having you guys back on. Find out more about Rebound FX in the liquid
and the powder available at mfolwarshealth.com. Theo and Dr. Wallach, thank you so much, gentlemen.
All right. Thank you. Super job.
Thank you, sir. God bless you. Okay. Again, I had those guys shut up last week. We have
somebody off from Young Jevity at least once a month. I really believe in it. And it supports
the info war. We're not like the government that takes your tax money and then gives it
to MSNBC or CNN or the governments of Bahrain giving money to folks over at CNN.
That's come out with Amber Lyon. All of that. We're gonna open the phones up in the third
hour. I'm gonna be honest with you. I am so shell shocked by the Second Amendment stuff
happening and all coming true, nightmare coming true that I was glad we had that health interview
shut up.
Normally, I would have just canceled it again because the news is so serious. I was glad
to become distracted with something I can do like go jog or take a vitamin drink or
something and try to help people because I am just completely freaked out. And I know
you're freaked out too.
It's just that sinking feeling. It's like I told you three months ago, I said I got
a bad feeling and I've never had one like this. And of course, it's intellectual too
with all the political information I had. I've been all over the map with you guys with
the clips of what's coming up next.
We're gonna come back from break and play a very important report Aaron Dykes did that's
just unbelievably important. Sheriff says teachers should be armed. Second Amendment
shall not be infringed. We're gonna play that but right now before we go to break cuz it
ties into the sheriff saying the same thing basically.
Here's Judge Head over one of the big West Texas towns. Lubbock, this is before the election
saying look, they're gonna try gun confiscation. There's gonna be a 1776 and I need more deputies
to get ready for this.
We're not gonna turn the guns in and then suddenly there's sheriffs and police chiefs
all over the country and city councils who are now moving in this direction. In fact,
so many of these are coming in. I can't even keep track of them right now. And you watch
the sheriff and he starts to cry.
You can hear him cuz he realizes what he's committing to. It's the sadness. He says I'm
so sad. It's not a fear of Obama. It's very sad. And that's the sound I feel like I should
make just. Man, they're gonna take everything. The fact they're going after the guns that
means they mean business.
It's time to pray. I'm gonna tell you right now because listen, they're gonna push till
you resist. They want you to resist. There's no way out of this. You understand that? There's
no way out. The only hope we've got is breaking the trance, breaking the spell, getting angry.
Now here's Judge Head. We come back, I'll play the other sheriff and others that are
coming out.
And I was watching this clip last night. I watched this morning, this sheriff. And you
can hear him getting chills. You hear him when he's talking and go, and it's not fear.
It's man, because everybody knows in their gut. That's why everybody's out buying 10
million guns a month right now. But you hear the, let's go to Judge Head. Here it is.
He is gonna try to hand over the sovereignty of the United States to the UN. Okay, what's
gonna happen when that happens? I'm thinking worst case scenario.
Right, right.
Civil unrest, civil disobedience, civil war, maybe. And we're not talking just a few riots
here and demonstrations. We're talking Lexington, Concord, take up arms and get rid of the guy.
Okay, now what's gonna happen if we do that? If the public decides to do that? He's gonna
send in UN troops. I don't want them in Lubbock County. Okay, so I'm gonna stand in front
of their armored personnel carriers and say, you're not coming in here. And the sheriff,
I've already asked him, I said, you're gonna back me? He said, yeah, I'll back you. Well,
I don't want a bunch of rookies back there.
All right.
True.
I want trained.
Full clip is up at infowars.com, so they're having to get ready. People say that guy's
crazy and never happened. No, that's the guy who knows what's going on. That's an American
right there. You either capitulate to the globalist and say, I give up, occupy us, carry
on a Gena 21 or resist.
Hey there, Frank Bates here. Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out
280 million Americans? This is really scary stuff. Defense experts warn that this odd
device poses the gravest threat we've ever known. In fact, just a few weeks ago, former
speaker of the house Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed piece for the Washington Post warning
about this deadly threat. I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up. That's why my friend
just created a free video at weirddevice.com that exposes this threat and blows the doors
off the conspiracy. Go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover
exactly what it is, plus discover the number one way you and your family can survive this
deadly attack. I'm not sure how long this video will be online, so go to weirddevice.com
before it's gone forever. Again, that's weirddevice.com.
You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa, where a nicely furnished cabin
with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine, and laundry service awaits. After
a good night's sleep, your adventure begins. You're on a golden stag safari for big game.
But it's not Africa, it's Argentina. One-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo, huger, bighorn
rams, wild boar, and the biggest stag deer in South America. All gold medal quality.
All the action you can handle. Land rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages,
hunting guides, ground transportation included, and more, all more affordable than you can
imagine. The adventure of a lifetime starts at goldenstagsafaris.com. The big game hunting
ranch. Goldenstagsafaris.com. We all know that Berkey water purification
systems are the most trusted name in water filtration. As an authorized Berkey dealer
for over six years and serving thousands of satisfied customers, the Berkey guy offers
amazing specials for Berkey water filtration systems. The Berkey light systems include
a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable black purification elements that purify water
by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria, cysts and parasites to non-detectable levels
and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides. Order the Berkey light system
today complete with two black Berkey elements for only $231 and the Berkey guy will ship
your order free of charge. With the purchase of a Berkey light, the Berkey guy is also
offering a set of fluoride and arsenic filters for only $39.99. That's over 30% off the
retail price. Call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653. That's 1-877-886-3653. Or order online at
goberky.com. That's goberky.com today.
My friends, do you want to be conquered? You want to be run by fire and ruthless, eugenicist
based banks who've wrecked every other country they dominate as a tool of control? Well,
you're going to get what you want. Everybody else better get real aggressive. Just like
I said a couple months ago when I said 1776, part two, we got to get politically aggressive.
We got to move for secession because the federal government's been taken over. Succede to re-upload
the republic, not to get rid of the republic. They're going to act like Obama used the George
Washington rolled into Lincoln and is there to save us.
That's how they're billing him and now they're officially saying that. He's going to take
your guns. Lincoln was a dictator. Obama can do it. That's the sales pitch and they're
trying to see if he can get away with it right now. They want to take this country over right
now. This is the biggest news since 1776. What's happening right now? They're going
for broke, okay?
Let's go ahead and go to Aaron Dykes special report on this. Here it is.
Aaron Dykes for infowars.com. Now we've already seen a big pushback against the system's gun
control agenda. Now we're hearing from Rahm Emanuel that if you're not in law enforcement,
if you're not a police officer, you need to shut your mouth and not weigh in on the Second
Amendment.
Put the police chief in the law enforcement community front and center. Everybody else
from politician to whatever, take a back seat because the police chiefs have a credibility
and authority and a voice on this.
First of all, we're not going to give up our First Amendment as you try to destroy the
Second Amendment. We will never give up our First Amendment. We will never give up our
Second Amendment. They're inalienable rights. They are not to be infringed. We're not going
to be lectured to by the mayor of the murder capital of the world, Chicago, as you try
to get these insane policies passed all around the country. But second of all, you haven't
been listening to law enforcement who've been speaking up across the country saying we will
not infringe.
We will not enforce any unconstitutional gun laws. We heard a week and a half, two weeks
ago from the Pennsylvania police chief of the small town who's introducing a Second
Amendment defense ordinance to protect and keep the Second Amendment and saying they're
going to nullify any laws which are unconstitutional and otherwise trying to infringe. We've seen
Wyoming lawmakers and others trying to introduce legislation upholding the Second Amendment
and reminding and sending the message back to Washington that they too will not be in
part of infringing on the Second Amendment.
And that's really what we need. We need people recognizing their legal jurisdiction at the
state, local and county level and saying no, we're not going to cooperate with the feds.
We will not participate in destroying our God given and guaranteed rights. Now we're
hearing from Sheriff Denny Payman of Jackson County, Kentucky. He too is saying he will
not enforce federal gun grabbing laws. He's standing up for his oath. He's recognizing
the fact that he is the highest law enforcement officer in his jurisdiction at the county
level and that even the feds do not have higher jurisdiction there and cannot tell him what
to do.
If Obama passes this, it doesn't matter what he passes. The sheriff has more power than
the federal people. They need to go back and they study that. We're a commonwealth. I can
ask the federal people to leave. They have to leave. I can ask state people to leave.
They have to leave.
And he's being asked by journalists how he's going to participate in confiscating guns
that dangerous task.
You're never going to pull a gun from Jackson County. I can't get their equipment to help
those people. My best help to them is to let them keep their firearm. I can't do it for
the other counties. I can't stand up for them, but I can't stand up for my people. And you
know, I was one of the first people to say, I think they need to arm school teachers.
Not all of them, but they need, there's somebody that needs to have a weapon.
And it's so clear what's going on that this sheriff is saying the founding fathers will
be turning over in their graves.
Second amendment, they said very clear and our forefathers made that very clear. Otherwise
they would have been so high on the amendment. It would have been down the list someplace
to me. And I would be ashamed if one of them was in this room right now and having to listen
to what we're having to talk about. I would be ashamed to have them sit here and listen
to all the people that have given their lives for this right for us. And we just give it
up so flippantly just because somebody says so.
First of all, you shouldn't want to participate in destroying the things that make this country
great. Our country was different. That's why the bill of rights and the constitution gave
us the quote 5,000 year leap. Second of all, this whole time, that full report is up at
info wars.com. Third hour coming up. You are listening to GCN. Visit GCN live.com today.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now. Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog. Waging war on corruption. Alex Jones on the GCN radio
network. Big brother, mainstream media, government cover ups. You want answers? Well so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
We are now into our number three. I am calling for the states. I'm calling for members of
Congress, everybody to circulate their own bill of particulars dealing with the crimes
of this administration and impeachable offenses. We need to issue a petition for the executive
wannabe dictator to be impeached.
Let's not talk about starting impeachment proceedings. We need to list the bill of impeachment.
That's what we'll call it at mfullawards.com with our points in case people don't know
all the stuff this president's done. I was sitting here thinking during the last few
hours during the breaks about all the different things, all the different things that Obama
has done that are completely unconstitutional.
The secret orders on cyber security and telling Congress they can't see him. Saying our troops
are under UN control and that Congress has no authority over that. Now saying you'll
sign executive orders on guns, lying to Congress, fast and furious. Congress not doing anything
about it. I know Congress is bad, but it's their job to impeach this guy. Do it, start
it now. This is super creepy.
You've got an armed to the teeth, crazy government, working for a bunch of foreign banks, training
at all these military drills to kill role players and John Deere hats and overalls.
And they practice killing grandpa, folks. I've been to the drills, I've shot video,
you've seen them. Troops have called in, yeah, no, we practice killing rural people. They
practice killing my granddaddy. They practice killing old men on tractors.
They know who isn't gonna go along with this. There's not many Americans left, I guess.
Go wipe out old country people. Bunch of sick traders, man, I cannot believe we've gotten
this low in this country. And I mean, is there nothing we won't put up with? Secret arrest,
warrantless wiretapping, torture, the government, we're running Al-Qaeda.
That's another thing, I wanna start impeachment over the Libya and Syria attacks when Congress
said don't do it and the president did it. And then impeachment for our government giving
weapons to Al-Qaeda, that's the big one. Now arming Al-Qaeda, arming Al-Qaeda. Let's go,
let's go.
Look, I don't like to get up here and say 1776 part two, states secede to get rid of
the federal government and then re-upload it. A novel approach to what's constitutional,
I've had constitutional scholars on to agree with my analysis. I told you months ago, people
are like, why are you calling for his impeachment now?
Why are you calling for 1776? Because they were saying what they were gonna do. And then
right on time, the enabling crisis comes and it smells to high heaven. So when we come
back, we're gonna be taking your phone calls here today. Specifically on what do you think
you should be impeached for? Or do you disagree with me?
And there's so many things that are impeachable. I'm thinking of new ones every few minutes.
So you call in with what we should call it. I mean, the Bill of Particulars, the Bill
of Impeachment for Barack Hussein Obama, that's what it's called, starts in the House. They
vote to then have a trial in the Senate. I mean, it's time to go after Obama. He's their
front man, he's their puppet, but he's the usurper.
And look, I'm not some macho guy looking for trouble, but I'm not gonna be a slave. And
I know what's going on. 800-259-9231 on this issue of treason, the executive orders. And
they're playing this game of, yeah, I can do an executive order. I can't take everything
with executive order, but I can take some stuff.
You can't take anything. The Congress can't even pass a law to take our guns, folks, because
it is unalienable. You cannot put a lien on it, inalienable. The Bill of Rights points
out what's already there organically. I am not your slave. You are not getting my guns.
And it's not the obsession over the guns, okay? My guns aren't even locked and loaded
except for handguns and stuff for self-defense. It's the bellwether, the canary in the coal
mine.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die? Start purifying your water with ProPure. My friends, I've done
a lot of research, and the best gravity filter out there bar none is ProPure. And it's available
discounted at infowars.com. Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required. It's NSF-42 certified. Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride
up to 95%. Easy to set up and use. Doesn't require electricity. Purify water from lakes,
streams, ponds, and wells. This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic. ProPure
is the best gravity fed filter out there. It's what my family uses. Infowars.com already
has the lowest price on ProPure. But if you add the promo code water at checkout, you
get an additional 10% off at infowars.com. You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers. The prognosis for the entire planetary
economic system runs from bad to worse. The globalist model is to shut down societies
and starve patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover. That's why we've assembled
the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarsshop.com. These are items
that I did research on that I personally use. You've got the life straw so you can turn
fetid water into safe water anywhere you go. The Ktor hand crank generator to charge up
key equipment during power outages or out in the field. Strategic relocation third edition
by Joel Skousen. When disaster strikes by Matthew Stein. TheraSafe used by Homeland
Security to protect yourself during any radiological event. Hand crank shortwave AM-FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com
and your purchase makes our Infowars possible. We're getting prepared. Are you? Infowarsshop.com.
Looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote
almost all the grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to
be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than
one day too late. I can warn you but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do what Alex
has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build your
food supply. It's the best tasting non-GMO long term storeable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
From the front lines of the information war it's Alex Jones. Well all of you claimed you'd
fight back if they came to confiscate the guns. Obama thinks you're weak and he thinks
you're going to turn them in.
Coming to you from the front lines of the info war and we're trying to keep it an info
war. Bloomberg is in the news. Those articles are up at Infowars.com saying defy Congress.
Just take the guns. The legislature has passed in the Senate a outright assault weapons confiscation.
Here's the Biden headline. Joe Biden. White House eyeing 19 executive actions on guns.
Executive orders. White House to announce the executive orders tomorrow. They are to
include assault weapons ban. Ban of magazines that hold more than seven rounds. It's the
Chicago gun ban. It's the Illinois gun ban. It's the universal background checks and limits
on the number of bullets magazines can hold. And that's retroactive. They're saying you
can't, you have to come in and register all your guns because you're not allowed now to
sell it to your neighbor ever.
According to sources familiar with the White House, or people working for the White House.
Iowa lawmaker calls for retroactive gun ban, house to house gun confiscation of all semi-autos.
CBS News, New York Assembly, Speaker, Silver. We are going to ban assault weapons, all semi-autos
to be turned in. And the bill has passed the Senate. It's in the legislative session in
the House. This is just unprecedented. And it says you come in and register them and
we can take them on the spot if we want.
That's what Cuomo called for two and a half weeks ago, remember? I mean, they got a plan.
We know what it is. And then they'll get most the guns in this push, then there'll be more
mass shootings. And they'll say that's it, just turn them in. And then they know there'll
be resistance. Let me explain what's happening everybody here, okay?
The toll free number to join us on air is 800-259-9231, 800-259-9231. And we will get
you up and on the air today. A foreign criminal banking mafia took over the United States
with the Federal Reserve with a beachhead in 1913. They used our energy, our power,
our taxes to dominate most of the world and set up a world government.
It's European banks, that's why we're merging with the EU basically. Those very same banks
funded Lenin to get him into power, to get rid of that national sovereignty the Russians
had. That's now been declassified. The same banks put Mao in to kill over 60 million people,
some estimates are 80 plus mil, and to bring in that tyranny, that's a deal.
They set up tyrannies all over the world. They put Muslim extremists in Libya and Syria.
They're bad, their fruits are bad. They're really vicious. The people running our government
have put real al-Qaeda in with al-Qaeda flags, al-Qaeda brigades, black uniforms with al-Qaeda
patches. They are cutting Christians heads off on camera, the news thinks it's great.
They are making father's suicide bomb or they kill their whole families. They are shooting
at passenger airliners and blowing them up. And our media is like good, al-Qaeda is good.
Back of the newspaper, al-Qaeda is doing a great job attacking Assad, who didn't do anything
to anybody.
That's how bold and how evil they are, okay? They think you're so dumb, the people running
our country run al-Qaeda. And that's mainstream news. And even Glenn Beck admits that now,
but calls me a traitor for saying our government runs al-Qaeda all these years. Why don't I
get an apology?
This isn't our government. And they have stolen 1.5 quadrillion in fake derivative money and
they've signed us onto it. And it's hundreds of times what we could ever pay back. It's
not our debt. Our real debt's about 16 trillion. And they use that to control us and tell us
how we're debtors all day from the most wealthy nation in the world to the biggest debtor
nation in the world in 50 years.
From the highest test scores to the lowest, from the lowest cancer rate to the highest.
We are a cursed, overtaken nation of debt slaves. They're now starting forced inoculations
all over the country of school children outside of parental consent, abortions without parental
consent. They just do what they want. And it's a felony every time they do it. No one
will enforce. No attorney general will go after them. No county attorney, no city attorney,
no one will stand up.
Now we're starting to see state reps and federal, mainly people in Texas, Kentucky, Wyoming,
places like that, places that the television demonizes, places the occupier collaborators
demonize. They're starting to say, look, this is gonna go 1776. We're gonna nullify taking
guns. Don't come in the state and do this.
Don't, don't do this. Don't, don't, don't. Cuz everybody knows they, when they come for
the guns, they're super bold, and they're gonna drop the hammer on 100 different fronts.
The globalists are all going to go to prison unless they go for it all. The Chicago mafia,
Emanuel, the DC mafia, the New York mafia, Bloomberg. They are the government mafia.
They are the federal family. So that's what Janet calls them in letters. You are the federal
family. The federal cancer, the federal family is taking over. The federal family is gonna
double your power prices. The federal family is gonna triple your, they do the same thing
in every other country, okay?
They have an IMF World Bank 112 point plan. They're gonna implement it, all of it, right
down the middle. And when you go bankrupt, they're gonna say, we got food stamps for
you. We got full steps. We got social security. They want you broke. And then they're gonna
have the conservatives say, make all these people hundreds of millions on welfare work.
Now you're gonna be in government work brigades. Now you're gonna be government security brigades.
This is the takeover. This is the collectivization. That's why they're going after farmers. That's
why they're going after ranchers. That's why they're going after anybody that's self-sufficient.
That's why they outlawed two years ago cash and secondhand sales in Louisiana. And they're
actually putting people in jail for using cash. That's why they're surveilling us. That's
why they're opening the borders.
That's why they're getting ready to legalize all the illegal aliens, because they're gonna
break this country. And they know you're not gonna turn your guns in and they're gonna
pick you off one at a time. And they know some of you are gonna start fighting back
and you're gonna be called terrorist on the news.
And as they see patriots getting arrested, as they see police chiefs getting killed that
don't play ball, as they see federal troops enter legislatures, they are gonna be on the
news calling us terrorist and calling Obama Abraham Lincoln part two.
Texas threatens to arrest any feds who try enforcing new gun rags. White House readies
19 executive orders. Obama to surround himself with children to announce the new gun controls.
See, it's for the children while he kills kids with the drones. Click on that top article.
It's also up at mfallwars.com. W-O-A-I, TV and radio, Texas proposal, jail any federal
officials trying to enforce new gun restrictions in the state.
And what did the feds say last year when the House voted unanimously to not let the TSA
grab our genitals and enforce party laws on the books? They said we'll have an armed F-16
blockade and we will shoot down aircraft entering or flying out of your state. Bring it, come
on, Obama. You already got Al Qaeda shooting down airlines in Europe or threatening to
and shooting them down in Middle East.
Go ahead, do it, you scum. You're an American usurper, you filth. We put that article back
up there. I mean, it's on. A Texas lawmaker says, I want them on right now, guys, call
them. A Texas lawmaker says, it's gonna be impossible in an hour. Everybody call that
number right now, get them on.
A Texas lawmaker says he plans to file the Firearms Protection Act, which would make
any federal laws that may be passed, yeah, we reported on this yesterday, by Congress
or imposed by presidential order, which would ban or restrict ownership of semi-automatic
firearms or the limit the size of the gun magazines illegal in the state.
WOAI 1200 reports, Republican Representative Steve Toth, good for him, says his measure
also calls for felony charges to be filed against internal federal official, how about
servant who tries to enforce the rule in the state. If a federal official comes to the
state of Texas to enforce the federal executive order, they already have all the states and
counties on arresting legal aliens, that's constitutional.
Why can't we do this? See, if a federal official comes into the state of Texas to enforce the
federal executive order, that person is subject to criminal prosecution. Toth told 1200 WOAI
Joe Pags, listen to Joe Pags on the morning. I heard Joe Pags say it's okay to pay off
the police when they want payoffs last week, I couldn't believe it.
Let's go back to that, let's just go back to that article, thank you. Toth told 1200
WOAI Joe Pags, he says his bill would make attempting to enforce a federal gun ban in
Texas punishable by $50,000 five years in prison. Toth says he will file the measure
after speaking with the state Republican Attorney General, Greg Abbott, who has already vowed
to fight any federal measures which call for restrictions on weapons possession.
Toth concedes that he would welcome a legal fight over his proposals. At some point, there
needs to be a showdown between the state and the federal government over the supremacy
clause, he said. Darn right, I want Toth on. You know what Toth means, and what is it,
Hungarian?
That's death to gun control right there. Dr. Death for the gun bill. Man, ladies and gentlemen,
we need to deal with this. I got a new favorite person, this state rep. I want him on, I want
him on, I want him on. We gotta get on the offensive now. It's gonna be horrible, Obama's
gonna be surrounded by little kids when we have to protect him. How about from government
tyranny?
How about from all the kids you've been drone attacking? It's for the kids. I mean, how
manipulative, how evil. We need to have counter demonstrations and counter press conferences
with children. And say the federal government took guns out of schools and then the media
advertise it as shooting zones.
The blood's on your hands. The blood's on your hands, man, I'm so glad I got in the
face of Piers Morgan. I'm so glad I raised the Paul Revere alarm. I'm so glad. That's
what's gonna beat him is getting hardcore, not backing off to this. 800-25-99231, 800-25-99231.
They're coming, they're coming, drums, drums, drums in the deep. Now they're here. Told
you I heard the drums, now they're here.
They are coming, they are coming. Your call straight ahead, straight ahead. Stay with
us. Spread the word. Everybody tune in now. Key intel coming up and I'm calling for the
impeachment. I'm writing the bill of impeachment.
My name is Stephen Huir. After 22 years of nutritional counseling, I've observed that
most brain malfunctions have at their roots some form of toxicity and brain damage. So
whether it is poor memory, poor focus, lack of creative thinking, or more serious matters
like inability to focus, speak normally, or remember things, the emphasis to getting one's
brain working optimally needs to be on detoxification. One World Way supports your body's number
one means of detoxification, which is glutathione production.
My name is Angie and my son has suffered from borderline autism and constipation. I got
him on One World Way and in two months his constipation is gone. He has become friendlier,
he can carry on a normal conversation with me, and he has made his first friend. He's
doing great and he looks forward to taking One World Way every day. You could offer him
a present or a cake and he would prefer the One World Way.
Go to OneWorldWay.com, that's OneWorldW-H-E-Y.com or call 888-988-3325, that's 888-988-3325.
We travel so much and having a fake TV gives added peace of mind.
Burglars look for houses that appear to be easy targets, but fake TV can fool even professional
burglars into thinking someone is home watching television.
As a recent widow living alone, it gives me great peace of mind to set my fake TV near
a window and know that passing motorists and pedestrians will think someone is home watching
TV when I'm actually away from home.
Fake TV easily plugs into any outlet, just like a light on a timer.
And they're so easy to use, you just plug them in and they're ready to go. Plus, they're
so affordable that we have one upstairs and downstairs.
Fake TV is only $34.95. Order your fake TV by calling 877-5FAKETV or go to Faketv.com.
That's 877-532-5388 or Faketv.com.
Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
Gold, it's like nothing else on earth. From the Romans through the Renaissance, from the
industrial age to the space age, gold has weathered the test of time. For 6,000 years,
gold has remained the ultimate store of wealth. According to the World Gold Council and the
U.S. Mint, demand is at an all-time high. The stage is being set for the reemergence
of gold as the common sense alternative to a fiat paper currency that gets weaker every
day.
Midas Resources is proud to offer the hard-hitting report that arms you with the truth you need
to protect you and your family from the Fed's plans for your hard-earned money. Don't gamble
with your future. Call Midas Resources today and ask for your free copy of As Good as Gold.
Call 1-800-686-2237 for the report the Fed hopes you'll never see. As Good as Gold can
be yours by calling 800-686-2237. If you have ever thought about owning gold, you must read
this report. Call Midas today at 800-686-2237.
Food storage? Check. Survival tools? Check. Weapons and water filters? Check. But what
about a permanent source of cooking power that can run forever without buying fuel or
paying for maintenance? Introducing Afterburner Stoves, home of the original patented rocket
stove, the Kelly Kettle, and the Solo stove. Afterburner Stoves has what you need and now
offers all GCN listeners our complete preparedness package with the means to cook meals and sanitize
water. Whether you dig in or bug out, cook almost any meal with just a handful of sticks.
We already have the lowest online prices guaranteed, but if you enter coupon code GCN at checkout,
we'll knock off an additional 15% and send you our amazing 6-hour solar rechargeable
light bulb absolutely free. All for only $249. Visit Afterburnerstoves.com or call 866-716-5214.
Afterburnerstoves.com. Cook hot meals with just a handful of sticks.
Okay, I'm gonna go to your phone calls as promised and Paul Watson out here in the brakes
are working on a bill of impeachment for Obama. So people can take our research and get it
into official documents. And that is the point of this. Bill of impeachment of Obama for
sedition and treason against the Republic of the United States of America. Boom, that's
your headline.
And then you take the Declaration of Independence and you basically rewrite it at the top. It's
the same thing. Whereas we've seen a long train of abuses against the Bill of Rights,
the Constitution, a president who's used his office to turn us over to NATO and UN control
that has publicly told Congress that the UN gives him orders and not the Congress who
has openly been fomenting and working with media, including foreign media, to overthrow
our Second Amendment.
And then you just break down the fact that it is an absolute imperative for Congress
not to have all of their just powers completely usurped. That Obama has signed secret directives
on cybersecurity and blocked Congress from seeing it when it is their right and their
duty. I mean, I've listed a whole laundry list of this, but it's two or three paragraphs
written like the Declaration of Independence.
You can read Clinton's bill of impeachment. It just states what he's done. That Obama
lied to Congress and lied to the people saying he didn't want the NDAA passed when he had
written it. And then said he wouldn't sign it and then did, lying. That's the president
lying to Congress. He wrote letters to Congress saying don't pass this when behind the scenes
he'd written letters saying pass it.
That's lying, that's perjury. Violating his oath of office on so many fronts, shutting
down power plants, implementing Kyoto protocols, even though Congress three years ago did not
pass the Kyoto greenhouse gas legislation. I mean, it's incredible. Giving selective
waivers to thousands of companies that are donors for that under Obamacare.
I mean, the list goes on and on here. I know Watson's listening right now. He's codifying
it all and I'll work with him more when the show's over. But we're gonna get this out
on infowars.com and prisonplanet.com. And it is absolutely essential that you get this
bill of impeachment because that's how impeachment works.
It goes through the House for a vote and you have a trial in the Senate. And if there was
any justice in this world, Obama would be impeached. We're gonna list Fast and Furious
and the lying to Congress about that. Look, look, look, he's getting away with everything.
And they're going to go for broke. And then finally, we need to state in the declaration
that we know that the criminals are moving, the usurpers, the occupiers for these corporate
foreign banks are doing this because they think they can win.
They think they've got enough dirt, enough blackmail, and enough everything that they
can get this through. And even if they can't, it gets us used to the idea of a dictator.
And whereas members of the Senate have pointed out that he's becoming a king, that's right.
And we kicked a king out of here in 1776, we've got to do it again.
And whereas Obama is trying to block arming the schools so they can protect themselves
and trying to bar the public from their ancient common right, common law right to self-defense,
he must be removed. And again, people say, well, Obama's a puppet.
Yes, they've all been puppets for a long time. But this guy is the head puppet and he's the
titular head of this treason. He's moving at warp speed. And Mitt Romney supported banning
guns as well.
I warned you folks that the fix was in either way you slice it. And if you think you're
just gonna turn your guns in and this is all gonna stop, you're gravely mistaken. There
will be people that resist this. And if there isn't, they will manufacture it to call them
terrorists to start the great purge. Homeland Security is a Soviet-style NKVD, okay?
That's what it is. That's why they popularized torture. By the way, he used to be impeached
for Benghazi, lying about that, saying he didn't know. Turned out they did know, add
that to the bill of impeachment. Missiles being sent to Al Qaeda with the Turkish ambassador,
add it to the impeachment, all of it.
There are crimes out in the open. Don't you wrap a bunch of kids up there around you on
the stage and say, I'm coming for your guns. Here's my executive order to see if you can
get away with this. Don't you do it. They want world government. These foreign banks
want unified, 80% worldwide taxes.
They can't stand the mafia in Chicago and New York that people are running down to places
like Texas and other areas that have lower taxes and more freedom. They want a worldwide
mafia where they're armed, you're not, and they can do whatever they want to you. Well,
I got news, thugs. You're going to lose. You've miscalculated. The sleeping giant is awakening.
10 million guns are getting sold a month.
We're on the march. The empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health at silver lungs. We are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver based products. Our most popular silver based products are
the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well
as our all natural silver soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver
gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver
at the surface, but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the
silver more effectively. Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver
based products are best for you. That's www.silverlungs.com.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to www.supernaturalsilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's www.supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key. Save money by not buying bottled
water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic. Propure is the best gravity fed filter
out there. It's what my family uses. Infowars.com already has the lowest price on Propure, but
if you add the promo code water at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at Infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center and the heart of the resistance.
Traveling patriots worldwide. You're listening to the Alex Jones Show.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm proud of Texas. We're not perfect, but you notice we're national
news everywhere. Texas has the bill to arrest feds down here trying to take our guns. Texas
tried to get the bill passed, got killed by Perry at the top, unanimously in the house,
passed it to arrest the TSA.
Texas just introduced the legislation and our state representatives calling for the
impeachment of Barack Obama for high crimes and misdemeanors. It's happening. And I come
to you from the capital of Texas, Austin. I come to you from the heart of the resistance.
We are here. We are standing to the end. This is only the beginning, ladies and gentlemen.
This is only the beginning. And again, if we give the guns up, it's over. If you give
the guns up, they're gonna take everything. They will steal everything. They will shut
the economy down.
That is the Agenda 21 plan. These are hardcore criminals in government. I know a lot of congressmen
and women listen to this show in Tennessee and Virginia, you name it. I know I've talked
to them off air. I've had them on as guests, a lot of them. And they know, they privately
completely agree with me.
Well, it's now time to go public. Time to get up there on the floor of the house and
go, you are a crook, Obama. Okay, we either get in their face hardcore right now, or they're
gonna bring in tyranny, martial law. They're gonna hunt us down. They are gonna one by
one come after us.
And then if we resist to defend ourselves, we're gonna be called terrorist. We have got
to hit them while we still have the Internet and we still have talk radio with everything
we've got and stop playing Mr. Nicey Pants. Paul Revere rode through saying, to arms,
to arms, the redcoats are coming.
All I did was go on stand and say, you're on notice. You know this is gonna start 1776
part two if you try this. You redcoat? He's a redcoat. A guy fleeing justice in England.
I mean, give me a pirate. I'm here where my family's been for 300 plus years in the United
States.
I'm here in Texas where we've been since 1830 or even before. I'm here. I'm here. I'm in
a corner. I've got a right to self defense. I'm not your slave. I declare that natural
right before God in the universe. And it's time you declare it as well. By the way, the
Bundesbank's pulling their gold out of the US.
How many countries? It's more than 20 countries in the last year, since early 2012, that have
pulled their gold out of the US. That article's up at infullwars.com. German Bundesbank to
repatriate gold from New York Fed. Trust in central banks by other central banks is ending.
That's a mainstream media headline by the New York Fed. The trust is over. That's why
they want the guns. These people are crooks. They should all be in jail like Bernie Madoff.
You put Ken Lay and Bernie Madoff in jail. You put all these banksters, these Federal
Reserve top board members, a lot of their own board members have been saying it's tyranny.
Even board members have been saying what's happening is wrong, cuz they realize they're
gonna bring the whole thing down.
You know they've had the Dallas Fed head, the Kansas City Fed head, and others come
out and say what the Fed's doing is criminal? Their own people are saying it's criminal
publicly, because it's criminal. And listen, I'm not asking, I'm commanding police and
military as a sovereign citizen.
Just like you have citizens arrest, I'm giving you a citizens order to another citizen. You
know why I give you that order? You swore before God and man to protect and defend the
Constitution from all enemies foreign and domestic. And our Constitution is in shreds
right now.
They're trying to burn what's left of it. And if you won't hit the streets right now
aggressively, I don't care what you've got to do. I'm thinking about putting bullhorns
on the top of my car and driving around at 2 AM in neighborhoods bullhorning. And when
the cops pull up with their lights on and jump out and freak out, I'm gonna go, what
am I supposed to do?
I'm just Paul Revere driving through the night saying you're in danger. Our government's
been taken over by foreign powers. And see, that's a psy-op of truth. People only pay
attention cuz they've never been warned in their sleep. I'm serious, I may put bullhorns
on my truck tonight and drive around announcing to people that the redcoats are coming.
Not saying the arms to arms, to info arms, because people will wake up. See, they're
in a comfort zone. They've got a normalcy bias. They've got a Stockholm syndrome, a
learned helplessness to put up with anything. I wouldn't ask you to do that. I am intending
soon to start doing midnight rides.
I'm gonna start driving through neighborhoods. And if the cops arrest me, so be it. Because
I'm gonna start telling people, get up, get up when they come out. I'm gonna get out with
a bullhorn at night and say, Paul Revere, road to warn you what was happening.
Our country's been taken over by foreign banks. They're like, what are you doing, crazy man?
I'm crazy. You think you're gonna be free watching ESPN all day? You think you're gonna
be free not knowing about politics and not being involved? No, you're gonna be overrun
and made a slave if you don't defend your freedom, Thomas Jefferson.
That's how domesticated and sick the public is, that they see it weird when you hang a
banner hang on the highway about tyranny. Or when you call into radio and get upset.
I was on The Young Turks on Al Gore's foreign-owned TV thing last night. And they're going, you
need mental help. You need to go, yeah, I need mental help, don't I? I need mental help
because I know they're putting cancer viruses in the vaccines.
The top friend of the royal family, it's now being confirmed doing satanic rituals with
little kids. And it's not even a news item that why was this guy given total access to
the royal family? And it just confirms everything I already know. These are a bunch of child
molesting devil worshipers that run the New World Order.
They're evil. And people are like, that sounds crazy, really, that you don't know history.
Have you studied any historical groups? Scum always gets in control. That's why our forebearers
were this multi-thousand year leap forward, pointing out the evil and corruption of humankind,
especially at the top, and systems to tie that down and control it.
And now those final bulwarks are under absolute Alamo-level assault right now. I mean, this
is it, okay? This is a full-on assault. I know that we've got eugenicist criminals running
things. I've read countless books, they wrote how they're poisoning our food and water.
They think you're so dumb, they write confessions how they're killing us. And they know using
psychology how to hide it in plain view. Every cop, every military person, I command you
to follow your oath and to speak out and to resist this tyranny.
I command you, who have taken oaths to protect and defend, to speak out about what's happening.
I command the union heads, the politicians, all of the people that aren't pure evil, you
better decide what side you're on right now. And I command you, in the name of the Bill
of Rights, the Constitution, and the Declaration of Independence, not just the military and
the police.
But the public who has sat there on your hind ends, I command you, if you claim you're good
and you serve justice, I command you, in the name of the Republic, to activate now and
to stand up and to get in a posture of total resistance. But you think I came out and called
for a second American Revolution a few months ago cuz I was playing games?
I know what's happening. I know what's going on. I know what's happening. Listen, if we
just had regular old corrupt groups in who were really misguided and all this stuff,
I would not be this freaked out. Because I would say politically, we can fix it down
the road.
You're not gonna fix any of this. The pendulum isn't gonna swing back. The pendulum already
swung back. They know you hate them. They know you don't trust them. They didn't really
elect Obama. It's all a fraud, and they're coming for everybody. They want a hot takeover.
And if you don't know what a hot takeover is, look at what the Soviets did in the Ukraine
and Czechoslovakia.
Look at what Hitler did in Poland. If you don't know what a hot takeover is, it means
absolute war, guaranteed, and the globalists want the police to be killed. That's part
of the plan. Then they'll bring their scum in as the second wave. Let me tell you, I
can see it in their eyes.
The globalists are excited now. They're engaged. They're confident. And you know why they're
confident? They've been on the defensive. They're confident now because they're going
operational. They've already jumped out of the back of the plane, folks. They're already
coming in. They already pulled the trigger.
It's on. It's on. It is on. It is on. It is on. False flags, all of it. It is on. It
is on. It is on. You understand? These people put in the newspapers, they run Al-Qaeda.
And they saw the public suck their thumb. They went, okay, we're gonna take your guns
now.
We're gonna give your kids shots without telling you. We're gonna take your 12-year-old, give
them an abortion without telling you. We will raise your taxes. They're already saying they're
gonna raise the taxes again. They're already raising the payroll taxes on the entire population
that works. Man, they're sick. Let's go to the calls. Michelle, that's Michael in Canada.
You're on the air. Go ahead.
Hey, listen, Alex. First of all, I wanna say a couple of things about your appearances
on mainstream media lately. And number one is I cannot believe what a slimeball coward
that Piers Morgan is. To drag out the victim's families, to hide behind and throw rocks at
you from, what an act of absolute cowardice, betraying their very nature. Next thing I
wanna say about it is you have no idea still yet just what effect you are having with your
anger on the mainstream media. It is awakening and anger that's been there the whole time.
You are rousing people, giving them the permission themselves to get angry. And it's gonna unleash
their reaction and the response needed at this time.
Well, I just said, God, whatever you want me to do on the air, do it. And I just got
mad at that guy and that's what I did. And it's up to you guys what happens out of all
this. I mean, I am right up on the tip of the spear. I need everybody's prayers, but
whatever happens, I'm not in fear.
I'm only in fear that I won't work hard enough, I won't do a good enough job. We've gotta
get America out of the trance. America is in a ninnying trance. The average American
would come out and shoot Paul Revere today. Okay, we've got to get out of this trance,
this learned helplessness. God bless you, Michael.
Let's go ahead and talk to who's up next here. Let's go ahead and talk to Mark in Kansas.
Mark in Kansas, you're on the air, go ahead.
Yes, Alex. Thanks for taking the call. I just want to first off say that my family prays
for your family every day and we appreciate everything you do. The local Prestitude Media
broke a story today that Walmart is offering to employ any veteran that wants a job here
on the local media. And I just want to call attention to that. I hope that our veterans
don't fall for this McDonald's trinket in the Happy Meal bobble that they're gonna hang
out there in front of them and fall for that crap.
Walmart shouldn't have sold the slave goods all these years and been used to deindustrialize
our country. And Walmart shouldn't have promoted NAFTA and GATT. But no, yeah, exactly. They've
domesticated you now and we're down here in the pits kind of like telling us rub the lotion
on our skin.
They just want a good skin when they skin us.
Better way to surveil and keep a thumb on our veterans than to try and bring them into
the fold for 29 hours a week so that they don't have to pay the Obamacare tax on them
again. That being said, I hope our military and our veterans understand what that's all
about.
The other thing is I just implore that your listeners do anything that they can with their
state legislatures to try and get them to abolish.
Everyone should be driving to their state house now, whether it's in session or not,
and running up and down the halls getting in everybody's faces. Everybody should be
doing banner hangs. Everyone should be spending hours a day fighting, okay?
I mean, and again, just get aggressive, get the buzz going, wake up America, and just
keep pointing out criminals run Washington. They're not misguided liberals. These are
horrible authoritarian mafia thugs.
Yeah, the listeners need to understand we are financing our own enslavement. And just
one thought in getting off the air, when we can no longer feed the beast, the beast is
gonna feed on us, and we're almost there.
Well, that's how it always works. You're absolutely right. You're absolutely right. And that's
where it always goes to forced labor camps because the parasites always destroy everything.
And then finally just say, okay, you're gonna work in a forced labor camp for me.
And then there's never even goods there, so they always invade the next country to loot
them. I mean, this is what we have been overrun by absolute criminals. God bless you. Yeah,
I was looking at impeachment reasons in the Constitution. We're gonna add to the article
that Paul Watson and I are putting together, impeachment for high crimes and misdemeanors.
Perjury of oath. Swear to uphold the Constitution, authorize for war. I mean, boom, right there.
Said that the UN and NATO runs it, not Congress. Second Amendment, NATO. Birth certificate
issues, NDAA. Abuse of authority, Second Amendment, Libya, Fast and Furious, TSA, Fourth Amendment,
NDAA hoax.
EPA versus Cole, lying to Congress, abuse of executive orders to circumvent Congress
and bragging about it to the press. Missiles to Al-Qaeda, Libya, Syria. Bribery. I mean,
what do you call it when he gives waivers to companies that give him campaign donations?
Intimidations, Valerie Jarrett, misuse of assets, the vacations, the selective waivers
for EPA versus Cole, failures to supervise Fast and Furious. So you don't even have to
be consciously doing it, just dereliction of duty. Get out of here, you scum. Okay,
you got caught lying to Congress about Fast and Furious.
How about you killed all those people in Mexico and the US, you're impeached for that, along
with your stinking Attorney General. Fast and Furious, lying about Benghazi, missiles
to Al-Qaeda, lying about radiation dangers in the wake of Fukushima. And the 48 leaking
nuclear power plants, dereliction of duty goes on. Conduct unbecoming, and we go through
a big list of those, refusal to obey a lawful order, authorization for war.
Congress sent him a letter, said you can't do this, he still did it. Said I don't need
you, he was belligerent to Congress. Man, man, they're planning something big, they're coming
after the guns. I can just see when they blow up some buildings and then pose as saviors,
it's gonna be so sick. And the public's so soft too. Mark in Oregon, you're on the air,
go ahead.
Hello, brother Alex.
Good, go ahead sir, welcome.
Alex, I've got what I think are two of the most important points that could be made at
this point in time. And number one is simply that Joyce Riley is having an expose of all
of the gross inconsistencies of the Sandy Hook shooting, including the big red circle
around Sandy Hook on the map in the Batman movie.
Today or tomorrow, I thought maybe you'd have her on and she could go over things with him.
Yeah, that's an interesting idea. We've done some expose of that, we pretty much broke
the Batman information. Before it happened, we said Batman's a trigger movie. And the
media is like, why are they pointing at Batman now? Like we just randomly went and looked
in Batman and found Sandy Hook.
Bain mailed out, the movie producers had Bain mail out to hundreds of different media groups
a map of targets and one of them Sandy Hook. And then the other movie, before it had a
bunch of triggers in it, so I hear you, I hear you. Look, I just haven't gone there
because the general public doesn't understand why they do this stuff, it's too esoteric.
Obviously there were other shooters, obviously the Batman shooting. Again, that happened
with the Batman film. You get it, it's Batman, Batman in Colorado. He was under government
funding.
Feeling like there are too many pressures and demands on you? Losing sleep, worrying
about tests and school work, either on the run because your schedule is just too busy?
You may be under too much stress and it may be affecting your mind. Get your mental edge
back with Neutropic Mind Power from mindregard.com. Neutropic Mind Power is not a drug, but a
natural supplement. It's 12 powerful ingredients are natural and non-GMO, plus it's gluten-free,
wheat-free and formulated by Americans for Americans by an NSF certified laboratory.
Neutropic Mind Power is available at mindregard.com, spelled M-I-N-D-R-E-G-A-R-D.com and comes
with a 100% money back guarantee. Free your mind with Neutropic Mind Power, a cognitive
supplement from mindregard.com. Mindregard, clearly see tomorrow and yesterday, today.
Hi there, my name is Frank Bates. What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could
get me in a lot of trouble. I just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com
that exposes the electricity monopolies and government agencies for what they really are,
incompetent line crooks that are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power
bills criminally high. Some have called this a conspiracy, others have called it a cover-up
and you will be shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy goes. My video at 123coverup.com
exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them and how you can beat them
too. Watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patriots have already seen
in the last three months. Go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your
power bill and protect your home. Go watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they
force me to shut it down. Again, that's 123coverup.com.
Digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of toxins. That bears repeating.
Digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of toxins. And ProEM-1 daily probiotic
cleanse is the key to digestive health. ProEM-1 is a powerful liquid probiotic, strong enough
to cleanse, gentle enough to use every day. ProEM-1 is dairy, wheat and soy free, contains
all natural and certified organic ingredients, contains no preservatives or animal products,
supports a healthy digestive and immune system, supports weight loss, improves absorption
of food nutrients, aids in controlling yeast infections, is never freeze dried, and uses
three groups of live viable beneficial microbes to cleanse and remove toxins. Order ProEM-1
daily probiotic cleanse at teraganix.com, spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X.com, teraganix.com,
or call toll free, 866-369-3678. That's 866-369-3678. ProEM-1, the raw probiotic.
I give you our leader Rahm Emanuel, our king. He says we don't need the people to be involved
in the debate. You're just scum. The police are God and they'll decide to take the guns.
Here is the Chicago Don Rahm Emanuel, Israeli officer. Here he is.
One, it's all about criminal access. It's not about gun control. It's about criminal
access to guns. That changes the debate. Two, put the police chief in the law enforcement
community front and center. Everybody else, from politician to whatever, take a back seat,
because the police chiefs have a credibility and authority and a voice on this, which is
why they're all there. I do believe, as it relates to both the type of weapon being an
assault weapon in this case, or the assault magazine, as Mike has, I think, strenuously
focused us on message on that, because the difference between a magazine that holds ten
and a magazine that holds 20 or 30 is a lot of different type of damage that's done.
And those are the three things I do think-
All right, folks, so there you go. The government has credibility. The police do. Even elected
representatives, you take a back seat, pandering to the police. These police chiefs are all
basically federal minions, almost all the big ones are. Just amazing that we've gotten
to this point in this country. And it's gonna get bad, but the offshore banks, they want
a civil war.
That's part of the plan. It's not that they don't care if you die. They want you to die
in a war with the American people. It's essential to call Congress, to call your state reps,
but to travel there physically. It is essential to print off news articles from mfallwars.com
and to physically bring them to the local radio station, the local TV station.
It is essential when these articles of impeachment, this bill of impeachment, but it will be articles
of impeachment. That's what we'll call it. That's the proper term. Go everywhere. It'll
be up the next hour or so at mfallwars.com and prisonplanet.com. It's essential. Let's
go ahead and go to John in Texas.
John, you're on the air. I'm not doing too good, man. They wouldn't be doing this if
they're not planning something else. They're gonna probably shoot up some more schools
and probably blow up some federal buildings to make themselves look like heroes.
That's true. Hey, I'm a professional dog trainer here out of Dallas, Texas. And I was in the
middle of one of my sessions the other day. And there was a lady, one of my clients, she
had a problem with her dog jumping on the couch.
That's a very simple thing to solve. And she kept telling me, she yells at the dog. She
tried to get treats to reel the dog off into the floor. And I just simply went up to the
dog and did a little, and just gave him a little poke and he got off the couch. He never
got back on the couch again. And she was amazed at how quickly I trained her dog.
These criminals are running wild. They're trying to intimidate us with all the weapons
and stuff that we paid for. And they need to be put in line.
Here's my point, Alex. This topic about our guns and the Second Amendment is not up for
debate. The dog on the couch, we don't have a debate with the dog. We don't ask him to
get off the couch. We are here to tell the government, do not take our guns. It's our
Second Amendment. It's in law. It's in stone. We know our rights. It's not up to you. We
don't belong to you. You belong to us. We pay our taxes for your salary. You got that?
I agree. Everybody should call Obama and call all their media publications and get aggressive
with them. Say, look, you gangster scum. You're not gonna run a New York operation here. You
got that?
We don't need to call them. They're listening to this right now. Better believe it.
It's important to put it into action. Listen, if you're not an approved little protest group,
they arrest you trying to hold a sign in front of the White House. They wanna turn America
into North Korea. And I wanna tell everybody something. They're already shutting the economy
off. They're already gonna shut your power off and increase the power prices. They're
already gonna, listen, they just want the guns because they wanna get a physical fight
going with us. The new world order has occupied America. The federal government is overrun
and captured. Red alert.
Thank you for listening to GCN. Visit GCNlive.com today.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad
spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver
solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning
and help improve wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph,
pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the ability to terminate
entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal
or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ
fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go
to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off. That's
SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Coast to coast, direct from Austin. You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, they're gonna devalue the dollar down to nothing. It's already started.
Foreign countries everywhere like Germany are jerking their gold out of the Federal
Reserve. Everybody knows America is run by evil. Everybody knows our government runs
Al-Qaeda. And I wish that wasn't the case. But I am proud of Texas. We got state reps
and federal reps fighting hard.
Those articles are all up at Infowars.com. Obama's anti-Second Amendment executive orders
may result in articles of impeachment. And we are putting out our own articles of impeachment.
I mean, the people's articles of impeachment, that's what I'm gonna call it. Where'd my
cell phone go? I was just, you had it with Watson out there on it. I gotta finish writing
this with him.
A German boondess bank to repatriate gold from New York Fed. Texas Congressman threatens
Obama with impeachment if he uses executive orders on guns. New York State Senator gun
bill passed in the middle of the night, turns law-abiding citizens into criminals. New York
Senate passes draconian gun bill. Walmart forbids new ammunition orders. Yes, that's
Chuck Schumer's order.
By decree of the king, there are some steps that we can take that don't require legislation.
I mean, it is just on, on, on, on, on. And folks, I mean, if they can take the guns,
they can do anything. Man, it's gonna be like a new drug war. I guess you'll get your guns
from the government in the future, like you get your drugs from the government.
You'll still get your guns, they can lock up whoever they want selectively. But I guess
you'll buy your guns from the corrupt police now. So ridiculous. Man, I have seen this
from every angle. I know exactly where it's going. Who's up next here? Let's talk to Jed
in Michigan.
And you disagree with impeaching our Lord and Savior Obama?
Yes, sir, I do. I don't think he should be impeached. I think he should be arrested immediately,
thrown into chains, tied to a pole, whatever you wanna call it.
He's a puppet, but his office is evil. And Obama does hate liberty. He is an authoritarian
scum who thinks he's better than everybody. And you can see him, like he said, I'm not
gonna act nice anymore. Now the mean Obama, when he has those little kids out there tomorrow
though, he's sure gonna use them, isn't he?
Yeah, he will use every single little avenue that he can. But every time somebody talks
about impeaching him, it reminds me of an example of if a McDonald employee was to give
me the keys in the middle of the night and I go in there and rob the place. And then
they think about, there's a debate on whether or not the guy should be fired from McDonald's
or not.
And by the way, Obama wants background checks to buy bullets and is gonna make it illegal
all your retroactive bullets. Look at the Washington Post right here. They're announcing
all the evil that's gonna be announced tomorrow. Unbelievable. Obama to Unville, broad gun
plan, including going after the bullets with executive orders. I mean, I'm sorry, go ahead.
Two days after Ron Paul gave his farewell speech, and during his farewell speech, he
said that he made a comment that the Constitution has failed. And I heard you agree with him,
and I love you, man, but the Constitution has not failed, okay?
We the people have failed the Constitution. And-
Wait, I didn't say the Constitution's failed.
You might have to go back, cuz I could have swore to God that you-
No, no, I say all the time, people say the Constitution or capitalism failed. We failed.
We're not following it is why things are getting so bad.
We the people have allowed this to happen. I mean, at every point in time in history,
we could have prevented this, but we don't have the fire under us, I guess, to do that.
You know, when Obama gave a little speech saying that he's not gonna, don't worry, I'm
not gonna come get your gun. I'm sitting there saying, don't worry, you ain't got the manpower
to come get our guns, all right?
There's 100 million of us. What are we gonna do? We don't even need guns. We can all just
pick up stone, throw it at the same time, and that's over.
It's just to order all gun owners licensed every five years. Bloomberg urges Obama to
defy Congress, 54,000 Mexican sign petition to take our guns. My gosh, I mean, this is
so bad. Feds delay arrest of illegal immigrant and registered sex offender working for senator
until after election.
They're a bunch of scum.