Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you so much for joining us on this Thursday, the 24th day
of January 2013 transmission. Feinstein had published on her Senate website a month ago
or more the bill and people said there's no way she's actually gonna introduce this. They'd
introduced copycats of her bill, so technically she hadn't introduced it a few weeks ago.
But it was the same bill introduced by others, which they may try to sneak through when people
target her bill. But she has now officially today introduced it, had the press conference,
we watched it. We're dumping down the full video clip right now so we can play clips
later.
She just concluded about, I don't know, an hour ago or so. Here's some of the headlines
that are up at drudgereport.com. We're also getting some of this news over to infowars.com
and prisonplanet.com. In fact, can you guys punch up Drudge for me? Fantastic, let me
punch that up then so folks can get that.
Or you can punch it up in there. Dems target 150 weapons, seek national registry. So they
wanna ban 150 handguns, rifles, they admit they're targeting everything. And the purpose
is to dry up the supply of these weapons over time. So there you go, outright move to ban
them over time, at least at admission.
Feinstein got special permission to display guns in DC, cuz he's trying to take them from
the rest of the country. And NRA boycott kills nation's largest outdoor show that had been
going along with the gun grabbing. And that's the way to handle these people. You've gotta
start boycotting Time Warner, because they're not letting gun ads for gun shops run on any
other systems.
While they put out some of those violent movies out there like the new movie coming out, Bullet
to the Head with foe tough guy, Sylvester Stallone. I shouldn't say foe tough guy, I
don't know if he's a tough guy or not. The point is, is that in the movies, his movies
are ridiculous and just totally unrealistic, but that's a side issue.
Guns ban targets, handguns and rifles, and that is in her official bill. Yeah, no, no,
it goes after shotguns that are pump, that hold four rounds. I mean, it just goes after
everything. In fact, it's worse than the original bill that she put up on her Senate website.
It's worse than the bill she introduced in 1993. It is unprecedented, and remember what
happened yesterday.
In fact, I'm gonna re-pull that article out of yesterday's stack, cuz I didn't get to
it properly. Kurt Nemo wrote about it and linked to the Australian newspapers. They've
banned everything down to bolt action and single shot, and now they want those bans
saying you have no reason to have these.
So first they take the full auto, then they take the semi-auto. Come on, none of us wanna
take your guns, just turn in the semi-auto and we'll leave your other guns alone. And
then they ban, of course, those. So that is now happening saying, hey, you could have
a school shooting with a bolt action.
Well, yeah, and a meteorite could hit a school, or a 747 could crash in a school, or a school
teacher could molest children, as we see more news out today. Does that mean you're gonna
ban school teachers? We're not all collectively guilty because you've got a bunch of wound
up Prozac heads out there and people with all sorts of neurological disorders from vaccine
damage more and more being linked to an upsurge in mental illness.
But overall crime is dropping because gun ownership is up. And we did file the statistics
from FBI.gov, locally compiled, 49% in the last 20 years in overall violent crime dropping.
Gun violence is actually even higher, it was better than I even said. So I was just looking
at the basic numbers and dead reckoning them, they're very complex. And 21% as I dead reckoned
that was accurate since 2007.
So the the drop in crime is accelerating, accelerating. That's violent crime and crime
with guns. People robbing your house when you're not there, people busting out your
windows robbing your stereo, people stealing bikes out of your yard, petty stuff where
they don't get their butt shot off.
That is increasing dramatically. All right, we'll be right back, ladies and gentlemen,
on the other side of this quick break. Stay with us, big transmission, Piers Morgan's
gotten sick from the flu shot as well.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben soap company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at five star soap.com or call 800-340-7091
for a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice
as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at five star soap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
You prepare by purchasing gold, food and firearms. But if you don't have a home security system,
then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection. When you're sleeping
or away from home who's watching out for intruders? Check out simply safe. It's a new do it yourself
home security system that is completely wireless. Go to get simply safe.com simply safe is independent
and off the grid. It runs on battery power. So even if the grid goes down, you're protected.
It's completely customizable, so you can use it in your home business boat trailer storage
unit or shed get simply safe.com simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself
in under 20 minutes. So there's no need to let a stranger into your home. If you move
or need to relocate, you can take the system with you wherever you go. You aren't always
at home but simply safe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day, seven days a
week. Again, that's get simply safe.com Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom
lovers. The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse. The
globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover. That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness
items at info wars shop.com. These are items that I did research on that I personally use.
You've got the life straw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The K tour hand crank generator to charge up key equipment during power outages are
out in the field strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes
by Matthew Stein, they're a safe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological
event and crank shortwave am FM radios. Everything that we've researched and found to be the
best is available at info war shop.com and your purchase makes our info war possible.
When you're getting prepared, are you info wars shop.com. From the front lines of the
information war, it's Alex Jones. Well, the Republican establishment is starting to wake
up and realize what is happening in this society. In fact, Rush Limbaugh has come out and pointed
out that Obama is trying to cause culture wars, financial wars, and race wars. And that's
exactly what Obama is trying to do.
And if constitutionalist, if libertarians, if liberals, if conservatives, if whatever
you call yourself, if you wanna have a free and open and happy, successful society, then
you desperately need to understand we have diabolical people in control of our country.
And not coming at it from the understanding that these are larcenous individuals that
wanna bankrupt the nation and domesticate the population, collectivize the population.
And then say that anyone, I mean, I have a Daily Beast article here, Piers pressure is
what it's called, where they admit, yeah, we're going under global government, we're
going under globalism, and it's good to put it in our face that the communist Chinese
are telling us what to do.
And it's good that our debt is owned by foreigners and it's good that Piers Morgan's a foreigner
and let Alex Jones try to fight us, we're gonna deal with him. And I read the quotes
yesterday and they went on to say, it's not just gonna be the blacks and browns against
the whites, it's not just gonna be the women against the whites, it's gonna be the government
and it's gonna be foreign governments helping us.
And it's like the weatherman wrote it or something, those weatherman testimonies that came out,
we played the video clips here that came out in the trials about how they would use foreign
governments to come in and use ethnic uprisings to bring in a communist state in America.
And even I have trouble believing they're actually trying this. And again, the public
is so dumbed down out there generally, politically correct, whites, you name it, that even when
they're on MSNBC saying we've got to deal with white people.
And even when we see moves out there by people like Rangel saying, we've got to overcome
the Constitution, that's a quote, we've got the video, you've seen it, posted it on Infowars.com
two days ago. We've got to overcome the Constitution, we've got to overcome Southerners. Now again,
that's more divide and conquer, play the North off against the South.
They're trying to re-upload the 1860s and Obama used to be Abraham Lincoln. And that's
why they say, you don't like socialist healthcare, you're a racist. That's why they come out
and say, you won't turn your guns and you're a racist. What does that have to do with race?
They go, shut up, racist. And again, there are black people all over this country that
have guns to protect themselves. There are people in California, there are people in
Michigan, there are people in Florida, I mean, people are people.
And gun crimes, crimes using guns has gone way down, it's the FBI's numbers. Overall
violent crime in the last 20 years, 49%, we showed you those numbers yesterday from FBI.gov
and have a video posted at infowars.com for radio listeners, you can go watch it right
now.
They are desperate to cover all this up and just get us all fighting with each other.
Women against the men, Hispanics against whites, whites against Hispanics, black against white,
white against black, Protestant against Catholic. While these mega banks, these globalists,
these collectivizers are busy bankrupting the country and sucking us dry. And it is
outrageous to every day see Fox Sports, CNN, MSNBC, I mean, I saw headlines yesterday.
Gun owners are the new Nazis, gun owners are Hitler. We defeated Hitler last week, CBS
News, Bob Shafer, we can defeat gun owners. I mean, it is now 100% clear that my analysis
over the last decade is spot on.
And the whole homeland security grid is designed and set up for the American people. The whole
thing is set up and designed and timed to unfurl this economic collapse to domesticate
as many people as they can and get you dependent. And tell you it's good to be dependent, ship
your jobs overseas and put taxes on American businesses so they can't operate unless they're
select insiders.
And then as the crime rate increases, it's been going down but they know during a collapse
they'll start going back up. They're going to demonize and are already demonizing people
that maintain law and order in their areas with firearms. And it's so crazy, I have an
article here, I actually bought this two weeks ago for my son, he hasn't put it together
yet, the Star Wars Jabba the Hutt Palace Lego set.
And the Austrian government is looking at banning the toy set. And the Turkish Association
there is calling for it, calling for apologies from Lego. And I guess George Lucas on top
of it, saying Jabba the Hutt is supposed to be an Arab. And because the desert building
has a dome, that it's bashing Arabs when actually that mosque is a Christian church.
It doesn't even look much like it. This is the type of crazy political correctness. We
had a video the other day that Mike Adams did about, we don't want kings, we got rid
of King George III. And I saw comments by black people who were serious, because I went
to their YouTube channels and looked.
Saying why are you bashing Dr. Martin Luther King on Dr. Martin Luther King Day on Monday
by saying, we don't want any more kings, we got rid of King George. The thinking the word
king was a code word for Martin Luther King. When actually Mike Adams talked about how
Martin Luther King wouldn't support Obama and his torture and wars.
And Martin Luther King went out to get a gun permit to protect himself, that's on record.
We actually had pro Martin Luther King stuff on the show that day. But see, it's like a
mental illness where you're gonna be put off guard and off balance. You said you didn't
like King George, perhaps code word for Martin Luther King?
And then there was a whole debate in that video on YouTube from the radio show of them
debating whether Mike Adams was a bad guy or not. And that type of mental illness really
hurts me, because I want those people to be free. I mean, black communities are being
targeted by eugenics, by the drugs being shipped in, by their leaders trying to collectivize
them.
By all these things, and you can't get through because it's all racism pumped in by the media
and their leaders and others to create division in the name of unity. And then they tag on
the agenda, support gun control, support socialism, support corporate fascism, support police
state, support control, or you're a racist.
And you're like, explain to me how not turning my guns in is racist. And they go, shut up
racist. And the media just says it and says it, and then everywhere. We went out and interviewed
people at UT, and I said, did you find them? They said, no, every woman we talked to, cuz
they show a couple of them that piece we heard yesterday, says, the South is racist and bad,
turn your guns in.
And these are white women, and they said it with pleasure. They go, the South is bad,
which is a code word for white people. And you just don't need guns, and that time is
now. I mean, totally disconnected from reality. Going to the University of Texas, guaranteed
you got middle class parents that buy into all this.
No idea what's happening worldwide, no idea about the new world order. Everywhere I go,
I'm scum because I'm a Texan. Piers Morgan wrote an article saying Texans are animals.
And how I have the paw, the giant paw of a gorilla. And how I'm like a gorilla that is
at the zoo at feeding time. And Texans are dumb gorillas and all this. Texans are dumb
gorillas, Southerners are trash.
White people are all racist, gun owners are racist, gun owners are Nazis. Meanwhile, Planned
Parenthood's main job was founded to, quote, kill black people, to kill black weeds. And
I'm like, hey, I don't want you to abort your kids. I wanna try to have them free and strong.
Shut up, racist. You're like, I understand it's fun to say that. Just you're just trying
to prove you're not a racist. We know you're a racist. It's a total mental illness.
And it is cultural programming. And the Democrats up there, the old white people, they're the
buddies of the, quote, minorities. And they're gonna get rid of the borders for you, and
they're gonna get you free welfare. And they're gonna take those guns, and they're gonna get
whitey for you.
I mean, it is nothing but them playing us off like two different Indian tribes, two
different Native American tribes. Early on, the natives outnumbered settlers at some points
100,000 to 1. There's like 15 settlers and estimated however many natives on the continent.
But during some of the biggest Indian wars, 10 to 1, 20 to 1, 30 to 1.
But it wasn't even the superiority of arms cuz there were the French and others constantly
always selling armaments to the natives who were very proficient with them very quickly.
It was that the natives were always fighting with each other. And well, they live across
that river. They all look the same, act the same, and they're basically the same culture.
But it didn't matter because the British intelligence and others could come in and manipulate them
off against each other.
And the French tried it. It's called the great game. Who can do it the best? The Spanish
tried it. They weren't as good. The British were the best at it, so they took over the
world. That's why global imperial, imperial measurement, imperial language is English.
The global imperial language is English. That's the global language. It's called imperial
in establishment textbooks. I speak imperial. Most of you speak imperial. And the point
is they don't want other people coming in from Mexico to ever speak imperial cuz they
don't even want you able to communicate in the culture. They want you under their control.
So we come down to this point now, ladies and gentlemen, where the Democrats have introduced
a bill worse than what she posted on her Senate website, worse than copies of her other bill
that she had before that other Democrats introduced, hoping that we miss those and they pass as
riders on larger bills that bans all semi-automatic handguns, most pump shotguns.
It's worse than what her other bill said. Dem set sights on 150 weapons seek national
registry, open press conference with prayer. Purpose is to dry up the supply of these weapons
over time. Feinstein got special permission to display guns in DC NRA boycott, kills nation's
largest outdoor show. Now remember, remember they're talking about banning a Lego toy cuz
the Arabs say Jabba the Hutt's supposed to be them. I mean, that's like saying ban a
tree cuz you're saying Arabs look like it. I mean, it's just.
Hempusa.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine, and probiotics.
And we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder absolutely free. Micro plant powder
only at hempusa.org. Call 908-691-2608. That's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder seeds
and oil can do for you. Only at hempusa.org. This offer ends January 31st.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson. Have you ever wondered why banks, stock workers, investment advisors
won't talk about gold IRAs? They've been available since 1986 yet the financial industry won't
recognize the value of gold for your retirement. Gold is outperformed paper investments yet
no word about IRAs. If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns. Call 800-686-2237. Secure
your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
Is 2013 your year to achieve more? More vitality, more health, more wellbeing? Hi, this is Pastor
Jenny. For 25 years I spent my life's work teaching others how to achieve more. But in
2010 I got a lesson of my own about RNA drops. I learned that there are millions of gene
switches latent in every single cell of my body that are waiting for an activator. I
learned by taking RNA drops I could begin to activate that power in my cells and achieve
the more that I desire. I'd like to share what I discovered with you and send you a
free 30-day supply of RNA drops valued at $50 for just the cost of shipping and handling.
Go to rnafreesample.com. That's rnafreesample.com. Or call me toll-free at 888-577-3703. That's
888-577-3703. Rnafreesample.com. Discover the more that's waiting for you.
3,795. It includes 20 varieties of pure, hardy, easy to grow heirloom seeds. Yes, only 3,795.
That's 70% less than our competitors. You could buy three survival seed vaults for less
than one of theirs. The survival seed vault from mypatriotsupply.com includes detailed
planting and seed saving instructions and shipped same day. Plus all orders over $49
ship free. Mypatriotsupply.com is American owned by patriots like you. Passionate about
freedom and preparedness. Call now. 866-229-0927. That's 866-229-0927. Or discover more emergency
preparedness items when you order at mypatriotsupply.com. Choose the original. Choose the survival seed
vault at mypatriotsupply.com. Is this the year you finally get serious about
your family's drinking water? If so, keep listening for a special offer from Big Berkey
Water Filters. Did you know that over 60% of municipal water is fluoridated? Berkey
Water Filters distinguish themselves from many other filtration systems with the capability
to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine, fluoride, arsenic and disinfection byproducts
from municipal water via the Black Berkey and PF line of filters. Then there's affordability.
At only 1.7 cents per gallon, Berkey Water Filters purify treated and untreated water,
even stagnant pond water. Stop and think how much money you could save by simply reducing
buying bottled water and using water filtered by your Berkey Water Filter. No need to be
constantly replacing expensive filters with a Berkey. A single set of filters can last
for 5 to 10 years. Choose the best size Berkey for your needs at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
And right now, all GCN listeners get 5% off all ceramic filter systems. Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY.
That's 877-99-BER-KEY or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com. Free shipping on every order over $50. Big
Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean water. You know, the British government and
others are warning that what should be listed as one of the biggest apocalyptic threats
is not terrorists blowing up a bus and killing 10 people, which turn out to be staged to
begin with. But antibiotic resistant bacteria, and there's a London Guardian report on that
I'm gonna be getting to a little bit later.
But what needs to be realized here is that over 100,000, some numbers are as high as
200,000 people die from infections that were preventable in hospitals. Are you seeing a
bunch of, five year old Billy died riddled with sores as the bacteria ate the flesh off
his body. And he went into a coma over two weeks and died. Tom Daschle or somebody like
Joe Biden, former and current politicians running around crying, they decide when to
punch the buttons.
They decide. And now we've got a press conference being opened by the Democrats saying, I believe
the gun lobby is no match for the cross lobby. And we're getting a full press conference,
it is unbelievably disgusting. And in there, they have forced buyback provisions. She lies
and says, we're not gonna take guns from anybody.
They always register, you have to come in and get them registered, they always confiscate.
It's been done in Europe, it's been done in Australia. Australia is down to bolt action
and single shot, and it is in their official newspapers. You can just type in Australia,
get to ban bolt action, and you will pull up the mainstream articles.
We covered it yesterday. So it's always the same pattern. England did the same deal. And
then they say, okay, you can keep the bolt action. It's gotta be checked in at a local
shooting club with police there, paid off duty when you shoot. And then they just ban
the hunting clubs.
Now they're banning those clubs. So this is how they totally eradicate them. And several
countries in South America are doing this where they're banning hunting and guns. So
they want it all gone. They try to make it about hunting, which it isn't, but they understand
that's part of the culture.
So they wanna kill that too. In fact, you think you're gonna hunt foxes that are breeding
like rats? That's why they have fox hunting. With your beagles and your other fox hounds,
you think you're gonna ride out in the country and have your dogs hunt like they're supposed
to?
So the foxes don't kill your cat. Paul Watson lives outside London. There are foxes running
around. He sent me photos of them. I've retweeted them at Real Alex Jones, just like roaches.
And they're vicious. Foxes have come in and killed babies and things. They're in the dog
family at about five times more vicious per pound.
And can't hunt them, so they're like roaches now all over the UK. Beautiful animals, but
they are like roaches. See, all the ancients knew what to hunt. You didn't hunt big, beautiful
animals. You hunted things that would get out of control if you didn't hunt them.
Like take here in Austin, we have whitetail deer getting run over everywhere, eating in
the yard, starving to death. I mean, I can barely drive home during the day or at night.
Just deer everywhere, I see them hit everywhere I go. But you're not allowed to hunt them
inside the city.
And sometimes they'll pay people like $3,000, $4,000 apiece to cage them and then fly them
to West Texas. And then they get out in West Texas with wolves and mountain lions, half
starved, they're domesticated, they get killed in hours. Thousands of dollars to fly mountain
lions free meals in helicopters, cuz you don't want them to die on a long truck ride.
So you fly them in a helicopter, half the time they die of having a heart attack. I'm
not kidding, they've had cases of up to $5,000. These yuppies will pay to have deer trapped
in their yards, put in big cages, they go in to get food.
And then they, see I'm already ranting, I haven't even gotten to it yet. Let's play
a clip of Feinstein saying we wanna dry up the supply of the quote assault weapons, which
is now your handgun. Here it is. Diane Feinstein in her press conference today, here's that
clip.
Hunting rights, we have tried to recognize legal defense rights. We have tried to recognize
the right of a citizen to legally possess a weapon. No weapon is taken from anyone.
The purpose is to dry up the supply of these weapons over time. Therefore, there is no
sunset on this bill.
There you go, there is no sunset on this bill and she literally smacks her lips with pleasure.
That is an insider trader, one of the top insider traders in Congress. When they got
caught, as you know, last year, they did a gangster trick on you, a mafia trick, a lawyer
trick, it's on record.
They said, it's not against the law for us to do it, which it actually was. We've done
whole reports on that. We'll pass a law making it illegal. And the law actually made it legal,
it's not constitutional. Where if the Ethics Committee of the House or Senate run by the
insider traders says it's okay, that it is. It's like, we got caught murdering, well murder
is not illegal for us, we'll pass a law making it illegal. And then the law says, well, we
can kill somebody if the Ethics Committee says it's okay.
I mean, that's the games that this big swollen, pus-filled pig of a woman, this tyrant is
engaged in. We'll be right back, stay with us.
Here on the march, the empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
How can you say that didn't make me sick? The biggest thing going against the flu shot
is a mom gives their five year old a shot and the kid swells up and has a convulsion.
That'll cure you of vaccines for the rest of your life. The biggest thing going against
the flu shots is my mother was, I don't know, it was like 10, 15 years ago, I forget, was
really into triathlons at the time and doing a great job even winning silver medals and
stuff at some big ones in her age group. And she was advised by the team coach, the local
sponsored group, going to be in this big state triathlon, take the flu shot a month before
because it's in the winter.
You don't want this to knock you out. And herself and some of the others got sick. And
I mean, my mother was sick for a month and she never gets sick like that. And this is
like hospital level bad. She didn't go to the hospital, but she was down. And we're
talking like a day after she took it. My uncle, my dad's brother, almost died when he was,
I think, seven years old from a tetanus shot, swole up, had to go to the hospital.
So the biggest thing running against him is cause and effect. To the point of now, before
they would deny, your kid had a convulsion as we gave him a shot to, it's normal to have
a seizure. But if you're going home and now the doctors tell them, this came out three
years ago, three and a half years ago, there were so many convulsions from the H1N1. They
said, look, just put something hard in their mouth, wooden or whatever you've got, not
metal to break their teeth off.
You gotta shove something in their mouth. Okay, I'm gonna give them this shot. And if
they have a convulsion today, it's quite normal. Just put something between their teeth. Imagine,
this is quite normal, but they may have a convulsion. And of course, I laugh because
it's so sick. It's the laugh of pain. I mean, I have been on vacation or on the streets
and you'll run into people and they'll have a five year old that's autistic sitting there,
talking to themselves.
Sometimes it'll be a younger child, older child, beautiful soul that had a great future
ahead of him. And I'll say, when did that happen? Were they born like that? Very nice
child. And they'll go, no, Billy was 18 months old and we went in for a second round of shots
and he couldn't wake up the next morning. He didn't talk for a week and he never talked
again.
He was talking so much and so happy and he hadn't talked since. And he's seven years
old now and we believe it's the vaccines, but the doctors say it isn't. Yeah, cuz the
doctors gave it to your kid. They're never gonna say they're wrong. Once the Nazis started
killing people, and Hitler said now killed millions, they couldn't say no cuz, well,
they've done the right thing before. Same thing with the Soviets, same thing with all
these pundits and people wanting to take our guns and wanting collectivism and wanting
tyranny.
They cannot and they will not ever say they were wrong. No matter how crazy it gets, no
matter how out of control it gets, most of them will commit to evil forever. If you see
the corruption, if you know about liberty, thank God you grew up, had the genetics, had
the locale, had the mentors to be able to have common sense.
People that get into fraud, it's like gamblers I've known. I've known people that are very
successful in business, but blow all their money on gambling. And I'm like, listen, stop
gambling and you can get out of all this. No, no, no, I'm gonna go gamble more and I'll
get on top of this. And I'm like, listen, it's designed that big thing out in the desert
and all these systems to separate you from your money.
The House will always win long term. They trumpet the winner, sometimes staged, to make
you think everybody's a winner, okay? But statistically, you lose about 70% of the time
or more. Don't be a sucker. If you wanna gamble, gamble in business and real life where you
have a chance of winning.
Cuz the gambling spirit is actually something genetically and chemically they've proven
in the brain that is actually associated with leadership. But they take it and misappropriate
it like a mind control system. It's like the snake in the Jungle Book trying to hypnotize
people. That is a facsimile. It is a fraud. You wanna go play poker with your buddies,
that's one thing.
At least you got an even chance of winning. That's why you don't see a lot of poker going
on at the big casinos. Blackjack, you might have a chance to win, but everything else
is a fraud at the end of the day. I mean, if you bet your buddies 20 bucks on a football
game as it makes more interest rate, I get that.
But how do I even get off into gambling? Vaccines. With vaccines, it is just a complete and total
fraud. And it's not my opinion of that. And I have a stack of articles here. Piers Morgan
falls ill days after receiving flu vaccine. In fact, let's work into these videos right
now and then back into the guns and then your phone calls.
Piers Morgan falls ill days after receiving flu vaccine. And I desperately try to get
mainline talk show host who are intelligent and see a lot of what's going on to talk about
vaccines. But they don't wanna do it because the corporate media has put a stigma on it
of quote, conspiracy theorist.
And run other hoaxes where they claim Dr. Wakefield was involved in a fraud. He's never
admitted to that. The evidence has been proven to be a fraud. Turns out the evidence against
him has been a fraud. There were three previous studies, two of them in England, finding what
he found years before. And there's a major association with autoimmune disorders and
vaccine contaminants in the intestines in the brain.
That's why you drink alcohol to affect your brain. It's the same thing. And so much of
what he said was dead on, that's why they've gone after him. So they run these hoaxes,
kinda like free energy or things like that. They run a hoax 20 years ago saying, no such
thing as that. And say, it was done in a mayonnaise jar. So it's all a scam. And then meanwhile,
all these real things that get developed never can be deployed as people were told it was
a fraud.
So there's all these hoaxes going on. But in Adan Salazar's excellent article, he links
to the CDC's own seasonal flu vaccine fact guide. In fact, I'm gonna get Adan to also
link to their adverse reaction page where it says death, seizures, narcolepsy. I mean,
just hundreds of things. And then I can show you mainstream news articles where they say
there is no side effects.
It's a conspiracy theory. In fact, I've read those articles where it says, crazy people
like Alex Jones and Dr. Blaylock. They say vaccines are causing brain damage and autoimmune
disorders and swelling in the brain. There is no proof and the government says zero side
effects. You go read the inserts of all these vaccines. All of them include death, death,
death. And it's so frustrating to know that aspartame and Diet Coke and thousands of products
causes macular degeneration.
And to know people that drink these diet drinks and eat the diet candy and go, hey, I hear
you're going blind. Can I give you some literature? No, I don't wanna see it. Cuz see, they don't
wanna admit they were wrong to do this. I mean, look, I know it's wrong that I like
to eat 30 ounce steaks.
I know it's wrong that I do unhealthy things. At least I know it. But I mean, a steak's
a lot better than aspartame. I know getting angry is not good for me, but I still do it
cuz it's who I am. This stuff is meant to hurt you. And people say, like the young Turks
guy, I admit it's all happening, but they don't mean it.
Well, I've got books where they admit, like Eco Science, they're doing it on purpose.
And see, that's the issue. That's what's so frustrating about this is that I have watched
people. I know two local talk show hosts. One says I can talk about it, the other says
I can't, that work at the same company who took the H1N1 shot, despite everything I said
to them four years ago, who got mild cases of Guillain-Barre, neurological disorder so
bad their hands and feet became numb.
Sometimes it totally paralyzes you and kills you. And the doctors even told them this is
a vaccine reaction. One of them was Dale Dudley, one of the top morning shows in town on 93.7,
the sister station to our AM 590. And I was on his show and he said, I haven't told anybody
this yet, but I'll go ahead and tell you how to go to the doctor's stuff.
The crew knows, remember for a couple months, my hands got numb, my feet, I went to the
doctor, I was so scared, I got a mild case of Guillain-Barre. Yeah, what about the articles
from yesterday, 800 European children developed narcolepsy after receiving H1N1 vaccine. Here's
another one, at least 50 African children paralyzed after receiving Bill Gates backed
meningitis vaccine, natural news, links to all the mainstream articles.
I mean, it's in major newspapers like CBS that 60 something thousand Indian children
last year got paralyzed, many of them died after taking the UN polio vaccine, because
it is polio. I mean, it's so cold blooded that Stalin said one man dies, it's a statistic,
a million dies, or one man dies, it's a tragedy, a million dies, it's a statistic.
And to know, it's like back of the paper, 60 something thousand kids, thousands of them
died. They're like, well, it's a side effect, no big deal. It's like, hey, yeah, 60,000
kids paralyzed. But you hear about the 20th Sandy Hook, yeah, I mean, it's so over the
top how they decide when to punch the buttons of what's said.
And Alex, what about the kids? Turn your guns in. I'm like, but crimes drop 49% violent
crime. Here, let me give you the actual, I don't believe those statistics. Thought you
don't believe the government? Well, no, these are locally compiled, some of the most accurate
statisticians world over say these are some of the most accurate in the world are the
example of what's accurate. It's something good set up 50 years ago, very accurate crime
statistics.
I don't wanna see that, I don't. They don't wanna hear the reality, but reaching out to
Piers Morgan, people say, well, why are you making a big deal to Piers Morgan if he has
a half million viewers? That blow up on air was aired on every major English station in
the world that I know of.
It's one of the biggest media events, not just of this year, but last year, and it's
been rated as such. And I didn't really do all that on purpose. I just said, God, whatever
you want me to do, have me do it, and that's what happened. And notice they're not having
me on all these other shows.
They could have me on MSNBC and get double ratings for the week. They could have me on
all these Fox News and increase their ratings, they know that. I mean, I've talked to executives
of these companies over and over again over the years. We really want you, we're trying
to get you, but there's no way that the execs are gonna kill it.
And I'm like, that's fine, I don't wanna be on there, stop calling me. But don't you wanna
come up here and shoot a pilot? I mean, they wanna meet with you and stuff, but they just
wanna know that, are you gonna work with them? No, I'm not gonna work with you, I don't care.
I can't be around all those plastic fake people and all the bleach blondes and all the soulless
people.
I'll build my own thing, thank you. But that's not what this is even about. My point is,
why haven't they had me back on these shows? Because they acted like and spun it. Discrediting,
look at the crazy gun owners. They don't want you getting out of your trance. They want
a calm English accent or an NPR accent selling you on tyranny.
They don't want somebody getting up and going, don't take the shots, they're designed to
hurt you. Here's proof, wake up, get out of your trance. Wake up, wake up, wake up. I've
been effective with my approach, not because I even calculated it, but because it's real
and organic and it speaks to people's common sense.
Everybody listening took the flu shot or knows somebody that did, that almost died. Everybody
knows they took the flu shot and got deathly ill that week. They're giving you the flu.
And the more people take the shot, they've got studies, the more flu there is that year,
cuz there's flu in it. And I've got top scientists on about this. How many medical doctors, how
many endocrinologists, how many virologists?
British studies, Canadian studies three years ago, it doubles your chances of getting the
flu when you take the shot. That's in Adan Salazar's article. I mean, that's why I'm
frustrated, that's why I'm angry. I mean, I know this stuff's hurting people. Every
time I go on vacation, every time I'm in a shopping mall, every time I'm in a restaurant,
almost every time in a movie theater, the whole front row is autistic kids.
Yelling and screaming during the whole thing, just their minds completely attacked. The
cerebral cortex attacks, so they can't process their subconscious info coming out. So that's
why things are so intense to them. These are damaged, partially wrecked human souls. And
it gets to me because I have empathy, ladies and gentlemen, not because I'm a hero.
My programming is if the children are being hurt, mine aren't safe. And that's not a conscious
cold-blooded thing. I can analyze why my programming gets upset. It's self-preservation, folks.
It isn't cuz I'm goody two-shoes. It's because I am a rootin' tootin', out of control hillbilly
Yosemite Sam. And I know corrupt thugs when I see it, and I go ape when I see it.
So I guess it's true, Piers Morgan, I am a gorilla from Texas. But this gorilla knows
which way his soul is pointed. This gorilla has his head turned around straight. And you
took the shot with Dr. Oz a week ago, and we said he's gonna get sick, or that's fake.
Cuz it's turned out the politicians in Europe have been caught taking fake shots, and they
get their own shot, or a sugar water shot that came out three years ago with the H1N1.
And he's on there with Dwight Yoakam. And Dwight Yoakam, well, I mean, here is the clip.
After he takes the flu shot, he gets super sick. He's having trouble getting over it.
And he's asking Dwight Yoakam why this happened. Here it is.
25 million records. Dwight Yoakam is much more than a country superstar. He's a talented
actor with a lot to say about issues that matter to America. Dwight's latest album is
three pairs. Welcome to you, Dwight.
Thank you.
If we go any further, you're a singer.
Yeah.
You must have had sore throat.
I hear this.
Well, as you can tell, things are deteriorating. Is there any advice you can give me?
Don't ever take a flu shot again. Now, I watched that night with Dr. Oz, and in deference to
Dr. Oz, I think he's, he seems like a completely competent doctor. And I don't understand any
of the kind of biological aspects of the meds that-
But we're both doing the maths, aren't we? We both saw him put that thing in my arm.
Yeah.
And within ten days, I've been struck down.
And I just, you know what? I don't want to tell anybody out there I'm not a medical advisor.
Get your vaccines if you, I don't believe in them. I'm just suspicious by nature, and
I saw you get it, and here we are.
Well, let's try, we'll try and plow on with the interview, not withstand the fact I can't.
Yeah, that's good. And you can go read the full transcript at info.wars.com, and Morgan's
like yeah, you can't disagree, I take it and I'm sick. And of course, that could be anecdotal.
But it's not with the thousands of cases we all know about, okay? I mean, my grandmother's
best friend, registered nurse, whole nine yards, constantly takes vaccines. Takes the
single shingle shot, gets the shingles.
And then my dad is a oral surgeon and a dentist, and he talks to people. And he goes, yeah,
I've talked to, this is like a month ago, I never told the story. Cuz I've talked to
three people that took the shingle shot and got it. I mean, it's just insane that this
is going on, okay?
And we're gonna come back and get into the guns, get into the whole Dianne Feinstein
situation, and then open the phones up in the second hour. And then you remember the
guys that dressed up like pimps and brought down Acorn and exposed Planned Parenthood's
open plan to kill black people, kill black babies?
The legends are gonna be joining us here on air, James O'Keefe.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not gonna wanna miss this exciting message.
Here's why. Our solar generators provide life saving electrical power. And unlike gas generators,
solar generators run quietly, emit no fumes, and produce electricity from the sun. So when
the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part. Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't
sell as new. We put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily
at the end of each year. We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like
new. Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait, they go fast. Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com. For the craziest
offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
It's not a drug, but a natural supplement. It's 12 powerful ingredients are natural
and non-GMO, plus it's gluten-free, wheat-free, and formulated by Americans for Americans
by an NSF certified laboratory. Neutropic Mind Power is available at mindregard.com,
spelled M-I-N-D-R-E-G-A-R-D dot com, and comes with a 100% money back guarantee. Free your
mind with Neutropic Mind Power, a cognitive supplement from mindregard.com. Mindregard,
clearly see tomorrow and yesterday, today.
Have you ever felt like the United States government knows way too much about your financial
affairs? I continue to hear stories about property seizures, frozen bank accounts, confiscation
of stocks and bonds. It makes me wonder if the U.S. citizen will ever again have the
right to life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness. Unfortunately, with the Drug and
Money Laundering Act, the IRS Revenue Ruling 6045 of 1984, and the Trading with the Enemy
Act in Franklin D. Roosevelt's Executive Order of 1933, some precious metal holdings
are subject to government intervention. For this reason, Midas Resources has prepared
a report explaining the boundaries of trading precious metals privately. Whether if you
have any intention of trading with Midas Resources or not, I have instructed my representatives
to give this report out free. Call for your free copy at 1-800-686-2237. When investing,
always proceed with caution. Again, call 1-800-686-2237. Exercise your legal right to trade metals
privately. 1-800-686-2237. You see, the globalists, they want to just
normalize everybody to get accustomed to tyranny and, ah, cancer rates up several thousand
percentage and everybody gets breast cancer and everybody gets testicular cancer early
and yeah, you know, childhood cancer didn't exist 100 years ago, it was super rare 50
years ago.
You know, now it's up over 10,000% on average. And yeah, if a girl has a Hello Kitty bubble
machine that is in the shape of a gun because it's handheld but it's not even called a gun.
My kids actually have had one of those, my four-year-old. The police come in, you get
questioned, we're gonna expel her. All of this is going on and it's insane and it's
political correctness and total control.
And then a girl draws a paper gun and the police are called. She just, again, it's an
attack on ideas. It's authoritarianism in the name of the nanny state and the people
running it, they're the ones buying the 1.6 billion bullets. They're the ones talking
about a revolution. They're the ones fantasizing about bringing in Chinese troops against us,
whether that's feasible or not.
They're the ones in the Daily Beast saying, we need to have the Communist Chinese tell
us what to do. Alex Jones is the enemy. I read those quotes yesterday. I mean, it's
bizarre stuff in the peers pressure story. Look at this article if you're watching on
TV.
A London Telegraph, Lego accused of racism with Star Wars set. Now, my son is building
this right now. And I'm gonna bring this in, I'm gonna try to get him to finish it, it's
really big. Lego has been accused of racism by the Turkish community over a Star Wars
model that supposedly resembles one of Istanbul's most revered mosque.
And folks, it has a slight dome on it, looks almost nothing like it. By the way, that's
Christian architecture there. That was a Christian church. So is the big church in Istanbul.
The point is it looks almost nothing like it. And they say Jabba the Hutt is meant to
look like Arabs. I mean, Jabba the Hutt is a giant space alien worm who talks like Cookie
Monster.
Teeny Jedi. I mean, this is what it's reached. Hello Kitty guns, bubble guns, Jabba the Hutt
things and the media takes us and goes, no, it's quite normal. Robin Page of the BBC was
arrested for saying rural communities deserve the same rights as homosexuals and Muslims.
And they said the word homosexual is judged to be mean and the guy's not even a conservative
and they go on arresting.
And of course the charges were dropped cuz there were no real charges. It's great the
idea of you have no speech. They're gonna be able to ban real guns if kids, I see articles
every month where somebody will do a zombie story. I've seen this dozens of times, I know
you've seen it.
They'll write an article about zombies that are so popular and about a fictional school
attacked by zombies and how they shoot the zombies and they will arrest you. And in one
article it was the dad's parents were split up, the grandparents were raising the top
honor student football player.
And though it was fictional, the grandpa called the police and they are charging him saying
it's terroristic threats even though it's a fictional school. I remember that a few
years ago. And it's like where'd Bob go? He drew a gun. I mean, all we did was draw army
fights and stuff when we were doodling as boys and the girls drew girls in dresses.
I mean, that's what you do. All we did was play soldier. They're making normal human
activity illegal. It's not illegal yet, but they're still acting like it is. To the point
of ladies and gentlemen, we own the job of the hut set.
I was playing with the figures last night saying you gotta get this built. And I was
looking at how cool, it's got like a dozen figures. I'm gonna bring it in here as soon
as it's done. In fact, will you call my house? I know my son's homeschooling today, but will
you ask him as soon as you can to get this done?
I wanna bring this in, folks. These creatures look nothing like Muslims. I mean, Star Wars
is incredibly politically correct and is all about all cultures and groups coming together
including aliens. It's like Star Trek, it's the opposite, is my point. But no, it's racist.
Job of the hut's palace makes the Arabs look bad. And in Austria, they're like, we may
shut this down actually, yes. Again, to set the precedent so they can shut anybody down
they want. Be sure and support the broadcasters who have read the word about it and get the
new Come and Take It T-shirt at Infowarsstore.com.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die? Start purifying your water with ProPure. My friends, I've done
a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is ProPure and it's available
discounted at Infowars.com. Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required. It's NSF 42 certified. Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride
up to 95%. Easy to set up and use. Doesn't require electricity. Purify water from lakes,
streams, ponds and wells. This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic. ProPure
is the best gravity fed filter out there. It's what my family uses. Infowars.com already
has the lowest price on ProPure. But if you add the promo code WATER at checkout, you
get an additional 10% off at Infowars.com. You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
Reaching war on corruption. Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. Big brother, mainstream
media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN
Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, I'm going to open the phones up in the next hour. Diane
Feinstein posted her bill on her Senate website over a month ago now, and people couldn't
believe it. And then others have introduced kind of copies of it themselves. So technically
I'd said her bill was introduced. It's officially been introduced today. And it's worse than
we even thought. We're going to be going over some of that. But I'd said, the way the other
one was written, it could be handguns, shotguns, even pump shotguns, or pump rifles.
People say pump rifles. They do have a lot of pump rifles, folks. You don't seem to be
aware of that. Anything with a pistol grip on it. It's just incredible. And she is so
disgusting in her press conference, we're going to play this clip coming up, talking
about the gun lobby can't beat the cross lobby. Using Christianity, is Diane Feinstein a Christian?
And speaking for Christians, even if she was a Christian, you do not speak for me, lady.
And I think it's just outrageous that people think it's okay to walk on Christians. Can
you imagine if I got up here and spoke for Islam when I'm not a Muslim or a follower
of the Prophet Muhammad?
Can you imagine what would happen? Can you imagine if I got up here and if I spoke for
Jewish groups? Or if I spoke for atheist groups? Well, as an atheist, I believe in God. And
as a Christian, I believe in turning your guns in, even though I'm not a Christian.
I mean, it is over the top. We're going to open the phones up in the next segment. I
want to give the number out in the next segment, we'll open the phones up then. But start your
engines, I want to specifically hear about that. But how big is this article? This article
needs to get out to everybody because you've got Dwight Yoakam on with Piers Morgan.
And Piers Morgan said, I got the flu shot and now I'm really been sick for a week. And
he's like, well, don't take the flu shot. I want to get Dwight Yoakam on, I've always
been a fan anyway, so let that word go out. By the way, my buddies here in the office,
Weldon Henson was hanging out with Mike Judge again this weekend. Aaron Austin and Mike
Judge, he's gone back to California, said, Alex, call me, I'll come on.
I got all these big guests I could get, but I've got to call them. And so, Chris, it is
a direct order at the end of the show that you are to make me, see, I hate calling people,
I hate bugging people. Yeah, no, but all of them, all the celebrities I need to call,
okay, it's just time for me to do it. I guess I could turn you guys loose on them, but it
didn't matter.
I was just watching Idiocracy a few weeks ago, I just got to get Judge on. Because we
are entering the Idiocracy where Lego accused of racism with Star Wars set, London Telegraph,
and the official Turkish group is complaining to the Austrian government. I mean, I guess
you can't show any desert motif or desert design. By the way, that design is a medieval
Christian design.
And it doesn't even look anything like the mosque. I mean, just incredible. I mean, obviously
those that built the architecture went for a desert look. I mean, it looks like a lot
of the Middle Eastern architecture, but a lot of what you call Middle Eastern is really
Roman or Christian. That's a Christian built building right there, the one they're saying
it looks like.
And so because in it is Jabba the Hutt, they say Jabba the Hutt's supposed to be Arabs.
Man, now everybody will think that cuz you said that, it's just bizarre. But again, it's
a political weapon. Here's an example, I'm gonna cover this when we come back. Sigmund
Freud said a fear of weapons is a sign of retarded sexual and emotional maturity.
Retarded just simply means lowered. But then the word retarded became politically incorrect.
So you can't say he's had retarded growth from lack of protein. My gosh, you're gonna
be arrested in England. But that's a hate term. They choose whatever it is. You called,
you said that bonsai tree by not giving much sunshine or water was retarded in its growth.
That's hateful. You hurt someone, you hurt someone. And it's just a weapon that is used
to then put guilt onto people.
You won't turn your guns on cuz you're a Klan member. What's that have to do with it? Don't
try to cover up your racism. We all know what you're really up to. It's to create division.
It's to create a race war.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad
spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver
solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning
and help improve wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as stress, death,
pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the ability to terminate
entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal
or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ
fighter. It is virtually nontoxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go to supernaturalsilver.com
today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off. That's supernaturalsilver.com and
like us on Facebook.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to supernaturalsilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, if you're joining us in the second hour, you probably
heard me break down the 150 plus firearms and their variants. The way I read our bill,
we've got a copy of it right here. The way I read the list, or their variants, it's way
more than 150. I know the Associated Press and others are saying 150, that is not the
case.
The way the ATF, in fact, man, sometimes I wish I could just be in their writing articles.
It's more effective than just being on air talking about it. But I'm putting it out.
People will go research it and get their own articles out of Not Our Guys, cuz we're just
overworked here. There's just too many baseballs getting thrown at us here, too many news things.
All AK types, including the following, and then it goes on. All of these types, all of
those types, they say it over and over again. So they list 150 firearms on this page. It's
way over that in her official bill from page TNW M2HB, and this is just one of the pages.
I mean, it's way over 150. It's almost all semi-auto handguns, rifles, shotguns that
have got grips on them, but then shotguns that can also take clips, even if they're
only designed to take four rounds.
I mean, it's over. They're coming after everything. They are coming after everything. And this
is just completely, completely out of control. So I wanna get your take on the official bill
here. But first off, I'm gonna give you the number. It's 800-259-9231, 800-259-9231.
And we will get you up and on the air about this situation.
Now also, I covered it last hour. It's a big deal. We have time, we'll play the clip again.
Dwight Yoakam, I'm a big fan of. Piers Morgan falls ill days after receiving flu vaccine.
And he goes on the Piers Morgan show and Piers basically goes, yeah, I got the flu shot from
Dr. Oz and then got sick a week later, and I'm really sick.
Whenever this flu is, it also attacks your lungs. You have like a hemorrhagic light form
of hemorrhagic fever. You have some of hemorrhagic, is that the proper term, response in your
lungs. And it is certainly not a fun thing. But this is the type of thing. People won't
read the CDC's own admissions that it can kill you or give you its own autoimmune response
in your lungs or brain.
They won't tell you it can cause Guillain-Barre permanently or kill you. They don't tell you
it can cause hundreds of things. People don't go look that up. The media just says there's
no side effects, don't listen to conspiracy theorists. But when Piers Morgan gets sick
after the flu shot and Dwight Yoakam says don't take the flu shot, that's the type of
thing that will get to the sheeple.
The sheeple, a lot of them will go, I still take it even though I get sick usually when
I take it. I've talked too long, but you don't think there's a cause and effect there. We've
gotta try to help these folks. It's easy to laugh at them and get mad at them, they're
victims.
They were set in front of the television set in the last 60 years in their diapers as a
babysitter being programmed to be a bunch of mind-numbed robots. And we've got to deprogram
them or they're gonna be used as an army, a tidal wave of foaming at the mouth, slobbering,
drooling, miscreant, gibbering is the proper term, lemmings to run us over the cliff with
them.
We have got to get in there and help them. Now, I mentioned political correctness earlier.
Here's the CDC website if you're watching us at prisonplanet.tv. You can go read the
different vaccine responses including death and depending on the vaccine you take. But
getting back to political correctness, there's an all out attempt to make toy manufacturers
not have GI Joe, Star Wars with guns.
There's an all out attempt to not let boys play with toy guns or girls. That's why the
police come when your neighbors call them because the kid's got an orange or pink Nerf
gun in the yard. You see that in the news every day now. Or a girl draws a paper gun
or a girl has a Hello Kitty bubble projector, it's not even a gun.
My children have had multiple Hello Kitty, the exact same pink ones. And we've had a
Choco Cat one that's black cuz we're racist. Absolutely, my kids wear Choco Cat outfits
because we're racist, okay? I mean, the cat is black, ladies and gentlemen, Choco Cat.
My wife's got a Choco Cat nightgown. Total racism again. And you're saying, Alex, don't
be silly. Folks, they mean it to be mindless and over the top. Let's punch up for viewers.
I covered this last hour, but I'm gonna segue this into guns, then your calls. London Telegraph,
Lego accused of racism with Star Wars set.
The official Austrian government's looking at it. The big Turkish council, the biggest
minority council in Austria is outraged and is demanding an apology. And there may need
to be reparations from Lego because, ladies and gentlemen, they say Jabba the Hutt is
a Arab. Maybe Michael Moore. I mean, is the Goblin King supposed to be Rush Limbaugh?
I mean, does Rush Limbaugh get angry and go on the air and say, I'm gonna sue the makers
of The Hobbit because that looks a little bit like me too. I don't mean to rush, the
point is, that's it. That's it, let's put the Goblin King on air, okay?
People watching just Google the Goblin King, it looks a little bit like me, a little bit
like Rush Limbaugh in our heavier times. And that's it, I'm suing Lego. I'm announcing
it, I am suing Lego because my son has the Goblin King set as well. And I'm telling you,
it looks a little bit like me.
That's it, that's it, you're racist against white people. You're racist against white
guys that are a couple pounds overweight and have big heads, that's it. I am totally blown
away right now by, there it is. Look at that, they are making fun of me right there, click
it for people that are watching.
This is outrageous. That's me when I wake up in the morning and I've had too much to
drink. I mean, this is incredible, I am suing Lego. I want a press release right now. I
agree that the job of the hutch is supposed to be Muslims, it's obvious.
And it's obvious that the whole Return of the Jedi is to make fun of Muslims, it's absolutely
proof. Even though it's a politically correct movie about integrating everybody, still it
doesn't matter. George Lucas should be arrested right now, he is a racist and gun owners should
be arrested because they're racist.
They're like Hitler, you hear it on every TV channel every day, everything, I agree.
Amazing, and by the way, if you're a new listener, I'm joking about the Goblin King stuff in
the lawsuit. The point is they really are looking at legal action in Austria over the
Star Wars job of the hut palace that I bought just about a week and a half ago for my son
at the Lego store.
Only reason to go to the mall is to go to the Lego store. The Turkish community said
the model was based on a mosque in Istanbul and that the accompanying figures depict Asians
and Orientals as people with deceitful and criminal personalities, the Turkish cultural
community.
Well, I guess Emperor Palpatine's meant to make white people look bad, I think this is
just total bull. Why is Mace Windu a good guy? He's a black guy, I thought mostly blacks
look bad, he's racist. The Turkish cultural community of Austria released a statement
calling for Lego to apologize for affronting religious and cultural feelings.
And they go on to say they believe that Jabba the Hutt is supposed to be a Muslim. I mean,
folks, this is so over the top, I just can't get over it, but they know what they're doing.
This is cultural Marxism, this is the type of control they admit they're using. Here's
an example, you use the word homosexual in a news article in England, you will be arrested
because they say the word homosexual offends people, even though it's the scientific name.
If you use the term Caucasian now, they're saying it's racist cuz it's a racial name,
even though it's just a scientific designation, caucus mountains. If you use the word Negro,
which comes out of Latin for Negro or black, it has nothing to do with the N word.
People think it does, and they get in trouble. I've seen articles where they take people
to jail for using that word. It's amazing how they do this. And again, it's to get you
so scared, you won't talk. I better not have Hello Kitty bubble gum, it shoots bubbles
as evil. Better not buy my son a Nerf gun to play in the yard, the cops will come.
I better not, I better not, I better watch my speech, I better, I better. And the other
night on the nightly news, we had this quote that I was actually familiar with cuz I read
some of the writings over a decade ago, Sigmund Freud. What he says is totally true. You notice
people that are anti-gun always say we have the guns because we have small members.
Which is just absolutely asinine, guns are about self-defense. But Sigmund Freud said
a fear of weapons is a sign of retarded sexual and emotional maturity. General introduction
to Psychoanalysis published 1920. And I read that book. That's why when I saw them, they
said, is this a real quote?
Well, it looked it up, confirmed it wasn't. No, actually, he does a whole chapter of how
ridiculous people are that are scared of weapons in the hands of citizens. He even talks about
when they see soldiers with guns, they're not scared cuz it's the state. They're scared
of other people having guns cuz they're scared of what they would do with guns.
That's why they're always talking about how they wanna kill people. Piers Morgan and Buzz
Bissinger and the rest of them because Bissinger on the show said, I'm mentally ill. I'm on
drugs. He said the next day when people said, why'd you say kill Alex? He goes, well, I'm
mentally ill. See, that's their excuse to be what they are because they are mentally
ill.
You understand? They don't want you having a gun cuz they're scared of a knife, the studies
show. I mean, I've been around liberals and people in college and pulled out a knife or
something to cut something. Watch out with that. I mean, they're just totally scared
of everything.
And then see, politically correct, Jacobson's like, man, I bet when you read that they're
gonna get politically correct. Retarded just means you didn't feed the bonsai tree enough
water so it's small. But the term becomes like a pejorative so they say, don't use it.
Sigmund Freud says they have never developed their sexual and emotional maturity. And the
word to describe that is stunted or retarded. But see, my gosh, I hear about talk show hosts
getting fired for using the word.
See how we're losing our language? Can't say cockazoid, can't say oriental, they say that's
racist now. Everything, put suicide nets around the Apple factory with hundreds of people
jumping off of it where they have to put suicide nets up. That's no big deal. Fourth abortion's
no big deal.
You wanna inject a bunch of Guatemalan kids with syphilis and kill them, go ahead. That's
the government. But hey, Hello Kitty, bubble guns that shoot bubbles. You know what? Let's
call the cops. I mean, let's call them right now. Let's call them immediately. The way
to handle this political correctness is what's happened with these outdoor shows that banned
guns at them. Everybody just boycotted it, now it's been canceled. Okay, that's the answer.
They're trying to boycott us and have a revolution against us to shut us down. We shut them down.
It's us or them.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just
in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box. I want you to know some very important information. In 1985, President Ronald Reagan
requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the
President could obtain this world-class healer. Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are
used around the world to keep people healthy. Now, you can protect yourself and your loved
ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond
to abnormal cells only without harming a single normal cell. If you want to stay healthy,
now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders
that don't belong in your body. Call 1-866-Venus-Fly or order from Carnivora.com. That's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-Venus-Fly or visit Carnivora.com. Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
HempUSA.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new Micro Plant Powder Gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine and probiotics
and we'll send you our travel-size Micro Plant Powder absolutely free. Micro Plant Powder
only at HempUSA.org. Call 908-691-2608. That's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder, seeds
and oil can do for you only at HempUSA.org. This offer ends January 31st.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson. Have you ever wondered why banks, stock workers, investment advisors
won't talk about gold IRAs? They've been available since 1986 yet the financial industry
won't recognize the value of gold for your retirement. Gold is outperformed paper investments
yet no word about IRAs. If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns, call 800-686-2237. Secure
your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
Hey there, Frank Bates here. Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out
280 million Americans? This is really scary stuff. Defense experts warn that this odd
device poses the gravest threat we've ever known. In fact, just a few weeks ago, former
Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed piece for the Washington Post warning
about this deadly threat. I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up. That's why my friend
just created a free video at weirddevice.com that exposes this threat and blows the doors
off the conspiracy. Go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover
exactly what it is, plus discover the number one way you and your family can survive this
deadly attack. I'm not sure how long this video will be online, so go to weirddevice.com
before it's gone forever. Again, that's weirddevice.com. James O'Keefe of the Veritas Project. You
know him from bringing down an acorn exposing Planned Parenthood, taking money to make sure
blacks get exterminated, and a lot more. Now they're going to anti-gunners houses and putting
up that it's a gun-free zone up front their house. So he's gonna be joining us in the
next hour.
We're going to your phone calls right now, but if you're watching on TV or a radio listener,
I'm not joking about the fact that they're talking about going after Lego and the Austrian
government and other areas because the Muslim groups say that the Jabba the Hutt is supposed
to be a Muslim. Lego accused of racism with Star Wars set, a set I own, that my son owns
and has nothing to do with it.
So I'm making the announcement. I believe the Goblin King, if Jabba the Hutt's supposed
to be Arabs, the Goblin King, I'm even a public figure versus just Muslims in general, and
I've had a little bit of jowls before being overweight and having a large head. So I believe
Lego, based in Europe, is racist and made the new Goblin King, even though he was described
in The Hobbit written 70 years ago or so, to look like this.
It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter if Star Wars was written back in the 70s. It has nothing
to do with Arabs. I am right now saying that is supposed to be Alex Jones. And I am going
to file suit on Lego for putting out a set to demean me and describe white people as
big and fat and ugly.
That's obviously me right there. And how dare them? Where do they make Lego? Is it the Fins
or the, yeah, Denmark, okay, the Danes. Well, that's it, they're racist towards white people,
and it's obvious. They've got white figures that are fat and ugly, and I'm going to sue
you. You are doing this to me. I'm filing a report with the FBI, and I'm going to the
cultural organization.
I'm going to the Austrian government too. How dare you? I think I'm going to put a press
release. I think I'm going to do that. I think I'll actually go and officially say, cuz you
know what? You're right, Jabba the Hutt is to make fun of Arabs. Shut Lego down, racist,
this is racist. Hello Kitty bubble guns, arrest the children, this is completely normal.
Blame all gun owners for bad people. Put everyone on Prozac so they kill more people, so the
psychiatrists get more money to put more people on it to kill more people. That's the answer.
I've been wrong all these years. The liberals are right. They're not authoritarians, they're
good people. They're right, gun owners are like Nazis. And we defeated Hitler, we can
defeat America.
I agree with all the people on MSNBC. I have been wrong, and I want to apologize here on
air right now. It's so obvious. My gosh, you can all sue. That looks like McAdoo, the one
with the beard. My gosh, it's racist towards, it's racist. My gosh, it looks like the crew.
There's Wes right there. I mean, that's us. It's obvious, I'm suing. It's my gosh, Lego
is so evil. And it's copyright infringement. They've used my likeness without getting the
authorization.
You should know I actually played the goblin king. Good to see you today. I'm glad you
could drop by. Actually, I'm gonna assume over Jabba the Hutt too. That's actually meant
to make fun of me as well. I mean, just total mass liberal schizophrenia. But the establishment
knows. Teenage Jedi. You guys gave me some of the text of Jabba's talk, but I think it's
from one of the later movies.
Yeah, this is Phantom Menace. Yeah, I need him from Return of the Jedi if I'm gonna do
a. I actually need him going to actually do a better one. All right, that's enough, ladies
and gentlemen. If you just tuned in, I'm illustrating their absurdity by just showing how out of
control this is. And of course, Han Solo, punch it up, is shown as silver.
That's racism towards the Tin Man. That's why they did that. My gosh, whoa, whoa, better
have the owners of the franchise of the Yellow Brick Road, the Wizard of Oz sue immediately.
I just can't believe the racism that we're seeing. See, you're meant to look for all
this imaginary stuff. Well, meanwhile, they're taking everybody's rights and select corporations
are exempt from taxes, but you and I aren't.
That's the real discrimination, but they want us all fighting with each other, divide and
conquer. We're all a bunch of mentally ill twits obsessed with political correctness.
My dad, at one of his dental offices, bought a bunch of 1920s Art Deco Vogue art. And in
one hanging in a dark corner, in a hallway, it's from the 1920s and it's Vogue. And it's
a bunch of women dressed as flappers and one of them has a cigarette.
And he's had now multiple people, we're talking about it again. One lady came to him and said,
I'm calling the police. It's illegal to show cigarette smoking. And he went, it's a museum
piece. And she just was freaking out and some other woman got mad. And imagine, this is
a poster with a woman about three, four inches tall.
You have the look of a bunch of people on it with a cigarette. And again, these people
want all the old movies banned cuz they show cigarettes. They already got most of the old
cartoons banned. They're gonna ban everything. These people are 1984 tyrants. They want control
of information.
I got a bunch of articles today where the EU is calling to be able to arrest any journalist
they want for any reason, if what they say is politically correct. In fact, that's on
infowars.com. I mean, it's out of control, I promise. Your calls on the other side of
this break.
We're on the march. The empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health. At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver-based products. Our most popular silver-based products are
the 32-ounce nano silver solutions, our 2-ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well as
our all-natural silver soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver
gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver
at the surface. But rather, we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin-nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the
silver more effectively. Visit www.SilverLungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver-based
products are best for you. That's www.SilverLungs.com.
Thank you.
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center and the heart of the resistance.
Okay, folks, let's go to your phone calls. As promised, again, I'm your host, Alex Jones.
The news websites are Infowars.com and PrisonPlanet.com, and they are some of the biggest and most
important and most accurate outposts out there trying to warn people about the incredible
tyranny that we're going into. And again, if we succeed and hold back the tyranny, which
we've done at many levels, then people say, there's no tyranny.
But if we don't succeed, well, then the show will just get bigger and bigger and bigger
until it's finally shut down because we're going to see the tyranny expand. And that's
why the show, the broadcast, the news organization is exploding right now is because the country
is going to hell in a handbasket. And all the different tyrannies that I've warned you
about are happening because the globalists write white papers.
The Rand Corporation has been public about this. Dianne Feinstein has said she wants
a total abolition of guns in the past. So has the Attorney General, so has Obama as
a state senator. The UN treaty, the UN has said they want the abolition of civilian firearms
on her ship because it threatens the legitimate power monopoly of a state.
That is a Unideer quote, July 7th, 2001, New York City, addendum to the treaty. I mean,
I know their goal. I've read their book. I've read their handbook. It's kind of like the
New England Patriots getting the playbooks and spying on the other team. They knew what
they were gonna do.
I mean, I'm sitting here, they're not even hiding it. They've got a whole plan. And then
they've got every day I see CNBC, MSNBC, CNN, you name it, running around saying to everybody
that gun owners, our Klan, our racists, our Nazis, we defeated Hitler, we can defeat them.
I mean, it's everywhere. You're seeing it. We're mass murderers. We're causing the deaths.
People have a right to have us not killing them as if our guns are killing them, not
criminals.
And this is an authoritarian takeover. And it's over the top because they're going for
broke. Meanwhile, they're saying Southerners are crud. Southerners have to be overcome.
The Constitution has to be overcome, Rangel and others. You go down to UT, talk to the
students, that's all. The Southerners must be overcome. We have video of them shot last
week edited over the weekend that aired after Rangel, and it's girl after girl.
The Southerners have to be dealt with. They must have their guns taken. He will be our
new Lincoln. I mean, this is the battle plan. And you're like, whoa, Southerner, I just
want freedom. What's this about Southerner? You're gonna be the Southerner, all whites
nationwide. You're the enemy, you did it. Unless you join us, well, okay, guns are bad.
I join you, I admit I'm evil. Meanwhile, they're so politically correct, you can't have a job
with a hut toy, that must mean he's an Arab.
As Ashenon is saying, I'm the Goblin King, or Rush Limbaugh is. And they're talking about
going after Lego in Europe because of the new Lego set I just covered. Notice how you
can't draw a gun. You can't have a bubble projector that looks like a gun with Hello
Kitty. You can't have that. But we're gonna kill you, Piers Morgan says, and his other
host.
And we're gonna take your rights, and we're buying 1.6 billion bullets and militarizing
police in black uniforms, marching like stormtroopers and federalizing everything. But we're liberal
and sweet, and you're a scumbag white person. I mean, they have white guys on, you've seen
them on MSNBC, going whites are scum, southerners are trash.
I mean, that's real bigoted attacks, real division. And a lot of whites are like, well,
I wasn't racist, I got a lot of friends. But man, okay, you're saying it's a race war?
You're making me do this? It's like prison. They send you to prison, it's how Wacken Hut
and all other big correction systems have it.
And it's shut up where, okay, you're white, you go in the white area. You're like, well,
why do I go there? Well, you're gonna get killed if you don't. You're gonna get beat
up, at least raped. You get in, they go, all right, we are the white supreme brotherhood,
or we're the Aryan nations, or we're the brotherhood of Krom or whatever.
And you're gonna deal drugs for us, and you're gonna do all this, or we're gonna let those
folks kill you. And you've got the white supremacists, the black supremacists, the Hispanic supremacists,
on the east and west coast, the Asian supremacists. Four different blocks in the prison, and they
all go to the warden, and the drugs are brought in, and the whole thing's run that way.
And if they want somebody politically killed, they just say, go ahead and take that guy
out. Go ahead and take that guy out. And see, it's a prison culture. I mean, I see it on
YouTube about, you don't wanna deal with the blacks and the Jews and kill them. They're
gonna kill us. You're working for them. Yeah, I learned that. You go to their website or
their YouTube channel, and you'll hear them bragging, yeah, I've been in the pen for ten
years for armed robbery.
I don't know how to deal with it. I mean, I know who you guys are when I hear you, cuz
you always talk about, yeah, I'd like to get you and rape you. It's always the standard,
I'm gonna rape you, cuz you're an ex-con, okay? You were put into a college to be brainwashed,
and you're tough cuz you got the prison tats and even, it's all social engineering.
See, I know how it all works. It's the same thing with the Mexican extremists. You don't
like it, we're taking over. When we get you, we're gonna rape you, Whitey. You're a convict.
See, my guns are to protect me from the government and their convict armies that they run. And
they run all the capos, the white supremacists they run, the black supremacists, the Mexican
supremacists, all government funded.
It's all come out on record, all of it, all of it. You're all government, you're a disgusting
disgrace. You're pathetic. You don't care about humankind, and it's all done under political
correctness. All this racial harmony crud is absolute bull to make middle class, wealthy
people. No matter what color you are, be all, I'm conforming, I'm not in part of any of
all this racial stuff that's going on.
I'm going to, okay, I said I go to your calls, I'm going to them right now. William, John,
George, Jerome, Truth, Raider, and others, but this is what's going on. This is what's
going on. I mean, I was at the airport about a year ago, a year and a half ago, flying
back from the talker's conference.
I don't think I've ever even told this story. Actually, I have, but Rob Dew was there. And
I guess this guy who I was, and he was a big white guy, tats all over him. I could tell
convict type guy, and he comes over. He gets to my face, obviously knew who I was, it was
some kind of setup, and grabs my breast.
That's what he called them, my pectorals, and twist them trying to get a response. And
I knew it was a setup, and I could see cops and stuff about 50 feet away. I was like,
okay, this is all a setup. And he goes, I'd like to get you, I'd like to rape you.
And I'm like, wow, they got a convict waiting for me at the Austin airport knowing I'm getting
off. I mean, I guess I do gotta get bodyguards just to watch my back, just so people can't
come up and do that. And he grabs me, total convict stuff, twist the skin on my pectorals,
twist them.
And then goes, I'd like to get you, I'd like to rape you. And he, I'd rape you. And that's
who they are. That's who they are. That's who they are. That's what they want. They
want to dominate, they want to control. They can't invent things. They don't know beauty.
They don't know strength. They don't know family. They never had a family. Their daddy
beat them.
They sat in a crib with flies all over them while mama smoked crack, or while mama did
methamphetamine. And then they grew up and went to prison and learned to be a tough guy.
And now that's all they've got. I've got justice on my side. I would have climbed up on top
of that guy and just rub his head right like that. You understand that, boy? You think
you're tough?
The devil doesn't give you strength. Life gives you strength. You're weak and you're
empty. And you grew up in crap filled diapers and I grew up with love. And that's why you
think evil's giving you strength, because you're a pathetic little boy. All of you who
serve evil, you're a joke. Let's go ahead and go to your phone calls. William in New
York, you're on the air.
That is good, Alex. I appreciate that. Listen, man, my family and I pray for you and your
family every day. I appreciate everything you're doing for everybody. But listen, we're
in a hell of a jam here in New York. I mean, I'm getting sick of it. What do you suggest
that, I mean, I know what I'm gonna do, but what do you suggest that people in New York
do about what's coming down?
I have to say we had a lot of affiliates in New York, great people in the big cities,
but also in the rural areas. I would leave. Or I would get super aggressive and try to
repeal it, but exodus is always the best thing. And then, of course, they'll corner you somewhere
else. But I'm not a big fan of the small community that tries to go to the local system with
bargaining power to be left alone.
I think it's good to go to areas where people know about liberty and you know there's a
lot of liberty lovers. And so that will percolate out into the system. I would do like a lot
of New Yorkers are doing. Come to Texas, man. The New Yorkers I meet down here in Texas
are all great people. Californians are great people, but the really nasty ones are the
socialists from California.
And they've just overrun everything and are trying to take over. And they even talk about
that. I mean, the agenda 21 shows a triangle map of San Antonio, Austin up to Dallas and
Fort Worth and Houston. And they say we are taking these areas over. And they go into
government, they go into the meetings, they are there as brutal authoritarians to take
control.
Wearing their camouflage of being liberals. What do you think of Feinstein as saying we're
going to phase out your guns?
I hate it. I hate it to death. I mean, talking is over, Alex. I mean, I know you talk a lot
about handling things through activism, rioting, protest, things of that nature. But I mean,
come on, talk is over. I mean, the talk key time, the only thing these barbarians understand
is aggression.
Listen, I hear that, but they're losing politically. Obama wasn't really elected. They ran a fake
guy against him. I'm seeing the numbers. A lot of you aren't public figures, you don't
know. I mean, I go sit in the hot spring on the Texas-Mexico border with 15 people wearing
a ball cap.
And one person hears my voice and goes, Alex Jones, next person, Alex Jones, Alex Jones,
they were from New York, California, San Antonio, France. I come back the next day to the hot
springs. Most of the people knew who I was. Everywhere I went, I'd be talking up on a
mountaintop and somebody 50 feet down would go, is that Alex Jones?
And I mean, let me tell you, the globalists are going for it all right now because they're
a paper tiger. And I'm not bragging, hey, I'm this big shot, everybody knows who I am.
If people know who I am and then say they agree with me, black, white, Hispanic, doesn't
matter, it shows. Now, obviously, that's gonna be a higher educated group that knows how
to go find a hot springs in the middle of the desert somewhere.
It's gonna be a more educated group climbing 8,000 foot mountains. But where you go and
there's like middle class, upper middle class, but also some areas of blue collar. Where
you find highly educated liberal idiots, they will spout Marxism and not even know it's
Karl Marx. And they're in their own world, man, and they are openly saying Obama is Lincoln
and is going to conquer us.
You can look it up, I mean, they're coming. So I hear what you're saying, but they wanna,
they provocateur events like Oklahoma City because they can't win the cultural debate
with us. So whoever fires first loses, that's why they're gonna fire and say we did it or
push people into a corner and get them to fire, okay?
So it's like, I don't want it to go to the shooting war, they want it to. So does that
tell you a shooting war is a good thing, William?
I'm really frustrated with the pain for our catered weapons and more security.
What would have happened when that guy grabbed my pectorals and tried to rip my, well, you
know what they're called, I'm gonna stand on radio. Did a you know what twister on me.
What would have happened if I would have attacked the convict?
Yeah, that wouldn't end well. Yeah, no, no, they were gonna have their victory. They had
a convict and it's on record, the police were ready to arrest him after the whole stage
thing happened.
He was like, what? Hey guys, come on, it was a wink wink. But I was smart enough cuz the
cops that were there watching it, they left when it happened and I didn't take the bait.
And then I went and called the TSA all that freaked out and was watching and called other
people and this all happened on record.
That's why that, well, anyways, it's a side issue, but they don't like me too much over
there. I have to go to the lion's den every time I fly. I mean, they were planning, see,
I knew, I mean, it hurt when the guy did it, it hurt real bad. He grabbed and twisted as
hard as he could, a full grown man.
And I just cut off the pain and went, what's your problem? You're gonna get in a lot of
trouble for that. He couldn't believe I just stood there totally calmly. I just turned
it off. Okay, just turn the pain off. So what are you gonna do? And then he called me a
wimp and said he was gonna rape me and all this waiting for me to do something.
And again, ABC Nightline implied that I have fake anger. No, I just let myself, where I'm
somewhat safe here, then I can show you what I really think. But out there, I know when
to hold them, I know when to fold them, I know when to walk away, I know when to run.
You never count your money when you're sitting at the table. There'll be time enough for
counting when the dealing's done. And the money I'm after is liberty. The goal I'm after
is freedom and defeating these globalists.
I take it personal, the children they brain damage with vaccines and GMO. I take it personal,
the children they abort. I take it personal, cuz you know why? It is personal. I'm a human
being and I have an allegiance to humanity and the God that created us. God gives you
life and joy and children and everything wholesome.
The devil gives you death and destruction and poverty and pain. And the New World Order
is the devil. Let's go ahead and talk to John in Pennsylvania. You're on the air.
Hey, Alex, thanks for listening to me. I just wanna thank you for being who you are and
also all those info warriors out there.
Well, thank you, brother.
Basically, what I was calling about is just, I'm just sticking here and all this spin.
And they keep on comparing the United States with other countries. I think, first of all,
the United States became the great country that it is today because of what we stand
for, not what other countries stand for.
Absolutely. I mean, did you go read the Daily Beast article that said, peers pressure? Or
it said it's good to have the Chinese and the Russians and peers telling us what to
do.
This is globalization 2.0. Let Alex prepare his flamethrower. We're coming for him. And
the ABC Nightline says Alex is now under very serious scrutiny. And they're saying they
wanna kill me and that my kids hope they're safe at night. I mean, that's who they are.
Look, guys, I know you're a bunch of gangster thugs or a bunch of wannabes. I get that I'm
in danger. And that's the point. I know America is in danger. And yes, they're trying to get
us used to foreigners telling us what to do under global government.
Yep. Also, also the fact is that, you know, they're using the oldest strategy, the divide
and conquer, you know, mind, body, spirit. We've been hit with that. I mean, I hate to
be redundant, but you've said it time and time again. As far as everyone who's listening,
the ones that are awake need to wake up the ones that are sleeping. And the spin is the
way they're doing it, divide and conquer. They wanna keep on pulling the Americans away
from each other. And we have to keep on using our voices and get out there and support our
local gun shops and speak to our neighbors and get out there and not text.
Because if we're using the technology, don't take it from us, too.
Well, we need to engage with the latest technology, but also engage with low tech and build multiple
pillars, multiple tentacles against the enemy. We need to move against them on every front
as they've moved against us. Listen, if somebody doesn't sell so-called semi-autos, assault
rifles, boycott them. I mean, I'll never go into exporting goods again.
And I've been in there and bought stuff. I will never support anybody. I mean, here's
the article, NRA Boycott Kills Outdoor Show That Banned Assault Weapons. The massive boycotts
sparked by NRA and other gun rights outraged by the nation's largest outdoor show.
Banned the exhibition of assault weapons has caused the show organizers to abruptly cancel
the week-long event in Harrisburg, Pennsylvania. It's gone on forever. It's the Reed exhibitions.
I mean, it's over. And listen, they want to intimidate us, take our language. I mean,
how mad does it make you? I don't care where you live. I mean, I always see these comments
in YouTube going, you dumb southerner, Texan, you pathetic gun owner.
And I always see folks, I'm from New York, I'm from California. It isn't about being
a southerner owning guns. See how they try to play that game and then say southerners
are racist. I mean, southerners, I mean, how many blacks in the South own guns? It's all
over generalizations. Can you imagine if I came out and said New Yorkers are scum, I
mean, what the media would do with that?
Imagine they're on TV calling everybody in the South scum. What do you make of that?
Yeah, absolutely. I mean, what I'm saying is basically as far as like they got to stop
these puppets. They think these puppets think that they've had loss. They don't know what
loss is until they've seen it, because I've seen it.
I've watched my family systematically get killed in another country.
I want to hear this from you when we come back. I want to hear about your family. Stay
there.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather a life storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
My name is Steven Heuer. After 22 years of nutritional counseling, I've observed that
most brain malfunctions have at their roots some form of toxicity and brain damage. So
whether it is poor memory, poor focus, lack of creative thinking, or more serious matters
like inability to focus, speak normally, or remember things, the emphasis to getting one's
brain working optimally needs to be on detoxification. One World Way supports your body's number
one means of detoxification, which is glutathione production. My name is Angie and my son has
suffered from borderline autism and constipation. I got him on One World Way and in two months
his constipation is gone. He's become friendlier. He can carry on a normal conversation with
me and he has made his first friend. He's doing great and he looks forward to taking
One World Way every day. You could offer him a present or a cake and he would prefer the
One World Way. Go to OneWorldWay.com. That's OneWorldW-H-E-Y.com or call 888-988-3325.
That's 888-988-3325. You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa where a nicely
furnished cabin with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine, and laundry service awaits.
After a good night's sleep, your adventure begins. You're on a golden stag safari for
big game. But it's not Africa, it's Argentina. One-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo,
huger, bighorn rams, wild boar, and the biggest stag deer in South America. All gold medal
quality. All the action you can handle. Land rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food,
beverages, hunting guides, ground transportation included, and more. All more affordable than
you can imagine. The adventure of a lifetime starts at GoldenStagSafaris.com. The big game
hunting ranch. GoldenStagSafaris.com.
We're back live. We're gonna go back to John and then George, Jerome, Truth, Raider. We'll
get to all of you before our guest comes on. Briefly, I wanna do a big roll out on this
tomorrow. This has been two years in development. A anti fluoride filter and heavy metal filter
in the regular silver-based ceramic filter in one. And if you go to Infowarsstore.com,
you can see the roll out with Propure.
By the way, we're discounting at 10% out of the gates. Normally, people don't do that.
And we don't do like Walmart where we increase the price and then discount it to say it's
a discount or others have been caught doing. You can get the new all-in-one filters made
in England, developed by scientists here in the United States. This is what I use. It
has just come out. It is amazing. No priming required. The new filters are available. It's
called ProOne from Propure.
And it fits into all of your Propure units. No one else has this. And it also takes out
the hydrofluorosolic acid base that the other filters don't. And all the scientific data
and side-by-side comparisons are up on the site and the studies. And it also cuts out
the sodium hexafluorosilicate, which is the real stuff they're putting in the water.
The truth is most other fluoride filters, and we've sold these too, only reduce it and
they don't get out a lot of the acid-based systems. But this does. It's the new Propure
ProOne available at Infowarsstore.com. And your purchase supports the broadcast or call
888-253-3139, 888-253-3139. Two years in development. In fact, I was first talking to Propure when
they were starting this development. It took them two years to get it all certified, made.
They can only get it made in England because of the high-tech process. England's always
been at the top of the chain when it comes to water purification because their empire
needed purified water.
The point is they've got the factories that can make this. So designed in the US, made
in England, and it's available right now at Infowarsstore.com. Okay, tell folks, and I've
talked to so many people from Ukraine, people from China, people from other areas of Eastern
Europe, where they come and take the guns, and then next, your family starts disappearing.
Stalin did that, took them to the 30s to start getting the guns, and then it was a mass culling.
Tell folks what happened to your family.
Okay, Alex, all I can say is the cost of disarming the people psychologically, physically, spiritually
is staggering. And those who cannot remember the past are condemned to repeat it because
I've experienced it myself, and the government is probably, you know, although they've given
me a new identity here in the United States, and I always promised myself I would never
get involved, but it's come to this where I need to speak out because my children's
future are at stake. But, I mean, they're hoping that, you know, those who have died
in the Vietnam War and those who are still alive are maybe too old to fight, but guess
what? There's still voices out there, and I'm one of the voices that, I've experienced
it.
What happened to your family?
Well, my grandfather was assassinated, and my whole family, we're only three of us that
are survivors here in the United States, but all of them were systematically killed trying
to leave the country, trying to speak up for their rights, and basically, you know, it's
terrible. And if people don't wake up now to see this, they're gonna be-
Where were you, Eastern Europe, Middle East, Asia?
Oh, yeah, Vietnam.
Vietnam, oh, so your family was trying to get out, what, in the early 70s?
Yes, sir.
And was this after they left Saigon, or was this before you couldn't get out?
This is after, or actually at the end of the, where they were starting to pull out everyone.
And of course, for those that don't know that they said, the North Vietnamese, turn your
guns in, we'll give you amnesty. What happened when you turned the guns in? We're gonna come
back to you after this.
You are listening to GCN. Visit GCNlive.com today.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast, and
molds. Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for
water purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support. And it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Coming up in the start of the next segment, James O'Keefe of the Veritas Project. You
know him from bringing down A-Kern and so much more. Going to be joining us. We're taking
a few more of your calls right now. You know, they took the guns in Turkey and then killed
over a million Armenians after they took their guns. That's just one of the smaller cases.
Paul Pot, the list goes on and on. Hitler, Stalin. But you're saying your family was
in southern Vietnam after the US pullout. And I've read the history. Tell people briefly,
John, then we'll go to others. The history of what happened. Because I remember reading,
they told people turn your guns in, we'll give you an amnesty, everything's fine. What
happened once the guns were turned in?
Well, they systematically started killing everyone that was against the government.
Basically I was born in Da Nang and my grandfather was a politician there and he was killed publicly.
And the rest of our family was killed for being part of the family. It's just the loss.
People don't realize the loss that they're gonna experience if they follow through and
they don't speak up now and pull together.
By the way, I've been around all these so-called leftists. They say the plan is to kill us
once they get our guns. I mean, these are monsters. These are not liberals.
The war's already been on. You're absolutely right. I mean, they've been working on us
psychologically, spiritually, and physically. And as an educator, I'm telling you, I know
I work with IDD children. And I'm telling you, there's no way in heck a couple that
are healthy and everything, and they keep on telling you that, oh, it's genetics. It's
not genetics.
There's something that they're doing. It's a slow kill. And this is a culling, cull,
whatever you like. But it's a depopulation program that has been going on for years.
And it's ridiculous. And I'm just at the point where the best defense right now is to speak
out and everybody needs to get out and talk to your neighbors and get everybody on board.
No, you're right. The globalists are all obsessed with organic and purified water. They won't
eat anything, the GMO, the vaccines. It's all a giant eugenics operation. God bless
you, and thanks for your testimony. George in Pennsylvania, thanks for holding here on
the air. Go ahead. What do you think of Feinstein and Cummings for all the semi-autos and more?
I'd like to cover one other thing first. On the vaccines, the government has a website,
Vaccine Adverse Event Reporting System, VAERS at HHS.gov, where if you have problems with
the vaccine, you're supposed to report it.
But no one knows that, so they don't report it. Or if they do, they try to cover it up
quietly, yes.
You might have a link on your site. One other thing about the vaccines, there's a group
of mostly physicians with vaccine-damaged children, autism.com. That's Autism Research
Institute and it has a lot of listings there on things you can do when the kids do get
damaged with vaccines, how to recover them, at least partially.
Second thing is we need to group together. I agree with that. And I think maybe political
correctness on your part would be a good thing. How about a constitutional recovery fund or
something to curb the illegal activities of the judges and the politicians?
We still have a process in place and I think we could be using it if you-
Well, look, they're on the news saying all gun owners are racist scum. The entire South
is filth, but then they're the politically correct people. No, they're a bunch of political
monsters obsessing on race cuz they use it as a weapon.
I mean, Lego can't even put out Jabba the Hutt toys now without the Muslims in Europe
saying it's racist. I mean, this is a way to attack us and tell us we're bad. And I'm
not bashing Muslims in general, the politically correct type. This is a cultural domination.
And then they're like, hey, be nice, have some hospitality, let the globalists run over
you.
We've got to get angry and get out of a cowed position. They're always telling us we're
suspect, we're racist, we're bad, we have guilt, we've done something wrong. Give them
control because we're bad. Let them in, let them boss us, give us their money. They're
intimidating us until we get into them.
Because the government's run by a bunch of raging criminals. And I hear you, I don't
know how it's politically correct to have a constitution recovery fund. Okay, our guest
is coming up, most of you know who they are, I'm just so excited to get them on. James
O'Keefe, the Veritas project straight ahead. Stay with us.
You prepare by purchasing gold, food and firearms. But if you don't have a home security system,
then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection. When you're sleeping
or away from home, who's watching out for intruders? Check out simply safe. It's a new
do it yourself home security system that is completely wireless. Go to get simply safe
dot com. Simply Safe is independent and off the grid. It runs on battery power. So even
if the grid goes down, you're protected. It's completely customizable, so you can use it
in your home, business, boat, trailer, storage unit or shed. Get simply safe calm. Simply
Safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes. So there's no
need to let a stranger into your home. If you move or need to relocate, you can take
the system with you wherever you go. You aren't always at home, but simply safe will stand
guard protecting your property 24 hours a day, seven days a week. Again, that's get
simply safe dot com. Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds,
flu and other illnesses. Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver,
a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology
have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses,
mold and food poisoning and help improve wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough
to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases
such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens. This new technology
has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times
the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says
Silver is our mightiest germ fighter. It is virtually non toxic and is emerging as a wonder
of modern medicine. Go to Supernatural Silver dot com today and use the promo code Silver
2012 for 20% off. That's Supernatural Silver dot com and like us on Facebook. Sick of the
globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as you get
sick and die? Start purifying your water with Pro Pure. My friends, I've done a lot of research
and the best gravity filter out there bar none is Pro Pure and it's available discounted
at info wars dot com. Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth. There's
no priming required. It's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride
up to 95% easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity. Purify water from lakes, streams,
ponds and wells. This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals which is key save money
by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic. Pro Pure is
the best gravity fed filter out there. It's what my family uses info wars.com already
has the lowest price on Pro Pure. But if you add the promo code water at checkout, you
get an additional 10% off at info wars.com. You can also call to order 888-253-3139. We
now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance. Rallying
patriots worldwide Monday through Friday 11 a.m. to 2 p.m. Central, blasting out on XM
over 140 a.m. and having affiliates the internet at info wars.com and prison planet.com streaming
video at prison planet.tv and info wars, nightly news info wars news.com. Now I got to play
a few clips to introduce this guy and for whatever reason over the years I tried to
get him on, didn't get connected, but we've got him on now.
And everybody listening probably knows who this individual is or you know his work and
this is the model. I've done a lot of similar things over the years when I was just out
doing investigations, but none of them ever exploded like this. But we had some big victories.
And this guy and his team is the model. In fact, I just want to say on air, I haven't
told him this shit. He ought to make a how to be a real muckraking journalist for Liberty.
He'll make a film about it, showing how it's done because what he does, the corrupt that
run this system and I've said this for many years. You can, let me introduce our guest
here in a moment and play some clips first.
You can go and fight the globalist, the collectivist, especially Democrats for whatever reason.
You can go follow them in their car when they're doing corrupt things and they will always
be doing something horrible. I mean, it's hard to not catch them. I've caught bribery
at the state capitol, just goes on everywhere, paying guys cash. The bill got defeated. It
was in the front page of the newspaper and that was back in 1999, just type in Alex Jones
catches bribery.
I've done more than 50 or 60 things just like this. Not because I'm some great investigator,
the corrupt do this right out in front of you, okay? The corrupt do this right out in
front of you and you've just got to go out and expose them and have the courage. But
if we just engage these people, it's over.
James O'Keefe is the president of Project Veritas. I was saying Veritas Project, no
teleprompter. James O'Keefe is a graduate of Rutgers University. He has received a congressional
resolution praising him for his work and a receipt, a recipient of the Robert Novak Award
for journalistic excellence.
He's best well known for the 2009 Acorn investigation, which exposed systematic corruption in multiple
offices, different cities, different areas. You walk in and go, I have an underage prostitute
I snuck in the country. We're gonna play a clip of that. And I want to sell her out.
How do I keep her under the radar? Well, just make sure you put her in school so the government
gets theirs, but everything's fine. Gonna pimp her good. And forced the group to be
disbanded, losing them millions of dollars a year, and that was one of their big syndicate
takeovers.
He's also exposed to NPR. The sting involved NPR executive Ron Shiller and senior director
Betsy Lilly. The two agreed to receive 5 million donation from a fictitious Muslim organization.
The two executives later resigned. The House of Representatives voted to defund NPR. And
again, folks, people don't believe I snuck into Bohemian Grove. They just can't believe
I got in there and did it.
You've never tried things. People can't believe. You have power is my point. That's what I
want you to understand. You are the ones that are gonna defeat these people. And the model
is somebody like James O'Keefe. The project veritas.org, theprojectveritas.org. And of
course it's supported by patriots like you, so go there and do that.
Through Project Veritas, James has personally trained and equipped dozens of citizen journalists
in an effort to create transparency in government and spending. And of course, that's what their
job is. But I'm saying put it out to everybody, which I know they've done some of. Now let's
play something he's not well known for.
And since then, there's new clips of Christians going up to abortionist and saying, hey, let
us adopt the babies. And they go, you don't want the ugly black babies. But you're racist
if you don't want them aborted. Remember that, cuz it's racist, don't wanna save them. And
it's racist if you don't like the communist Chinese and apple suicide nets if you wanna
save the Chinese little girls.
You're liberal if you just let them all die. See, the liberals are eugenicist. I made the
film Endgame, exposing that. So let's go to this first clip, then a short clip of the
next, then we'll do the rest of the hour with our guests. But it's so exciting, okay, because
I've been doing this type of thing for 17 years.
He's been doing it, I don't know, for six, seven years. We're gonna talk to him in a
moment, James O'Keefe of theprojectveritas.org. But let's go ahead and go to this first clip
of him calling in to Planned Parenthood. This has been duplicated by others. Planned Parenthood
was set up to, quote, kill the black weeds, Margaret Sanger, John D Rockefeller.
Let's go ahead and play the clip.
Afternoon, this is Autumn. Hello, Autumn. I mentioned making a donation today. Fantastic. What about abortions for the underprivileged minority groups? Oh, absolutely. We have, in fact, wonderful, fantastic news. We just received a very generous donation to our Women in Need fund. Wonderful. I wanna specify that abortion can help a minority group. Would that be possible? Absolutely. Like the black community, for example? Certainly. Okay. So the abortion could be, you know, I could give
money specifically for a black baby. That would be the purpose. Yeah, absolutely. If
you wanted to designate that you wanted your gift to be used to help an African American
woman in need, then we would certainly make sure that that gift was earmarked specifically
for that purpose. Great. Because I really face trouble with affirmative action and I
don't want my kids being disadvantaged, you know, against black kids. I just had a baby.
I want to put it in his name, you know. So that's definitely possible. Oh, always, always.
So I just wanted, can I put this in the name of my son? Absolutely. The name of my son,
great. He's trying to get into colleges. All right, let's stop right there. You know, and
you can go online and go to the Veritas project and see that report in full and others. And
I have protested back when I had more time to do it. I'm protesting on air now, abortion
clinics. And here in Austin, also in Dallas, and I've had them walk up to me and they go,
no one wants these black babies.
These people are a problem. And I'm telling you, most liberals at that level are not liberals.
These are flaming racist. See, real racists aren't wearing Klan outfits. Usually those
are feds, you know, meaning to make gun owners racist or something. The real ones are trendies.
I want to go to our guest. We'll play the famous clip of him dressed as a 70s pimp.
Totally obvious with an underage girl telling him she's underage. And discussing how to
get the tax exemptions and things for his pimping operation and how to run little girls
into the US. We've all seen that, so I won't play it now. We'll get to it later in some
other clips.
James O'Keefe, great to have you on. Again, I just salute you. You were on The Nightly
News with Sha'Carri Jackson last week. You just heard the comments I made about liberals
saying how much they want to kill the black people while saying all gun owners are racist
against blacks.
How did you wake up to all of this? And let's just get into where you see the state of this
country right now.
Well, Alex, I think I was going to be on your show five or six years ago. We did that Planned
Parenthood investigation with a young woman named Lila Rose. And we called up, I'd say
about seven or eight Planned Parenthoods across the country. And I heard about Margaret Sanger,
who was a eugenicist back in the early part of the 20th century. And we called up these
Planned Parenthoods. And right before you cut the clip, the vice president of Planned
Parenthood actually said that it's understandable and exciting to abort black children. Because
I said there were too many, I was acting, I said there were too many black people in
this country and we need to abort them, is what I said to Planned Parenthood. And the
vice president of Planned Parenthood resigned. And it was a national story at the time. And
that kind of got me into thinking that the way to expose malfeasance and corruption and
fraud is to kind of just take it right to them and make them live up to their own principles.
And that's sort of what we do at Project Veritas. We make people live up to their own book of
rules, which is right out of Saul Alinsky's rules for radicals.
I remember, in fact, I interviewed people six or seven years ago about this. Have I
interviewed you then?
We were gonna connect and for whatever reason, we just didn't connect.
I just remember playing the clip at the time because, listen, it's not like you're trying
to find a four-leaf clover and there's only a few of them that are eugenicist. I'm saying
about 80% of mid-level or higher ups I run into will go, listen, we gotta get rid of
these black people. Stop protesting. What's wrong with you? You're white.
And now more and more videos of that have surfaced. You don't want ugly black babies.
The point is, I want the left out there, the mainline left who's idiots to understand.
These people are monsters. Go ahead.
We found it. I mean, it's all on tape. I let the people speak for themselves. We call the
New Mexico Clinic. This is Planned Parenthood, New Mexico. And when I said, and I'm acting,
of course, I'm acting like a racist, and I say, well, you know, it's just, it's terrible
what's going on in our country with black people and affirmative action. And this Planned
Parenthood vice president said to me in New Mexico, she said, it's a strange time for
sure. And this is what she's caught on tape saying when she does not know that she's being
videotaped. And it really cuts to the heart and soul. Why do they put all the clinics
in the inner city neighborhoods? And what's really remarkable, Alex, is that the media
tries to ignore it. But the good thing about Project Veritas is we, because we get results,
because these people resign or they're forced to resign, the Associated Press does not have
a choice but to write coverage about it. And that's how it kind of gets it. And Lila has
gone on to do a lot of other videos. She did a video on Planned Parenthood and statutory
rape. That got on CBS News. So the interesting thing about what we do as citizen journalists
is that we force this stuff into the mainstream media.
And I think that more people need to do that. Being around these people infiltrating them,
I've discovered they're almost all really sick people and criminals are a mix of the
two. In all your investigations, I mean, I found it's not like again, it's not like it's
hard to find this. This is a really group of vicious people. And do you agree that the
biggest hoax ever is that the liberal establishment is liberal? They're not. They're a bunch of
monsters.
I found it, the word that I use, and a lot of people think that it's absurd. I think
it's fascism. In my experience as a citizen journalist, I have been arrested. I have been
falsely accused. I did a voter fraud expose last year on Eric Holder and a number of states
giving out voting ballots in the name of other people. And these are facts, ideal in fact
as a journalist. And exposing this stuff on videotape, the reaction is always arrest O'Keeffe,
prosecute O'Keeffe, silence O'Keeffe, censor him, silence him, arrest him. And that to
me is not a liberal mentality. There's nothing liberal about wanting to jail journalists.
And this is not, this is just, I'm being straightforward. I was arrested in New Orleans.
Let's talk about that. We're going to break riveting a live interview with James O'Keeffe
from theprojectveritas.org.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book Cancer Step Outside the Box.
I want you to know some very important information. In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested
that carnivora be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the president could
obtain this world-class healer. Now, 27 years later, carnivore capsules are used around
the world to keep people healthy. Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in
this age of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal
cells only without harming a single normal cell. If you want to stay healthy, now's your
chance to literally wake up your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that
don't belong in your body. Call 1-866-VENUSFLY or order from carnivora.com. That's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VENUSFLY or visit carnivora.com. Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration. As an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years and serving thousands of
satisfied customers, the Berkey Guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration
systems. The Berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable
black purification elements that purify water by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria,
cysts and parasites to non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides
and pesticides. Order the Berkey light system today complete with two black Berkey elements
for only $231 and the Berkey Guy will ship your order free of charge. With the purchase
of a Berkey light, the Berkey Guy is also offering a set of fluoride and arsenic filters
for only $39.99. That's over 30% off the retail price. Call the Berkey Guy at 1-877-886-3653.
That's 1-877-886-3653 or order online at goberkey.com. That's goberkey.com today.
Do you know how much the dollar has lost in its value against other currencies in the
last 90 days? Ever think about how inflation will change your life, your savings, your
retirement plans? Remember inflation in Zimbabwe, Argentina, the Weimar Republic? Put another
way, who cares if your investments go up 10% but you lose 40% of your purchasing power?
Gold is the only monetary asset as no one else's liability. Gold still buys the same
amount of stuff it always did. Gold does not require trust in a third party. You can possess
it in your hand. You can take it with you. Gold is real money. Gold is honest money.
My name is Daniel Larson from Midas Resources. To find out how you can protect your savings
and roll over your IRA funds into precious metals accounts, please call me at 800-686-2237
extension 134. That's 800-686-2237 extension 134. 800-686-2237 extension 134.
It's time for a home security quiz. Answer this. What effective home security device
is smaller than a coffee cup fakes out burglars into thinking someone is home at your house
while you're away, plugs into any wall outlet, is recommended by many police departments
and sells for less than $35? Yes, it's fake TV. This year about one in every 50 US homes
will have a break in with burglars usually picking the easy target, a dark house that
looks like no one is home. Fake TV is a small electronic security device that makes it look
like someone is home watching TV by simulating the light from a real TV. It's like a lamp
on a timer, but far more convincing. And for only $34.95, fake TV could be the difference
between coming home to a secure house or one that's been ransacked. Go to faketv.com or
call 1-877-5FAKETV. That's 877-532-5388 or go to faketv.com. Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you're listening to this for the first time and you think this
is hyperbole, there are scores of clips on their website of acorn people saying, yeah,
we'll help you do this illegal thing. We'll help you run child prostitutes. We'll help
you do that. And this is just how the system works. And they want to make every city like
the big Chicago, New York mafia style systems. And we need to have the people in Chicago
and New York and other cities stand up against this.
And the way to do it, if you were to follow a Planned Parenthood person, let's say you
work next door to a bar and walk over and record them. Make sure it's a state where
you have one party consent saying, hey, we need to kill the black people. Why do you
work there? They're gonna agree to you. They've all been told don't talk about it on the phone
when you call.
And how it's a great civil right and all this stuff. The point is, these people, all of
them are so sick that if you just engage them, they're all involved in bizarre behavior.
Going back to our guests, this is a short segment, long segment coming up. We'll play
some clips during it. James O'Keefe, the head journalist of the Project Truth, Project Veritas,
continue.
You were talking about how they're authoritarians, how they're always wanting you arrested for
exposing their activities.
Exactly, there have been a number of occasions where I've been subpoenaed. Most famously,
there was a huge story where I was in New Orleans investigating Senator Mary Landrieu,
and she was not answering her constituents' phone calls during the health care debate
in 2010. I went into the federal building with a camera, a recording device, and as
you pointed out, one party consent states, so it's legal to do it in Louisiana. But I
was in a federal building, I was arrested, and they were gonna let me go as a journalist.
They said, oh, you're just there to ask questions. And then they found out that I was the acorn
pimp. I went into acorn posing as a pimp and hooker, and they said, well, you know, based
on the senator and these other situations, we're gonna have to keep you overnight in
federal prison. And then I wake up the next day, and I find myself charged with some ridiculous
felony. I had to get a lawyer, spent six months fighting it, finally got it down to a misdemeanor.
The US attorney resigned in disgrace just recently for going online. It's just so corrupt.
And I've been, as a citizen journalist, I'm not like David Gregory. I'm not immune from
being prosecuted for committing crimes. But it's just unbelievable what they wanna censor
us and silence us and even jail us for exposing them on tape. And the good news is I'm still
standing, and we haven't given up, and we've got a ton of stories under our belt. We're
developing a track record now.
Talk about some of the other intriguing investigative reports you put out that haven't gone mega
viral that people may not be aware of.
Sure, after the acorn story, the MTR story was on the front page of all the major newspapers.
But after that, we did a story on Medicaid. Medicaid, entitlement programs in this country.
We went into Medicaid offices in Ohio, Virginia, and Maine. And we said that we were Russian
drug dealers. We talked about pimping girls. We talked about importing exotic sports cars
and putting drugs in. And we said, we just want Medicaid, even though we're multimillionaires.
See something, say something, like the Social Security Administration sending hundreds of
millions to one address in Austin knowing it's a fraud.
But then literally, the police are told to spy on gun owners and we're criminals.
In the case of Medicaid, what the woman actually told us, and this is on YouTube, it's got
100,000 views, is I said, you know, what are we going to call our illicit drug business?
And she said, just say that you're a babysitter. And she was fired. This worker in Medicaid
was fired. And the state of Ohio said they were going to retrain all their workers.
We did it in Virginia. We got the same response. The Medicaid worker told us not to put it
down on our forms. We did it in Maine. The governor of each state launched an investigation.
There is a criminal culture to liberals. I've got to be honest. Again, I don't like the
Republicans either, but downright local Democrats, when you really get near them, they're crooks.
As evidenced by the videos that we've produced, they certainly don't have a problem with helping
give money, give government-
Telling somebody to falsify forms to cover up drug dealing is a crime.
That's absolutely right. And by the way, the police have gotten involved. They have Cuccinelli
in Virginia. He launched a criminal investigation, a criminal probe, and then most recently with
our voter fraud video in Virginia. Many people, your listeners may know this story. It was
all over the mainstream media, but Congressman Jim Moran's son resigned in October over telling
one of our undercover reporters how to vote twice to elect President Obama, a forging
utility bills, voting in the names of other people. So this is a Congressman's son who
was his field director. His name is Patrick Moran. He resigned and the police got involved.
The detective in Arlington County called me, wanted me to cooperate with this investigation.
And then I find out this detective might be bought and sold by the Congressman. So it's
really, it's difficult being a citizen.
We'll be right back. This is amazing.
Here on the march, the empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just
in time to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at FiveStarSoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at FiveStarSoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog. Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom
lovers. The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse. The
globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover. That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness
items at InfoWarsShop.com. These are items that I did research on that I personally use.
We've got the LifeStraw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go. The
Ktor Hand Crank Generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out in the
field. Strategic Relocation Third Edition by Joel Skousen. When disaster strikes by
Matthew Stein. Ferro Safe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological
event. Hand Crank Shortwave AM FM radios. Everything that we've researched and found
to be the best is available at InfoWarsShop.com and your purchase makes our info war possible.
You're getting prepared. Are you InfoWarsShop.com.
I know we've had some callers holding for the last hour. You'll get a chance to bring
up your gun issue and also ask our amazing guest a question. Again, Alex Jones here back
live James O'Keefe of the Project Veritas. Project Truth is on with us. The Project Veritas.org.
Of course, our sites are InfoWars.com and the nightly news is transmitted out via prisonplanet.tv.
By the way, one membership for $5.95 a month now is 11 memberships. Your membership and
10 other people simultaneously can use the same username and passcode. So use an original
username passcode that's simple and then give it to friends and family because probably
it's like 20 people.
There's no way that usually all 11 people are gonna be tuned in at seven o'clock every
night when Info Wars Nightly News goes on. That's part of Operation Awaken the Sleeping
Giant. We will officially launch the $100,000 film. I've gotten so behind with all the gun
grabbing all the tyranny we're facing that I have not lost the big $100,000 contest for
films yet.
We should have done that like three weeks ago, but we're gonna launch it with a film
promo tomorrow on the show premiered here. I shot the video, wrote the rules, went over
it with legal. It's $115,000 in cash prizes, $100,000 first place. That will be announced
tomorrow on the radio.
I know I said I would announce it a few weeks ago and never got to it because quite frankly,
everything comes secondary to free speech and the Second Amendment. I mean, when that's
getting attacked, you notice I haven't even plugged in products or things until last week.
And a little secret about radio, most of the real funding of the syndicated show itself
is what they do live on air.
You listen to most talk show hosts, it's into the show with a plug, out of the break with
a plug, five, six, seven plugs an hour. And quite frankly, I should be doing a couple
hour because that's how I can fund this operation. They're like, hey, there's not a lot of money
coming in, better plug stuff.
Plus I plug things I believe in, like the new Infowars.com come and take it shirt with
an AK-47 and inside of it the words, the right to keep and bear arms shall not be infringed.
And also, two years in the making, designed by scientists engineers in the US, now made
in England with the latest technology. And two years being built and approved and certified,
read all that information side by side, gravity fed filtration system by ProPure.
It's called ProOne and it is two filters in one. It's got the silver base system impregnated
with silver and ceramic. Under it, the system's to reduce down to 95% hydrofluorosolic acid.
The big secret is the other leading filters, and we've sold these with ProPure cuz it's
good to get most of it out. Only get around half of it out because the hydrofluorosolic
acid goes right through it.
This 95%, okay, this is amazing. In fact, the other filters don't even really do anything
to hydrofluoric acid, but it tends to break back down. The point is it loses electron
or they pull an electron and then add it. All the science stuff's up on the site. This
is a revolution. We are the biggest distributor of ProPure because I did my own research two
years ago and got them as a sponsor.
You notice for a year I didn't have a gravity fed sponsor because the quality unfortunately
with some of them out there just wasn't even good enough for me to promote it. You hear
ads on the network where I've already been approached and offered $500,000 in a year
to promote this. I go, no, I'm not gonna promote it. I don't believe in it. If I believe in
something, you're gonna hear me promoting it.
And this is an amazing system, ProPure, infowarstore.com, infowarstore.com, or 888-253-3139. And it's
10% off on all the stainless steel systems, the Traveler, the Big, the King, all of it.
And 10% off even the new filters that are launching today. Today, today, today, made
in England. Not even factories that can make this in the United States or places like China
or India. You can see right there on the filter it says made in England.
So there you go. All right, enough of me ranting and raving about that. It's just that your
purchase makes the transmission possible. So infowarstore.com or 888-253-3139. Films
like Strategic Relocation and others that I produced also available at infowarstore.com.
Or to understand the eugenics angle, infowarstore.com with end game blueprint for global enslavement.
I wanna go to this pimp clip in a moment. But continuing here with our guest James O'Keeffe
of the Project Veritas. What else do you wanna impart to viewers and listeners about the
state of the world right now?
I mean, I think the biggest thing I would ask you is, what is your rallying cry? Because
your rallying cry just from truth is what mine is. Evil men and tyrants flourish because
good men and women do nothing. These people, a lot of these people that run the system
are really stupid. But it's our weakness in bowing down to government that empowers them.
It's the ether in which these slugs thrive. You've got the floor, my friend.
Well, one thing that's unique about Project Veritas is that I don't advocate policy solutions.
I don't tell people who to vote for. I don't tell people what to believe. I'm a strong
believer in the following statement. I believe in the, I have an infinite faith in the power
of free people. That if they're just making their own decisions, if they have the truth
available to them, that they will make the best decisions to create a great, lasting
and moral society. I think what we need more of, we need more journalism. We need more
people exposing the facts. And the fact of the matter is that there aren't a lot of journalists.
There are a lot of stenographers, people who, you know, they write down what the politicians
say at the podium, or pundits, people who are, you know, on television, or they take
preexisting content. But Alex, one thing I actually admired, you did, I must have seen
this video maybe eight years ago, but on YouTube, you went into the DMV, and they asked you
for identification. You took out eight pieces of identification. What you were doing is
important. I mean, that's a direct action. You went in there and you sort of, you taped
it, you exposed something. We need more people doing journalism, pure journalism. And I think
that people are smart enough. This recent video we did on the guns in New York and the
people pushing gun owners, I went up to the journalists and I asked them, would you put
a sign on your lawn that says that your home is gun free?
By the way, let me stop you there. That's the original reason I wanted to get you on
last week. Start over, and the video is on your website, it's amazing. We can probably
play some here for viewers while he's talking, then I have the pimp clip. But I mean, this
shows their incredible hypocrisy. The truth is they've got guns, they've got bodyguards.
Their kids go to schools with armed men like David Gregory. So start over and tell people
about that.
Sure, I was inspired to do this because of David Gregory and because I have been arrested
and falsely accused and faced political prosecution. And the judge destroyed my videotape so that
no one knows what I actually did in Louisiana. But when David Gregory on NBC News brought
a magazine into the studio, which is a felony in Washington DC, and he was not prosecuted.
In fact, the DC Attorney General released a statement, I believe it was two weeks ago,
and the district, I actually have it in front of me here, he said that it was a clear violation
of the law, what Gregory did. But it didn't, quote, serve the best interests of the people,
unquote, to prosecute David Gregory. Now, he does have prosecutorial discretion-
So he's Judge Dredd now. They tell juries we can't judge the law and the facts, which
of course we can. But the police, especially high level ones, they're not supposed to do
that. It's a grand jury and it's the people. Well, that is, I know I've done a lot of constitutional
law research. What that prosecutor did, I think was wrong.
I think it's wrong because I think the Supreme Court says equal justice under law. And if
I did that, if I, for purposes of a YouTube video, if I brought a magazine in the District
of Columbia from an AR-15, I'd be prosecuted, no question.
If I did, I'd be arrested, you know it. There is a different, so I'm just getting
to what inspired me to do this video, which I think is important, is the fact that there's
a different class of people, the politicians, the journalists, they consider themselves
protected from the law. And then I got to thinking, now, what if I made them live up
to their own principles, and I went to the, okay, you obviously don't like guns.
So will you advertise that to the public? Will you put a sign on your lawn that says
this house is proudly gun free? Because journalists, you're willing to advertise to the world who
owns a gun, you're willing to publish law abiding gun owners, therefore you should have
no problem with doing it. They're terrorists, they're not journalists,
they're saying the South is all scum, gun owners are scum, publishing where we live
that we have guns. It's time to get angry at these people. I mean, that newspaper needs
to be sued. We need to get aggressive with them. I'm sorry, go ahead.
No, I mean, my way of doing that is by exposing them. I think that we need to, I went to their
homes. I mean, there's nothing more aggressive than going to somebody's house and knocking
on the door. And I went to their homes with a camera. They didn't know they were being
taped. And I said, you know, I said that to the publisher of the Westchester Journal News,
that's the newspaper that printed all the gun owners in Westchester County. I live in
Westchester, New York. That's where I'm from. I'm only a few miles away from these people.
And we said, would you post the sign on the lawn? Nobody would post the sign. In fact,
if you watch the video, the most extraordinary thing about this YouTube video is that all
these editors and reporters are justifying the Second Amendment. They're pro gun. They
just don't know it. Instinctively, their human nature informs them that they don't want to
tell people they're gun free. And that's what I'm trying to tell you. My message at Project
Veritas is that I have faith in free people if they're just given the facts that they
know what's good for them and their families.
Well, I'll say this. They're trying to physically make us turn our guns in, register them, ban
them. They're assaulting us. And our founders, you know, physically went after them. We need
to just go and get in their faces at public events. If they're publishing people's names
and where they live, we need to go to their house and say, hey, I'm out here with a bullhorn,
buddy.
Anybody who got your name published in the newspaper, they assaulted your privacy. They
told criminals who to go rob. It's time to go to their houses and bullhorn them and to
come back the next day and bullhorn them. When the cops show up videotape it and go,
officer, here's my name in the newspaper where I live and I have a gun.
I have a first right to be here and do this. And then if they arrest you, you sue them
because of the hypocrisy. I mean, it's time to get aggressive. Here's an example. 1996.
They are taking veterans' homes, $2,000 a day fines. They had some registry at the hospital,
I discovered. I learned this from hospital workers that they would know when somebody
had bad cancer or had a heart attack and was a widow, a widower.
They would then go to the nice home in the million dollar area that they wanted to get
and force into foreclosure. They put $2,000 a day fines on it for three inch grass. Well,
a good cop called me and said, hey, I know where all the city council people live. A
bunch of them have like three foot grass, the middle of the city, holes in the roofs.
I don't know why they did. So I went to Jackie Goodman's house and others, went to the health
department.
Showed they had like foot tall grass and trash on the ground and said, okay, let's put $2,000
fines on you. And they dropped all these fines on old people. Here's the problem. My phone,
I was one guy, two guys, ringing with old people having their houses taken for two inch
grass.
And they always were like, let me ask, you should have a heart attack. You can't walk.
Yeah, you just got out of the hospital last week and the notices are coming. Let me guess,
you got, so you're dying of cancer. Yeah, I got a few months to live. They just want
your house. They want to lean on it. I mean, that's a mafia right there. And you know what,
I couldn't, I bet it's still going on.
That's the frustration. We need 50 Alex Jones's in Austin. We need 50 in Rochester, New York.
We need 100 in Chicago. I mean, people are being abused, folks. And folks go in and turn
their TVs on and watch sitcoms at night. And they don't know the old lady's having their
house stolen.
Go ahead, I'm ranting.
No, I would respect if these journalists, for example, would put the signs on their
lawns. I would at least respect that because they would be philosophically consistent.
But the fact that they're inconsistent, the fact that they would be willing to publish
gun owners but be unwilling to advertise themselves as not owning guns. We went to MSNBC's Toure.
Toure is a commentator on MSNBC. And he was unwilling to post the sign. He was stumbling
and stuttering when we asked him to. He said, you know what, I don't know if I want to do
that.
And that's what makes them frauds and cowards. And nobody, nobody likes a fraud or a coward.
And nobody rides for free either. I'm sick of these slugs feeding off of us.
And what we tried to do, we want to measure the courage of their convictions. Do they
actually believe in this thing? And at the end of the video, one of the most telling,
I think this is the most fascinating thing about the video, is that one of the reporters
for the New Jersey Star-Ledger, who supported outing gun owners and printing their names
and addresses, told us that he hates guns, he wishes they were banned and everything.
But if, this is his words, he says, when the right wing takes over the government, we need
to be armed to defend ourselves from that government. So even though he's putting an
ideological spin on it, he's actually making some type of justification for the Second
Amendment.
But they're so dumb, they don't get that right wing, left wings control at the top, there's
gonna be Republicans in later. No, liberals, I all knew, went out and bought guns under
Bush. And now they're like, let's turn them in.
It's just mindlessness. These people have no sense. And you know what, I wanna hold
you if you can do it a little bit in the next hour and go into overdrive, cuz I promised
to go to phone calls. And I wanna play some of these reports of you going and doing the
guns. Can you do 30 minutes more into the next hour?
Sure, yep, absolutely. Okay, fantastic. I wanna play now, though, the pimp clip. Do
we have that queued up? Yep, cuz we're gonna go to the pimp clip first. Because this is
what you're more, I mean, this is super mega viral for months, brought down Acorn, got
it defunded. How many billions did it get defunded?
It was allocated $5 billion in the stimulus package. And of course, they went bankrupt
after the videos, so they weren't given any of that.
Tell people a little bit more about that case, if they may have forgotten.
Sure, Acorn Association of Community Organized for Reform Now. President Barack Obama was
an attorney for Acorn, I believe in the 80s or 90s. Acorn, it has a couple different branches,
but they claim to help giving low income housing for people. What they mostly do is they get
out the vote efforts, they help with voter registration drives.
What we wanted to uncover was, what exactly this group is doing, where its money goes.
We visited Acorn branches across the United States, and I posed as a pimp. Of course,
I'm not the most pimp-like individual, but I-
No, welfare and all this, cuz I've talked to people involved, it's all designed for
fraud. You can go in and get 20 kids signed up. You can go in and they want control and
they want to bankrupt the country. Let's go to this clip where you're saying, this is
my underage girl I brought in from another country, I want to bring in more.
They're like, hey, we'll help you falsify everything, just make sure she's in school.
Here it is.
Cops on us before.
Right, and anything that's in Maryland, anything that's not governing the food, it's always
against the law. That's rule number one.
Do you default to taxes?
No.
Well, she gets paid mostly in cash, which makes a lot of money, though, so you could
afford something.
Okay, let me get somebody here for taxes so they can talk to you about how do you do this.
It's not like that.
It's against the law, and law enforcement is very prejudicial towards us.
But she's going to make us illegal books of this. That's like, yes, I got the taxes.
How can she do that, though?
Because she is good. I'm going to tell you, she won't know how you can make it legal.
She's really good. She's not going to get drunk on herself.
The type of business or service she provides, let me make sure there's a code for it, okay?
A code for prostitution?
Well, yeah, because I have to have a name and a code number.
Well, I don't know if there's going to be a code for it.
But I'm going to look in there, I'm going to get my list.
Okay.
She's going to sit up and say she's good, that's what I'm saying.
She's going to make us illegal books of this.
Well, how can she do that?
Let me make sure there's a code for it, okay?
A code for prostitution?
Okay, let's see what we got here.
Combination, food service, and drinking places.
Business and food department.
Service out of the collection agencies.
Credit bills.
You might have to name it something else.
I mean, there's hours of this stuff, and then they get into the underage people they're
going to bring in.
That's all great.
We're going to go to break.
Come back with our guests.
Go to some of your calls that have been holding.
Jerome in Illinois, Truth Raider in Oregon, and others, and we're going to go into overdrive
with our guests.
With more, straight ahead, I'm Alex Jones.
If you've ever wanted one of our best-selling generators, but were waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not going to want to miss this exciting message.
Here's why.
Our solar generators provide life-saving electrical power, and unlike gas generators, solar generators
run quietly, emit no fumes, and produce electricity from the sun.
So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part.
Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse, and we discount them heavily at the end of
each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait.
They go fast.
Go to scratchanddentsolar.com.
That's scratchanddentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com.
Other than decomposition, the Bokashi system uses fermentation to break down waste, so
it takes less time to create nutrient-dense humus for crops or gardens with no turning
and no obnoxious odors.
To learn more and order your Bokashi online, visit tereganics.com and click on the orange
button.
That's tereganics.com, spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X dot com, or call 866-369-3678.
That's 866-369-3678.
Call all your food wastes in about six weeks with the Bokashi food waste recycling system
from tereganics.com.
Tereganics.
Life's getting better.
Hi there.
My name is Frank Bates.
What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble.
I just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are, incompetent line crooks that
are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high.
Some have called this a conspiracy, others have called it a cover-up, and you will be
shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy goes.
My video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them
and how you can beat them too.
Watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patriots have already seen
in the last three months.
Go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect
your home.
Go watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down.
Again, that's 123coverup.com.
All right.
In this segment, the next, we're going to take some calls with folks that have been
holding on the Second Amendment with James O'Keefe.
Then we'll do 30 minutes with him in overdrive, which a lot of stations carry, into the fourth
hour.
We always do three hours.
For a while, I did four hours, so we still keep doing the fourth hour sometimes because
there's a bunch of other news I want to cover after he leaves us as well.
But it's official.
They're coming after the handguns too, and we're going to play some of the clips for
radio listeners and TV listeners of James O'Keefe going to Eric Holder's house and saying,
will you put up a gun-free zone sign?
I mean, Eric Holder is a gangster, folks.
I mean, hardcore, Fast and Furious, OKC, involved in it all.
And this guy's got gigantic huevos rancheros.
James O'Keefe is our guest.
Folks have been holding Jerome, Truther, and others.
Jerome in Illinois, thanks for holding here on the air about the Second Amendment, I believe
you called him.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
Thanks for having me on your show, Alex, and it's good to hear that there's other people
in the world that share my thoughts about gun control.
You know, I keep hearing people ask the question about assault weapons.
Do Americans really need an assault weapon to defend themselves?
And my answer to that question is absolutely yes.
I believe we do need assault weapons because it levels the playing field.
That's right, the criminals are going to have them, so we need them.
But I mean, they use that debate.
It's about enslavement.
Let's ask our guest.
Why do you think they're coming after the guns?
I mean, I think I know the answer I'm going to get.
Oh, you're asking me why do I think they're coming after like AR-15s and things like that?
It's because they love you, right?
They want to help you.
I mean, I think they're coming after them in order to...
I think that they may have good intentions, but they're emotional and they don't understand
that when you take away law-abiding gun owners that you, you know, you increase crimes.
Come on!
Diane Feinstein is a crime boss, insider, I mean, come on.
You're a smart guy.
You're not that naive.
You know the criminal elements the government want our guns to enslave us.
They even admit that in some of their white papers.
Sometimes they do admit it, and you're right.
Other times, sometimes they're well-intentioned.
They just don't realize the policy outcome of when they do that, when they ban law-abiding
people from owning guns.
Well, yeah, I mean, some of the little chicken necks and stuff that, you know, didn't have
somebody take them out shooting and things.
They're scared of them, I agree.
I'm talking about high level.
Why does the, why does the UN want guns worldwide?
That's beyond my pay grade.
They want to be the only ones with guns.
That's their plan.
That's, yes, that's, that's very true.
I mean, you know about the UN worldwide, what they do?
I mean, they line people up in Africa and Latin America and just shoot villages to take
their property on record.
They killed 4,000 people in Burma on record in the 90s, just went in and killed all the
villagers to take their property.
The UN is a giant murder crew, but they constantly have every Miss America saying, oh, they're
so sweet.
They're helping the children.
They go in and start the wars, but they're the UN, so it must be okay.
One of the interesting things that I've found in my research, one thing that we're working
on right now is the sort of, just like with Planned Parenthood and the racist elements
with that, some of the racist elements with gun control.
Clarence Thomas wrote a concurring opinion on McDonald v. Chicago, and he goes into the
Ku Klux Klan and disarming African American people and what that means in the inner city
communities.
And there are some people who are practitioners in the Heller case in DC.
That's a very interesting angle.
No, exactly, and that's why they call guns racist, which makes no sense, is to flip it
because you notice it's the black areas where they always have the gun control so that only
the criminals have the guns and the crime rates explode.
They know it's gonna make it a crime pit.
And also, a lot of black people are dying because they don't have the ability to defend
themselves.
Jerome, anything else from Illinois?
Yeah, one other comment.
I also wanted to say that I heard Alan Dershowitz say on Pierce Morgan's show that he would
be afraid to go into your home and have a disagreement with you because he would feel
uncomfortable thinking that you might go for one of your guns.
And I would like to ask Alan Dershowitz how comfortable would he feel if he had a disagreement
with it?
Stay there.
Thank you for listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu, and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold, and food poisoning, and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day, while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as stress, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus, and
other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Fantastic Coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, we're into the fourth hour of overdrive here on this Thursday edition, and we're joined
by James O'Keefe.
I get so relaxed by the fourth hour, I stop even pronunciating.
It's not like I'm drunk.
I've been on radio so much and TV so much the last 17 years.
Probably more airtime than anybody else out there.
I just kind of get like, man, yeah, next guest up, let's go to, I'm like, oh, wait, I'm on
the radio.
Let me actually pronunciate my words.
James O'Keefe, and he heads up the Project Veritas, and we're very excited to have him
on with us in another 30 minutes.
We're gonna start taking more of your calls, and then after we're done taking a few calls,
we're gonna get into some of the other things they're working on right now and play some
more of the videos of him going to Eric Holder's house to say, hey, why don't you put a sign
up saying you don't own guns?
Oh, no, he needs guns to protect himself.
There's a lot of other key news up at Infowars.com right now, but Jerome, you were pointing out
that Alan Dershowitz, after I was on right before him on Piers Morgan, said I wouldn't
be in that man's home if he disagreed with guns, implying I'm psychopathic and I'm gonna
kill somebody with a gun.
This is a guy that promotes torture, secret arrest, all this stuff.
He's a joke in the legal system.
He's represented all the, some of the most horrible criminals ever known.
And he is a monster, and he's implying I'm violent, I'm bad, cuz I said, look, foreigner,
stop trying to take our guns.
But what did you wanna say to Dershowitz?
I wanted to ask Alan Dershowitz, how would he feel if he had a disagreement with a dictator
and that dictator ordered that he be killed, cuz that's what dictators do.
You're absolutely right, let's take another call with our guest.
But James O'Keefe, before we do that, do you wanna comment on my Piers Morgan appearance
or the overall attack on guns?
I mean, I think it takes all kinds to make the world go round, but I think it's good
sometimes to get in their faces.
If what I did was discrediting the gun owners, which they tried to spin it, why would they
have me back on other shows?
Why was the producer crying and screaming, get out, get out, get out, if it was a defeat
for gun owners?
My comment on Piers Morgan is I only wish that Project Veritas went to his house and
asked him to put a sign on his lawn, cuz I've actually done some research and I actually
have both of his addresses out there in California.
So I think he has one property in Beverly Hills under a different name.
So maybe you might see a video from us in the next week or two coming out on that subject.
Oh, a little sneak peek, you're gonna be visiting Piers.
Maybe.
What do you need funding for?
I bet you're doing good.
Oh, yes, well, we do need funding.
How about I underwrite you go into Piers' house, and then I get a plug for M4wars.com.
You want some help there?
We might be able to talk about that, yeah.
Maybe I'll go to his house.
We would like to go to his house and maybe not that idea because it might be he may have
seen the video, but maybe something else, we'll have to think about it.
Oh, I'll tell you, of course, Piers can't really come out during the day, though.
He is a vampire, so I would, who sucks the rights out of country, he's already into England
now, he's run over here, I would not go, I would go during the night if you wanted to
actually come out.
That's a good idea.
Maybe when he gets home, I don't know, when he gets home for the weekend or something,
he's not working very late at night or very early in the morning.
Yeah, well, I mean, it's well known he won't come out.
He's never been hit by sunlight.
Is that so?
Yeah.
I'm being sarcastic.
All right, we're gonna go to break.
This is a short segment.
Come back with Truth Raider and a few others, and then we're gonna get into, for folks that
haven't seen it on your website, you went to Holder's house, you name it.
How did you have the huevos to do that?
It was actually, I have to compliment my reporters, we got about 18 to 24 people that go out there
and do it, and there were three girls that went to his house, and no more than five seconds
after they knocked on Eric Holder's door, the FBI police showed up.
We're going to go to break, back it up, great job guys having that ready.
That was seamless.
We're going to come back and take a few calls, then play that, and then recap it.
But notice the FBI's there to protect him because he's a big man.
You the common slaves though, you don't get a gun, so he agrees with the Ku Klux Klan.
The commoners don't get guns, only the big master gets the guns.
Hello, I'm Alex Jones.
Myself, my family, the Infowars.com team want to relay to you and your families that we
are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front.
Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats, but we can't do that without
your help.
By getting the films, bumper stickers, and t-shirts at Infowars.com, you will wake up
people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before.
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here.
It's an Infowar.
The spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book Cancer Step Outside the Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the president could obtain this world-class healer.
Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally
occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune
cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VenusFly or order from Carnivora.com, that's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VenusFly or visit Carnivora.com.
Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
In this unpredictable world, disaster can strike anyone.
That's why an essential part of any emergency survival plan must be stove in a can.
When power goes out and gas lines are down, the portable, safe, easy-to-use stove in a
can cooks food up to four hours and boils water in as little as five minutes.
Stove in a can comes with everything you need.
The stove, fuel, even waterproof matches, all in a compact, durable, heavy-duty container.
Plus, the all-natural, non-explosive, 100% waterproof fuel source can be stored indefinitely.
Say goodbye to the hassle and danger of propane, lighter fluid, or gas.
Stock up now and protect your family with Stove in a Can, starting out at $29.99.
Special bundle offers now available with a 100% satisfaction guarantee or your money
back.
Order yours today at StoveInACan.com.
That's StoveInACan.com.
Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Yes, and riding shotgun with us from the bottom of the hour, James O'Keefe.
He, of course, is the legendary investigative journalist, a young guy as well, in the last
five, six years, has brought down Acre and exposed Planned Parenthood, gotten a bunch
of resignations and congressional investigations over NPR.
We're going to be going back to him and a few of your phone calls that have been holding,
and then we're going to get into his program.
We're going to play some audio and video clips here.
Audio for radio, video for prisonplanet.tv viewers.
Going around to Eric Holder's house, the Attorney General, saying, hey, you want our guns, will
you turn your guns in, or will you put a gun-free zone sign at your house?
And within 30 seconds, the FBI pulls up.
So they've got your tax money guarding all their houses, but you're not going to get
see.
They're going to have guns, and they're going to have armed guards and red carpets.
But you don't need to have a gun, okay, because they're government.
Some of the news up at infowars.com, Feinstein rolls out draconian attack on the Second Amendment.
That's all detailed in the well over 150 guns to be banned, because it says this gun and
all others like it, basically, it's that interpretation, it's so dangerous.
Congressman, Obama only upholds the Soviet Constitution, very powerful article that a
congressman's come out and basically made some powerful statements.
Here are the children murdered by drone attacks at the hands of Obama, showing you care less
about children.
An Iranian ambassador, only war can stop us now.
And Michael Bloomberg's Twilight Zone, key article by Kurt Nemo, women to be drafted
under Pentagon plan.
That's what all this women in the military thing's about, is they want universal service.
But the women will just be the domestic enforcers, that's their own words, the Chicago boss's
words when he was at the White House.
Missouri law will force gun owners to register with schools.
This is the new thing to shame us, as the Attorney General has said, well, he should
be ashamed.
But we're gonna take a few calls and then get to James O'Keefe's breakdown of going
to people's newspapers that publish gun owners names saying, why don't you put a sign saying
no guns?
And going to Holder's house, the Attorney General, that's coming up.
But right now, Truth Raider in Oregon, thanks for holding her on the air.
Hey, buddy, hey, buddy, go ahead.
I've been vaccinated.
I'm sick.
Oh, are you Piers Morgan?
No, I'm glad I'm not him.
I would have terminal illness if I was that guy.
Okay, hey, you've been holding a while, what's on your mind, bro?
Well, this is what's frightening.
I did a beta test, I went down to my local mall, wore a padded jacket.
I walked through, and anytime I say, wow, this is scary.
I could have had a Glock 19, a Tech 9, a Ruger, what have you, and I could have done business.
Well, you're never gonna stop people that wanna do bad things, I mean, especially with
a sheep-like population, what's your point?
I mean, what is going on here?
They want to take our guns from us, but then they leave everything open for fair game.
Everything is left open, and it's like it's a hunting season.
Everyone's-
No, no, that's what they do, and they introduce the hunting season for crazy people is the
public schools to go shoot people where they've disarmed everyone and made sure, hey, here's
where the victims are.
So, let me go back to our guest on that subject, James O'Keefe of Project Veritas, investigative
journalist, Parx Salon.
What about making the school's gun free and then advertising and hyping it?
I mean, it's like they're hoping for another mass shooting to get our guns.
Well, that's one of the things that I thought about doing with this recent Citizens Against
Stencils Violence mockumentary we made on YouTube.
I thought about going to the Sidwell School.
This is the school where David Gregory's kids go in Washington, as well as Barack Obama's
kids go.
And I just thought it was too risky because there's secret services there, and it'd just
be too risky.
They'd probably arrest me immediately, but I would have loved to go to the Sidwell School
where David Gregory's kids go and offer them to put a sign up that says this school is
gun free.
But see, that's your First Amendment right.
Maybe I should go there and do that.
And if they arrest you just to get some more news coverage, MSNBC and others said people
are attacking their kids.
No, we're not.
Their kids are protected by armed guards.
Why are they trying to block our children being protected?
Why do they tell them crouch down and wait to be killed?
I mean, we're not being aggressive to them.
They're trying to make sure we can't protect ourselves.
They're trying to make sure we're fair game.
They're assaulting us.
Well, maybe you should go to the Sidwell School and do it.
You'd have more moxie than me if you chose to do that.
I've been arrested, Alex, and I have to raise the money privately, and it's difficult for
us sometimes.
No, I've been arrested quite a few times too, but I always drop the charges because I haven't
done anything.
I mean, if I went up to the edge of the school and started and saying, I'd like to offer
or knock, knock.
Hi, I'd like to offer you this sign that you're a gun free zone.
Oh, but you've got guns.
Well, why is that?
Why do you have guns?
Do you not like children?
You want to support the death children or something like that?
Yeah, but I mean, and again, in the free country, we'd get arrested.
Well, let's talk about this clip, because some stations just joined us.
Tell folks what you did again, and then we're going to play the clip of going to the Attorney
General's house.
So we posed this group called Citizens Against Senseless Violence.
We posed as an anti-gun group, and we made a little advertising campaign to go along
with it, with white t-shirts, and we said, we want to save the children, guns kill children,
guns are bad.
And we went to the homes of politicians, journalists, and Attorney General Eric Holder, MSNBC, Star
Ledger, Westchester Journal News.
They printed the names of gun owners.
And we went to the home of Eric Holder, which is a clip you're about to play in northwest
Washington DC, and within five seconds of knocking on Eric Holder's door to put a sign
on his lawn that says this home is gun free, the FBI police showed up.
Now imagine if the public schools had a couple cops at them, or just teachers trained and
armed, it would be the same thing, but no, only he gets 24 hour guard service.
And Alex, not only does Eric Holder get FBI police protection 24 hours, journalists at
the Westchester Journal News had 24 hour armed guards protecting their homes as well.
Yeah, I saw that because the evil gun owners had been calling them and my gosh, they better
have armed guards now.
I saw that in the news.
Did that happen after you went to their houses or before?
That happened before that started happening.
There was a program on Fox, Judge Janine, she actually went to two of their homes a
few days before we did, and she caught the same thing.
So they had been there.
And so they were scared of a Fox TV host like they were gonna come kill them.
I mean, again, these people are nuts, and then they have guns protecting them.
I mean, it's just, and they always say, Israel doesn't have guns, don't bring that up, NRA's
wrong.
It's wrong to say we're armed.
They say we're discredited by bringing this up because it's what discredits them.
And they're saying, please, throw us in the briar patch, stop doing this.
They know it's effective, that's why they're telling us, this isn't effective, stop it,
stop it.
Right, well, even the Washington Post, Alex, put out a piece that was very positive about
this recent investigation.
So some people in the mainstream media appreciate the fact that we're exposing frauds.
I think it's a winning issue when you expose them to be frauds and cowards.
Well it's more than that.
When the Washington Post came out and said don't publish people's names, this has happened
over the last few decades, people always get mad.
The Washington Post doesn't wanna upset us too much.
They're telling the other liberals, we'll get them later.
Don't rile them up, because they're scared of us coming to their houses.
They're scared of us pointing out they've got armed guards, they wanna shut this down.
They don't wanna be, the journalists definitely do not want to be personally exposed.
But that's what they've been doing to us peasants, I call us peasants.
That's what they've been doing to the common people for decades, so it's time that we expose
the journalists.
Absolutely, it's time.
Let's talk to, no, let's go ahead and play this clip.
Here's the clip with the group going to Attorney General's house.
Home of Eric Holder, US Attorney General, Washington DC, here it is.
We're on camera, they say, three women, how can I help you?
Less than 30 seconds, the police, federal police.
We're in a newly formed group, the hair not home right now.
Four slam two, signs rejected two.
Why you don't want us to know that you don't have guns, cuz we know you do.
We're assuming this is a gun-free household, I think that's correct.
Thank you for the visit, I'm not gonna speak on your signs.
I appreciate what you're doing, but by the same token, I'm gonna pass on the signs.
Yeah, nobody wants to say there's no gun in their house, they're all gonna have guns,
they've all got their little commie cards.
Violence, can we sign you up?
No thanks.
Yeah, any particular reason, are you gun owners or?
I agree with you, I don't want to sign you up.
These so-called liberals, these authoritarians are so dumb, they're like, I agree with you,
every home should be gun-free, but no, I'm not taking your sign.
Police getting called on them.
A single member of the media, willing to live up to the strength of their convictions.
Now a final parting thought from our good friend Bob Braun at the Star Ledger, which
also wants to target law-abiding gun owners.
I was trying to get a nasty note from one of my most progressive friends who says, because
I wrote a column, I'm a columnist, and I wrote a column against, for sure your gun was, and
he said, you're a fool because when the right wing takes over the government, we're gonna
need guns.
So he's worried the right wing's gonna take over and then?
Yeah, and there'll be guns to fight them back.
Then I said, but they got the army, you know, they got the army and the navy and the marines
and everything else.
Right, so he's gonna be a revolutionary too, but you know.
There you go, the insiders are talking about a revolution.
This is their revolution to get our guns and take over.
Final segment with our guest straight ahead, we'll give you the website as well to go see
all the videos.
I'm Alex Jones with infowars.com, and we're streaming video at prisonplanet.tv.
Hello I'm Alex Jones, myself, my family, the infowars.com team want to relay to you and
your families that we are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front.
Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats, but we can't do that without
your help.
By getting the films, bumper stickers and t-shirts at infowars.com, you will wake up
people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before.
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here, it's an infowar, the spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e-foods direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all of the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e-foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Read the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on efoods direct.
Hempusa.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine, and probiotics
and we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder absolutely free.
Micro plant powder only at Hempusa.org.
Call 908-691-2608, that's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do
for you only at Hempusa.org.
This offer ends January 31st.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson.
Have you ever wondered why banks, stockbrokers, investment advisors won't talk about gold
IRAs?
They've been available since 1986, yet the financial industry won't recognize the value
of gold for your retirement.
Gold is outperformed paper investments, yet no word about IRAs.
If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns, call 800-686-2237.
Secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
Time and time again.
You need to come here and help us.
We need assistance, please.
Those we should be able to depend on, let us down.
Federal and state and local officials saying help is on the way, while the folks here in
Bell Harbor say show me.
Don't depend on the government to save you.
Take action now so that you're prepared for the next disaster with MyPatriotsSupply.com.
Get the best prices on storable food, non-GMO seeds, water filtration devices, home canning
equipment, survival and self-reliance books, and more at MyPatriotsSupply.com.
Call 866-229-0927.
We are hurting down here and we need help immediately.
Before it's time to survive, it's time to prepare.
MyPatriotsSupply.com.
Don't worry, this show is documented.
Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
By the way, you know, I've got to spend time trying to make money to fund the syndicated
radio show, the crew, the filmmaking, the nightly news, all of it.
And you guys have done a great job out there supporting us over the years with the products
we sell at Infowars.com.
I got approached last year by one of the, and I wasn't even a big skater, though I did
like skateboards.
I just wasn't very good at it compared to my friends.
You know, we go skate at the parking garages, all of it growing up.
But I mean, everybody knows Alien Workshop, probably the name in skateboards.
They approached us about six months ago and said, would you like to put out a custom line
of Infowars skateboards that come out at the regular price but are custom?
And I said, absolutely.
So those are now available for sale at InfowarsShop.com and they're gonna come out with more and more.
But custom Infowars, limited edition, Divide and Conquer, look at that artwork inspired
by our work.
And they're great artists of the left and right and how they control both Republicans
and Democrats.
Divide and Conquer Alien Workshop, that's just one of them and they've got a brainwashing
one.
And this is just a test, Brainwash Skate Deck, 49.95, Divide and Conquer, 49.95.
I mean, that's a super high quality skateboard, $49 and you put your wheels on it wherever
you custom have there and like.
So there you have it and there's gonna be a bunch more coming out, but those are limited
edition, available right now at InfowarsStore.com.
James O'Keefe, we gotta talk in the next few days off air when you get time and I get time.
I've been meaning to get a hold of you for years, stuff falls to the cracks.
I salute what you've done, I salute your work.
We've got a lady who wants to talk to you, Susan, real fast in California, who says you
inspired her.
Susan, real fast, you're on the air with the head of the Project Veritas.
Thank you very much, Alex and James, I met you a couple of years ago at a pro-life block.
You made a very inspiring speech telling everyone that even though we may be small in number
at the time, that everyone can make an action that causes a reaction.
And because of you, I started speaking up about the problems within Girl Scouts and
how they have a very pro-abortion agenda and-
Oh, it's total brainwashing, total brainwashing.
I would love for you to cover this because this is cookie season.
I mean, they are at the height of their selling at this very moment.
And if you would let your listeners become enlightened on how deep they go into indoctrinating-
Oh, no, no, no, type in Girl Scouts trained to fight terrorists.
And then you actually get the training, it's what are mommy and daddy doing?
In fact, were you aware of this, James, it sounds crazy, but it's really happening.
I've heard something about the Girl Scouts and abortion.
I haven't- Tell him what they're doing, Susan.
It's beyond that, just last month in December, the Girl Scouts representing its 10 million
members around the world were at the Global Youth Forum in Bali.
They actually were on the steering committee.
And they came up with a statement asking for legalization of prostitution.
Oh, my God, that's breaking news.
Do me a favor, send that to showtipsatinfowars.com.
Show tips, okay.
Yeah, show tips, and it's all about trafficking women, it's all about exterminating them once
they have babies, aborting them, just amazing.
We'll look into that, showtipsatinfowars.com.
James, thanks for all the time, we got three minutes in closing here in this segment.
What else would you like to impart to everybody out there?
Well, I wanted to reemphasize what I said before.
I believe the way to change the world is through journalism.
And the listener in California just said, I actually did do a little site, it's remarkable
that it's a small world because I was out in California about three years ago giving
a talk.
And she's right, you produce a consequence that produces a reaction.
And if you expose something that's so outrageous that forces people to react to you, and it's
that reaction that gets into the news, and then whenever they, like in this case when
Toure reacted to our gun video, I'm sure the MSNBC people were saying, Toure, don't say
anything, you're just going to give oxygen to a story.
So we have proven that citizen journalists can actually change laws, force politicians
to act.
And in the next year, we're going to triple our efforts.
You can follow us at Project Veritas, that's Project Veritas.com.
And if you want to get involved in one of these video projects, if you want to be a
videographer, if you want to be trained to go undercover, contact our website, send us
a tip, and we'll put you out in the field.
There you go, info warriors.
The fight is now, the war is now, whether it's We Are Change or Veritas, or you want
to say you're an info warrior reporter just uploading to YouTube, then we can use clips
on our show.
It doesn't matter, help out Veritas, help out info wars, get involved in We Are Change.
We're all in this together, and it is so exciting to see the powerful alternative media now
really together.
We overshadow the dinosaur media, and that's why they're panicking with the DrudgeReport.com
and WorldNetDaily and countless others, very, very exciting.
Hey, tell my producer here, James, as you leave, when is a good time for me?
A couple of windows to try to give you a call the next few days, okay?
Okay, will do.
All right, James, thank you so much, very, very exciting, ladies and gentlemen, thank
you.
Ladies and gentlemen, they're attacking us right now, okay?
So I'm not looking for any trouble, but they started the fight.
I say we stomp their butt in the info war.
We're on the march, the empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.