big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
ladies and gentlemen it is Thursday the 31st day of January 2013 I am your host
Alex Jones we're going to be here obviously live for the next three hours
and each day it just gets more insane
Larry Pratt the head of gun owners of America had met on with us in a few
weeks
he's going to give us a update on the latest legislative developments that are
taking place with the attack on the Second Amendment we've got absolutely
key news in that area
Homeland Security has advised for confronting mass murderers in their new
training seminars they say fight back with scissors
that's right now government all has bodyguards with guns and billionaires
all have bodyguards with guns and Diane Feinstein has it and people like
Bloomberg people like Michael Moore but you need to fight back against someone
with a semi-automatic with scissors so I can't make that up
we've got thousands of Green Berets signing a petition and signing an open
letter to the White House saying we will not be part of taking guns over a
thousand Green Berets signed letters supporting Second Amendment
that's all up at our news websites infowars.com and prisonplanet.com and
I'm going to cover that again next hour when Larry Pratt joins us
I'll get into some of it coming up the next segment Paul Watson's popping in
because we picked up earlier in the week on a report of a British defense
contractor thousands of pages scanned passports British social security
numbers I mean it looked like a real hack or if it was a forgery I mean it
was like you know writing a five-volume book it looked very accurate and the
companies come out and said yes it was a real hack but somebody inserted a few
emails claiming that we were getting offers to help stage a chemical attack
there in Syria to be blamed on the Syrian government well that fits in with
Israel saying if we think there's any nerve gas we're gonna start attacking
government facilities because we're worried about rebels getting them rebels
backed by the West and there's even a libertarian party blog out today saying
Israel and the Syrian opposition strange bedfellows because then as you know
Israel launched a bunch of airstrikes on facilities they claim were transferring
nerve gas to rebels I mean the last thing Assad would ever do who has no
history of aggression to outside countries would be to use or give rebels
nerve gas I mean that that's that's the pretext to attack them and then they've
said that this is all a setup this has been on going now for quite some time
23 months or so that the West has been funding al-qaeda as the leadership and
several other jihadi groups out of Saudi Arabia Qatar and a few other nations
against that country and they already of course handed Libya over to al-qaeda I
mean this is just unprecedented to have the United States NATO France right at
the head of it and now Israel openly involved trying to knock out the Assad
regime and then al-qaeda will come into command and then meanwhile they're
saying everyone will be fully groped by the TSA the TSA at the Super Bowl and
they're running checkpoints on highways and roads in every major city including
Austin now as of last week saying because of al-qaeda I mean it is just
absolute balderdash and they're now converting over from saying well it's for
al-qaeda it's for conservatives libertarians constitutionalists so we
are living in a twilight zone world Russia concerned with Israeli attack in
Syria reportedly a Russian MIG then went into some Israeli controlled areas until
warned off Syria Iran threatened consequences for Israeli strike Israel
jet blast arms shipment inside Syria that's what the Wall Street Journal just
just just goes with this as if it must be true this is a new level of brazen
bizarre onus by the ruling establishment globalist we'll be right back ladies and
gentlemen big transmission lined up introducing pro-wine all of your
filtration in one system portable on the go no more do you have two or three
filters to just reduce sodium fluoride you have a system that cuts out the
sodium fluoride and up to 95% of hydrofluorosolic acid advanced
manufacturing technology combines silver impregnated white ceramic with new
aqua medics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals all
in one filter element it is the only one that does it and out of the gates we
have it discounted at 10% off with promo code water this is the only system that
in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides herbicides chloramines
ammonia and chlorine hydrofluorosolic acid the most common form of fluoride
not covered by other fluoride filter brands and sodium hexafluorosilicate get
your pro pure with a new pro one filter today at info war store comm or by
calling 888-253-3139 the new year is a great time to take charge of your health
and wellness get serious and make a stand with supernatural silver this is a
breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver can be taken orally every day to
help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds supernatural silver is
also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water purification
it is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness go to
supernatural silver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting
chance that supernatural silver.com check out our new low prices and like us
on Facebook you prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms but if you don't
have a home security system and you're missing a critical weapon in your
arsenal for home protection when you're sleeping or away from home who's
watching out for intruders check out simply safe it's a new do-it-yourself
home security system that is completely wireless go to get simply safe comm
simply safe is independent and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if
the grid goes down you're protected it's completely customizable so you can use
it in your home business boat trailer storage unit or shed get simply safe
comm simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20
minutes so there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you move or
need to relocate you can take the system with you wherever you go you aren't
always at home but simply safe will stand guard protecting your property 24
hours a day seven days a week again that's get simply safe comm we now take
you live to the Central Texas command center in the heart of the resistance
you're listening to the Alex Jones show
ladies and gentlemen you have got it frontline seats for the open birth of a
planetary fascistic world government that uses socialism at the grassroots to
basically enslave the population like flypaper while an international global
fascist elite writes the world laws and exempts themselves from taxation and
regulation designed to impoverish and destroy middle classes worldwide the
ancient enemy of all oligarchs corrupt kings and criminal syndicates is the
independent yeoman farmer that Thomas Jefferson talked about being the key to
any free society the free middle-class independent yeoman farmer has always
been the enemy of tyranny the yeoman farmer in the last hundred and fifty
years since the acceleration of the Industrial Revolution is the middle
class is the shop owner is the business owner is the small factory owner is the
restaurant owner but still the farmer is the number one enemy that's why you've
seen programs to bankrupt and annihilate the family farm now that is incredibly
incredibly rare okay just want to lay out the battle plan of the globalist
here world government is being openly announced again as the solution to all
our problems we're going to get into that incredible Second Amendment
development news some good news some bad news some ugly news and a lot of news in
between that is all coming up today as well Larry Pratt had been on in a few
weeks head of governors of America will get an update at the start of the next
hour constitutional lawyer Ron Paul's chief legal advisor advisor to Congress
Bruce fine was gonna be on yesterday he got stuck in court on an important
matter he'll be joining us today had been on in about four months to chart
the incredibly draconian developments that we've seen just since he was last
on I guess about three months ago so that is coming up as well just bizarro
announcements by Homeland Security on the Second Amendment here's one of them
Homeland Security has advice for confronting mass murderers scissors not
firearms you can't make that up we got a link to that New York Post article up at
info wars calm and prison planet calm obviously we're also going to get in to
a story out of ABC News that when I saw it I instantly thought of Spaceballs
where they have the canned air the president of the planet's baseball and
and he's telling the media oh no there's no air shortage don't worry and then he
opens a can of air they're now selling cans of air in Beijing because the air
has never been this bad except in 1954 now again folks the jet stream of China
blows right across the Midwest and dumps in over the United States and that's why
people are sick all over the Midwest okay there's major university studies on
it I'm going to pull them up again and do a report on that soon because the
media is not picking up on this they're saying we've got to shut down basically
everybody's cars factories you name it that are totally clean in many cases
because the particulate is going off the chart from from the worst area is from
about New Mexico over to Mississippi and then right up to as far north as
Chicago that's where that main jet stream dumps in it comes into about a
thousand feet over mainland China if you look on the globe we're lined up with
China the Midwest is and then it comes in and dumps in right over right over
the Midwest and right over Texas it's just that's what's going on that's why
everybody's so sick and China is just there's no controls there I saw an
article where their biggest river was bright red the other day it was so toxic
every week a major river set on fire there's there's there's hundreds of
riots a week by the people rebelling there's suicide nets being put up at
hundreds of factories people are finding any tall building and jumping off I mean
it is just cuckoo land over there and we are competing with that
they're kicking the Chinese off all their rural area where they were happy
and providing food for themselves and forcing them into compact cities they
chain their kids to power poles and then go in and work in the factories all day
now we're not going to compete with that there's no way and they're bringing more
regulations in on us we're done that's the plan totally shut us down now all of
that and I'm gonna get to it after Paul Watson leaves us at the bottom of the
hour all of that pales in significance there's something right out of biblical
revelation right out of the Bible where you've got Russia that's described by
the ancient name and Syria described by its ancient name Syria in a war with
Israel I mean this listen the Russians according to Israeli press we're going
to get into that sent fighter jets into the Israeli border the Russians are
saying they may respond openly the biggest part of the Russian fleet is
right off the coast one ship alone 2,000 Marines this is a 23 month proxy war
with the bankers that run America NATO and now Israel Turkey's the main
staging ground with u.s. bases training al-qaeda using heavy artillery to sweep
areas to insert more al-qaeda al-qaeda is cutting Christians heads off burning
churches Assad is no angel but compared to al-qaeda he is an angel he's never
attacked outside countries but he's not part of the New World Order his dad
wasn't more of a tyrant he's been probably ten times better than his dad
the point is this is a war crime being committed by the West but we're run by
the globalist and they have put al-qaeda in Libya they have now are trying to
take over Syria and Syria is fighting back with the Russians and again the
Russians are corrupt in their own way but they are not expanding worldwide
they're not launching 30,000 drones worldwide and 30,000 domestically they
want the next 10 years they're not putting cancer viruses in their vaccines
they're paying people to have children in Russia because they openly say we
were under eugenics under the Soviets it's even in Pravda that used to be
known for lying that the New World Order is running things the communists were
financed by Western banks to reduce our population the Russians at least part of
the Russian hierarchy who's also corrupt understands the program and they're to
be taken out as well but again I'm not again Israel's upon in this this is a
master game ladies and gentlemen and here's some of the headlines Russia
concerned with Israeli attack in Syria claiming chemical weapons we told you a
year ago they try to claim they had chemical weapons that we're going to use
them and they say rebels may get chemical weapons so we have to attack
them when the rebels and this whole conflict were started by the West
remember the first six months they called them peaceful protesters blowing
up police stations I mean this is so immoral that's why they've had so many
members of CENTCOM including the head of it being fired because they're not
going along with this our government gave weapons to al-qaeda and made them
the head of security in Benghazi they're the ones that killed the ambassador and
then and and the Pentagon was told to stand down for eight hours and not send
aid that was a mile down the street they had three drones overhead well one
manned gunship two drones that was a stand down that was a that was a hit why
why the White House wanted al-qaeda to kill the ambassador he was there
reportedly transferring the missiles maybe they want to get rid of how
al-qaeda is getting 10,000 heat seekers because when the al-qaeda blows up jet
airliners folks in Europe and here and all and it's already started in the
Middle East when they start shooting down jet airliners they're gonna have TSA
on the street and when the TSA wants to search my car I'm gonna say you are part
of the terrorists that armed al-qaeda you will not search my car I want to
search you I'm not playing this game anymore
Syria Iran's written consequences for Israeli strike there's that report
Jerusalem Post Israeli jets blast arms shipment inside Syria the West is now
commandeering passenger planes flying into Syria beating up men women and
children on board u.s. Israel must withdraw from Judea and Samaria that's
another headline Israel attacks strange bedfellows on Syria LCR blog wise
Israel funding al-qaeda now Russia slams Israeli attack on Syria u.s. forces in
Jordan on alert debkah file Israel attack desperate bid to save failed
Syrian campaign yeah they want to get Iran and Syria to respond so they have a
preemie this is so incredible we I take you now to London and Paul Joseph Watson
who but with us this segment the next Paul you have been on top of this on top
in the last week saying there's gonna be a stage chemical weapon strike now it's
all happening what's happening Paul Watson
well good to be back Alex yeah there's still debate and argument about what
exactly the target of this Israeli air strike was because the Western media is
saying that it was this arms convoy that was traveling from Syria into Lebanon
for Hezbollah but the Syrians are saying that the actual target that was hit was
a weapons facility in a place called Jamraiya I'm not sure about the
pronunciation Debkah file that's basically Mossad is saying the same
thing but the two targets are far away from each other the web the supposed
weapons shipment was on the Lebanon border whereas Jamraiya is near
Damascus so it's a completely different geographical area so Israel hasn't even
admitted that they've committed any kind of air strike so far it's multiple saying
that it was a weapons facility and that it turns out that this facility is
engaged in long-range missile research so it looks like the Israelis have just
used an excuse created this lie about weapon shipments to target a facility
which was engaged in this cutting-edge research which might have been used to
target Israel at some point in the future and bottom line we have the
spectacle of 23 month attack by the West with al-qaeda and now even the LCR blog
the libertarians are saying why is Israel helping al-qaeda well it's
amazing isn't it because we had this story come out a couple of hours ago
Syria may respond to Israeli air strike says ambassador and everybody's freaking
out because they might defend themselves they might fight back so I I put the
comment out you know imagine if Syrian fighter jets attacked targets inside
Israel there'd be instant international condemnation be nuclear warm yeah I mean
Obama couldn't send the f-16s to bomb Syria quick enough cutting no they knew
come they'd nuke them yeah but Israel targets Syria complete violation of
their sovereignty and hardly anyone bats an eyelid and it's just like oh yeah
that's par for the and Syria took it and the media is like how dare you you we
bombed you you that's violent what you did I mean it's just la la land level
la la land stay there I want to get in when we come back to this report you put
out that got picked up all over the world concerning this and now admitted
hack of a British defense contractor looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves
how did we ever survive from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the
devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous
economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at e foods direct
we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New
York City wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed but I managed to get
my e foods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece it is better to
be prepared ten years too early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't
feed you heed the warnings and do what Alex has done call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three today or go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and
build your food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term storable food
on the planet call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three or e
foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct feeling like
there are too many pressures and demands on you losing sleep worrying about tests
and schoolwork even on the run because your schedule is just too busy you may
be under too much stress and it may be affecting your mind get your mental edge
back with new tropic mind power from mind regard calm new tropic mind power
is not a drug but a natural supplement its 12 powerful ingredients are natural
and non-gmo plus it's gluten free wheat free and formulated by Americans
for Americans by an NSF certified laboratory new tropic mind power is
available at mind regard calm spelled m-i-n-d-r-e-g-a-r-d.com and comes with a
100% money-back guarantee free your mind with new tropic mind power cognitive
supplement from mind regard calm mind regard clearly see tomorrow and
yesterday today oh great now I've got to go to court meet Tina now facing a
future court date I can't afford an attorney and learn how to represent
yourself in court step by step without a lawyer how online at how to win in court
calm how to win in court calm how to win in court calm was created by a 27 year
veteran attorney so you can know how to win without a lawyer now I can go to
court with confidence learn how at how to win in court calm the leader in
lawsuit self-help since 1997 hi this is Ted Anderson have you ever wondered why
banks stockbrokers investment advisors won't talk about gold IRAs they've been
available since 1986 yet the financial industry won't recognize the value of
gold for your retirement gold is outperformed paper investments yet no
word about IRAs if you would like to have gold for your retirement call 800
six eight six two two three seven don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns call
eight hundred six eight six two two three seven secure your future and call
one eight hundred six eight six two two three seven time and time again you need
to come here and help us we need assistance please those we should be
able to depend on let us down federal and state and local officials saying
help is on the way well the folks here in Bell Harbor say show me don't depend
on the government to save you take action now so that you're prepared for
the next disaster with my patriots of fly dot-com get the best prices on
storable food non-gmo seeds water filtration devices home canning
equipment survival and self-reliance books and more at my patriots apply
dot-com call eight six six two two nine zero nine two seven we are hurting down
here and we need help immediately before it's time to survive it's time to
prepare my patriots of fly dot-com my patriots of fly dot-com
all right we're back live Alex Jones here Paul Watson joining us from London
Paul you did a story what was it on Tuesday was it Monday well break that
down they got picked up by a bunch of British newspapers like the Daily Mail
they didn't do a retraction they just pulled the whole article what yesterday
when the British defense contractor that you contacted on Monday you know for
comment finally responded but to the Russian national news saying look we did
get hacked the thousands of pages of documents scans of passports that's why
we said it looked like a real hack but we pointed out could be that somebody
inserted fake stuff into the hack they're saying the emails where they're
discussing a staged chemical event which has been discussed by the news
everywhere that they were contacted by Qatar to be part of this and that they
had said no we don't want to be part of it now again sounds like something the
Russians would do hack it then add BS to it or it could be real Paul Watson
describe what was in there the plan to stage a chemical attack and then blame
it on the Syrians because that fits into everything we saw lining up this week
well I mean for months we've been tracking this plan to stage a false
humanitarian crisis the chemical weapons attack because Obama you know Francois
Holland all the NATO people have made it clear on several occasions that that is
quote their red line on direct military intervention in Syria so that's all they
need to justify it in their eyes so we were tracking it for six to eight months
before this all came out and then at the end of this last week it was a German
hacker that hacked into Britam defense which is basically a defense contractor
in their denial that these emails were real they claimed they were merely a
commercial outfit well if they've got information about their activities in
Iran and that was only commercial and that would be illegal because it's
illegal to do business in Iran they've got mercenaries in Iraq they work
directly with British Special Forces so their claim that they're only a
commercial company that advises people smacks of dishonesty is to my mind but
yeah they left it simmering for days this email communication supposedly
between the founder and the business director of this Britam defense
organization which talked about the Qataris proposing a deal which was quote
approved by Washington to basically deliver a chemical weapon to Syria that
was similar to the ones that Assad has and the implication was obviously to
blame it on the Assad government so they came out they let it simmer for days
they came out yesterday to voice of Russia because it was a big story in
Russia and said basically yes we were hacked these these all these documents
PDF files Word documents scans of passports they're all true but these
emails are false they're hoaxes and it is a potential that they are hoaxes
because the time stamps on two of the emails are the same the dates are
different but the time stamps are exactly the same which leads you to
wonder why would a hacker go to all that trouble and then leave the time stamps
the same and leave a red herring for people to later discover that it was a
hoax so whether it was the hack was not a hoax it was genuine and there's a lot
of documents in there but they're saying now that the emails were a hoax and
that's probably why the Daily Mail pulled it but as you said they should
have just issued a retraction I mean we added to our story that denial by
Britam that the emails were real but it's you know it's very interesting
Paul I mean this is this is so over-the-top I don't have words to
describe how insane it is to have the whole world including Israel ganging up
on Syria who's done nothing to to to massacre Christians and Muslim
minorities to put al-qaeda in and they've taken about a third of the
country and shoot mass rally videos where they say we blew up your towers
we're going to attack America after Syria and then the government you know
stages Benghazi and kills the ambassador and I mean it's just what's coming next
why is the government so mad dog arrogant I mean in the past they would
try to cover stuff up like this what what is going on why are they so
arrogant well because they know most people don't pay attention I mean when
they came they're trying to differentiate the terrorists like al-nusrah
the al-qaeda groups have killed us troops in Syria and the rebels like
they're different organizations when as soon as the u.s. designated al-nusrah as
a terrorist organization the 29 other Syrian rebel groups immediately came out
and pledged their allegiance to al-nusrah so they were saying yes where
with the terrorists then as the New York Times admits al-nusrah the terrorist
group coordinates all the bombings leads all the rebel groups it's the commanding
force in Syria so you can't differentiate it and say oh we need to
go into Syria to get al-qaeda in support of the rebels because the rebels are
al-qaeda they're all basically one group they've pledged allegiance to each other
all right Paul stay there do five more minutes with us I want to see where you
think this is going March the Empire's on the run Alex Jones and the GCN radio
network
millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other
illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a
revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution recent advances
in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily
to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while
powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep
staph pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology
has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions the
Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook introducing pro wine all
of your filtration in one system portable on the go no more do you have
two or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride you have a system that
cuts out the sodium fluoride and up to 95% of hydrofluorosolic acid advanced
manufacturing technology combines silver impregnated white ceramic with new
aqua medics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals all
in one filter element it is the only one that does it and out of the gates we
have a discounted at 10% off with promo code water this is the only system that
in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides herbicides chloramines
ammonia and chlorine hydrofluorosolic acid the most common form of fluoride
not covered by other fluoride filter brands and sodium hexafluorosilicate get
your pro pure with a new pro one filter today at info war store comm or by
calling 888-253-3139 looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever
survive from natural disasters like hurricane sandy in the devastating
summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our
hearts go out to those that have lost everything at e foods direct we hear
from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm
by having a supply of food on hand after hurricane sandy Danny from New York City
wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods
just in time to be able to help my sister and niece it is better to be
prepared ten years too early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't
feed you heed the warnings and do what Alex has done call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three today or go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and
build your food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term
storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four zero nine five six three
three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct
waging war on corruption it's Alex Jones coming to you live from the front lines
of the info war coming up we're gonna break down the unbelievable new attacks
on the Second Amendment another Mazzaro behavior by the kleptocrats who who
openly have introduced bills at the state and federal level that are the
main bills and in the Feinstein case where the government officials not
servants are all exempt and can have whatever guns they want but we've got a
register ours and turn them in of the ATF feels like it I mean just absolutely
incredible and it doesn't really translate well on radio because it's
visual but MSNBC has been caught again just like with Trayvon Martin and
they're getting sued where George Zimmerman in the 9-1-1 call is like okay
the guys looking around walking around by cars what's he look like looks like a
teenager we've heard the tape he's wearing a hoodie he's walking around and
they asked him well well well what color is he looks like he's black well they
edited it to yeah there's a guy walking around looks like he's black and then
went on and said looks like he's black can you believe the racism of this
cracker they now say that all the time on MSNBC cracker Southerners are trash
white people are bad and it's white people saying this Chris Matthews and
Carlos Watson and that woman yesterday said it what's her name Finn Finney
Finney yeah these crackers you know these old crackers and you even got
Jindal you know the Republican governor going yeah these old white men are the
problem I mean again you're like well wait a
minute I mean whites have intermarried totally embraced political correctness
you know agreed that we're the worst people on earth and now we're told we're
the cause of all folks it's it's racial division the system wants racial
division and so this will make white people very racist and very suspicious
because they haven't been racist or suspicious
believe me I'm white folks I know okay I grew up the supposed south okay whites
totally bought the full guilt deal even though you know young whites had
nothing to do with any of this stuff there's been all sorts of oppression
throughout history they give a victim identity to the system they give a
victim identity to to impoverish and control and manipulate quote minorities
so they're under government control while their futures being destroyed
whites are being destroyed we're all being destroyed by the New World Order
we're all having our power prices increased we're all having our payroll
taxes go up we're all having the Social Security money stolen we're all being
screwed but meanwhile CNN and MSNBC are saying cracker white people Southerners
well I'll sharp and we got to overcome the white Southerners I mean it is folks
if white people talk like this it'll be the end of the world but now they go
support gun control you're racist all right here's my guns support socialism
and death panels you're racist all right support aborting black babies you're
racist all right all right I supporters the money to kill them that's very
liberal now that's right killing black people is pro-black saying you want to
own guns is racist and you know and and the job of the hut Lego place that is
racist we gotta ban it you're like that doesn't make any sense how does a green
pig and a skeleton and I mean we actually own the toy set we even I even
have it at the office I even owned it before this came out that it's racist
and I just I look at it and can't again Hello Kitty bubble guns illegal or
arrest people you're like doesn't make sense it makes perfect sense this is the
authoritarianism where they have the moral high ground and then real racism
real real discrimination as the mega banks get 47 trillion dollars of taxpayer
money the last five years plus that's an old number and sign us on to 1.5 global
quadrillion in fake derivatives oh no no that's discriminatory having our
factories all shipped to China India and Mexico which doesn't even help those
people because it's so horrible they're living in you know dormitories where
they have forced abortions and suicide nets and hundred square feet per person
I mean it is it is insane the Chinese sky is so toxic it catches on fire
sometimes the rivers catch on fire they're having canned air we have the
canned air clip people aren't gonna believe this okay I'm gonna go back to
Paul Watson to finish up on the Syria issue but here it is China's filthy air
prompts mask rush and sale of fresh air in cans ABC News I'm not joking for the
fourth time this year a murky haze is descended over North China leaving
residents of Beijing choking on toxic smog China's air hasn't been this bad
since 1954 according to the state-run People's Daily because the winds have
kind of slowed down the prevailing winds the trade winds and above those the well
they're all prevailing winds but the the jet stream don't worry it's all coming
to the US anyways for whatever weird reason we're bound to China and we get
there of their smog the globalist smog but all there's no calls to clean that
up the globalists are using them having no environmental standards to leverage
out the West nobody can compete bankrupt everything oh I talked to Austinites
every couple days I ran into a guy last night just getting gas where he's got a
kombucha microbrew very popular I've actually heard of it well he's actually
connected one of our graphics people that's how he knew me but and he's had
to move out to Hays County because Austin would not let him would not let
him I'm gonna say that again would not let him make kombucha in Austin that
they just harassed him it's you can't build anything in Austin now unless
you're an insider globalist we're the model of this whole country just like
the Jersey coast nobody's allowed to rebuild but insiders are saying you
can't rebuild Gen 21 sell your property off ten cents on the dollar to big guys
if you want old family-owned little motels and hotels one of the most
popular destinations on the East Coast very beautiful Jersey Coast one of the
best things about you know New Jersey that people run down and talk bad about
all day Jersey Coast pretty nice you know they got shows about it making fun
of it but the point is is that you can't operate Ted Anderson moved out of
Minneapolis because of the code enforces harassing him I mean it's a radio
network and it's guys on the phone you know brokers selling gold and silver so
he moved to st. Paul they harassed him out of there I mean every time I talked
to Ted he's got some state agency in his office he says it's not just me
Minnesota's one of the worst he says it's everybody then he bought this big
house that had been up for sale for years that nobody could get near an
industrial park and they said don't worry we're gonna give you the permits
for this to be a business go ahead and move in he buys it he fights him for
four years they harassing they should basically shut him down he moves now
they're saying we're not gonna stop you can't have a business we're not gonna
let you sell it as a house or a business he was what do I do with this big giant
house you know before I had an office park they go hey do whatever you want
and actually laugh at him they want to destroy us they've been given the orders
you understand it's called agenda 21 it's in other big sociological papers
we've broken down for 15 years bankrupting us is the goal it is the
goal they don't want tourism they want nothing I was reading the other day I
was told about it a year ago by Michael's whirling that owns two stations
were on out in California MZ but then I actually saw it in the news where Noah
the Weather Service has now got guns and they go out and arrest surfers if they
get within 50 yards of a whale or a or a or a seal or anything and they're like
wait tourists are coming here to surf they're like we're arresting everybody
they just don't arrest dozens of people every day right off the you know coast
right there in the area that he's in I'm just ranting it's just a total
takeover okay I mean I'm down there at Big Bend watching illegal aliens go back
and forth all day and ride horses on both sides border patrol does nothing
they're ordered to stand down and I watched the park Rangers who most I'd
say hi to him and they would literally not talk to me I shot a video about this
one guy I said hi and he goes he was like a big huge guy he actually went
like Hulk Hogan and then I ran into other people who said man we ran into
this this guy and I describe they go yeah that's him and they go yeah he you
know we talked to him and he went so imagine hey I do it and then I'm down
there at the hot springs I'm going back to Watson right on the the Rio Grande
watching the illegals go back and forth we have video this we're finally gonna
premiere on the nightly news tonight just we've been so overwhelmed with more
hardcore news and we've got people on horseback riding back and forth broad
daylight and the border patrol is there with the park Rangers I'm sitting there
in the natural hot tub by the Rio Grande just absolutely gorgeous and I feel
somebody looking at me and I look up there's about 15 people in this big hot
tub and there's a there's a park ranger staring right at me like he wants to
kill me and I wasn't drinking we're gonna go on another hike after this we
just been on a long one like a I don't know four miles of a mountain and back
down and I'm sitting there and he's looking at me and I go why is he looking
at me I look over and there's a curves light sitting next to me and a woman in
a red bikini sitting right next to me and he's looking at me like it's mine
and I just knew what he's looking at I went you know the universal thing of my
hands like that's not mine and I said to the guys that we got to get out of here
they're about to raid all these people and they said oh no they're not it was
like a bunch of UT lawyer alumni like 40 year old guys out there and with their
girlfriends and and they're throwing a football back and forth they're having a
couple beers and there's a little bitty sound when you drive into that area
saying alcohol is not not permitted here a little bitty sound on the entrance
the run us we got to gather I'll call you're being paranoid Rob do and my dad
and others who were with us you're being paranoid and I said no get the stuff I'm
getting out of here I go they now arrest people who haven't even been drinking
I'm got no to get out of here they want to stay 15 more minutes and I didn't
get video this because I had a gut feeling we were gonna get arrested so
we're pulling out all sudden Border Patrol shoots in for the parking lot at
the hot springs there this is how crazy this country is I'm thinking oh my gosh
they do something about all the illegals you're right there coming them back and
forth across the border this romantic setting and they start putting body
armor on and then two two more park Rangers but the cop type pull up and
they're getting armor on and I walk over through a water bottle away in the trash
the recycler they go hey how's it going on what's going on and I'm okay and then
I hear him talking the guard I got my tickets ready you're gonna back me up
they're like yeah we're ready to back you up and they proceeded and again I
was on my vacation I'm usually I would have done something I just I can't handle
this anymore I'm like let's get out of here news like I'm getting the GoPro out
I mean I brought a camera we'll tape it I'm like no I just can't handle it we
got some of it I just can't handle it anymore man you can't go anywhere and by
the way there were illegals just crossing I talked to locals I said at
night hundreds come across there and get picked up by localities the Border
Patrol is obviously all paid off that's come out on record the citizens are the
target you know the government's arming al-qaeda but UT alumni guys can't have a
couple beers on the Rio Grande while felonies are being committed all around
them and they had big things of tickets rubber hand you know the plastic
handcuffs on their side and and and then we're driving out and more more Border
Patrol more guards more park rangers are pulling down the little road you know
the dead ends by the hot springs is like how did you know that I said I saw the
look in his eye man he wasn't about to give tickets the guys too scared he
wasn't about to give tickets to 15 people these guys see us as the enemy
he's not worried about the coyotes going back and forth literally 20 feet from
him I said they're gonna arrest these people
and later I ran into a woman at the lodge that night he said there were a
bunch of tickets being given out one guy was being put in handcuffs I just can't
handle it anymore man I can't even go down and just be at a national park I am
the prey I am the food I am the food and I knew I said we're food let's get out
of here I mean I can't handle it anymore I'm sorry Watson I've had John hold
finish up with Syria then I'll get into all the other news it's it's it's just
getting so bad oh I meant to play this China's filthy air prompts sales of
fresh air cans I mean I guess they got the idea from space balls let's play
that clip and go to Watson here it is planet space ball I can assure both you
and your viewers that there's absolutely no air shortage whatsoever yes of course
I've heard the same rumor myself yes thanks for calling and not reversing the
charges yeah bye oops I wanted to bleep that guys I said check it let's bleep
that we bleep that John it's a 40-second clip only various huffing out of a
Perrier air can okay there goes the clip we had to bleep part of it as I forgot
there was a cuss word in it okay there you go from space balls Paul Watson
going back to you my friend you finish up with the whole serious situation where
do you see it going where I mean they may start nuking Syria and and you know
the videos come out of them cutting Christians heads off and our media is
like the New York Times even praised the al-qaeda rebels and then the public
said boy but those are al-qaeda killing and blowing up churches and the New York
Times pulled the video I mean I guess they really want to sell us on this I
guess they think the public are total jellyfish Paul where do you see this
going well they'll end up giving those rebel commanders you know refugee status
in the United States like they did with Iraqis Iraqi terrorists after Gulf War
one that helped the United States and as he said they'll then start attacking the
United States and it'll be all forgotten that the United States created arms
funded them in the first place but there's a headline Syrian rebels steal
credit from Israel for attack now they're claiming that they hit the
weapons convoy so it looks like there could have been two separate attacks but
far as where it you know where's where's it going they've said that Assad's fall
is imminent about three times that the rebels are closing in on Damascus I've
literally heard that three or four times within the last year never happens now
it looks like it's a stalemate you know the country's completely destroyed
they've got thousands of refugees streaming out into Jordan but the
difference between Libya and Syria is that you know Libya had a 15,000 man
army Syria's got something like 150,000 ten times the amount Syria's got an air
defense system which Libya basically had no air defense system but if this
actually happened this incident today and Israel's flown a fighter jet all the
way nearly to Damascus and bombed a weapons facility then how good a Syria's
air defense is not very good if you know they can penetrate them with no
resistance whatsoever so that might be a test case for the pro bomber now to
send in the drones and for the fun to begin because obviously that was their
main concern that Syria's air defenses would be too strong and they will
actually get on the news and say how dare the Syrians not nuke themselves I
mean if the Syrians don't March all their kids out to al-qaeda and chop
their heads off their bad I mean how immoral has the West become that they're
doing this publicly Paul what do you predict coming I think as the Brookings
Institution report from March 2012 said the perfect opportunity for them would
be a massive humanitarian crisis which is already happening but I think they're
going to stage some big event they've already said they're going to do it
whether it be chemical weapons you know babies thrown out of incubators or
whatever some fake prison camp like a fake Serbian death camp that ever
existed they'll try and fake another stage humanitarian crisis and that will
be presented as the final straw and then the fun will begin incredible
incredible you heard me rant about all the stuff that's happening it's not even
the tip of the iceberg Homeland Security is officially saying everyone should
have scissors in their office or school in case there's a mass shooter that
that's been officially put out on recovering that I mean it's just they're
they're they're SWAT teaming and expelling people for Hello Kitty bubble
projectors paper guns Legos I mean it's we're going and the same thing in
England you're under the same mind control system I mean they just how much
crazier will it get I guess a lot crazier well the problem is that a lot
of people have been driven crazy by a lot of this and they can't differentiate
between fact and fiction but what's really happening is while the
Department of Homeland Security is doing that and saying protect yourself with
scissors they've just bought 7,000 fully automatic assault rifles they've bought
over 1.6 billion rounds of ammunition so they're building you know detention
camps in Georgia and places like that I saw another report just the other day
they're training for confiscating guns is down the army manual and it's like
hey giant guys in Darth Vader outfits huge armored command bases checkpoints
everywhere totally safe Hello Kitty bubble projector in the hands of an
evil five-year-old everybody run in fear I mean they're they're creating a
responsive Oh a citizen with a bubble oh I got a Darth Vader you know classic
tyranny oh I love it oh I feel safe Thank You Paul Watson editor of prison
planet calm stay with us this is Alex Jones with five good reasons you should
consider buying a solar power generator number one new climate legislation could
easily double or triple your electric bill number two our new energy czar
wants to control how much power your electric company allows you to have it's
true total government control of electricity in the name of smart grid
technology is coming number three in some areas of the country the power grid
is dangerously overloaded and now new socialist legislation is only
compounding the problem number four dangerous weather is always a threat to
local grids every year thousands of families lose their power from weather
related images number five a solar power generator provides powerful backup
insurance and peace of mind folks I really believe in the solar power
generators offered by solution from science one of my oldest sponsors you
can get more information at www.my solar backup.com that's my solar backup.com
remember the government doesn't own the Sun so go to my solar backup.com or call
1-877-327-0365 is this the year you finally get serious about your family's
drinking water if so keep listening for a special offer from big Berkey water
filters did you know that over 60% of municipal water is fluoridated Berkey
water filters distinguish themselves from many other filtration systems with
the capability to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine fluoride arsenic and
disinfection byproducts from municipal water via the black Berkey and PF line
of filters then there's affordability it only 1.7 cents per gallon Berkey water
filters purify treated and untreated water even stagnant pond water stop and
think how much money you could say by simply reducing buying bottled water
and using water filtered by your Berkey water filter no need to be constantly
replacing expensive filters with a Berkey a single set of filters can last
for five to ten years choose the best size Berkey for your needs at big
Berkey water filters calm and right now all GCM listeners get 5% off all ceramic
filter systems just call 1-877-999-BERKEY that's 877 99 BERKEY or
visit big Berkey water filters comm free shipping on every order over $50 big
Berkey water filters for the love of clean water hello this is Ty Bollinger
author of the best-selling book cancer step outside the box I want you to know
some very important information in 1985 president Ronald Reagan requested that
carnivora be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the president
could obtain this world-class healer now 27 years later carnivore capsules are
used around the world to keep people healthy now you can protect yourself and
your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds
that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell if you want to stay healthy now's your chance to literally wake up
your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in
your body call 1 866 Venus fly or order from
carnivora.com that's car ni vo ra.com that's 1 866 836 8 7 3 5 1 8 6 6 Venus
fly or visit carnivora.com protect your immune system it's the only one you've
got trouble so hard don't nobody know my trouble for God don't nobody know my
trouble so I am the piranha of Liberty gnashing my little teeth together in
anger against the globalist again I'm your host Alex Jones the websites are
infowars.com prison planet calm they're the big news sites and also we're
streaming video at prison planet TV don't forget operation sleeping giant
you can get 11 memberships your main membership and 10 more for $5.95 a month
or get the yearly membership or running a special get 5.3 months free off the
regular price when you get a year membership so you pay for 6.7 and you
get 5.3 free and we only run that in December and January so that's about to
end but I haven't been plugging it a lot so I may extend that that special a few
weeks but the other specials is in perpetuity you get a membership whether
it's monthly or yearly and it's 11 people can simultaneously log on to the
daytime radio show and see the video and all the documents adds multi dimensions
to the info is while I'm talking about stuff the crew is putting the articles
up on screen to document things you know it's radio to the next level and I've
been doing this 17 years adding the video and things for about 10 and of
course it's now being duplicated by everyone else which I think is a good
thing it's good to show people what you got show people the facts so I think
that's the greatest form of a flattery is imitation now the issue here is again
you can go to prison planet TV or info wars news.com and get your membership or
if you already have a membership get another one to support us and then
create easy to remember username passcode that's centric only to prison
planet TV you know a new passcode that you can share and then give that to
friends and family it's more like 20 or 30 memberships most people are not going
to tune in every night at 7 o'clock for the nightly news that we put a lot of
work into at many levels it's much better than even the radio show that's
why we're playing a lot of the produced pieces here and we come back from break
in that little no-man's land the first five minutes that some stations carry
some don't we're gonna change our clock soon where we don't have that and come
out at 6 after but the point is we're gonna hear Aaron Dykes's report on MSNBC
hoax gun advocates heckled Sandy Hook father and they ran this clip all over
the news MSNBC put the hoax out a bunch of other TV networks picked it up all
the Democratic Party organs picked it up saying look at these fathers you know
this poor father lost his child he said you know and then look for no reason
they laugh and heckle at him and say shall not be infringed just out of the
blue they interrupt him the father really says can any of you tell me why
we need semi-auto can you and everybody's quiet people go oh yeah a
Second Amendment you know right keep their arms shall not be infringed well
they just cut the question out and MSNBC delays their feeds about 15 seconds
we've been watching this most TV doesn't do that so they acted like the feed cut
for a minute and then ran with it and even after it came out they said oh no
we're defending it no no that's what he said just like they got caught in Trayvon
Martin editing the tape to have him go yeah it's a guy with a hoodie it's a
black guy they're like what color is the person it looks like he black again
they're being sued over that this is what they think of you this is what they
think about you I mean it I make mistakes sometimes I get up on air and
flip a number or say a name wrong and I you know hear it later and I'm like oh
no it wasn't Thomas Jefferson said that it was Benjamin Franklin but most people
don't even catch my mistakes and I make them I hear him I can't stand it but
when you're up here without teleprompters it happens imagine
consciously editing feeds sitting there watching and this is the stuff we're
catching and then meanwhile going yeah gun owners are crackers white people
saying that in Al Sharpton yeah we got to overcome the south and whites yeah
everybody owns guns as a clan and a Nazi CBS News Bob Shafer yeah we defeated the
Nazis will defeat gun owners I mean this is an open occupation force they're
obviously the enemy these are evil people ladies and gentlemen and what
they're doing is illegal
this is GCN the Genesis communications radio network if you want an American
company with American products made by Americans here is the cow Ben soap
company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years these
all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut
oils that are earth-friendly and safe see them on the web at five star soap
calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog buy the one to two months sample
package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now or save
big with a one to two year supply of soap for all your cleaning needs this is
an amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way
real soap makes you feel see them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800
340 7091 for a free catalog
waging war on corruption Alex Jones on the GCM radio network
Aaron Dykes here for info Wars calm now we've seen already how the gun grabbers
will stop at almost nothing to advance their agenda as long as they get to rain
in the Second Amendment right because the fact that individuals have rights is
very threatening to any authoritarian government whatever its stripes
political stances or colors but the latest hoax we saw on MSNBC is just
incredible they went out of their way to distort gun owners and advocates of the
Second Amendment right who were in testimony Monday with the parents of the
Sandy Hook victims and MSNBC deliberately edited testimony of Neil
Heslin the father of Jesse Lewis as he advocated restricting assault rifles
banning high-capacity clips which is fine you can understand his grief why he
would speak out on that even though I think it's a misguided position I
certainly sympathize with the families who lost children with anyone who's lost
children or family members in a tragedy but what's not okay is the way that
Martin Bashir Lawrence O'Donnell and other figures on MSNBC blogs across the
internet went with the hoax on purpose where Neil Heslin in the middle of his
testimony asked the rhetorical question who of you in this room can answer this
question why does anyone in this room need to have an assault rifle or a high
capacity clip and he waits a few seconds there's silence and he says no one can
answer that question in this room and so a number of gun rights advocates who
were there at the hearing spoke up saying that you shall not infringe on
the Second Amendment I asked there's anybody in this room that can give me
one reason or challenge this question why anybody in this room needs to have
an assault one of these assault-style weapons or military weapons or high
capacity clips
now one person can answer that question
all right and what they did was edited this part of the testimony edited out
the part where the father asked the question and just made it look like
people were interrupting this father's testimony who had just had children die
and Sandy Hook and obviously it's very sympathetic moment they were all
entitled to our own opinion and I respect their their opinions and their
thoughts but I wish they'd respect mine and give it a little bit of thought a
father's grief interrupted by the cries of a heckler that was the scene today in
Hartford Connecticut where the parents of children killed at Sandy Hook
Elementary testified before an audience that wasn't always friendly deliberately
distorted just like they deliberately out edited the audio of the Trayvon
Martin shooting to make it seem like it was racially motivated when in fact it
turned out that Zimmerman had often worked with the black community he
himself was a mixed race and really race shouldn't have been the main issue of
that certainly it's legitimate to question if his death was justified we
get that MSNBC is state-run propaganda for the Obama administration just as Fox
News was blatantly state propaganda during the George W Bush years and the
next time they roll out of president maybe they'll switch networks again or
maybe MSNBC will continue on its current track I get it what do you expect from a
pig but a grunt but what I don't understand is why they always paint
anyone who asks questions anyone who stands up for rights anyone who says
that we're being delivered hoaxes in the media to push an agenda why those people
are blamed and why they always say how dare you ask those questions or defend
those rights because of the families who have victims from this tragedy why don't
any of the parents from these tragedies whether it's 9-11 or Sandy Hook or any
of the Colorado shooting anything why don't they get mad at the establishment
using their tragedy to advance the establishment's agenda it's very clear
we know that Feinstein was pursuing the assault weapons ban before the Sandy
Hook shooting it's very clear that Rahm Emanuel said their policy that the
Obama administration's policy is to use crises don't let a good crisis go to
waste you never want a serious crisis to go to waste and what I mean by that it's
an opportunity to do things that you think you could not do but we know that
the Patriot Act was written beforehand and on the books and the ocean
administration was looking for the excuse to get it put into law we know
that the project for a new American century wanted a Pearl Harbor style
attack to advance an American Empire agenda a multi-theater war overseas we
know they have agendas they announced them they've been uncovered found by
researchers but they always say how dare the researchers question how dare you
question those in power who admittedly are just seeking more power and will use
any tragedy to find it Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers
the prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse
the globalist model is to shut down societies and starve Patriots out until
they acquiesce to the global takeover that's why we've assembled the most
vital and important preparedness items at info wars shop calm these are items
that I did research on that I personally use you've got the life straw so you can
turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go the K tor hand crank
generator to charge up key equipment during power outages are out in the
field strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by
Matthew Stein thorough safe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself
during any radiological event and crank shortwave AM FM radios everything that
we've researched and found to be the best is available at info war shop calm
and your purchase makes our info war possible we're getting prepared are you
info wars shop calm millions of people are going to get sick this winter from
colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with
supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution
recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that
can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help
improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every
day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as
stress staff pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new
technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at
several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions
the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook introducing pro 1 all of
your filtration in one system portable on the go no more do you have two or
three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride you have a system that cuts out
the sodium fluoride and up to 95% of hydrofluorosolic acid advanced
manufacturing technology combines silver impregnated white ceramic with new
aqua medics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals all
in one filter element it is the only one that does it and out of the gates we
have a discounted at 10% off with promo code water this is the only system that
in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides herbicides chloramines
ammonia and chlorine hydrofluorosolic acid the most common form of fluoride
not covered by other fluoride filter brands and sodium hexafluorosilicate get
your pro pure with a new pro 1 filter today at info war store comm or by
calling 888 2 5 3 3 1 3 9
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
ladies and gentlemen again thank you so much for joining us on this Thursday
last day of January 2013 already about to go into the second month of 2013 hard
to believe 2012 went by in the twinkling of an eye this year is moving even
faster okay coming up at the bottom of the hour the latest on Israeli strikes
inside Syria and even the libertarian party is officially asking why is Israel
now backing al-qaeda rebels why is America backing al-qaeda rebels we now
know why the head of CENTCOM has been relieved and so many other top generals
they're not going along with this they have been voicing their concerns like
retired head of Special Forces general Boykin and others and that is the good
news up at info wars dot-com over 1,000 green berets sign letter supporting
Second Amendment and on the big special forces website that were linked to where
they did this this public letter to Obama a professional soldiers calm they
actually quote me you know it says Hitler took the gun Stalin took the guns
mal took the guns this is what tyrants do we're going into tyranny and they
basically talk about how our military is now being set up to be used against us
they're having drills all over the country to acclimate the troops the
police and the citizens for occupation it's in the new army manuals that they
want to use the military against the American people in there they said this
Monday at the law enforcement conference that big sis ran that the new threat is
not al-qaeda it is the gun owner the libertarian the conservative the
returning veteran and the quote radical extremists the malicious so they're
announcing you know this whole homeland security thing it's set up for people
that don't like the new world order oh I told you that many years ago but now
this is public information let's go over some of the other Second Amendment news
is out of the New York Post when I saw this actually went and looked it up and
homeland security actually says said this homeland security has made just one
of the most ridiculous statements ever by these people homeland security has
advice for confronting mass murderers scissors is your workplace getting
shown up by a crazed gunman no problem just grab a pair of scissors and fight
back that's some of the helpful advice in a new and structural video from the
Department of Homeland Security that was posted on the agency's website just a
month after the massacre at Sandy Hook School in Connecticut yeah they had a
similar video last year that we covered where you know it said fight back
physically well how about with guns if you were caught this is a quote from the
video videos up at info Wars calm if you were caught out in the open and cannot
conceal yourself or take cover you might consider trying to overpower the shooter
with whatever means are available
says the narrator in the video which shows an office worker pulling scissors
out of the desk drawer we're gonna show you and play the audio of that video
coming up here in just a little while but again it's up at in fall Wars calm
and the New York Post has done a report on this here's some of the other
headlines we're going to Larry Pratt who just joined us the head of gun owners of
America the chairman Arizona Senate panel passes bill barring
enforcement of federal gun measures so some some good news Wyoming House
approves bills exempting state from federal gun control measures yeah the
state's getting legally let illegal aliens run around above the law how about
they just let the Constitution stay in place and actually follow their oath see
the oath means null and void stuff that's unconstitutional probably have
juries to to judge the facts as well as the law doesn't matter if the judge says
the law says this put them in jail I order you that judge is a tyrant fraud
in a black robe here's another one Super Bowl fans to face mandatory TSA pat
downs which they've got those going on in Austin now on South Lamar you're not
touching me by the way I'm done over 1,000 Green Berets mention that doctors
killed 2,450 percent more Americans than all gun related deaths combined great
article by Mike Adams from natural news calm up at prison planet calm right now
and again vast majority of gun owners would defy ban poll shows yeah new
workers are going public and I'm not turning my guns and gun shop owners are
going public they're going public people say don't go public the why they'll get
you you'll be on a list good look I'm public you're the criminals you're the
people saying George Washington's bad and the Second Amendment's bad and I
should fight off an attacker with scissors now joining us is Larry Pratt
head of gun owners of America gun owners dot o RG hadn't been on in a few weeks I
wanted to get his breakdown on the semi-auto ban the fact that it would
make the quote officials the authorities are masters not servants exempt just
including that that's a title of nobility and and and other key bills and
attacks that we're facing and what these executive orders mean he's one of the
busiest Liberty fighters somebody fighting for freedom out there and we
appreciate Larry Pratt joining us Larry give us the state of the Second
Amendment in this gun owners alert oh hi Alex it's really good to be with you
one thing I'd like to lead off with there's a an old saw among those of us
who fight to protect the Second Amendment that when guns are outlawed
only how laws will have guns well one of the examples that just popped up on the
blogs today the chat by the name of Jerome McCrory McCrory and he lives in
Ohio in the Dayton area and he's been rather prominent leading a demonstration
against the easy availability of guns at gun shows and yeah I can see what a guy's
concerned about folks like you and me having guns he's a convicted rapist
Jerome McCrory the face of the anti Second Amendment crowd I just had to
share that it just is sometimes a reality is just you can make it up right
anyway to the question of the bands at the I think it's pretty clear even from
the hearing yesterday in the Senate the the Senate doesn't have the votes to
ban neither guns nor magazines I think and it's I think it's actually more
sinister point of attack against us is to make universal the background check
that way if you can't even give to your neighbor sell to your neighbor give to
your son without going to a dealer and giving the dealer all that information
for the background check there's absolutely no way that we should be
trusting the government with that information it's the fact our
registration I went and bought a 50 Cal Barrett a few months ago and the whole
thing was in a computerized form I mean I feel most gun shops now it's
computerized in a government form you know they're getting that info I mean
you know the the next system is a background check and a registration that
you're a gun owner right there now they're legally required to destroy the
names after 24 hours and Alex if you know somebody that believes that real
estate office that I'd like to have them come over and do some business they've
been caught memory serves a few times actually keeping the names of course and
the fact is that they refuse to say that they are destroying the names they don't
I guess when I get caught in an outright lie so they just hardball the thing they
will not say well then there are times when yes they have done searches of
their data and it turns out oh yes we ran a search well how'd you do that if
you're not destroying the day if you if you are destroying the names after 24
hours so if they get a gun registry then it's all over baby if that's when they
can come the next time Rahm Emanuel has one of his crises well it's time to
collect the guns mr. and mrs. America we can't trust you anymore with your guns
and Diane Feinstein's dream would be fulfilled that if she'd had the votes
she could have gotten them all well she'd know where to go if she had the
registration system and frankly a government that'll send guns into
Mexico and get Mexicans killed hundreds of them at this point so we know of we
we're gonna trust them with our information about our guns protected by
our Second Amendment not theirs ours so yeah I think we're at a very crucial
moment and the fight Alex if I could ask people to make a call to their well
right now they're senators but also their representatives that soon enough
it's I think we've got the bands pretty well under control but where they're
going to try to rope us is on the background check that's where they're
going to make the big play if they get that they've got the whole enchilada
what about the issue of another mass shooting I mean they've already set it
up where we're bad because we own guns we are guilty of mass murder when
someone else does something wrong the collectivist Soviet-style well somebody
your neighborhood you know shot at one of the NKVD secret police show now
everyone in the neighborhood is being sent to a gulag I mean this is the new
Soviet model or we're collectivized with health care so now the government tells
you what you can eat what you can do and yes there's death panels for people
overweight and death panels for people with genetic disorders I mean you know
we know their plan what about what do we do with the next attack how do we get
back on the offensive and point out that these people have bodyguards and that
these people wanted to be exempt where they can still own guns doesn't that
fully discredit them I think that's one of very very important counter-attack
and another one is kind of like unto it we've been calling for the dismantling
of the gun-free zones particularly in schools it's been in the gun-free zone
where most of our mass murders have occurred and it kind of makes you wonder
if maybe that doesn't have something to do with it you know and so happily
representative Stockman the first day within probably the first hour to put in
a bill it's HR 35 that would do away with gun-free school zones that would
take away the magnets that have drawn these maggots who want to rack up big
body counts children nobody to protect them what we've been urging it really
instead of a time let's stay there let's hear what you're urging to get on the
offensive looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves how did we ever survive from
natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy in the devastating summer drought to the
family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to
those that have lost everything at e foods direct we hear from customers
every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm by having a supply of
food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the
grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be
able to help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too
early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the
warnings and do what Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today
or go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best
tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet
your life on e foods direct you land in Buenos Aires then our shuttle to Santa
Rosa where a nicely furnished cabin with all amenities Wi-Fi executive food and
wine and laundry service awaits after a good night's sleep your adventure begins
you're on a golden stag safari for big game but it's not Africa it's Argentina
one-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo, huger, bighorn rams, wild boar
and the biggest stag deer in South America all gold medal quality all the
action you can handle land rovers top rental guns with scopes all food
beverages hunting guides ground transportation included and more all
more affordable than you can imagine the adventure of a lifetime starts at
golden stag safaris.com the big game hunting ranch golden stag safaris.com
hempusa.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved
detoxification product order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with
vitamins minerals iodine and probiotics and we'll send you our travel size
micro plant powder absolutely free micro plant powder only at hempusa.org
call 908 691 2608 that's 908 691 2608 and see what our powder seeds and oil
can do for you only at hempusa.org this offer ends January 31st. Hi this is Ted
Anderson have you ever wondered why banks stockbrokers investment advisors
want to talk about gold IRAs they've been available since 1986 yet the
financial industry won't recognize the value of gold for your retirement gold
is outperform paper investments yet no word about IRAs if you would like to
have gold for your retirement call 800 686 2237 don't get left behind by
rising inflation and low returns call 800 686 2237 secure your future and call
1-800-686-2237 we all know that
Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration as an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years in serving
thousands of satisfied customers the Berkey guy offers amazing specials for
Berkey water filtration systems the Berkey light systems include a set of
self-sterilizing and re-cleanable black purification elements that purify water
by removing chlorine pathogenic bacteria cyst and parasites to non detectable
levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides order the
Berkey light system today complete with two black Berkey elements for only two
hundred and thirty one dollars and the Berkey guy will ship your order free of
charge with the purchase of a Berkey light the Berkey guy is also offering a
set of fluoride and arsenic filters for only $39.99 that's over 30% off the
retail price call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653 that's 1-877-886-3653 or
order online at go berkey.com that's go berkey.com today
the Genesis communications radio network proudly presents the Alex Jones show
because there's a war on for your mind the head of gun owners of America gun
owners org is the number one defender of the First Amendment out there a lot of
the great people like Ted Nugent and others and of course I count myself
amongst the defenders of it and I'm proud of that that is the pure Americana
heritage our new issue of the magazine just came in off the truck the last two
issues sold out in way before the month was over I'll tell you about this the
next segment it's the tyrants why the tyrants want your guns of the new issue
is about 80% Second Amendment key info the five minutes we've got left with
Larry Pratt you were talking about Steve Stockman the Texas congressman that you
said wait wait till he gets in Congress he's gonna go on the offense tell us
about that legislation and how we get that rammed rammed through and grab a
victory from the jaws of defeat well it took him about an hour the first day and
he had HR 35 to show for it and this is legislation that would overturn the
school's own gun bans and as we know it's every single one of our mass
murders in the last 20 years with one exception was in a legally required no
gun zone and it just kind of makes you wonder if maybe these dirt bags don't
have that figured out going in so we got to get rid of them
Stockman's right on that and we're just very grateful that somebody with his
energy and determination is willing to lead on the fight now President Obama as
you know last Sunday came out and we played the clips here and I'm sure you
saw it he said look gun owners need to listen to me a little more carefully I
support the Second Amendment I love to skeet shoot it's in the news today he's
never gone skeet shooting except for one photo op it's kind of like his club was
saying I'll never come after your handguns your rifles your shotguns your
semi-autos none of it so the incredible disdain and lying how he tries to tries
to play possum with people and we've also seen the red coat Piers Morgan say
oh I've lost the gunfight I've seen them play possum more than once I mean we
know what the bills do what do you make of this double game where they go well
you don't want your guns we've just introduced all the bills to do it
meanwhile Schumer and all of them are saying we need to lean on gun
manufacturers and retailers not to sell semi-auto I've now talked to three
separate gun dealers one of them I know personally who had the ATF come in and
say why don't you stop selling these and we'll we'll go nice with you how do we
deal with the extrajudicial attacks but that's B a what do you make of this
playing possum that is just not to be believed and the word the operative word
is playing it's not for real these guys clearly are on a crusade and when
they're doing that to gun dealers they're also doing something else and
this is why we've never agreed with the 4473 form being required we've never
agreed with the background check being required that the ATF agents are going
into we're getting multiple reports going into stores either making copies
or scarfing up at 4473 forms that everybody has to fill out when they buy
a gun at a store and whether they bring them back or not we haven't heard but
they're taking them so they can obviously make copies they want to make
sure that nothing falls through the cracks they want a registration list
and there's only one thing governments do with registration lists they don't
fight crimes with them because they're not useful as crime fighting tools but
they are useful for one thing they know where the gun owners are and you know
maybe you only bought a say an ar-15 through a dealer and you bought handguns
and shotguns privately from people you knew or at a flea market or whatever
once they know you've got one gun they don't think they're going to stop with
the one when they come to your house they're going to want to search the
whole place they'll tear it upside down because we're criminals if we own a gun
that's their mentality we must stop this drive for a universal background check
Alex that is going to be the gunfight of 2013 whether or not they can complete
their grab for every gun owners data through the instant background check for
everybody even if it's father giving a gun to a son they're saying oh that's
gotta go have an instant background check it really Larry are you getting
are you getting Intel on the same thing that I'm hearing that they're there and
we know Schumer said let's go lean on the gun dealers and make them not sell
these and that's public statements he and others have said that are are you
getting the reports I'm getting that the ATF saying why don't you not sell these
we're getting all kinds of reports the ATF seems to be in hyper activity such
as they weren't even in the most of the last four years a lot of this stuff is
now ramping up now that Obama has been elected doesn't have to ever run again
for any political office it's pedal to the metal this is going to be a tough
fight because this guy doesn't play fair he doesn't care about the
Constitution he doesn't care about federal gun laws all he wants is to make
sure that he can accomplish his socialist agenda and grabbing the guns
is a big part of any socialist agenda gun owners dot o RG you told me during
the break you can do a few more minutes I want to come back and ask you two or
three more final questions Larry Pratt coming back and then the rest of the
news we're on the March the Empire's on the run Alex Jones and the GCN radio
network if you want an American company with American products made by Americans
here is the cow Ben soap company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap
products for years these all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality
vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and safe see them on the
web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog buy the one
to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps or all your
cleaning needs this is an amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel see them on the web at five
star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog
tyranny is here the grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality it really
says that the state is God the United States is now recognized globally as one
of the most impressive police states on earth this film conclusively proves the
existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being expanded nationwide this
documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an
all-powerful shadow state police state for chronicles the sickening depth to
which our Republic has fallen prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency
dictatorship body scammers sound cameras citizen spies stage terror and cameras
on every street corner it's only the beginning of the New World Order's
hellish plan the police state isn't coming it's here secure your copy today
at info wars calm or see it online in the highest quality at prison planet
talk TV now that we have moved into the winter season there is an increased need
to support our immunity and health at Silver Lungs we are committed to meeting
your needs by providing a full selection of silver based products our most
popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our two
ounce nano silver nasal applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps just
released is our 100% natural silver gel our new silver gel is not based on
synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the
surface but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin
nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin
while delivering the silver more effectively visit www.silverlungs.com
and click on our store page to find what silver based products are best for you
that's www.silverlungs.com I have sworn upon the altar of God eternal
hostility against every form of tyranny over the mind of man Thomas Jefferson
it's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network
Monday through Friday from 11 a.m. to 2 p.m. central time we are here live I come
back Sundays 4 to 6 p.m. with a live Sunday transmission because so much news
always happens over the weekend that broadcast has become incredibly popular
and is on close to 100 a.m. and FM stations and many of the affiliates we've
gotten now our stations that pick up the Sunday and get great response great
ratings and then they move us to nighttime rebroadcast and almost every
station then segues us to live during the day well over a hundred and fifty
a.m. and FM affiliates right now very very exciting and we're very very
blessed and thankful for all the listeners the a.m. and FM affiliates out
there and our sponsors now speaking of people were thankful for I've read that
now the NRA had a quarter million new members in the first month of this year
well part of December into January and that now it's over three hundred and
fifty thousand new members that's great okay but but the NRA was founded by the
federal government and the NRA helped pass the 68 gun control act and I love
Charlton Hessen interviewed him several times he was even manipulated into
support of a 68 gun control act that's why he came out that's why he came out
so so strong for the Second Amendment later because he felt guilty about that
and he talked about that gun owners of America's never sold out never made
mistakes never back down in there I don't know 30-something years of history
they're the second biggest gun group they're the group we don't need to hear
about NRA as being the only group that represents gun owners and and and and
you know is a default we need to hear about gun owners dot o RG and Larry I
know you've gotten a lot of members I know you didn't come on for this today
but we wouldn't probably have a Second Amendment if it wasn't for your
organization and your members so many times it's you guys that actually get
the job done and you forced the NRA to get more hardcore again and I've got to
say the NRA has gotten better you don't like to talk about the NRA can you
briefly talk about the NRA talk about how many new members you've gotten and
the history of this and where we are right now that I've got a few other
questions for you well we've had probably I would say could be a 20%
increase in our membership and there's the easiest way to understand the
difference between the two groups is and you alluded to it the NRA was formed by
Civil War veterans from the Union Army who were distressed about how poorly the
Union recruits shot many of them have been Irish immigrants and probably
didn't even know which end of a gun was which when they got drafted and so the
NRA was set up to make rifle awareness and practice more commonplace so that if
there were another war or when there was that the United States could draw upon a
better trained pool of men so they were set up to help the government about a
hundred years later we were organized gun owners of America to oppose the
government to oppose the gun control that was beginning to be a regular topic
of discussion in Washington and after the 68 gun control act and you alluded
to the fact that the NRA really hadn't been very effective in opposing that
that was kind of it our founder a former California state senator decided we
needed a group that was going to oppose the government and so those those two
different founding motives really kind of carried through even to today well
time flies so how long has gun owners been around when was it founded we're in
our 35th 36 year now yeah we're we're really delighted to see the way the
growth has come in part I guess well for one thing a lot of your listeners have
joined that's been a over the years that's been kind of noticeable somebody
who say oh you must have done Alex Jones today the numbers spiked again tonight
when people go online and then Piers Morgan bless his British heart did a
little it is fair share to increase our membership and we're very grateful to
Piers Morgan I think I'm not quite grateful enough to form a fan club but I
do have to acknowledge that even though he didn't intend it it has I think
frankly not only did he help our membership and the NRA's membership but
I think he provided what we may look back and say that was a pivotal moment
when he started lecturing yours truly about how the United States ought to
operate with that bloody supercilious British accent of his that just kind of
fills most Americans right up to the gag point it certainly does well gun owners
dot o RG people need to go there and join or at least sign up for the free
email alerts that are absolutely vital and again I have seen you for years I
tried to get you to talk about the history of the NRA you finally went out
of both barrels I don't know about six years ago and then they really have
reformed themselves to a great extent but I've got to say I've studied
history here gun owners of America without you we would have lost and I
know you don't like to toot your horn you're a very you know restrained calm
guy but Larry Pratt be honest would we have lost most of these big battles if
it wasn't for the members of gun owners of America supporting your your system
because I mean I mean you guys are I mean you guys are the soldiers that have
kicked the New World Order's but I mean I got a I got to tell you that's why I
support you and and and you know sit here and drive for people to sign up
with you guys because if we didn't have you I think we would have lost am I am I
incorrect I think our most successful lobbying accomplishment is when we can
get the NRA to move in our direction and now they are opposing the expansion of
the background check to private sales the back with the very background check
that was their idea to begin with so that's that's right me that's progress
that's right it's not where it ought to be but as long as we see forward
movement it means that over in the Congress it's gonna make it a lot
tougher because they're not going to be able to say as easily well the NRA
supports those piece of gun control so what's your problem well I mean I mean
I've been following this the reason I got on air was because they were had
bills to ban people under 18 being able to even shoot guns it was gonna ban
shooting sports in Texas and then I I mean so many draconian shut down gun
shows I got on the air I mean I had a hunger and went and took RTF and all of
it because I wanted to defend the Second Amendment not because I even am obsessed
with guns more obsessed with you know hiking and stuff than I am guns or
fishing it's that I understand how important it is historically and so
that's why I followed the NRA standing there or even supporting stuff at the
Texas level in the mid 90s when you guys were there fighting tooth and nail with
with you know ragtag money so that's why I'm just gushing over you because I can
authoritatively say we would have lost most of these battles if it wasn't for
Larry Pratt and his leadership and what you guys have done so I I salute you in
closing I appreciate that the gun free school zone was something supported by
the NRA we opposed it now I think they've moved substantially not entirely
but substantially to oppose that as well as you know our objective is to make it
so a teacher a janitor anybody with a concealed carry permit could carry in a
school they're not going to be identified with a uniform so a dirtbag
comes in and tries to kill a lot of kids they're going to find out that they
don't even know where the next gun is going to be coming from because there
might be two or three in a school and they're all going to be pointed at the
dirtbag I remember many years ago they had concealed carry had just gone in and
I was listening to Dallas radio and a guy that had a bunch of carjackings it
was as violent as Chicago some years more violent and the carjacker on
Central Expressway was stop-and-go traffic he he jumped out ramped the
ladies sports cars have been a fancy car and and and and told her get out he was
going to steal the car and he had a gun and a guy stopped behind him got out and
pumped three rounds into him the guy fell over dead and that was like two or
three days after concealed carry officially went in so there's an example
right there it people say oh you'll never have your gun ready when the
attack comes concealed carry is about the criminals don't know where it is and
it's I bet that was the point where carjackings took a nose dive in Dallas
oh yeah they went did they started dropping massively in fact they're unheard of now
the criminals get the message pretty fast that they're working environment
just got a lot more dangerous that's the message we're trying to send to school
mass murderers you're working we know you might want to commit suicide at the
end but we're going to keep you to one or two shots how does that suit you
exactly like you're not going to be able to kill 25 27 people how about you shoot
one or two then we kill you that's exactly right and that I think is a time
there's an idea is time hopefully has come and I'm just really excited that
Steve Stockman did exactly what I hoped he would do he's taken leadership by the
way there's another congressman Massey from Kentucky it seems to be pretty much
of one mind with Stockman he's got a I think a similar identical bill in so
we've got more than one this thing has its own momentum already but what needs
to be done now if your member your listeners would please call their member
of Congress and urge them to get on congressman Stockman's bill HR 35 that's
the next step in building momentum to get this past the leadership of the
Congress that never wants to do anything controversial and guns are always viewed
as controversial even though that's what gets Republicans elected that dummies so
get on the horn please call those members of Congress tell them to
cosponsor HR 35 absolutely all right Larry Pratt final point here when do we
really get on the offensive because you're hardcore in defending the Second
Amendment but look I know the law of interview hundreds conservatively
constitutional lawyers I've studied it quite a bit I know what racketeering is
I know what torturous interference is I know what color of law is I know what
harassment is if I tried to just verbally get people to pressure a bank
to say get rid of all of their customers that are gun owners or if I tried to put
pressure on a sporting goods store to not sell a particular product and I did
things and said things and and and and talked about trying to withhold money
from them and lobbying against them that would be torturous interference when you
have the mob boss of Chicago we're on Chicago right now talking to him
Rahm Emanuel and you've got the mob boss Bloomberg and you've got the velo groza
the mob boss of LA all these guys and the mob bosses of San Francisco saying
disarm the American people take the guns while they've got bodyguards lean on the
banks and banks are saying we don't want gun manufacturers we don't want gun
dealers Time Warner all their violent movies they're out there saying that you
know we won't take gun advertising on any of our cable systems I mean they're
really trying like not like the Nazis first embargo Jews and others that's how
the tyranny starts not letting them have businesses or harassing them I mean this
is this is criminal things that we can do to fight back and we've already seen
a spate of bills go into a number of legislators around the country
nullifying one and another and sometimes many anti-constitutional federal actions
and some actually say that they'll arrest a federal official who's trying
to enforce an unconstitutional measure yeah what we need then is to have a
state or even a county in where a sheriff is willing to take them on say
okay in this bank we love firearms manufacturers and we'll be happy
assuming assuming you've got a good balance statement to make you alone we'll
be happy to do business with you we'd rather you not be with Bank of
America just like Christians put the little the little fish on their company
I think people need to start advertising their pro bill of rights period pro bill
of rights would have a certified group meaning you support them all and and and
have a little symbol of the gun on there I think it's saying welcome America I
mean America was born out of self-defense now I want to play you a
short clip and then let you go Homeland Security has advisors running around
putting out videos saying don't have guns have scissors in a new training
video they're advising people in in in in not in federal buildings they have
guns but other office buildings and things to have scissors to fight someone
that comes to kill them with a gun let's play a clip of that thank you from the
view of the shooter quickly choose the best option if you are caught out in the
open and cannot conceal yourself or take cover you might consider trying to
overpower the shooter with whatever means are available show scissors to
protect your hiding place lock the door if you can okay block but let's stop
right there let's block the door and then the person comes knowing they're
all hiding and shoots them in a fetal position why not concealed carry holders
statistically have dropped crime 49% in the last 20 years FBI numbers so we
suggest you have a company shooting club to ensure that on the off chance one in
10 million that someone goes crazy others are there to equalize their bad
activity I mean that's what they should be saying correct yes and when they
encourage many people in the work excuse me the workplace to be armed they're
really making it so that the person that might have quote unquote gone crazy will
just probably be able to restrain himself because he'll realize that that
kind of crazy isn't going to go anywhere absolutely and if you look at the mo of
these guys they love the helplessness of little kids and knowing no one can stop
them and on record a lot of times they urinate on themselves when the police
get there and kill themselves or wait to be killed I mean these are it's the same
they're always the last four or five guys were all devil worshippers in a row
I mean why are we profiling devil worshippers devil worshippers who
overdid video games and I did say overdid I didn't say use them at all but
overdid video games it's just like you can overdo booze or food or anything
else and and so those are common elements in these attackers and I think
we better come to grips with that make sure our kids and our grandchildren or
if they got some of these video games that there may be an hour or two a week
rather than three or four a day sure what about suing what about suing Rahm
Emanuel and Bloomberg they're always suing gun makers and gun manufacturers
and publishing our names what about what about suing them for torturous
interference and I believe it's racketeering I mean I mean when they get
together as cities to try to overthrow our Bill of Rights and Constitution and
tell us we're bad and tell us they're gonna lean on gun dealers until they
stop selling guns I mean that is a gangster tactic well and one response
can certainly be what Texas has already done and it's told firearms manufacturers
hey it liked up in New York and in Connecticut the environment politically
they're pretty nasty for you y'all come down here yeah why doesn't Remington
leave Connecticut and come right down here Larry give out the number for folks
that don't have computers so they can call and sign up tell them how much it
is to support the tip of the spear in the defense of the Republic well for 20
bucks you can do what Alex is saying folks call triple 8 double 8 6 guns
that's 8 8 8 8 8 6 g-u-n-s and then for everybody else it's gun owners org and
what is Ron Paul say about you the only no compromise second amendment lobby
Larry Pratt thanks for the time we've got you back on the nightly news Monday
have a great weekend coming up you too my friend thank you very much Wow
amazing guy he's so polite tell him bye for me all right folks that is an
amazing individual right there I've been in the fight for 20 years I can tell you
I've been there a hundred times or more without that guy you would not have most
of your guns right now they've already taken them all in Australia but bolt
action single shot they're now trying to ban them it's the same thing they take
the semi-auto they register everything else then they take it all we'll be back
if you've ever wanted one of our best-selling generators but we're
waiting for an offer so crazy you couldn't refuse then you're not gonna
want to miss this exciting message here's why our solar generators provide
life-saving electrical power and unlike gas generators solar generators run
quietly emit no fumes and produce electricity from the Sun so when the
lights go out you'll always have the power you need now here's the best part
every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as
new we put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily
at the end of each year we call them scratch and dead units but they're
really just like new each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special
bonuses you just won't believe don't wait they go fast go to scratch and
dense solar.com that's scratch and dense solar.com for the craziest offer we've
ever made go to scratch and dense solar.com that scratch and dense solar.com
hey there Frank Bates here have you heard about the weird device that could
wipe out 280 million Americans this is really scary stuff defense experts warn
that this odd device poses the gravest threat we've ever known in fact just a
few weeks ago former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed
piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat I can't believe
that more people aren't talking about this it may be because the liberals and
the government are trying to cover it up that's why my friend just created a free
video at weird device.com that exposes this threat and blows the doors off the
conspiracy go watch the shocking video at weird device.com right now to discover
exactly what it is plus discover the number one way you and your family can
survive this deadly attack I'm not sure how long this video be online so go to
weird device.com before it's gone forever again that's weird device.com
we travel so much and having a fake TV gives added peace of mind burglars look
for houses that appear to be easy targets but fake TV can fool even
professional burglars into thinking someone is home watching television as a
recent widow living alone it gives me great peace of mind to set my fake TV
near a window and know that passing motorists and pedestrians will think
someone is home watching TV when I'm actually away from home fake TV easily plugs into
any outlet just like a light on a timer and they're so easy to use you just plug
them in and they're ready to go plus they're so affordable that we have one
upstairs and downstairs fake TV is only $34.95 order your fake TV by calling
877-5FAKETV or go to faketv.com that's 877-532-5388 or
faketv.com fake TV the burglar deterrent
Oh man what an important interview we just did with Larry Pratt speaking of
supporting people our local AM and FM affiliates are the reason we're reaching
millions and millions and millions more people a week now it's much bigger than
the internet much bigger than YouTube much bigger than prison planet TV it is
where we reach the big massive audiences I just got the numbers on 590 a.m. and
and they're airing of our Sunday show it's in fact I had him I was gonna show
them it's not with the instant people meters it's not only number one in talk
radio it's number one period by huge margins I mean just just just massive
and that's what's happening on stations all over the country little stations are
putting us on and within six months to a year sing double tripling
quadrupling of ratings thank God they're getting rid of the old diaries that
people just lazily figure you know fill out and they're going to the instant
meters where people you know subscribe and sign up and they put a machine in
your car to track what you're listening to they've got other ones that actually
can dial into what you're listening to because every receiver actually
broadcast at a micro level but those are intrusive so those aren't really being
deployed but I mean it shows that truth is popular so let me just say this
support our local AM and FM thank them for the show spread the word about the
broadcast if you're a local business sponsor them so that we can have people
on like Larry Pratt to support them to support our liberties wars take money
and it's also important to support info wars calm to go there and get the
propure water filtration a 10% off of promo code water to get the new film
strategic relocation breaking down the safest areas in the United States on a
region by region basis and the book it's important to subscribe to the magazine
you can buy them in bulk or get a yearly subscription info war store calm and
here is the new magazine it's got the 50 states forming a gun a handgun and it
says why the tyrants want your guns our last two issues sold out very very
quickly and so I want to encourage everybody to go and get the new
February issue of info wars magazine today get it and it is a big color 60
page incredible glossy magazine that is a info bomb against the globalist and
hand these out everywhere you can buy them in 10 up to 100 at cost or get the
subscription and get 12 delivered to your door King Obama 23 executive orders
to restrict firearms ownership breaks down how they're doing it the attack
plan how to defeat them every different angle of this covered the 1% mass
killing breaks all that down more guns less crime all the statistics big color
graphs what a world-class graphics crew I've got with these articles it's all in
here ladies and gentlemen the big poster in the middle is come and take it with
the ak-47 with the Second Amendment inside of it with the Texas-style come
and take it revolutionary flag it's the variant of our best-selling t-shirt
great to hang up on your wall at home or at the office or to hang up in public I
mean this is a big color pamphlet like the founders had they just had black and
white to wake people up and believe me in the age of digital stuff folks really
pay attention to print as everybody gets out of print we go into print it's been
wildly successful infowarsstore.com and sign up at infowars.com forward slash
newsletter as five days after the magazine comes out that'll be next
Wednesday we will send everybody that signs up for the free newsletter the
free eversion digital copy of this where you can flip the pages click on the
links everything show the new magazine look at this big pharma it's got the art
of counterthink in it you're breaking down the disarmament just just just
breaking it all down it's so incredible and I'm just so honored to be working
with such an amazing team everybody here at the infowars operation couldn't do
it without them get the new infowars why the tyrants want your guns magazine
while they're available
you are listening to GCN visit GCN live.com today the new year is a great time
to take charge of your health and wellness get serious and make a stand
with supernatural silver this is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver
supernatural silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses
infections yeast and molds supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound
care and is highly effective for water purification it is the number one choice
for thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect
choice for your emergency preparedness go to supernatural silver calm today and
give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance that's supernatural
silver calm check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook waging war on
corruption Alex Jones on the GCM radio network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
all right I've got to get into the economy and I'm gonna do that about 40
after after constitutional lawyer Bruce fine comes up and joins us for part of
three segments two segments and part of the next segment man I tell you it's
just looking at all the good things that are happening it is booing to my heart
and soul to know people are fighting back but at the same time the corruption
is so ridiculously over-the-top that I mean it's just cuckoo land things have
things have entered absolute total hell male complete cuckoo land and I know you
know that and it's because America and the rest of the Western world because of
TV and the culture slowly incrementally getting more and more out of control has
taught people how to not care how to not be involved and how to feel powerless to
where it's not even they feel powerless you know the zombie like jellyfish
everybody talks about you're either awake or you're not it's that they don't
even know they're jellyfish they don't even know they're spectators they don't
even understand what that means to go through life and never really even be
conscious and I've got to be honest with you in the last few months I've been
really wound up as you can notice and it's taken a toll on me mentally because
I can't turn my brain off I I've gotten to the point where all I think about is
this because you come to the realization of the global is saying humanity's
obsolete and they made the decision to bring in robotics to replace human labor
and drones or replace the military and they say well we've got to have an arms
race somebody else will get it but you realize bad guys are running our
political system and that they've just decided the general public's obsolete
and not just a cheap human resource as we've always been to the establishment
but now garbage that has to be taken out and that's really my message to everybody
is that really corrupt elites are in dominant control and there's always been
different facets of society there's always been a different veins of society
the good the bad the ugly the people that don't care the people that do care
the people that are mean well but are misguided the truly evil the
opportunist but now it's just such a cold-blooded corporate global system
where mega corporations tie into government and use government
regulation to shut down their competition government regulation to
conduit banker bailout and corporate welfare to themselves and then they
sick the government on corporations and companies that don't cheat to where you
can't compete with it because it's a fraud you can't compete with suicide
nets around the factories in China that have tax incentives 22 billion dollars
in taxpayer money to ship General Motors to China I mean it was hard to kill the
free market in America it was hard to kill jobs it was it was hard to kill five
percent of the population that had half the world's wealth I mean we were
amazing but now they've got us where I was reading Wall Street Journal
yesterday that you guys pull this out of yesterday's stack if you have a chance
the financial stack where it said that we're set to have double the debt every
year that we have GDP I mean that is just that's like making $50,000 a year
and you've got credit card bills every year of $100,000 I mean and that's where
they want to take us that's where the collectivists want to take us they they
brag about it it's agenda 21 it's the different sociologists that have you
know that are popular that say bankrupt things to bring in socialism this is
their plan and so I wanted to get a constitutional lawyer when I come to him
in the next segment here would have gone to him now but some stations don't carry
this segment that we're preparing to move the clock back to six after not
eight after and have a news segment produced very soon that we're gonna air
for three minutes and so we'll just go directly to our guests but that's an
exciting thing I'm gonna announce later we also have the new $100,000 prize we
got three months to do it go read the rules info wars.com forward slash
contest who is the next great documentary filmmaker they'll find out
at info wars.com forward slash contest you prepare by purchasing gold food and
firearms but if you don't have a home security system and you're missing a
critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when you're sleeping or away
from home who's watching out for intruders check out simply safe it's a
new do-it-yourself home security system that is completely wireless go to get
simply safe calm simply safe is independent and off the grid it runs on
battery power so even if the grid goes down you're protected it's completely
customizable so you can use it in your home business boat trailer storage unit
or shed get simply safe calm simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install
yourself in under 20 minutes so there's no need to let a stranger into your home
if you move or need to relocate you can take the system with you wherever you go
you aren't always at home but simply safe will stand guard protecting your
property 24 hours a day seven days a week again that's get simply safe calm
looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural
disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family
hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that
have lost everything at e foods direct we hear from customers every day that
are fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand
after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the grocery
stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to
help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too early than one
day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what
Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or
go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best
tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet
your life on e foods direct millions of people are going to get sick this winter
from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with
supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution
recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that
can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help
improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every
day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as
strep staph pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new
technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at
several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions
the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook crashing through the lies
and disinformation it's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network
coming up at 40 after I'm gonna go through a bunch of news concerning the
economy very very serious very very serious developments they're set to have
the national debt be double double the G GDP just just absolute financial rack
and room we're gonna be breaking that down because exposing it may may have
the political system reverse course we've also got unprecedented attacks by
Israel inside Syria while the West is funding the rebels in just unbelievable
information ATF's Milwaukee sting operation marred by mistakes and
failures we're gonna be looking at some of that but for the next 40 minutes
we're joined by constitutional lawyer Bruce fine and he was the main policy
adviser obviously to Ron Paul during his presidential run as as weld and Bruce
fine was associate deputy attorney general and general counsel to the
Federal Communications Commission under President Ronald Reagan he served as
research director for Republicans on the joint congressional committee on covert
arms sales to Iran and on the American Bar Association's committee on
presidential signing statements which we have some news on and also his recess
appointments and he's a constitutional lawyer again he has been a visiting
fellow for the constitutional studies at the Heritage Foundation an adjunct
scholar the American Enterprise Institute mr. fine is the founding
member of Bruce fine and associates Inc a law corporation is the principal of
public advocacy organization the Lynchfield group he is the author of
constitutional peril the life-and-death struggle for a constitutional democracy
and American Empire before the fall which I've read is an excellent book mr.
fine presently serves a senior policy adviser again to the Ron Paul 2012
presidential campaign that was the latest on his bio and he's advised
Congress generally as constitutional scholar obviously the guns up front
constitutionally I want you to get your take on the whole waterfront on this but
they've now got state bills and the main Feinstein bill that says basically I
call a violation of the Constitution because it's titles of nobility where
where the all the government bureaucrats and the police are given immunity from
having their semi-autos registered and then taken under the New York model but
but then everybody else has to turn their guns in or can't buy these guns or
can't transfer these guns you're the constitutional lawyer so to quantify
just my crude understanding where am I correct in the Constitution Bill of
Rights because I know there's some sections in there I want to make sure
I'm right on these I mean that's like them saying you know blacks are
two-thirds humans so they don't have rights again and this is the fundamental
deal when you know you're in North Korea where they have a hereditary
dictatorship it's royalty when the royalty is exempt the government is
exempt is that not royalty constitutional lawyer Bruce fine and
what do we do I mean you would think that would discredit Diane Feinstein
immediately when she says well Congress will be exempt but they're already
exempt on Obamacare they're already exempt on insider trading I mean how
have we gotten to this are they only missing the gold crowns and how do we
redress this when the the Congress is all there at the trough where's fine
that's quite an introduction let's begin by I think articulating the fundamental
issue that we confront and I guess it confronts all the nations that emerge
from a state of nature and it goes back to what is the final end of the state
and our founding fathers believed that the final end of the state was to make
men and women free to develop their faculties and to seek their fulfillment
in their unique ways and that the exception to Liberty was a government
intrusion but that required passing a very high threshold of need but the
final end of the state was not to make government big it was not to go abroad
in search of monsters to destroy it was not even necessarily to have an
unemployment rate that was low or GNP that was high but Liberty was the final
end of the state for the individuals to choose to develop their faculties and
what you've described is really an inversion of that understanding at
present because now the presumption is government should be permitted to
regulate anything unless it would reduce you to complete serfdom like you know
citizens under Nazi Germany which is I say a total perversion of our
understanding of what we are as a nation and how the Constitution is intended to
operate now with regard specifically to the Second Amendment right to keep and
bear arms the issues vary depending upon what the statutes say but to give some
beef background the United States Supreme Court has held that both the
federal and the state governments are limited by regulating guns to permitting
those that are in common usage and and otherwise were relevant to performing in
the militia at the time of the founding it hasn't other than these two major
cases saying that there's an individual right to gun ownership and not
articulating all the scope of the regulations permitted this largely in
the aftermath it's gone down to lower courts to decide whether or not
regulations for example forbidding any gun to be used in public or disclosed in
public the courts have come out in different ways I think if we want to
try to break them down Alex in terms of the constitutional issues one is a due
process and fair warning are the arms AK for assault rifles or whatever are they
described with sufficient particularity that somebody would know whether they're
in or outside the box that's been a huge problem because it's not like doing
Euclidean geometry and describing what is a so-called assault weapon and say
that's you have a due process right to know what's what's being forbidden or
not a second issue so they call it just compensation issue if you take handguns
other firearms that are in common usage and suddenly say they can no longer be
used have you taken someone's property without just compensation do you have to
pay fair market value all the inventory that stranded in gun owners or dealers
are taking a weapon that can be used now and then it's made illegal it's become
worthless or its values been substantially depreciated it's another
one then the basic right and insofar as their absolute prohibitions the question
is whether or not the weapon the firearms being banned are and have been
in common usage in the United States and that can vary of course from firearm to
firearm so in the areas that I think that will be confronting in the
aftermath of the Newtown killings in the burst of legislation certainly in a
handful of states New York Maryland seems clear to follow California is
always in that line for some kind of avant-garde prohibition on liberty and
at the federal level it's it's still uncertain whether there will be some and
the extent of any federal legislation but I want to go back to the basic point
Alex and that's our understanding of where we are as a nation because the
other items that you enumerated for discussion whether it's ATF invasions
and the going abroad and having our military involved now with predator
drones in Mali and in Niger and Burkina Faso places people can't even understand
all of these are symptoms of the inversion of who we are as a nation from
one where the final end and goal of the state is liberty to one where the final
end and goal of the state is bigger government attempting to control and
dominate everything and I want to go to that big question because humans live
75 years on average basically the Bible says they live that long 3,000 years ago
the Old Testament said that's how long you're given 75 that's still the average
today it's amazing on average worldwide we know humans act the same do the same
thing over and over again the founders knew that they tried to tie down the
tyranny and create checks and balances but I want to get into the fact that
there's this race to tyranny and why empires always follow this exact paradigm
that you've written about with such gravitas but you know I your latest book
and and then how to stop it by understanding it or are we still going to
be hoisted on our own petard you know reliving this Groundhog Day nightmare but
but I'm asking you as constitutional lawyer I know you spoke to it some
obviously how does Congress exempt itself from everything it puts us under
isn't that grounds for impeachment of all of the scallywags that have gone
along with us impeachment is for high crimes and misdemeanors and you're
absolutely accurate that Alex that at the founding it was thought
inconceivable that that members would be exempt from the rules that apply to
everyone else indeed one of their sense of assurance that the system would
operate with the proper checks was the idea that the members would invariably
at some time returned to the general citizenry and be subject to the same laws
they had passed and they didn't conceive of what we know today are professional
politicians who remain forever in office and therefore are never subject to their
own laws that they pass and that's a breakdown a important law should not be
the ultimate sin should we make that into a bigger deal you don't even hear
this discussed yes I I admit that that is something that could be considered as
a constitutional amendment as I say the founding fathers couldn't even conceived
of a professional politician I mean George Washington left very clean after
two terms and you had to yank him to to stay more than one term and if you look
at the average longevity of the initial member of Congress of the Senate it was
very short let me ask you that historically as you are historian not
just constitutional lawyer from your research what what made our founders
different they were the only revolutionaries to ever take over and
not become tyrants everybody else does I mean why were we blessed with people
this good and now they're demonized all over the news like the scum of the earth
one is that I think the political culture was far different than at
present and ears of the irony if you will Alex maybe irony is the wrong word
maybe paradox is better that we had in some sense a much higher political
culture in 1776 1787 that understood that politics wasn't a football game
where you had the red team and the blue team and you hope one team lost and one
team won and everything was fixated on just remaining in power they actually
thought of politics as the art of making everyone win and although there could be
differences the the unity of values would keep the country afloat they
wanted to build a powerful wonderful society correct we were Liberty was the
North Star not big government and empires and part of that too however
Alex was because our founding generation was born knowing what tyranny felt like
because they were the subjects of tyranny they were the ones who
confronted George the third and the tyrannical acts no taxation without
representation where the Lords were exempt from everything they were under
that that hit that hypocrisy come back and give us that history less than I
want to get into your fights currently the recess appointments some of the
things that are happening where this Imperial Empire is going Bruce fine top
constitutional lawyer is our guest we'll talk about the state's rebellion against
the tyranny we're seeing as well and his new book is excellent American Empire
before the fall I must read I'm Alex Jones
introducing pro 1 all of your filtration in one system portable on the go no more
do you have two or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride you have a system
that cuts out the sodium fluoride and up to 95% of hydrofluorosolic acid advanced
manufacturing technology combines silver impregnated white ceramic with new
aqua medics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals all
in one filter element it is the only one that does it and out of the gates we
have it discounted at 10% off with promo code water this is the only system that
in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides herbicides chloramines
ammonia and chlorine hydrofluorosolic acid the most common form of fluoride
not covered by other fluoride filter brands and sodium hexafluorosilicate get
your pro pure with a new pro one filter today at info war store comm or by
calling 888 to 5 3 3 1 3 9 hi there my name is Frank Bates what I'm about to
tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble I just
created a free video presentation at 1 2 3 cover-up calm that exposes the
electricity monopolies and government agencies for what they really are
incompetent line crooks that are counting on your ignorance and fear to
keep your power bills criminally high some have called us a conspiracy others
have called it a cover-up and you will be shocked to find out how deep the
conspiracy goes my video at 1 2 3 cover-up calm exposes the truth and shows
you the secret of how I beat them and how you can beat them to watch the
controversial video the thousands of other smart Patriots have already seen
in the last three months go to 1 2 3 cover-up calm and discover one weird
trick to slash your power bill and protect your home go watch my video now
at 1 2 3 cover-up calm before they force me to shut it down again that's 1 2 3
cover-up calm stop the pain from broken shift and damaged nails and eliminate
toenail fungus with a revolutionary new nail hardener nails of steel just apply
one drop of nails of steel over natural or polished nails and go with nails of
steel there's virtually no drying time and it's guaranteed try this all-natural
antifungal and herbal formula for women and men call eight one six eight nine
six eight three zero seven or get free shipping at nails of steel calm nails of
steel calm it's like a salon in a bottle we the people grow cotton we fabric in
grave ink embed strips and fibers to protect from counterfeit and carting to
a private bank having it led back at interest forcing taxes to service debt
this capitalism or was Jefferson correct when stating a central bank issuing the
public currency is a greater menace to the liberties of the people than a
standing army hi Ted Anderson I'm placing a silver dollar in a book
explains our monetary system call for your copy eight hundred six eight six
two two three seven it's time to understand the system call eight hundred
six eight six two two three seven that's eight hundred six eight six two two
three seven digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of toxins
that bears repeating digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of
toxins and pro-em one daily probiotic cleanse is the key to digestive health
pro-em one is a powerful liquid probiotic strong enough to cleanse
gentle enough to use every day pro-em one is dairy wheat and soy free contains
all-natural and certified organic ingredients contains no preservatives or
animal products supports a healthy digestive and immune system supports
weight loss improves absorption of food nutrients aids in controlling yeast
infections is never freeze-dried and uses three groups of live viable
beneficial microbes to cleanse and remove toxins order pro-em one daily
probiotic cleanse at tereganics.com spelled t-e-r-a-g-a-n-i-x.com tereganics.com
or call toll-free eight six six three six nine three six seven eight that's
eight six six three six nine three six seven eight pro-em one the raw probiotic
Monday through Friday 11 a.m. to 2 p.m. central we're here short segment now long
segment coming up we're just fine constitutional lawyers our guest are you
got cut off by the break you were getting into a higher political culture
people being more aware and then you were starting to get off into what we've
become now I mean secret arrest NDAA checkpoints TSA in Austin searching
people without warrants now my dad sent me a bill this morning I meant to get to
where they're now going to levy a thing for it's a state bill where every
medical examination you get a piece of money is sent in a fee for state
teachers state teacher retirement funds I mean it's it's just turning into a
total orgy of thieving all the government arms against us openly what
do we do when an empire starts doing this and and what do you predict is
going to happen next in this insane orgy of tyrannical behavior start at the
beginning our founding fathers had first-hand experience with subjection to
charity and overreaching and so they were much more embracing of libertarian
ideas because they could see the temptations of tyranny taking a nation
through a nation as it did Great Britain ultimately but the the founding
generation basically died off with John Quincy Adams presidency terminating in
1828 and it became more and more situation where the leaders of government
had never been subjects they'd never been the the brunt of tyrannical action
and they began to want government to be bigger because that meant their office
holding had more stature and more power and it's been a steady trajectory since
really the Mexican-American war where the purposes of government have changed
from liberty of the individual to power for the government and how do we change
this because now we're sort of at the high-water mark of the Empire so I call
it the psychology of Empire where the government does everything to try to
make your you know a risk-free existence and in the name of a risk-free existence
you lose all of your liberty and freedom and that's also true not only
domestically where we'll have surveillance drones throughout the
nation probably before our lifetimes ends Alex and we go abroad in search of
monster to destroy anything that moves anywhere in the world there's the United
States say in countries can't even be pronounced by most people how many people
would know where Molly is or Niger or Burkina Faso or Yemen or things of that
sort and again it's this idea that government and strength and power and
domination coercion is who we are as a nation it's making us resented abroad
just as it's evoking resentment in the United States at home now how does this
kind of psychology change it really can change in my judgment only with
leadership because ordinary people don't quite understand that a risk-free
existence is an exchange sort of a Faustian exchange with vassals that you
can't have a risk-free existence without making everyone a candidate for prison
for detention because we're all capable of evil even if the capability is small
and someone has to stand up and say no we'd rather be free than risk-free and
as a leader saying I want to renounce or scale back or downsize government not
increase it government doesn't know better than you you are master of your
soul you're a captain of your fate you have the pride and dignity of determining
your end point where you make of what your endowments are a government just
has a give you an even playing field but other than that we would destroy your
own dignity if we attempted to give you a crush for it and the goal is to get
everybody on welfare in the system how do we reverse it then because we know
historically where the Empire goes next it starts imploding everything and as
things get worse it starts confiscating more and more and then it only
accelerates is there any way out of the nightmares that are caused when empires
begin to rot well Alex there have been about 72 prior empires tracing back to
the Roman Empire and the Ottoman Empire and all the Romanov Empire I don't need
to identify them all and not a single one has been able to escape you know the
clutches of ruination as you've described them bigger bigger government
risk-free existence everybody's dependent that the tax receivers get
larger the taxpayers get narrower and the question is can the United States be
the first empire in history that sees the precipice and walks back my judgment
can be done but only with extraordinary leadership I still think people given a
proper impeccable character and understanding of who we are and the
dignity that attends controlling your own fate taking moral accountability for
your destiny is one that would resonate but at present we have no leaders with
that kind of character and ability to inspire individuals to make certain it's
the better angels of their nature rather than the more sinful or vice prone
angels that become dominant sure constitutional lawyer Bruce fine final
segment with you coming up I want to get into some of the current things
happening and some of the courts striking down a King Obama's activities
straight ahead stay with us
we're on the march the Empire's on the run Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
if you want an American company with American products made by Americans here
is the cow Ben soap company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products
for years these all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable
and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and safe see them on the web at five
star soap calm or call eight hundred three four zero seven zero nine one for
a free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are
twice as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year
supply of soaps or all your cleaning needs this is an amazing deal you can
save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
see them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free
catalog the new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness
get serious and make a stand with supernatural silver this is a
breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver can be taken orally
every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds
supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective
for water purification it is the number one choice for thousands of people for
immune system support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency
preparedness go to supernatural silver calm today and give yourself and your
loved ones a fighting chance that's supernatural silver calm check out our
new low prices and like us on Facebook now that we have moved into the winter
season there is an increased need to support our immunity and health at silver
lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver based products our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce
nano silver solutions our 2 ounce nano silver nasal applicators as well as our
all-natural silver soaps just released is our 100% natural silver gel our new
silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate
and leave the silver at the surface but rather we have formulated our silver gel
using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly
penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively
visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver
based products are best for you that's www.silverlungs.com
from the front lines of the information war it's Alex Jones
we are back live ladies and gentlemen thank you for joining us doing a few
more minutes with constitutional lawyer Bruce fine we've talked about the
history we've talked about where we currently are is it that Obama is worse
than the last few presidents or is it that the power structure has just gotten
more accustomed to tyranny because historically you see where tyrants and
tyrannies creep up corrupt systems do and then finally the bottom falls out
when they realize hey we've got our people in almost everywhere we've got
the force we can just do whatever we want and clearly we're reaching that
that tipping point I hope as Ron Paul has said and as you've said and for many
years use the tipping point to go back into Liberty and we do have the
Constitution and Bill of Rights the power structure has been blaming for our
problems when clearly when we followed it we had half the world's wealth and
5% of the population we leave it to our ruination I mean it's total cause and
effect so so so answer that question and then run through some of the other big
issues that are front and center for you the good the bad and the ugly I know
there's been some victories against tyranny lately but also some defeats but
are we not approaching that flashpoint or do you think it'll just continue to
be a creeping rotting because I see the power structure grabbing everything it
can really I think out of a sense that they know we know Bruce fine
constitutional lawyer you know your take on that I think that we have across the
Rubicon into at least a psychological tyranny Alex I have regularly postulated
that if the current president or a future president called a press
conference in the evening and stated that the Constitution was being
suspended and the executive was asserting all power in order to make us
safe and comfortable and prosperous that such an individual would not be impeached
by Congress there would not be calls like it Watergate for Nixon's ouster
that the people would accept a tyranny if you will and I don't believe that
politically a president would find that necessary and wise to do at present I
don't think Obama is likely to do it but at some point we'll get Caligula in the
White House and the precedents of unlimited presidential power lie around
like loaded weapons ready to be used by any successor in the White House and if
we just want to give as an example of the ultimate apogee if you will of
tyranny just think of what the president is saying about his authority to use a
predator drone to kill the US citizens anytime anyplace anywhere he says on
secret evidence that you are an imminent threat the United States there's no
accountability all this is done in secret we have given one person in the
Oval Office the ability to play judge jury prosecutor and executioner all in
secret now think of that Alex it is impossible to endow any one individual
with more power than to choose anybody on the planet for vaporization that's
where we are the other things that the president claims authority to do and is
exercising like intercepting our emails and telephone calls without any warns
without any suspicion it's incredible it is it truly incredible especially to me
because my baptism Alex was Watergate where a third-rate burglary ultimately
ended up being an impeachable offense that drove mr. yeah the president spied
without warrants and he had to step down or he would have been convicted the
Senate let me go back to the drone for a moment and then get back into the
eloquent points you're making with constitutional lawyer here best-selling
author Bruce fine take take the drones Al Sharpton came out and said hey don't
worry about your guns we're gonna take them we got predator drones and I see on
the so-called left who aren't really left in my view Thomas Jefferson was a
liberal these people are authoritarians they say it on no exaggeration 2030 shows
I've seen and news articles they go hey forget your guns we got drones we've got
artillery we'll use them on you and I feel worship by those gathered around
the state with a reflected glory they are getting off on executive power like
it's a god they're worshipping or a golden calf you are up there on Capitol
Hill obviously battling all this you have to be around these people but but I
mean I've been following this intensely for 20 years there is a demoniac glow to
a lot of the minions activities now higher level globalists look scared but
a lot of the minions Bruce look really really animated like dancing around
their idol can you elaborate on that or have you seen them gloat on their
military firepower and how they'll use it on us domestically I don't know
whether that is widespread domestically except in metaphorical ways I will say
this however that it's not a party issue the members of Congress are what I call
you know invertebrates they do not want the accountability they do not want to
accept the responsibility which the Constitution fastens upon them to
oversee to check to block executive power when the founding fathers are you
know we're writing the Constitution they feared a bloated executive and they
couldn't have imagined Congress being so so kind to voluntarily surrender the
decisions to wage war or not you know to levy or taxes or to spend all this is
now delegated to the president separation of powers you'd have power
hungry people in all three branches not letting the other have the power yes but
what they didn't anticipate Alex was the polarization created by the party system
they did not think that Democrats and Republicans in Congress would sell their
souls for a mess of pottage with that they would believe their loyalty was not
to the Constitution or their institution but to their party so you always have
one party in Congress willing to block the other party's effort to check the
president and in that way the presidential power simply grows it
metastasizes like a cancer and it's been true under Republican and Democratic
presidents alike and under Obama presidential power it has reached its
apex it's never been this authoritative before and when we can ask a president
who refuses even to explain to the public or to Congress why he thinks he
has this legal authority to kill us all and all of it is a secret secret law
that even Caligula didn't practice in Roman times and he gets away with that
with a complacent public in a Congress that doesn't demand that he will have no
money you will be impeached unless he explains why he thinks what he's doing
is legal it shows you how can we give more power to an executive than that
it's a very very dismaying situation and unless we have a leader who comes to the
White House and gives back the power because Congress will take it back only
a president who says I understand the folly of of tyranny and I don't want to
exercise it if that doesn't happen we will not be a republic we will be
totally ruined as an agent in 20 or 30 years time we simply cannot go forward
with one person making all the decisions in secret and no one accepts accepting
constant I mean responsibility and plus no criticism being permitted because in
the executive branch you descend from the president you are crushed you know
they will attempt to badmouth you to assassinate your character and otherwise
and there you can see it with a six espionage prosecutions for so-called
whistleblowers and look at the CIA guy that exposed illegal torture and just
got 30 months he should be getting he should be getting a medal and a
whistleblower award instead the secret torture continues and Obama's been caught
lying about that and a guy that tried to work through channels and nothing stopped
lets them an investigative journalists know without even giving away you know
code names and things so that an investigation could start and they put
him in jail and see that's the paradox people say all the tyranny is not that
bad we still have some liberty running but if you look at what they've put into
law as you said the Nazis did all this stuff in basements and in secret
facilities but they didn't put open stuff like this on paper the Soviets
didn't I mean it's so amazing that they've put it all on paper and then the
mainstream media goes oh you're a kook you said we're going into tyranny we
need guns the parasols from the tyranny there's no tyranny well the gentleman
you spoke of John Kiriakou of a work where he's a very admirable person and
and it is an example of the one person who set the dynamic for prohibiting a
torture waterboarding is the one who goes to prison all the ones who
participated in the waterboarding the church or get off scot-free it is
another situation I'm working with a fellow named Tony Schafer I used to work
at at DIA and they're trying to revoke his bronze medal because you know he's
in a retired status now because he's criticized the tactics in Afghanistan
and elsewhere somebody who risked that last full measure of devotion for the
country now has his bronze medal under attack because he has the audacity to
say you know maybe you're not omniscient in the White House and you're exactly
right when those kinds I say these are the people who you and I read about
where the Sakharov's and Solzhenitsyn's getting sentenced to prison in the
Soviet Union but we're not supposed to be the Soviet Union and yet we are
aping their rather dedicated approach to government Bruce fine we've got to get
you back up soon and I mean our only hope I think is to point out why things
are getting bad point out historically why it's wrong and just stand against
them and I think there's enough enough vestigial liberty there not in the
Congress but in the spine of the American people that if we all just say
no and we all take action we've seen the court striking down the recess
appointments and some I mean we are seeing a few good signs hopefully we can
turn this around but we know this it's only gonna get worse if we don't stand
up so the only course is say no that is absolutely correct and remember the
saying of Tacitus as the Roman Republic degenerated to the Roman Empire the
worst crimes were dared by a few willed by more but tolerated by all we don't
want to be subject to that kind of stigma it needs us to tolerate it and
that's why they shout down I see articles where they go how dare the man
go to City Council and say you don't want to turn his guns in how extreme
they take normal behavior look a little girl said let's play with our bubble
guns after school so the SWAT team was called but the government's wearing
stormtrooper outfits and saying they'll secretly kill you if you want oh that's
to keep us safe you know we should be totally horrified by that and resisting
it but instead they teach us Pavlovian Lee someone made a Lego gun at school so
we evacuated I mean this they're trying to turn us into gibbering mental
patients and I have faith because of the internet and Ron Paul and yourself we're
going to defeat it constitutional lawyer Bruce fine author of American Empire
before the fall thank you so much for the time thank you Alex Wow amazing
interview with constitutional lawyer Bruce fine I want to get into some
financial news here in just a moment but before we do that some of the other
incredible news I mean when you see the NFL coming out saying we shouldn't own
guns I told you to boycott it people said oh that's Bob Costas that is at the
hold NFL here is the NBC same same culprits Sandy Hook chorus to sing at
the Super Bowl and that's the way to take the 70 million viewers now the
number one show in North America and to shove a bunch of anti Second Amendment
garbage down our throats and reinvoke all this hey how about we have the
acquire from Mexico of schools where the drug cartels or government comes in and
kills you know a hundred people they've almost had sixty thousand killed more
than Vietnam the last six years why don't we have that or or you know the
kids killed by fast and furious guns the president ordered ship down there why
don't we have the family of the dead Border Patrol agents killed by fast and
furious guns of the police officers how about they go and shing at this event I
mean they are just shoving this garbage down our throat absolutely shoving it
wholesale down our throat and again there's nowhere to run ladies and
gentlemen the whole world's going under global government same mega banks run it
they're exempt from the law they have government shut down your your your life
I want to show people some articles here if you're watching on TV if not you can
just go to info wars calm or prison planet calm we have these articles
posted right now US debt headed towards 200% of GDP even after fiscal cliff deal
okay now again they they know they're bringing us into bankruptcy that's the
plan and then after they bankrupt things we'll accept total socialism Bloomberg
jobless claims in US rose 38
it's more than 38,000 last week to 368 368 thousand claims for US
unemployment benefits increase more than forecast last week boom they've got
articles about the economy contracted faster than they thought oh you didn't
think massive payroll tax increases would contract things and they said poor
people we're gonna cut your taxes they raise them and then there's an
investment tax and all these new ones gold trades near one week high on US
economy Fed stimulus US stocks fall as investors weigh earnings economy US
unemployment up you know all of this report IRS hiring new employees well
somebody's hiring of course all the elites are basically left alone I wanted
to bring up Ted Anderson and yeah it's gonna be a gold pitch but that's not why
he's really here I saw some gold deals we're gonna talk about gold with the
economy with Ted Anderson the founder of Midas resources and the Genesis Network
and I got went and got he was a sponsor before he started this network because I
go out and get people that sell numismatics at at at bullion prices but I
called Ted this morning I said I heard a radio ad last night on one of the
biggest talk show hosts in this country and I'm not even gonna say names you
know who it is they've been in trouble for this before I said what were they
really selling stuff for we're gonna skip this network break as I'm so far
behind I can do this plus it's important to get this out so station shouldn't be
going over this in about three months as a network break but Ted I call tick
because I know about the gold silver business pretty good I've been in it for
17 years and Ted started the network 15 years ago I've been working with him 17
years about 16 he was a sponsor right away I was a local radio as I went out
and shopped and found the real folks and did some research and I've been with Ted
ever since and I heard this ad for a coin and I knew the coin was a hundred
and fifty percent higher than it should be it's great for a company to have five
percent maybe on something was hard to get a 10% markup that's great you gotta
be able to make money to keep your lights on you know hold the stuff sell
it do all that on on average Ted's got about a five percent markup he's got
deals where he loses money where you can get two silver dollars at cost two films
and a book for free called a loss leader but I'm not differentiating the
competition that's the oldest trick in the book saying you know that their
hamburgers are crap we don't where's the beef ours are off beef patties check
this out for yourself a lot of the big national talk show host one of them
lives right here in Texas move down here it's gonna leave it at that got in
trouble for stuff with a hundred percent markup this is a hundred and fifty I was
hearing and I just it just blows me away that Ted Anderson on average is about a
five percent markup and and and that Ted is it's got it's doing such a you know a
good job at what he's doing and I just think people need to know people need to
price check they need to shop and they need to call Midas resource we'll get
into the economy in a moment I just want to get this out here upfront like let me
go to info Wars calm I meant even show people to go to info Wars calm and you
scroll down you see the little Midas resources banner just with some gold
coins there click on that and it takes you there where you can see the the
Obama deception the American dream film great animated film about the private
Federal Reserve in the Rothschilds and then another book about the history of
gold and money a book and two videos two silver dollars seventy two dollars I
mean you can't even get them hardly anywhere for that price plus the two
free films and the book I mean it's a totally insane deal yeah click on that
for folks I want people to be able to see this I mean we've had this deal for
a year no this is the best deal in silver anywhere no one can top it
dishonest money the book American dream film Obama deception eight hundred six
eight six two two three seven I said Ted come on and do a money report about the
big runs on silver that are happening right now I've got some of those
articles rush to safety Americans by nearly half a million dollars of gold
and silver in January but the media is trying to keep the price down with
different manipulations which is a great buying opportunity I mean ladies and
gentlemen try to find two silver dollars especially these that are collectible
but he's selling them to get bullion prices for seventy dollars with the free
shipping the shipping is included in that as they do bait and switches with
that and the films and all the rest of it I mean that is that is insane asylum
level deal eight hundred six eight six two two three seven but it's just that I
know Ted's got over a thousand affiliates Ted is getting with all his
shows most of our libertarian or constitutionalist in base he is
absolutely launched this show standing behind me for 15 years to the cover of
talkers magazine to over 150 affiliates and exploding right now with this
hardcore message it's the truth but it you know imagine this is on the air big
stations now all over because people now know it's real they now know I'm not
crazy I was ahead of my time I wish I wasn't being proven right this is this
is a big deal folks my point is Midas resources is the place to buy your
silver and gold and if you want numismatics you want collectibles they've
got them okay and they've got the best deals on collectibles compare their
numismatics to what you're hearing I hear some good deals on other radio
shows but I mean some of these are just horrible you will get the best deals and
I stand behind what I promote okay I've been approached by big giant gold
sponsors and and and offered unbelievable amounts of money but I will
not sit there and sell old ladies a coin that should be $1,000 for $2,500 I will
not do it hell would freeze over plus people get mad at you because in the
market you know it's gone it's gone from 300 bucks to you know 2,000 and then it
goes back down to 1,700 people get mad they're not looking at the long-term
graph it's only going up they get mad when you sell them stuff at a great deal
and then and then and then they manipulate the market and it goes down
they apologize later when it goes back up I don't buy it for an investment I
buy it as an emergency backup but it's been about the best investment out there
unless you're doing insider stuff in the last 12 years it's gone from 300 it was
even lower but I've heard about about 300 like 260 or something up to right at
2,000 you know the point is and then drop back down some I got Chad on about
financial news but I'm just an honest person you know with a little gold pitch
in there as a sponsor I just start plugging what I believe in Midas resources
is the place and when it comes to bullion when it comes to bullion with
people that actually sell it to you see some deals occasionally because I've
looked around before I've seen deals where they claim something you call up
over out of that we have this you don't get dealt with Midas resources Ted you
know hits the escape pod you know the ejection seat on brokers in about 10
seconds when he discovers you know anything and it could because again the
the whole gold and silver industry is people don't have the facts is a snake
pit that's why I'm telling you ladies and gentlemen Midas resources 800 6 8 6
2 2 3 7 and now is the time to support the biggest sponsor you not only get
great deals you support the guy that stood behind me like nobody else you
know I don't have the others of America as a sponsor I was thinking when he was
on I'll try to get him a sponsor because he says we're one of the biggest groups
getting a members but I'm doing it because they're a group defending my
Second Amendment you know they don't pay me to get them on and say join them now
Midas resources does but they're the sponsor I've got and they're already you
know sponsoring the website they're the sponsor I've got because they were the
best group I could find and they're still the best group you know I've come
to Ted before when he can't spend more money on can you spend more so I can
expand my operation he goes I'm sorry I just can't I'm like one being offered
three times more money by somebody else right now your contract but let me tell
you most you say well I would do the same really really somebody comes and
offers you millions of dollars to screw people would you do it see I say no and
does that mean everything's absolutely perfect and you won't get the very best
deal the galaxy ever saw none of this is perfect but Ted has a great operation
and the best prices I found consistently 800 6 8 6 2 2 3 7 800 6 8 6 2 2 3 7 and
just like we stand behind gunners of America we just stand behind people like
Ted because now is the time to get your gold your silver from Ted Anderson now
Ted I wanted to get you on about currency manipulation what's happening in
the economy the statement by the White House that they're gonna go ahead and go
with dollar devaluation QE unlimited what this signifies but I know I talked
to you this morning and I said well we got to do a report on this not nasty not
even naming names but I'm morally have to just tell people that you know and
it's not that I these people attack me and I don't attack them is the point
because they see me as competition because they copy what we cover it just
blows me away the cutthroat crap I see and then to see you down there honest
and people running off and getting a hornswaggled I mean I guess it's legal
what people do it's just and it's okay to make a profit I just I just when
people advertise great deals I've got a right to say it's not a great deal
Midas resources is the best deal out there consistently 800 6 8 6 2 3 7 I mean
Ted explain to people this what I'm talking about here as much as you want
to say well the thing about it is Alex is that I see a lot of this advertising
for you know we've got this exclusive deal on a country coin that's brand new
you only can buy it from us problem is you typically end up paying a big
premium for that kind of stuff and you're not going to get it back when you
go to see you told me it was a hundred fifty percent on what you heard
yesterday a hundred fifty percent I've seen it all the way up to four hundred
percent Alex it gets it goes out of this world you don't like to talk about this
it's like Larry Pratt doesn't want to talk about the NRA you know it's you
know it's sort of the it's sort of the dark side of the industry but it does
happen and I I just need to tell people to stay away from that stuff I mean
you're just because a country goes in and makes a new coin a lot of the times
it's the coin dealer that comes in and approaches the country's mint and says
hey you can make a lot of money on this we'll promote it and and they make up
the special deal and people end up paying a big price it's gonna be the
next greatest collectible folks the coins that are collectible are known and
certified and whether it's a revolutionary penny which I happen to
have been gifted by a grandfather didn't even know I had it oh yeah I think I'm
gonna probably sell even though it's an heirloom to fund the operation the point
is is that is that Ted here's an example let's not even what are some of the best
numismatics and people are really into those I mean what are the classics that
are really are worth a lot that you could go to New Zealand and they'd open
a coin book and know what it was well I mean the the obvious coins are the
$20 st. God and $20 Liberty $10 liberties 10 Indians I mean the stuff
that was used here as currency in this nation I even have a tendency to stay
away from the higher premium graded stuff at this point just because I can
see what's going on in the economy we're looking at a depression and because
we're looking at a depression I think it's more important to have something
like a survival bag of dimes than it is to have one coin that's worth five six
seven thousand or I've seen coins go for 250,000 300,000 and there are
legitimate coins that so yeah I know there are a lot of great collectible
coins the thing is you better get a red book that Midas sells at cost you better
learn your stuff you know it'd be like you know becoming a horse trader you
won't start buying selling horses great you better spend 20 years learning about
it right exactly that's what I mean Alex it's more important that people get
their core position something that they can fall back on I've got a million gold
and silver right now that's that's exactly where I think people should go
or if you're gonna go into Numa stay close to melt that's the main thing
that's the thing you sell a lot of coins that are collectible but that are
actually close to melt and that's the biggest winner folks for my research
that's what I do 800 686 2237 800 686 2237 I want to look deeper into the
world economy when we come back thank you for listening to GCN visit GCN live
calm today looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from
natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to
the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to
those that have lost everything at e foods direct we hear from customers
every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm by having a supply of
food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the
grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be
able to help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too
early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the
warnings and do what Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six
three three today or go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your
food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term
storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four zero nine five six three
three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct
coast to coast direct from Austin you're listening to the Alex Jones broadcasting
network network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
ladies and gentlemen last week and earlier this week we played clips where
White House advisors are telling top hedge fund managers that they're gonna
devalue the dollar that's their plan and I mean I'm already seeing prices explode
everywhere I don't know how people are paying their bills because you know I'm
what you'd call upper-middle class or whatever I invest most of capital back
in this operation but I mean I mean if these bills give me a sting and I'm
wondering how working folks are making it I mean this is hellish and you really
go places down you see less people and you see stores shutting down and we're
in a depression I mean that's what's going on and people that bought gold at
three hundred four hundred five hundred a thousand fifteen hundred when we told
them to I didn't say do it as an investment they made out like bandits
because they didn't listen to the globalist Soros and all the elites are
buying gold Ted this is what I wanted to get you on how big is it that the
Germans don't trust the private Federal Reserve and want their gold back and now
all these other countries that signifies the creep towards the exits are
accelerating well I mean if you have the Germans the central banks in Germany is
saying we'd want our gold back I mean what does that mean they don't trust the
United States they don't like the 85 billion dollars that we're making brand
new money and putting into our economy every single month way too much stimulus
it's obvious that the handwriting is on the wall paper is not going to hold
value for the future gold is so is silver that's why they're asking for it
it's obvious it's just simple you know the Rothschild's taking on huge amounts
of gold and getting away from paper I mean these guys print the stuff and they
don't want it I mean why it is the people of the United States it's like
they're asleep at the switch or something it just doesn't make sense
that they're sitting here accepting the economy that we have looking at the
numbers unemployment numbers shooting up you know like you said Alex you're seeing
stores closing down we're walking into a depression and and and half of the
country thinks this president is so great because he's going to try to take
away our guns and and and to me it just doesn't make sense when you see the the
big traders in the marketplace getting away from paper money you better do the
same because these guys can see what's going on the handwriting is on the wall
besides the fact like you say Alex they would just as soon destroy the United
States currency and force everybody to take their new world traded currency and
lose the sovereign the sovereignty of this nation absolutely we've got some
breaking news Ted just briefly here school officials confirm shooting in
Atlanta middle school sounds like a gang related deal 14 year old shot and it
goes on to say the parents even though the shootings been over a while are not
allowed to pick up their children so the government's setting that precedent
where you can't get your kids and they teach them to get the fetal position to
hopefully get a higher death count so they can take our guns that's Fox News
Fox News calm reporting that and obviously drugs report calm will have it
all have the latest at info Wars calm and prison planet TV Ted what about the
two silver dollars for $72 with the two free films and the free book I mean
that's like a $60 free retail value on top of the silver dollars at cost well
that's the thing I mean if you were to buy the silver dollars from you straight
you'd be paying over $78 for the two silver dollars plus you'd have to buy
the postage which is at least 10 bucks you know so that particular deal is I
mean nobody's got any nobody's got a deal like that out there in silver
period this is the greatest way to get a couple pieces of silver in your hand
especially if you can't afford to get into the marketplace in any great extent
and you can use your credit card if you want to Alex it doesn't get better than
that $72 for two silver dollars we all know that silver is trading in the 30s
you're not going to be able to find that anywhere else plus the video I mean your
Obama deception the American Dream you know the dishonest money by Joe Plummer
it's going to teach you what's going on as far as what's happening in absolutely
eight hundred six eight six two two three seven and you know you're getting
great deals and supporting the broadcast and all the other shows that Ted
Anderson produces eight hundred six eight six two two three seven eight
hundred six eight six two three seven or Midas resources calm to find that
special link through at info Wars calm on the big banner thank you so much Ted
key Intel and more info straight ahead on the serious situation with Paul
Watson