Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you so much for joining us. This is going to be a particularly
powerful broadcast today. Dr. Jerome Corsi of WorldNetDaily, and of course, of all the
New York Times, number one bestsellers, is scheduled to be in studio with us coming up
later in the hour.
And obviously, I'm gonna be covering a lot of important news in the meantime. The news
is all so completely out of control and over the top that I don't even know how to respond
at this point. If you go up to Infowars.com, airport terror announcements now being played
in hotels.
I mean, this is beyond 1984, where Big Brother's only in government buildings saying, watch
your neighbors, look out for terrorists. This is now in the hotels. And they spy on the
patrons and fill out data sheets on you even while you're eating. This is 5,000 plus major
US hotels signed on to do this, all official.
TSA is now conducting random warrantless checkpoints on South Lamar, that's about a mile and a
half from where I'm sitting, and are searching people's persons and bags. And they announced
they're just gonna do whatever they want. And I was told this about three months ago
by a senior Austin police officer.
He said they'd been told that they can't search someone without a warrant, but that the federal
government is basically putting us under a civil emergency quietly. And that they're
being told that you can do it when the TSA is there with you. And Austin police bullied
people into being groped. And it's on local ABC News, we have the clip up there.
This is going on yesterday while I'm on the radio. And reportedly, they're gonna be back.
So it's gonna be a semi-permanent deal, just like Dallas and Houston. And I tell people
five years ago TSA was showing up in Dallas and people said, that's not true, I haven't
seen it on the news.
But I talked to family that saw it. And about two years ago, they started having it in the
news. There's no way you're gonna have feds searching people on the side of the road.
Well, it's going on right now. And I mean, they had the army out at public events searching
us in Austin, and they never announced it. It's there to acclimate in condition. All
the border is wide open. In fact, I have video, we haven't even aired yet, we've been so overwhelmed
and busy of illegal aliens just crossing in droves on the Texas-Mexico border.
While the border patrol backs up park rangers harassing a UT alumni group of lawyers sitting
around drinking a few courage lights. And they were writing them tickets, everything
else. And I'm like, hey, there's illegal aliens right there, and just laughing at me. And
then driving 70 miles from up by the border into the US and coming to a checkpoint where
they wanted to search the vehicle.
But I basically got in their face and told them, no, well, we've got all the footage
of this. I mean, it's us, we comply, so we are slaves. And then I have off the chart
video in Illinois where the neighbor and the homeowner, the police come and go over their
fence without a warrant with the power company to put smart meters on that on record eavesdrop
on you.
And dial into all your new smart appliances on record and control how hot or cold your
house can be and double charge you and all the rest of this garbage. It was developed
by Enron 15 years ago as part of their fraud program. And the police, they're standing
on the street and the police say, I don't give you authorization to fill me. The woman
put it on YouTube and the police came, this is in the Chicago Tribune, and arrested her
and are charging her with resisting.
They say, in the affidavit, talking to them was resisting. And the woman's like, you don't
have a right to be in my backyard. I don't want this smart meter. I've told them I don't
want it. And the police say, we'll do whatever we want. And they look like total guns. And
then they came and arrested her and they said, you're lucky we're not charging with a felony.
Actually, the courts have thrown it out over 100 times in Illinois. They're doing it as
the misdemeanor so they can trick her in the regular court to not getting her jury trial.
I mean, this government is absolutely rapacious and criminal. We're all in grave danger. The
founders warned us, keep government on a short leash or it'll put you on a leash.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die? Start purifying your water with ProPure. My friends, I've done
a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is ProPure.
And it's available discounted at info wars.com. Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent
bacterial growth. There's no priming required. It's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters
can reduce fluoride up to 95% easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity purify
water from lakes, streams, ponds and wells. This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals
which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the
plastic. ProPure is the best gravity fed filter out there. It's what my family uses info wars.com
already has the lowest price on ProPure. But if you add the promo code water at checkout,
you get an additional 10% off and info wars.com. You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben soap company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at five star soap.com or call 800-340-7091
for a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice
as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at five star soap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog. You may be arrested and or subject to other police
crimes. Tyranny is here. The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality. It really says
that the state is God. The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most
impressive police states on earth. This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret
network of FEMA camps now being expanded nationwide. This documentary exposes how the continuity
of government program has established an all powerful shadow state. Police state four chronicles
the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen. Prepare to enter the secretive
world of emergency dictatorship, body scammers, sound cameras, citizen spies, stage terror
and cameras on every street corner. It's only the beginning of the new world order's hellish
plan. The police state isn't coming. It's here. Secure your copy today at info wars.com
or see it online in the highest quality at prison planet dot TV. We now take you live
to the Central Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance. You're listening
to the Alex Jones show. It is Friday, the 25th day of January 2013. I am your host,
Alex Jones, and we're going to be here live for the next three hours. Dr. Jerome Corsi
is here. He'll be in studio with us coming up in about 25 minutes, and we have other
guests today coming up as well.
Okay, where to start? Number one, Dianne Feinstein's gun confiscation bill, because that's basically
what it does, and it bans hundreds and hundreds of guns, not 150, exempts police and retired
police and other government workers for life from these laws. This is a title of nobility.
That's what nobility was. You could be signed up as a sir, was the lowest level, and then
ride up to lords and dukes and barons. If you would serve the system, well, you're exempt
from all the laws.
And that's what one of the Rockefellers told the late, great filmmaker Aaron Russo in Hollywood.
He told him, look, we're all gonna have a microchip that says, kiss my butt, using the
more pejorative term, kiss my you know what. Where we're just above the law, national security,
we go around the checkpoints, around the body scanners, around the control, we're exempt,
you're not.
You'll all be face scanned and controlled. Well, Rand Corporation, MIT, they've all said
that is the plan. And we are going under martial law, incrementally, checkpoints all over the
highways, police taking blood without warrants. Now gang gun checkpoints all over the country
where they randomly from New York to Texas, pull you over and search your car.
Totally illegal, but it's being announced. We got the video coming up with this and the
audio for radio listeners, the article's up at infowars.com right now. TSA conducts random
checks at Austin train station. Well, actually, they did it out on South Lamar on the road
downtown. And we have the video, that is coming up.
We have, again, Feinstein gun control bill to exempt government officials. That's anybody
in government, federal government, for life and police. See, the police are like, well,
I don't wanna give my guns up when I retire. Well, they're saying, don't worry, you're
gonna be exempt.
They told the Russian military and the Russian federal police the same thing in 1917. And
so they went along with the gun confiscation of the general public. And of course, you
know what happened to the police and military after that. This is a totally unconstitutional
discriminatory, but see, you're taught discrimination is black, white, North, South, man, woman,
Hispanic, white, Catholic, Protestant. You're taught all that.
No, discrimination is the big mega banks exempt from taxes, lobbying to have your taxes raised
to give themselves corporate welfare your money. Discrimination is governments exempt
from smart meter corporate taxes, but you are double, triple charged. Smart meters,
and all of this are the tools of total control. And we actually have articles here out of
the Daily Caller, but also one out of the Huffington Post where they quote the Democrats
and Governor Cuomo and others is saying, it doesn't exclude retired police officers.
So all of them have to turn in their guns and magazines and stuff like that. He said,
what they did is disarm the good guys and make sure the bad guys outlaw them. That was
said by a police officer. But so now they're talking about trying to pass a law in New
York so the police can keep their guns. Here's another one, Feinstein gun control bill to
exempt government officials. Not everyone will have and be able to abide by Senator
Dianne Feinstein's gun control bill.
If the proposed legislation becomes law, government officials, not servants, they are officials,
they are royalty. Red carpets, everything, and others will be exempt. And it goes on
to say feds, police, and others that can get a federal waiver. So see, that's out of the
weekly standard. Ladies and gentlemen, this is what our forebears revolted against.
You could not buy land unless you were nobility in the colonies, large pieces of land. You
couldn't get an export license or an import license unless you were, quote, part of the
gentry nobility, a sir or above, a lord's son. And so everybody sat there, not able
to do business, not able to live, watching lesser men run everything.
George Washington couldn't manufacture carriages, he wanted to. He had to buy at five, six times
what they cost in England on top of the shipping, his gentleman's carriage. You had to buy
the finished clothes from England. There were laws, you couldn't make firearms, you couldn't
make hammers, you couldn't make nails, you couldn't have finished goods here.
As a globalist tool, mercantile tool, to not let development take place and to make everything
be back in the home country where the globalist, where the empire controlled things. Just like
today, it can only be made in China because of regulations here that make it impossible
to be competitive.
Well, back then, they just outright outlawed it. This is why our forebears were willing
to lose everything and die because they were sick of literally being spit on by the royals.
And now government with the red carpets and the officials and the titles. I mean, I saw
Dianne Feinstein and all of her minions up there yesterday with all of the traitor police
chiefs or the big city crime syndicates that they brought in.
And they had two cordons in front of the guns going, we have to have two cordons in front
of this. None of the media could even walk by the assault weapons, the semi-autos, because
they're so dangerous. I actually have CNN saying this, we're gonna play the clip later.
Just total mind control, talking to us like we're three years old, saying the boogeyman's
over there. And Feinstein saying, I got a special waiver to even have these unloaded
guns here.
Like, they're so deadly. Again, I've always told you they have these sitcoms and dramas
based in New York where guns are banned. Where everybody sees the image of guns being illegal
and people going to jail for having guns to wear a carpet cleaners in your house, sees
a gun case and calls the police in Texas or Arizona.
This happens all the time. And the future, they're saying Homeland Security will respond
to any reports of even legal guns and go ahead and take them to, quote, make sure you're
not a criminal and then make you go through psychiatric evaluation if anyone calls on
you saying you have guns.
This has all been announced, okay, so they know what they're doing. Behind two cordons,
we have the guns, they're so deadly. And these police chiefs say, ban them. And they themselves,
the New York Police Department, it's in the news right here in my stack, is lobbying to
have a new bill passed so they can keep their guns when they retire.
Unbelievably wicked criminals, vicious, hateful. And they say in these quotes, we've gotta
protect ourselves from criminals once we retire. There's a quote in the Huffington Post, the
irony is not lost on anybody saying, well, I mean, once we retire, we gotta have guns
to protect ourselves.
The criminals are still gonna have guns. Really? The criminals are still gonna have, you're
gonna have guns because you're the new royalty. You're the officials. You're the authorities,
not the servants, not the peace officers. You are the law enforcement officers and the
movies and the culture show nothing but the citizens groveling to the police.
Now, I'm gonna get to the TSA checkpoints where I live. See, the army was out a few
months ago. And Austinites should just rise up and go to the city council and the state
capital. This is all illegal. I want them out. This is illegal. And it's all getting
you ready. Why are they getting you ready for trips on the streets and TSA checkpoints?
I mean, down the street from me, on the road, searching people. Illegally, violation of
the Fourth Amendment, Tenth Amendment, Ninth Amendment. Why are they doing this?
Ladies and gentlemen, because they're criminals. They're collapsing the whole society and they
know they're all going to jail if they don't totally take over and arrest their opposition.
They've stolen tens of trillions of derivatives. The people running things make Ken Lay look
like a choir boy, an angel, literally. They are total ruthless mafia and they know that
we're waking up to them.
They know there's a 9% approval rating. New evidence has come out on CNN that I'm gonna
be airing tonight. That's all I've got to say concerning the Sandy Hook shooting. You
know I have questions about it. I always do. They have a history of staging these things.
So I believe and know people were killed there from the evidence we have. But there was definitely
all the signs this is being managed.
In fact, now it's pretty conclusive. I'm gonna air that tonight. I'm shaken to my core right
now. I mean, again, every instinct I've got is to flee this country right now. And I know
others are bad as well. But I mean, this country is gonna be the center of the nastiest stuff
the world has ever seen if these crooks get their way.
And all of you that serve the system, you're gonna wish later you'd done something. The
prosperity, everything, it's gone. It's gonna be totally gone, like oxygen out of the room.
I saw footage this morning when I got up at about 6 AM at infowars.com and prisonplanet.com
that Paul Watson did an article on that really hurt me. Now I've had the people on charge
with life in prison for filming cops in public in Illinois.
Courts throw it out, state appeals, they wanna put you in jail for life for filming them.
This is an upscale neighborhood, the footage up at infowars.com. The neighbors friends
with the attractive redheaded housewife. And the police are going over their fence, putting
in the smart meter, and she goes, look, wireless makes my son sick.
We've discovered this, I've discovered it, it's certainly happening. But regardless,
the things spy on you on record and tie into all the new electronics, they admit that,
that are designed so they tie into it. They brag about this. And the police look like
total scary goons. And they are now charging her with resisting police for talking to her,
I've got the affidavit.
And they're charging her for eavesdropping, and they arrested her. They came back and
said we saw that on YouTube, you didn't have a right to film me in public while they film
us and put smart meters on the spy on us. And break the law crossing their property
to put this on their house, while she's telling them don't do it.
And then the police chief of the town, I have it all listed here, it's also the Chicago
Tribune, they're reporting it like it's good, came and arrested the neighbor who was there,
her friend called her. The woman's barefooted in the cold, cuz her neighbor called her and
she's like, please, you don't have a right to be on my property.
The cops just pushed past her, bust open the fence, go in, they're placing it. The woman's
standing on the street filming and they imagine the police came and arrested her. Next, they're
going to disappear us and they want life in prison for the woman. Life in prison, we have
links to them, life in prison for filming them on the sidewalk.
Now folks, tell me we're not living in a FEMA camp.
Coming back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought, to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Time and time again. You need to come here and help us. We need assistance, please. Those
we should be able to depend on, let us down. Federal and state and local officials saying
help is on the way, while the folks here in Bell Harbor say show me. Don't depend on the
government to save you. Take action now so that you're prepared for the next disaster
with MyPatriotSupply.com. Get the best prices on storable food, non-GMO seeds, water filtration
devices, home canning equipment, survival and self-reliance books, and more at MyPatriotSupply.com.
Call 866-229-0927. We are hurting down here and we need help immediately. Before it's
time to survive, it's time to prepare. MyPatriotSupply.com. MyPatriotSupply.com.
Do you know how much the dollar has lost in its value against other currencies in the
last 90 days? Ever think about how inflation will change your life, your savings, your
retirement plans? Remember inflation in Zimbabwe, Argentina, the Weimar Republic? Put another
way. Who cares if your investments go up 10% but you lose 40% of your purchasing power?
Gold is the only monetary asset as no one else's liability. Gold still buys the same
amount of stuff it always did. Gold does not require trust in a third party. You can possess
it in your hand. You can take it with you. Gold is real money. Gold is honest money.
My name is Daniel Larson from Midas Resources. To find out how you can protect your savings
and roll over your IRA funds into precious metals accounts, please call me at 800-686-2237
extension 134. That's 800-686-2237 extension 134. 800-686-2237 extension 134.
Is 2013 your year to achieve more? More vitality? More health? More well-being? Hi, this is
Pastor Jenny. For 25 years, I spent my life's work teaching others how to achieve more.
But in 2010, I got a lesson of my own about RNA drops. I learned that there are millions
of gene switches latent in every single cell of my body that are waiting for an activator.
I learned by taking RNA drops, I could begin to activate that power in my cells and achieve
the more that I desire. I'd like to share what I discovered with you and send you a
free 30-day supply of RNA drops valued at $50 for just the cost of shipping and handling.
Go to RNAfreesample.com. That's RNAfreesample.com. Or call me toll-free at 888-577-3703. That's
888-577-3703. RNAfreesample.com. Discover the more that's waiting for you.
Ladies and gentlemen, we even have video of it. Alex Jones here back live at 5,500 plus
major hotels in the US. We have the press releases up there from the companies. They
are now announcing what we first showed you about two years ago with the FEMA training
videos for TSA.
Where you walk around the hotel and it says, look for terrorists, report suspicious things.
Or you go on the Walmarts and there's the telescreens. They're now going in everywhere.
And when you go up, not just to get a rent car, but to check in, they ask you, who you
coming to see? What's going on? They are entering it into a Homeland Security database. So imagine
everything is a police conversation.
This makes the East German Stasi look like cavemen when it came to spying. And it's all
happening quote for Al-Qaeda, who our government publicly now runs. Do I get an apology from
everybody? Britain's and other westerners told to leave Benghazi after imminent terror
threat by Al-Qaeda, the same Al-Qaeda they gave Libya.
And they think you're so dumb you won't remember that. Now they're saying we've got to have
checkpoints on highways as I predicted. In fact, I have that because Al-Qaeda may have
gotten heat seeking missiles out of Libya. I don't even have time to toot my horn. How
many times I told you in the last year since they got all those heat seekers, 10,000 plus
of them, they'd be saying that now they're saying heat seeking missiles.
Our government gives them the heat seeking missiles and now is gonna run checkpoints
where I live. And I will not put up with it, you terrorist. I know you did it. And again,
it's not, quote, even our government. Most of the government's compartmentalized. It's
the foreign mega banks. This is how they're gonna take over. They tell you it's for Al-Qaeda,
it's for the American people.
Now, Illinois is the worst about this. We're on several stations in Illinois, including
Chicago. And I see these videos. We've had people on from Illinois who've been charged
with life imprisonment, got thrown out by the judge. But the state came and did a brief
and said, no, we want this guy in jail. Now this woman calls her neighbor, she comes up
with her filming. If you're a radio listener, I'm gonna narrate it for you.
They go, a very nice neighborhood. It looks like they're $500,000 houses or more. Nice,
and again, my point is nice, attractive, conservative looking women. I mean, no one's safe, folks,
okay? And the police look like total goons. They have that arrogant sly look, like we
do whatever we want.
They have the look of gangsters. I mean, I've been to towns where they got good police.
You can instantly see they're good guys. They're baring how they act. They're humble, but
they're serious. These are thugs, in my view, just watching them. And then they go across,
violate her Fourth Amendment, put it in, the video's up at Infowars.com, it's so incredible.
It's gotta go viral. And her neighbor films it for her and their friends talking from
the sidewalk. And they're now charging her with, well, I'll read the article in a moment.
Here is just some of the audio for radio listeners and video for people watching us right now
at Infowarsnews.com, here it is.
Here's UPA installers crossing over locked fences.
Climbing them over. Against consent.
Bolt cutters.
They are going onto people's properties with police permission. They are crossing.
The permission? Well, the government's gone.
Laura, do you give consent to have this-
No, absolutely not. This is putting my child in harm's way. My child has a chronic illness
and it could affect her illness and make it worse. And I absolutely don't agree.
Can I step away from the fence for a minute?
Why?
So I can get through.
Okay, so police are now crossing locked fences without homeowner's consent.
Just do whatever they want.
And opening. Laura, do you give consent?
Those look like million dollar houses, actually.
82 million dollar.
Protecting the city. It's like a dictatorship.
Guarantee these women are listeners. We're gonna get them on.
Officer, do you feel comfortable with what you're doing?
No, he doesn't.
We're already saying they're not gonna be putting smart meters on your house, ladies.
So, Laura, you're the homeowner? Those two men that are on your property-
They take what they want. They always do in history.
Knowing that my daughter is chronically ill and this could affect her illness.
That's enough. The whole video's up there. There's a lot more of it. And you can go read
the article here. The Chicago Tribune is very excited about wanting to put this woman in
jail.
Illinois, cuz that'll teach the slaves. Cuz people are part of the ruling class. This
is fun to route us. It says, Illinois, citizens still being arrested for filming police despite
court ruling which blocked unconstitutional law. So in your own property, you don't film
God.
Illinois citizens are still being arrested for recording police officers despite a Seventh
Circuit Court of Appeals ruling last year that blocked the enforcement of the law on
the grounds that it was unconstitutional. They say public filming is eavesdropping.
Following yesterday's story concerning residents of Naperville who attempted to resist utility
workers by speaking to them, invading their private property to install so-called smart
meters which have been linked with health issues. It emerged that one of the Refuseniks,
Malia Kim-Vandis, was arrested on attempted eavesdropping charges for recording police
officers during the incident.
They charge her for other stuff too. The irony of citizens being arrested for supposedly
eavesdropping on cops in public where there is no expectation of privacy while simultaneously
the government forcibly installs devices on people's property on record that do eavesdrop
and spy on everything you're doing in your home is incredible. We'll be right back with
a lot more It Gets Worse.
The
New Year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
You prepare by purchasing gold, food and firearms, but if you don't have a home security system
then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection. When you're
sleeping or away from home, who's watching out for intruders? Check out SimpliSafe. It's
a new do-it-yourself home security system that is completely wireless. Go to GetSimplySafe.com.
SimpliSafe is independent and off the grid. It runs on battery power so even if the grid
goes down, you're protected. It's completely customizable so you can use it in your home,
business, boat, trailer, storage unit or shed. GetSimplySafe.com. SimpliSafe is also ridiculously
easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes so there's no need to let a stranger into
your home. If you move or need to relocate, you can take the system with you wherever
you go. You aren't always at home, but SimpliSafe will stand guard protecting your property
24 hours a day, 7 days a week. Again, that's GetSimplySafe.com.
There's an old saying in Tennessee, I know it's in Texas, probably in Tennessee, that
says, fool me once, shame on, shame on you. Fool me, we can't get fooled again.
He aligns himself with the truth and it's time for you to choose a side. You're listening
to Alex Jones.
All right, we're going to be joined here in just a moment. He's sitting around next to
me by Dr. Jerome Corsi, a WorldNetDaily best-selling author, worked with the State Department and
other intelligence agencies. He can certainly speak to Benghazi and the whitewash there.
Several zones that Communist Chinese are setting up, Inside America, NAFTA and GATT, expanding
the North American Union, the gun grabbing that's going on. We're gonna talk about all
of it with him in just a moment.
But first off, I said I would announce this a few weeks ago, I've just been too busy,
but it is the biggest contest we've ever had. And it is for $115,000, our new film contest,
$115,000, first place $100,000 cash prize, second place $10,000, third place $5,000.
And then you will be in a pool in the running to have Infowars.com and our news operation
finance your film to then put it out not just on the Internet for free like I've done with
all my others, but what we've seen Dinesh D'Souza and others do, putting them in theaters.
Now I've always known how to do this. And it's not that I shrink from work, it's just
that I know the model, I have a lot of Hollywood contacts, as people know. And so that is going
to be the plan. Now they may shut everything down by then, but regardless, $100,000 sounds
like a lot of money and it is.
The biggest contest out there is Doritos, it's 100,000. So this is the biggest contest
next to Doritos, Twin Peaks up there. And with the other 15,000, it's the biggest. But
for the bang for the buck Liberty films that are put on YouTube, whether they're three
minutes or two hours, that's the rules between three and two hours long.
It can be history, it can be drama, it can be fiction, nonfiction, Gena 21, Second Amendment,
you name it. I'm gonna talk about that at the bottom of the next hour when Dr. Courtney
leaves us. He's with us for the rest of the hour and then half of the next hour. And I'll
play the special video announcement that will be posted in the next 30 minutes or so up
at Infowars.com.
I'll play that four minute announcement for everybody up at Infowars.com. So that press
release and more coming in T-minus about 56 minutes from now. That will go live at prisonplanet.com
and infowars.com. And again, for $100,000 or $115,000, they'll probably be 500 films
made. A couple hundred of them are gonna be excellent.
A few of them will be off the chart and it'll be a win-win. Everybody that enters is gonna
be a winner, cuz you get the word out about The Globalist. This is Operation All Revere.
And the Bombay doors are open. We're over The Globalist. We drop the bomb, the info
weapon, in T-minus 55 minutes and counting. We're gonna turn loose the power of the people.
This will be our 22nd contest. We've already paid out over $150,000 over the years of these
contests. We're gonna do that basically all in one fail swoop. And then you'll have a
chance to be part of the production of three films a year, big films and over a dozen smaller
films.
We've put everything into this fight. So keep buying the books, the videos, the t-shirts,
the propure water filters at infowarstore.com. Keep supporting our sponsors. Keep spreading
the word because we're taking those Federal Reserve notes in and turning it right back
against the enemy. Wars cost money.
And the reason we've been so successful is we have history, we're dogged, we're focused,
and we are putting the money back into the fight, not into private jets. Okay, so that's
what's happening here, ladies and gentlemen. Now, Dr. Jerome Corsi joins us here in studio.
He received a PhD from Harvard University in political science at 72. And he's also
currently a senior staff reporter for WorldNetDaily. He's had a whole bunch of number one best
sellers like Unfit for Command and others.
And again, he's had five number one New York Times best sellers, I guess. He's just amazing.
And he also worked in security and other highly classified areas for the State Department
and for unnamed intelligence agencies. And he joins us here to break down what's happening.
Doc, before we get into Benghazi, before we get into agenda 21, before we get into the
total rush that's happening and Feinstein saying titles of nobility to government people
to be exempt from gun laws even after they're out of office and police.
Before we get into all of that, what do you make of airport terror announcements now in
hotels, highway checkpoints here in Austin now looking for terrorists while the borders
are wide open? I mean, they are really accelerating things. What's happening?
Well, I think it's a whole clamp down, the whole decision by the government to get as
much information on the populace as they can get. I mean, you gotta remember, it wasn't
just the Nazis confiscated guns. The Nazis were experts in censuses and getting people
to tell them what they owned, where it was.
When the Nazis came to take the Jews away, they could say, where is that bracelet you
described in such and such a census? And you said you used to keep it in this drawer, where
is it now? I mean, it got down to that kind of specific information.
Everyone just loves submitting.
And submitting, people say, we gotta fill out all these forms, we gotta do all these
census reports. And by the way, Alex, I never worked as an employee of the government, I
worked with these agents.
You were a consultant.
Consultant, I just wanted to make that clear so people didn't think I was misrepresenting
anything I've done. I'm always precise on that.
And you've worked in finance for some of the big outfits.
25 years in finance for banks around the world and still have all my securities and insurance
licenses.
Well, we know all the real agents actually aren't in the agencies.
It's better not to be in the agencies. But anyway, look, the whole purpose right now
is to collect information. My corporations, we just got forms coming from, I believe,
the Census Bureau or the Commerce Department, all kinds of detailed information.
My point was, you worked high level in the State Department in security. Tell folks,
since we never brought that up, what you did do in that area.
It was a period of time I was working with some top psychiatrists here, actually in Dallas.
And we went into the State Department and trained State Department personnel on hostage
survival techniques. This was right after the takeover of the embassy in Tehran.
I spent almost two years doing high level work on survival of terrorist incidents and
developed protocol for the State Department and the State Department employees around
the world.
A lot of that information is being used today. I developed a computer model that predicted
the outcome of terrorist events, published it in an international journal of conflict
resolution at Yale.
My point is, you can really speak to Benghazi. That's why I brought all this up. I mean,
we've even got General Boykin coming out. Let's get into that now.
Well, I mean, first of all, the Benghazi issue is one that we have to, first of all, figure
out what they were doing there. And what they were doing, as far as I can figure out, Stevens
and the others, is they were, it was another kind of fast and furious operation bringing
weapons into Libya.
With the ultimate intent, they were gonna end up with Al-Qaeda. And a lot of those weapons
today are ending up in Syria. The same weapons, if we could track them, I would believe the
weapons that were brought in by the US government through Libya-
Well, that's what the former head of Special Forces Boykin, General Boykin's saying.
I think some of them were used by the Mali Al-Qaeda terrorists in that attack. But if
we could find and track those weapons, you've got-
Why would the State Department want, because they had a huge weapons cash at that safe
house.
Yes.
And then why would for eight hours the White House be caught lying? We now know, order
a stand down. Were they trying to get rid of people after the transaction? Or was it
a double cross by the Al-Qaeda security they hired to run Benghazi?
Well, see, first of all, I think there's so many games going on on this. First of all,
Stevens, you remember, came into Benghazi when Gaddafi was in power. He came in through
a cargo ship or something. He kind of snuck in.
Tripoli.
Yeah, Tripoli. He came into Tripoli, ended up in Benghazi.
Yeah, the Commando invasion.
And was funding and providing weapons to eliminate Gaddafi. So these people who ended up killing
Stevens were actually funded and gotten weapons to them and to their allies. But then now,
see, Stevens is turning on them. We realized we're missing maybe a million weapons. We
don't know where they are. And Stevens is trying to find out where those weapons are.
Al-Qaeda was taking and shipping those weapons into Syria. We're beginning to find out these
weapons are-
Well, of course, the West wants that. They're running the whole attack.
And in fact, it's the same thing as we did in Fast and Furious. We provided the weapons.
The weapons ended up in the hands of the gun cartels. Look, I just did this big expose
on HSBC Bank. HSBC Bank doing major money laundering for the Mexican drug cartels. They
just paid something like a billion dollars in fines on the information that we helped
to develop.
It comes to the final realization, look, we are the drug cartels. You don't money launder
a billion dollars of money, bring it to the Tijuana branch in $100 bills and having it
put into an account without the federal government knowing about it.
When I take $1,000 out of the bank, they act suspicious and ask me what I'm doing. I get
the big argument with them. It's none of your business. I mean, they won't even let Gerald
Salente get 10,000 out.
The idea that we're preventing terrorism, and we're running the terrorist operation.
They get the law to know everything about your business and collect the data.
So just like Fast and Furious was to be blamed on the Second Amendment to take that away,
they give Al-Qaeda all these missiles, let them take out the Syrians, then we gotta take
your rights cuz there's 10,000 heat-seeking missiles missing.
Exactly, and we've gotta make sure that we clamp down on guns in America because look
at the violent level.
And now they're saying Homeland Security is now for guns, not for Al-Qaeda. It's for the
gun owners, it's for the libertarians, it's for the conservatives, it's for the returning
veterans.
See, we're gonna be defined as anyone who doesn't go along with the agenda, anyone who
objects, anyone who raises questions, immediately you're on the suspect list.
How do we respond to that? Because again, I mean, you've been there at the highest levels
of the system in banking and in consulting and everything. You've written books that
brought down your major presidential candidates. You're a big insider. You don't say that,
but let's just admit you are, Dr. Corsi, Jerome Corsi.
Where are we going? Cuz I see this as a Vichy French sympathizer takeover where the foreign
banks are like the Vichy French. The generals stand down, they turn America over to it,
and that's what I see. I mean, they admit it.
Well, first of all, Alex, you're doing a great job. And we at WND, we work with you, we support
you, we think you're doing a great job. We're on the same team. The first job is you're
exposing, you're calling the agenda and you're opening people's eyes.
So what is the agenda? I mean, do you concur with my analysis?
The agenda, absolutely. The agenda is complete domination of the American people. It's totalitarianism.
This is the-
And there's no doubt now. It's 100% naked.
This is the left, it's most bald ever running to the finish line.
I mean, yeah, I mean, every instinct I've got is get out of the country.
They're saying, next we'll take your property. I mean, the whole agenda here, collectivism.
You don't own that. The government-
You didn't build that.
We didn't build that. We own it. We need this to redistribute it. The whole plan of getting
people out of their houses-
Okay, well, I've studied the 1917 takeover, as you have. From everything I know, they're
using that plan. And I'm not just saying that for theatrics, you've got the floor. I want
you to break that down. From everything I'm seeing, they're planning to try to start a
civil war and call him Lincoln.
It is always the same plan. The plan is disarm the people. The plan is call the people the
terrorists. Get information on the people. And then divide, find out which is the group.
Is it gonna be the Jews? Who's it gonna be this time? There's a scapegoat group that
has to be collected. It's gonna be the white militia.
They're now saying that.
It's gonna be anyone white who still believes in Jesus Christ and professes religious.
Wow, they actually say that.
Sure.
No, it's in the manuals.
This is the plan. These are the people that are gonna march-
No, no, no, no. The peer's pressure thing article actually said, let them get ready.
We're coming for you. And the communist Chinese are gonna help. That's Newsweek. It says Newsweek
on the byline is saying they're that confident.
Well, look, the whole plan of the United States being bankrupt. I just wrote a short book
on the power pivot theory. That it's a plan to bankrupt the United States.
Yeah.
And with the Chinese owning as much of our debt as the Federal Reserve owns, they're
one and two and competitors. China is saying already, we'll take equity instead of the
debt. We'll manage your ports. We'll take land. We'll have occupation zones within the
United States that we create as free trade zones.
I wrote an article this week in WND where China is buying oil rights in the United States
that George W. Bush prevented China from doing with the UNICAL deal saying it was a national
security threat.
Now today under Obama, China's signing left and right, oil and natural gas deals. Well,
we're still dependent on foreign oil.
He won't let us develop, does everything he can to block it, while giving huge swaths
to the-
China.
China just bought the biggest oil fields in Texas, hundreds of thousands of different
acres. I can drive 20 miles and show you Chinese owned areas.
And China just made a big deal, bought one of the major companies in Canada, which owns
rigs in the Gulf of Mexico, in US territory. China is going to own and operate those rigs.
China is gonna be essentially producing oil out of resources while we're buying oil and
natural gas, especially oil, on foreign markets.
It makes no sense at all. Why are we buying foreign oil and letting the Chinese? Well,
because again, the plan-
That's why they gave them the Panama Canal. That's why they give them all the industry.
That's why, I mean, this is so diabolical.
Take a look at this little ebook I wrote. I wrote two ebooks, I think are very important.
One is on Saul Alinsky, the evil genius behind Obama. And the second was on the coward pivot
theory, which is the plan, Obama's plan to bankrupt the United States. That's what it's
called.
These two sociologists came up with the conclusion the only way to transform America into a socialist
state was to bring it to its knees economically by overloading the welfare of the welfare
state with obligations that could not be met.
That's the plan. Look at the Daily Peace article. It says we need the Communist Chinese government
to tell us what to do. This is globalism. We've got to get Americans ready to have our
TV foreign owned like current TV.
Somewhere Alex Jones is readying his flamethrower. Let him. And they go on to say we're gonna
use the minorities and basically racial division and we're gonna use women. They're actually
admitting what Rush Limbaugh finally said yesterday, they want a race war in this country.
Look at how the campaign was run. Obama ran a race war campaign. Saul Alinsky, the rich
are not paying their fair share. So you flame the economic resentment, get all the minorities
to feel the white majority has stolen your money. They made you-
And have Obama raise taxes on poor people, so they're hurting even worse.
Well, and again, it's part of the plan to bankrupt everybody.
Yeah, exactly.
Because under the lie that he wasn't gonna raise taxes, he did raise taxes, 87% of the
workers in the country.
Yeah, exactly. It's so diabolical. It is so diabolical.
Lying, lying, lying all the time.
So how do we stop them? Because I mean, this is a real Soviet style takeover.
Yes, in fact-
John Brown just came out and said Obama only is faithful to the Soviet Constitution.
In fact, go back and ask, what has Obama done for the African Americans? Look at the unemployment
rate among African Americans. What has he done-
They've been hurt the worst.
The worst. Look, what has he done for the youth who have voted for him? Highest unemployment
rate, the slimmest chances of jobs of any generation that we've ever had in America.
These are the Obama zombies that in college-
And he re-legalized US funding for basically forced abortions in China, where they give
the women money if they get aborted.
And kill the babies left and right, force women to have abortions in China. China, look,
you go try to bring a Bible and profess the religion of Jesus Christ in China, you'll
be in prison. China-
But I mean, Doc, even though I know all this stuff we're going to break, I can't believe
it's really happening.
The Bank of China has had meetings with the United States government. The plan is set
for China to transfer its debt into equity, own parts of the United States, manage-
That's official.
It's official. The meetings have happened.
That's why they said in the People's Daily a month ago, you will take the guns.
The meetings have happened.
So they want the property, they know we're going to fight.
And China wants to disarm the United States before this plan is implemented.
We are being conquered by the globalists leveraging China.
Absolutely. China wants us to have no weapons.
I mean, this is so- and I want to talk about the military.
It's a plan. The Howard Piven theory, Obama's plan to bankrupt-
A Soviet globalist comming plan. We'll be back.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not going to want to miss this exciting message.
Here's why. Our solar generators provide life-saving electrical power. And unlike gas generators,
solar generators run quietly, emit no fumes, and produce electricity from the sun. So when
the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part. Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't
sell as new. We put them in a special spot in our warehouse, and we discount them heavily
at the end of each year. We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like
new. Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait. They go fast. Go to scratchanddentsolar.com. That's scratchanddentsolar.com. For the craziest
offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com. That's scratchanddentsolar.com.
Feeling like there are too many pressures and demands on you? Losing sleep? Worrying
about tests and school work? Either you're on the run because your schedule is just too
busy? You may be under too much stress, and it may be affecting your mind. Get your mental
edge back with Neutropic Mind Power from mindregard.com. Neutropic Mind Power is not a drug, but a
natural supplement. Its 12 powerful ingredients are natural and non-GMO, plus it's gluten
free, wheat free, and formulated by Americans for Americans by an NSF certified laboratory.
Neutropic Mind Power is available at mindregard.com, spelled M-I-N-D-R-E-G-A-R-D.com, and comes
with a 100% money back guarantee. Free your mind with Neutropic Mind Power, a cognitive
supplement from mindregard.com. Mindregard, clearly see tomorrow and yesterday, today.
It's time for a home security quiz. Answer this. What effective home security device
is smaller than a coffee cup fakes out burglars into thinking someone is home at your house
while you're away, plugs into any wall outlet, is recommended by many police departments,
and sells for less than $35? Yes, it's fake TV. This year, about one in every 50 US homes
will have a break-in, with burglars usually picking the easy target, a dark house that
looks like no one is home. Fake TV is a small electronic security device that makes it look
like someone is home watching TV by simulating the light from a real TV. It's like a lamp
on a timer, but far more convincing. And for only $34.95, fake TV could be the difference
between coming home to a secure house or one that's been ransacked. Go to faketv.com or
call 1-877-5FAKETV. That's 877-532-5388, or go to faketv.com. Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
No matter how hard you try, you can't stop us now.
Folks, the reason I keep talking about since yesterday, this Piers Pressure article that
I came out January 21st, I didn't see till the 24th, is that I haven't had time to read
it on air yet. And it says, yeah, we're getting rid of America, we're getting rid of sovereignty.
We're going under globalization, new world order, and the gun owners are gonna have to
turn their guns in. And the communist Chinese, thank God other governments are gonna help.
I mean, it's everything I saw in the weatherman trials, going back and seeing the old footage
where they plan to bring in the Chinese and all this. And it sounds crazy, here we are
30, 40 years later, and they're really gonna try it. I mean, and I believe they're gonna
fail, but there's gonna be a civil war.
Ron Paul agreed last week with us on air. Countless others, every analyst I've talked
to, let me ask you that, Dr. Corsi, best selling author here in studio with us. Hey, how are
things going for them? They're teamed up with China, that much is clear. Do you think they're
able to actually execute this?
How do we defeat them? What is the timeframe? Well, first of all, exposing them is critical.
What you're doing every day is critical. The timeframe is now, it's immediate. The plan
to bankrupt America is ongoing today. Cloward Piven theory is in-
22 billion to ship General Motors overseas.
Not to read the Cloward Piven theory, I wrote it out in this little ebook. And it explains
you bankrupt the United States by overloading welfare with demands that welfare can never
meet, including Obamacare, including, wait, they'll take the student tuitions and forgive
all those loans.
It's all designed to bankrupt.
All designed to bankrupt. China has had meetings, China wants assets. And see, the New World
Order people say, well, China's the future. Why? Cuz China's communist, but they combine
capitalism under communism and a model-
And the elites are exempt.
Then the elites are exempt. The elites get to lead a privileged life with weapons, go
into any federal building. What do you find? You find armed guards, you go through metal
detectors, all your property is searched. The federal government's gonna be well protected
and they're gonna have weapons everywhere.
And they're gonna take our weapons because China does not wanna take over the United
States with an armed citizen.
It's unbelievable. And they're planning to just have a slow motion red dawn with all
the infra, and give China tax incentives, as they've announced, in these free trade
zones where no one can compete.
Look, I wrote about, you've even got Governor Perry back with Sintra rebuilding the parts
of the trans Texas corridor.
That was super highway.
Super highways. They're coming back in with toll roads. They're under the radar. They
signed something like $20 billion.
Everything is bankrupt. How is it going for them?
Done incrementally so you can't see that it's happening in little pieces. It's going well.
I mean, Obama reelected, they've got a socialist agenda set out. They got the Republicans on
the run. What's gonna stop them is the Second Amendment and the American people finally
waking up and saying no.
And Alex, you're playing a big role in this. Every day getting the information, we at WND,
every day getting the information in front of the people, the truth. Look, I just wrote
about the fact of oil. We are selling to the Chinese oil rights throughout the United States.
For nothing.
For nothing. And George W Bush would not, remember, UNICAL was gonna be taken over by
I think 2005.
And that's what government land is all about, so they can just give it away.
They can give it away.
I remember 15 years ago reading about the UN World Heritage sites where they admitted
the buffer zones, hundreds of thousands of square miles around it, was being pledged
to the national debt. And who owns the debt?
China wants to manage the ports.
China.
China wants to manage the ports. They're managing the ports right now.
No, that's the deal. We'll use your dollars for slave goods our slaves make with suicide
nets around the factories. But you give us the Long Beach and the Panama Canal and the
infrastructure and the oil.
The Panama Canal, China is. They're managing the zone.
Everything, everything.
Tanzania. They're ready to manage Los Angeles. And they want free trade zones in the United
States where communist Chinese can come in and set up business.
This is a takeover.
It's a takeover. It's a step-by-step takeover. And it's happening. And our debt is giving
China the leverage they need to demand assets.
And in the global issues, our military, what's left of it, has the leverage point to keep
the commie Chinese in line.
We don't have to have a military. China has one.
We'll be right back.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, Almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late. I can
warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com
slash Alex and build your food supply. It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable
food on the planet. Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods
Direct.
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. Big brother, mainstream
media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN
Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Big things afoot here in Texas. You know, Dr. Corsi, I'm noticing there's like a gathering
in Texas. It's also happening in other states like New Hampshire, but everybody is really
moving to Texas and the globalists see Texas as the resistance to their new world order
takeover. And I know they've got to get the guns, but I think as the founders said, you
won't need the Second Amendment until they try to take it. As Thomas Jefferson said,
elaborate on what you mean by the Second Amendment is going to save us. And you were telling
me during the break, people are finally starting to get it. This has been great banter we're
having.
Well, I think, first of all, the broadcast you're doing, at WND, getting the word out.
People are understanding that, oh, it's a conspiracy theory. It's not a conspiracy.
It's a conscious plan to bankrupt the United States, conscious plan to take away our freedoms.
You get the Patriot Act coming in after 9-11. You get now the, you know, terrorism is expanding,
so we've got to be able to take guns away, school killings. All these fear elements end
up in taking fundamental rights from the American people while we're being indebted to China.
And China wants the assets. The new world order people, communist socialists, say China's
the future cuz China is communist, but they've figured out, you know, the Obama people-
Well, they're really just slave masters.
Capitalism, they're slave masters.
Yeah, yeah, communism for the slaves, palaces for the controllers.
I mean, you know, Obama gets, you know, multimillion dollar vacations.
$10 million vacations, red carpets, they're the new Hollywood.
And celebrities, and, you know, so does Nancy Pelosi. You go into a federal building, you're
gonna have to go through a metal detector. Your property is gonna be looked at. They're
all gonna be protected, the federal government, by guns and weapons. And by the way, they're
not part of Obamacare. Nobody in the Senate and the House is part of Obamacare. Nobody
in the Senate and the House will be part of any gun restrictions. When China comes in-
Unbelievable.
China comes in-
And the Trans-Texas Corridor was the first salvo in this. And out of it, look, China
is still managing the Panama Canal. They're managing these ports in Mexico like Lazaro
Cardenas in Manzanilla. China wants ports. The Bank of China has met with the federal
government. They've said, we want assets now for our debt. We'll get it. And the coward
pivot theory drives this. Because the coward pivot, two sociologists who had a plan, they
bankrupt New York in the 70s with this idea, overloading welfare. So capitalism crashes.
You blame capitalism. You reconstruct socialism. Let the Chinese come in and show us how to
do it. The Chinese understand capitalism the way it works. And we're just being prepared
for it.
The discussion today in the Senate about guns is to sensitize people. Remember, same sex
marriage. 20 years ago, people were offended. Now everybody's desensitized. The same with
a gun takeover. You introduce the idea. You show Newton, all these school. You wanna protect
the schools, put armed guards in them. That's what they do in the federal buildings. It
works for the federal.
Federal buildings are not no gun zones. The federal troops have federal officers in every
House and Senate-
But how do you beat it when they've got all the illegal aliens voting and everything?
What they don't have is you've got the people of the United States, those left in America
who understand that the founding fathers created-
We have to get aggressive and realize how much trouble we're in and go after them politically,
legally. People have got to make this a full-time deal.
And take it seriously.
Yeah, this isn't a joke.
It's not a joke. I mean, this is now when pre-prepared, all these, the census data,
the data about filling out all this-
The smart meters watching everything you're doing.
They're collecting data right now to know where everything is. So when they come to
get the guns, they all say, well, give us the one you got in that closet. You registered
it. We know you've got it. Hand it over. You know, this is where the information-
And they know when people fight back, then it'll be, oh, there's a new terrorist threat.
All we want to do is register the guns. What's wrong with that? Well, as soon as you've registered-
Then they take them.
They know where they are.
They go, but you can keep your bolt action. Now Australia is banning bolt action.
Well, and again, what's an assault rifle? Well, the assault rifle is going to be anything
they decide is an assault rifle.
That's why they're now saying, oh, it's handguns too we're going to ban.
Anything you want is an assault rifle. And again, the Second Amendment was designed for
this very situation for people to stay there.
We got to talk about what the Second Amendment was designed for with Dr. Jerome Corsi coming
up, and then we'll get into all the other huge issues taking place right now.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu, and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them. Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad
spectrum antibacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver
solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold, and food poisoning,
and help improve wound healing. Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day,
while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph,
pneumonia, colds, flus, and other harmful pathogens. This new technology has the ability
to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness
of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter. It is virtually
non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today
and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off. That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like
us on Facebook.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
The New Year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and
make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver. Supernatural Silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification. It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system
support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance. That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Again, it's Friday, the 25th day of January, 2013. We've got Dr. Jerome Corsi here with
us for another 25 minutes or so and then he's got to leave and get on an airplane. Again,
he is a Ph.D. from Harvard University in political science. I work with the State Department
and other agencies in highly classified areas as a consultant and of course has written
five New York Times bestselling non-fiction books, many of them number one and he writes
for World Net Daily and he's got a bunch of ebooks out right now.
And yes, there are a lot of different sociologists and that's how communists operate during the
infiltration phase because they want to bankrupt things, then blame free market and they get
so many dependent they can take over. Now, Doc, we've had great banner, everybody's saying
powerful radio earlier, but I want to be able to now just sit back and have you recap everything
you've said that this is the global mega banks, anti-free market with the socialists and the
communists.
To recap last hour, leveraging with the communist Chinese using limited capitalism where they
exempt themselves from the rules, basically modern slavery to take over and how we beat
them and what we're facing and how they use the drugs, how the big banks are behind that.
You wanted to talk about that. I'm going to just sit back now. You've got the floor.
I mean, there's so many. First of all, I want to start out with the Second Amendment. I
want to say this about the Second Amendment. Second Amendment was written for a time like
this. It was written for a time, you know, Revolutionary War was when the British were
taking everything over, British making a final play to dominate the colonies.
And the militias then at that point, people being armed were critical. An armed public
today, Second Amendment is a powerful tool. It's why it's being attacked. It's critical
to maintain. Now, the next thing I want to say is, look, and Alex, we are the drug cartels,
the government of the United States. You got the NSA, which is reading everybody's emails.
Now, you mean to say, and I showed and published with John Cruz, the whistleblower, the information
about HSBC money laundering, money coming from the drug cartels. That has to happen
with the US government knowing about it. You mean Treasury, Federal Reserve, NSA, CIA didn't
know that Mexican drug launderers were driving into Tijuana with a truckload of $100 bills
sitting in the high net worth area, drinking espresso while that's being processed into
the bank and shoveled all over the world on behalf of the drug cartels.
We facilitated that. I've talked to the Air Force and Army officers who sit there with
the surveillance blimps and the aircraft, and they're told let that through, let that,
stop that. Why do we have more heroin coming out of Afghanistan
today than when the Taliban ran Afghanistan? Again, we are the drug cartels. We are the
gun runners of the world. Fast and Furious was just the tip of the iceberg. You mean
guns are being run worldwide and the NSA and the CIA doesn't know what's happening and
can't catch anybody. It's nonsense. Drug cartels penetrating into the United States. You mean
we're able to sell billions of dollars, I'd say the drug business may be a trillion dollar
business-
It is.
To drug addicts in the streets of Colorado and every other city of America, and the CIA
and the FBI can't find them?
Well, I mean, Wells Fargo with Warren Buffett got caught laundering $378 million two years
ago with Wachovia.
The major profits I think today being made in the banking system worldwide come from
money laundering. The money laundering laws that are out there are not to catch the drug
cartel.
They're to harass us.
They basically permit the federal government to track everything you're doing in the bank
where your money is. Make sure you're not using any cash. The catch who's being caught
with the Patriot Act are legitimate citizens who just do one or two things wrong.
No, no, no, I know someone in Texas who has a successful business, no criminal record,
and over two decades had saved up a couple $100,000 in cash, went to put it back in the
bank-
They'll be harassed.
Or was arrested.
Yeah, right, exactly. And see, but yet you come into Tijuana with a truckload $100 bills,
hey, you're a preferred customer. And that money is gonna pass right through the entire
system, gonna come through banks. HSBC was money laundering in Long Island.
We had the data stealing people's social security numbers, creating false accounts, running
millions of dollars through these false accounts, closing the accounts. So there was no trace
of them. We turned the information, John Cruz, the whistleblower, I wrote about it in WND.
We went into the Department of Homeland Security in New York, turned over this information,
turned it over to the Congress.
And nobody was doing anything until we started publicizing it, writing the articles about
it, exposing it. I've exposed HSBC in India, all around the world, HSBC is a criminal bank.
It's engaging in these activities. And if HSBC wants to sue me, hey, I'll save them
the problem.
But I mean, wait a minute, it's in the news. It's in the news that all the big Federal
Reserve member banks and others have been caught.
Laundering money. They are laundering, it's the only way the drug business-
That's why they keep it illegal to keep the price up.
You can't have a drug business if the governments don't cooperate.
Now doctor-
It's the same with the guns. The guns are the same. The federal government wants a monopoly
on the weapons so that they can put the weapons where they want them.
And selectively arrest us.
And selectively arrest us if we dare have any. But they'll be happy to get them in the
hands of Al-Qaeda. Where does Al-Qaeda get the weapons?
Missiles.
Let's track the weapons that were used in Mali. Let's track the weapons that are used
in Syria. And find out they track right back to the state department.
Now let me bring this up since you said that. People always in the mainstream media spin
it. That I'm saying, and this is a quote of Chris Matthews, that Bush was at the towers
with a plunger.
Bush is a teleprompter reading puppet like Obama to many levels. Though Obama and more
and more we're learning is actually enjoying what's happening and in there running some
of the things.
I've always said criminal globalist elements are financing and using Al-Qaeda as a pretext
to menace us into slavery. And as a pretext to bring in a police state and look at the
homeland documents. It's all about returning veterans gun owners. I mean, don't I get an
apology from the national conservatives out there who spun it?
That I was saying the whole government was doing 9-11?
I would say forget about it. The issue is that you're right in tracking the information
and getting it out. This is, apologies whether you'll ever get-
Sure, sure, I don't even want that. My point is, is I'm saying there's a criminal globalist
element in the government using Al-Qaeda.
We have a criminal government. Our government is running drugs, permitting it to happen
and running guns.
And running Al-Qaeda.
And running Al-Qaeda. We are the drug cartels. We are Al-Qaeda. This is a fundamental-
You know 100 miles into the Texas border, all over the state, anywhere I have to go,
they have border patrol checkpoints. And when I pull up now and they go, I want to search
your car, I go, you know the government ships the drugs. And they go, all right, you can
go. I mean, they all know it.
And look, Al-Qaeda right now, we have a group of expatriates out of Libya. They've been
sending us information. Al-Qaeda has taken over Libya.
They fly the flags there.
And they are, in fact, raging a tribal war where they're killing other tribes that were
favorable to Qaddafi. We're not saying, we've got to use this doctrine to protect people
as the UN go in.
Well, they're ethically closing the blacks.
Because as long as Al-Qaeda is killing people, our government's gonna stand down. I mean,
the whole Arab Spring was a takeover by the Muslim Brotherhood of all these countries,
one after the other.
So where's it all going? How do we beat this?
Well, again, exposing it is fundamental. People waking up and understanding that we've got
a criminal government. It demands investigation. When you were calling for investigations,
Alex, you need to have you on the investigating committee.
Get some Warren Commission that you get the State Department and the Justice Department
saying for the first 24 hours, we gotta make sure Lee Harvey Oswald's found as the culprit.
Paper over it. Put the critics on the investigating committees, give them the power, and let's
prosecute the federal officials.
How about Nancy Pelosi? How about Barack Obama? In terms of criminal activity-
Rand Paul said bare minimum, Hillary should have to step down. Obviously, the White House
has been caught lying.
Quit lying. I wanna know, for the eight hours this embassy was under attack and we had drones
there, do they sit and watch it in the State Department House?
Of course they did.
Do they go to bed and let our people die in the field over there? While in fact, we had
Al-Qaeda attacking and we were running drugs. We'd rather have those ambassadors die than
admit they were there with guns that were run, that was a cache of guns that were illegally
brought into the United States by the United States headed to Syria.
If they didn't die, we were gonna expose our own gun running. So the White House and over
in Pentagon and CIA, they watched them die rather than call in military-
And ordered the CIA torture base down the road to not help.
And stand down. Some of the, I believe at least two of them, the government official,
the military that were there dying in Benghazi, basically violated orders and went in.
That's right, yeah, the Navy SEALs-
Navy SEALs violated orders, they weren't gonna stand for this. They were there begging for
help. They were calling in trajectories, giving target locations. Well, that was because the
drones around there had to be armed.
For eight hours, you had up to 500 people with anti-aircraft guns cranked down to the
ground, firing into the building.
What does Obama and Hillary come? They say, it's because of a movie. Again, using the
incident to try to quash free speech. They were insulted over this movie.
Well, they recycle everything they do to attack freedom.
Attack freedom, it's all back on attack the United States citizens. Take the guns away,
take the First Amendment away, and use any incident that happens.
Let me ask you this, if we don't stop them studying this worldwide, reading their own
white papers, their own sociologists, where does it go if we don't stop them?
If it doesn't stop them, we might as well read Nazi Germany again, cuz we're gonna be
the victims in another Nazi Germany. There's gonna be no place to go.
These are authoritarians.
Yeah, and let's let Congress know that if Congress doesn't listen, everybody in Congress,
we vote out. Anybody who's there, we just vote out.
It's time to be freaking out. I mean, this is openly-
And demand hearings, demand investigations, press the information. Every day, Alex, when
you're out there, showing people what's really in the news, your audience, what we're doing
at WND, this is an extremely important function.
Get the truth, the trans-Texas corridor, when people realize that they were gonna take four
football fields wide to Texas, and give it to Spain to develop as high-
That's globalism.
And finally, Texans came out of these meetings, they told Rick Perry and the Texas Department
of Transportation, they could shove this plant.
But six years later, like a roach, he creeps back.
Come back, it's constant vigilance. Jefferson was right, constant-
And anyone who approaches the jewel is an enemy.
And they will target us as the enemy.
That's fine, we're committed, we're going all the way. We'll be back with a final segment
to talk about the new royalty. Stay with us.
Coming back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought, to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all of the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared ten years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e Foods Direct.
Hey there, Frank Bates here.
Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out 280 million Americans?
This is really scary stuff.
Defense experts warn that this odd device poses the greatest threat we've ever known.
In fact, just a few weeks ago, former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed
piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat.
I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up.
That's why my friend just created a free video at weirddevice.com that exposes this threat
and blows the doors off the conspiracy.
Go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover exactly what it is plus
discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack.
I'm not sure how long this video will be online, so go to weirddevice.com before it's gone
forever.
Again, that's weirddevice.com.
Stop the pain from broken, chipped and damaged nails and eliminate toenail fungus with a
revolutionary new nail hardener, Nails of Steel.
Just apply one drop of Nails of Steel over natural or polished nails and go.
With Nails of Steel, there's virtually no drying time and it's guaranteed.
Apply this all natural, antifungal and herbal formula for women and men.
Call 816-896-8307 or get free shipping at nailsofsteel.com.
Nailsofsteel.com.
It's like a salon in a bottle.
We the people grow cotton, wheat fabric, engrave ink, embed strips and fibers to protect from
counterfeit and carting to a private bank, having it lead back at interest, forcing taxes
to service debt.
This capitalism or was Jefferson correct when stating a central bank issuing the public
currency is a greater menace to the liberties of the people than a standing army?
Hi, Ted Anderson.
I'm placing a silver dollar in a book explains our monetary system.
Call for your copy, 800-686-2237.
It's time to understand the system.
Call 800-686-2237.
That's 800-686-2237.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the president could obtain this world-class healer.
Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of super bugs with 17 naturally
occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune
cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VenusFly or order from Carnivora.com, that's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VenusFly or visit Carnivora.com.
Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
Final segment with Dr. Jerome Corsi, he's got a big book coming out in a couple of months
exposing just the death panels that didn't exist and that they now are saying are so
great.
It is just unspeakable how evil these authoritarians are and it's not authoritarianism for domination
because they have some grand plan to help people.
The globalists, I've studied them, really hate humanity.
They're very unhappy, nasty people, but you mentioned something earlier I wanted to flesh
out here.
Here's the weekly standard and it is in the new bill, Feinstein Gun Control Bill to Exempt
Government Officials.
And I have the Huffington Post here with one of the police patrolman associations in New
York saying, well, we need guns to protect ourselves from criminals.
So the police now under this federal bill are saying, well, we're gonna take all of
your guns, but we'll still be able to have guns to protect ourselves cuz criminals won't
follow laws.
This is new titles of nobility.
This is what our founders fought because the police and all former feds, just like you
said earlier, Congress exempts itself from Obamacare.
Exactly.
I mean, that is so discriminatory.
Obama gets to have all the vacations he wants, travel anywhere he wants to go.
Look at how Nancy Pelosi flies around.
This is all, they have their own health system in Congress.
They have their own lifestyle, their own parking lot, their own restaurants.
It's a scenic cure for life, pensions forever if you're in for one term.
You know, look, Alex, this entire plan, the entire attack on God, that's what my new book
is on, the ACLU.
It's on the plan to remove God, it's called the Bad Samaritan.
Gloria Steinem wears shirts saying, I got an abortion, it's beautiful.
We're celebrating abortions.
Now the next thing, if we're celebrating abortions, the next plan will be to celebrate the killing
of the old.
You must not watch a mainline new TV.
No, no, no, the sexy thing is to talk about how ugly old people are and how great it is
to kill them.
Right, because they're useless.
They're just wasted, they're old, they can't do anything, they can't contribute, kill them.
But at the same time, all the groups that are supporting Obama, all the leftist-oriented
groups, the minorities, are being used as dupes.
Nothing is in return to them.
Go into the-
Obama won't even go talk to them.
Remember what Maxine Waters said.
Go to the African-American communities, look at the highest unemployment.
Look at the biggest crime and drug use, dropouts from schools-
Exploding.
Families.
What is any federal government doing to, you know, the-
Chicago, where the dawn runs, thanks.
Go into Detroit.
Take a look at the comparison, it's circulating in the Internet, between Detroit and Hiroshima
at the end of World War II.
Hiroshima is a thriving community, Detroit, under socialism, is devastated.
That's the future of America under socialism, Detroit.
Go look at it.
No jobs, the jobs to China, everybody in poverty, everybody facing either go into the drug-
And when I say to socialists that are mid-level and really mean well, they go, everything's
gonna collapse, austerity, you wanna kill old people, and meanwhile it's the eugenicists
saying they're gonna kill the old people.
And my book, this whole thing, gotta look at the Cloward Piven theory.
The plan is to so bankrupt the United States with new entitlement programs, Obamacare,
you've got, you know, all the food stamps you want, well, they'll roll out entitlement
after entitlement, because the idea is we'll never be able to pay for them, we'll be bankrupt,
and the collapse of the United States, they'll blame capitalism, then they'll open the door
for the Chinese, the Chinese will own the debt, and the socialists-
They already do.
The Chinese know how to run capitalism, we'll just use the Chinese system.
Constitution's an old document, we've already had the Georgia-
They're already saying that in the Piers Pressure article, do one on this.
This article says we need to do what the communist Chinese say, read it, and then I'll be dealt
with.
And that's gonna be for everybody right here.
Actually, did you see Piers Morgan say he wants to shoot me?
Yes, I saw that, I saw the entire series-
Have you been around the so-called liberals privately where all they were talking about
is killing people?
Look, the whole agenda is a death agenda, it's killing babies, how are we gonna celebrate
killing babies?
Killing old people.
How could the free market pay for everybody, and now socialism, nothing can be paid for?
In fact, look, people don't understand, this is not an economic downturn we're in.
This is a created, manipulated, structural unemployment, where even if the economy improves,
the jobs created are in China.
They've doubled the food stamps, that's on goal.
They've had increasing dependency on the federal government.
And they're saying, and they've even got Rand Paul going, we've gotta adapt or die, that's
psy-op to make the Republican Party just the right wing of the left.
The Republican Party and the Democratic Party are essentially one party.
It's a psy-op.
It's one party.
People are rejecting socialism.
And people have gotta continue to reject socialism.
People have gotta start taking strong measures, demanding-
And it's time to start-
Federal investigations.
I agree, but isn't it start to not complying as well?
It's also, first of all, the Second Amendment is fundamental.
People have got to retain their guns.
The Second Amendment was created for times when tyranny is on the run.
And it's here.
It's here.
And it's here, and it's on the move.
You know, our founders are fighting for us from the grave.
And we've gotta listen, because the words that they gave us, the instructions and the
tools are right there.
First Amendment, Second Amendment, and we've gotta demand the federal government as a criminal
government running drug cartels-
Tell you what, come back and do five more minutes with us in the big announcement.
I want you to finish up plans to turn this around.
Okay, fantastic, here we go.
We're on the march.
The empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver-based products.
Our most popular silver-based products are the 32-ounce nano silver solutions, our 2-ounce
nano silver nasal applicators, as well as our all-natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and
leave the silver at the surface, but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the
natural skin-nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the
skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver-based products
are best for you.
That's www.silverlungs.com.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At eFoods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarshop.com.
These are items that I did research on that I personally use.
You've got the LifeStraw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor Handcrank Generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out
in the field.
Strategic Relocation, third edition by Joel Skousen.
When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein.
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Handcrank shortwave AM-FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com
and your purchase makes our info war possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you?
Infowarsshop.com.
Live from Austin, Texas, broadcasting worldwide.
It's Alex Jones.
Here's a surprise, tyrants.
We can see you.
We can see for miles and miles and miles and we know your playbook.
We've been warning people for decades and now that we're coming down to the wire, people
are going, wait, Ron Paul, Dr. Corsi, Alex Jones, G. Edward Griffin, countless others,
Bob Chapman, the list goes on and on, Lou Rockwell.
They all warned us about this and exactly what they said is now happening.
They told us 10 years ago the smart meters were going to hook into all our electronics
and track us in taxes and surveillance and the government said it was a conspiracy theory
but now it's admitted.
Well, wait, Alex said the NSA was spying on us 10 years ago without warrants, non-terror
related.
Now they admit it.
Alex said that it was really for the American people, Homeland Security.
Now it's admitted.
Again, it's all happening.
We've got a chance to beat these people if you realize they're really bad people.
They're not misguided liberals, environmental wackos.
I wish Rush Limbaugh would stop saying they're idiot wackos.
These are, cuz I've been in hundreds of their events and they always come over when the
cameras off and punch you in the arm or grab your shirt and say I'm gonna get you.
One day we're gonna get you.
I'm sure that's happened to you, Dr. Corsi.
In closing, we've got some huge news coming up after you go.
Kissinger predicts nuclear war with Iran, infowars.com.
Holder begins gun control push trying to raise money for the Democratic Party on the back
of it, fireside chats, assault weapon ban lacks Democratic votes to pass Senate.
Don't think they won't have another shooting, ladies and gentlemen.
Now that is just some of the stuff we've got here.
We're gonna make the big announcement on the $115,000 biggest contest ever after he leaves
his operation, Paul Revere.
That's going live with a red link right now at infowars.com and we'll post it to prisonplanet.com
as a backup.
But doctor, we've had great banner for the last hour.
Other points you wanna add about solutions, I just wanna first get your take on this.
Look, if this is real, I mean, you're more steeled than ever knowing it's real.
We've talked privately.
It's now all manifesting, our worst analysis being proven right.
Again, people better take this serious.
What can you say to police and military?
I'm talking to police and military, and they're either totally waking up, and the majority
of them are, or they're deciding to just sign on to evil.
How will the system deal with that?
Well, the police and the military have got to the oath keepers, the whole plan to reach
out and say, look, because the new world order will turn on the police as well.
They always do.
But if they don't sign on, they'll be equally victims in this.
But again, Alex, it's a plan.
The Obama plan to bankrupt America.
Your book.
That's what I've been pushing that people to read, you understand that once we are indebted
to China, we can't tell China to stay out.
Once you've sold current TV to Al Jazeera, Al Jazeera owns the airwaves.
That's globalism, have foreigners come in and buy everything.
And I wrote a book America for sale.
I warn people, you're gonna be reduced down to living in the safe places where you can
find to live, burying your guns, having food to live, and even that's not safe.
How long are you gonna last?
No, they know we've got the food.
But people can understand what you've been saying is true.
Fast and Furious occurred from the top.
It was a administration concocted plan by Eric Holder to take the guns away, to attack
the Second Amendment.
They have these guns show up at events, killings and murders and say, look, the guns are being
sold.
That came out in the memos.
It was out and he tried to get the truth.
The memos won't be released.
The testimony, even Hillary's testimony, lying testimony, testimony where Hillary did not
say, where are the 25 people who survived Benghazi?
Why can't we talk to them?
What was the White House doing and the CIA for the eight hours of this attack?
Were they watching it occur and not sending in the military to save our troops?
Why do the two SEALs have to essentially disobey orders to go to protect Stevens?
Again, what were the guns we were running there?
You do not launder billions of dollars through HSBC for the Mexican drug cartels.
All admitted, fines now out there.
We've been publishing it in WND without the government knowing-
The cartel leaders said in trials, hey, we have a national security pass.
We were doing this with the government.
We are the drug cartels.
We are Al-Qaeda.
We're arming Al-Qaeda.
We're arming the drug cartels and you've got to have, let's have criminal investigations
of Hillary.
Let's get the documents.
Let's demand the documents.
Why are they so bold?
How could they publicly use Al-Qaeda in Libya and Syria and then go on the news and say,
you got to give your rights up.
Al-Qaeda got weapons in Libya.
Well, the compliant press with Piers Morgan, with all these other people, Piers, bring
the foreigners in here and have them lecture to us on gun control.
They actually says that and they're going to get me.
Yeah, exactly.
And the whole idea is avoid investigation.
That's what the government wants to do, no memos.
Where are the memos and the investigation on Ben Gotti?
Take the head of the EPA when they caught her using a dummy email.
HSBC, let's have a hearing.
How did that happen?
And the Federal Reserve and didn't know about it.
Why won't the Congress do it?
Blackmail threatened?
Look, the Congress is part of the deal.
Congress is being offered the lifetime royalty, as you say.
They've got their positions.
The Democratic and Republican Party are basically in agreement.
And now they're offering the cops lifetime royalty.
Take the people's guns.
You can keep yours after you retire.
Cops, if you believe that, you're idiots.
And just as believing the fact that if we let them go on this one, why don't we have
a Watergate style investigation of the entire Obama administration?
I agree.
They admit, it was done 1,000 times what Nixon did, 10,000 times.
They admit it's the cops holding up, going after the guns, cuz the cops know they're
gonna have their guns taken and the cops know it's gonna be a civil war.
Cops better protect us because the cops are next.
That's the point.
The Communist Chinese would be happy to come in here with their military and tell the local
law enforcement, we don't need you anymore.
Well, they'll tell them, turn your guns and then they're gonna kill them.
But look, you've got the NSA.
The NSA can read your emails, read my emails.
You mean they couldn't read the emails of HSBC laundering money?
They couldn't read the emails of the drug cartels coming across the border?
They couldn't read the emails from Ambassador Stevens saying, we're not protected here running
guns without kind of taking over.
You talk to a lot of corporate and government people, are they concerned right now?
Increasingly, because again, the corporations, the whole idea is, well, corporations will
be fine in globalism.
They use all the labor from China.
So they don't need American labor.
American labor is useless.
It's a detail.
Don't need expensive American or European-
Don't all these rich people know they're gonna get double-crossed?
That's the whole point.
You're not gonna be safe by being ignorant.
They're idiots.
You're not gonna be-
The governing class is gonna slit their throats.
And this is the big move towards globalism.
It's the one chance where they think if they can just bankrupt the United States, eliminate
the military, step by step, China will move in.
We become a colony to Communist China.
We become the globalists.
That's why Dinesh D'Souza's film gets it wrong.
It's not that Obama hates nation states and is an anti-colonialist.
Well, no, he does hate nation states.
It's that this is a reverse colonialism of the globalist and collectivist governing class
to get rid of the nations and create a giant world government.
Even when the Georgetown professor says the Constitution's an old document, ignore it.
Because they think nation states, God, they think God is old.
How is D'Souza's film wrong?
Well, D'Souza's film is wrong in that we want to colonialize America.
Obama-
That's right.
America's been colonialized by the globalists.
Obama doesn't mind colonialism as long as he's the one doing the colonizing.
Exactly.
It's a total lie.
Globalism is corporate colonization using communist methods.
Let the banks do it because the banks will control the money.
If England thinks it's going to vote out of the EU, they're not going to get a chance
to do that.
That's not going to happen.
The EU, again, bankrupting the EU, bankrupting-
And their own documents admit it was designed to bankrupt.
It puts more power in the hands of the global bankers who want to say, we'll be just fine.
And the EU bureaucrats are all exempt from the taxes.
Look at the money.
Same deal.
The only money in the United States today is held by the Chinese of the richest country
in the world.
The drug cartels have more money than the corporations of the federal government.
The federal government has been intentionally bankrupt.
A criminal takeover.
Criminal takeover.
It's a criminal takeover by the globalists of the federal government.
And they're just criminals.
That's why they use criminal tactics.
Obama is heading a coup d'etat from within.
A criminal cartel, foreign criminal cartel coup d'etat.
We are, the United States government is the drug cartel.
We are the drug cartels.
We are Al-Qaeda.
We're funding Al-Qaeda.
We're putting guns- Again, the criminal groups that have come in and hijacked are.
Right.
And killing Qaddafi.
I mean, Obama, why did Obama turn on Qaddafi?
He'd come in and worked with him.
Qaddafi funded Obama through Louis Farrakhan.
Reverend Wright met with Qaddafi.
He funded Sarkozy.
That's even come out in the news.
And then Obama turns- They double-crossed their own guy.
Grew Qaddafi to the wolves because he had Al-Qaeda coming to the floor.
Al-Qaeda's taken over all the criminal groups- Which, again, is Saudi Arabia.
The whole idea- That's the deal.
The whole idea this Arab Spring- Turn everything over to the Saudis.
Only more of the Muslim Brotherhood, the radicals, taking over all of North Africa.
So it's Saudi Arabia, the communist Chinese, and the mega banks all teamed up against any
country they don't control.
Any country they don't control.
And bankrupting the United States people, making the United States people feel like
if they don't get their social security checks, look at the number of people that are on the
verge of bankruptcy in the United States.
Number of people facing losing their homes.
The plan is to take the homes away from Americans.
And nationalize that.
Plan is to reduce Americans to poverty.
And this whole Claubert Piven theory is a conscious attempt to bankrupt the United States
in order for globalists to gain power.
It's domestication for slaughter.
Dr. Corsi, you've got to go catch an airplane.
We're going to have you back on very, very soon when the new book comes out.
In fact, I want to tell Weldon Henson back there over our department.
I want to carry- Bad Samaritans, bad Samaritans, you'll have
it.
I want to carry all your new books.
All right, Dr. Corsi, thank you for being with us.
Alex, you're doing God's work.
Keep it up.
Thank you, sir.
Wow.
Ladies and gentlemen, he's got to leave us to go get on an airplane.
There it goes.
Dr. Corsi will help him get unhooked in here.
And just amazing times that we live in, absolutely amazing times.
And I've studied history.
I became obsessed with history when I was about 10 years old and became a good reader.
And I've studied communism, fascism, socialism.
I've read the books of Dr. Carol Quigley, the books of the White House Science Czar,
the books of the Rockefellers, their foundations, their statements, everything that they stand
for.
And their game plan is 100% public.
So when people ask, how do I know that TSA was coming to Austin?
Well, they've announced they're gonna be in every city, and now they're here running checkpoints
on the road.
I also have my police sources.
I mean, people ask, how did I know they'd start putting smart meters on with armed police?
Well, they announced they would.
How did I know they would start double and triple charging during peak times with smart
meters?
And then smart meters would dial in to all the new appliances 15 years ago.
And now it's just happening, cuz it was all MIT documents.
You can't go buy a dishwasher now, or any major appliance that doesn't have Bluetooth
or wireless hookups, TVs, you name it, with cameras on them, dialing in through the smart
meter, watching and listening to you.
I mean, it's beyond 1984.
Cancer viruses and the vaccines, thousands of documents, sterilizing people, killing
people.
I mean, we're living in a stinking nightmare, but it's all scientifically rolled out.
And 95% of the government people in corporate don't know all this.
That's why they haven't killed me.
Because it's all a joke, go listen to that loud Texan.
Wouldn't you be loud if all this was true and you knew it?
Well, it is true.
Of course I'm upset, man, I'm on the front lines of this thing.
And if you'll just get out of your stinking coma, we can turn this thing around.
Now I wanna make a big announcement, Roger, I have to skip this network break.
You know what, I'll make the announcement with this video, and then come back and make
some other comments.
The video just went up at infowars.com with the contest details and rules.
It's all up at infowars.com right now, red linked in the featured news area and at prisonplanet.com.
Infowars launches operation Paul Revere.
Here it is, this will be a huge blow against the globalists, here it is.
If you are receiving this transmission, you are the resistance.
Fellow freedom lovers, Alex Jones here with the biggest contest announcement we've ever
made.
This is so incredibly exciting.
We are launching operation Paul Revere.
What did Paul Revere do?
He rode through the countryside in New England saying, to arms, to arms, the redcoats are
coming.
One is by land, two is by sea.
And all that evil men and tyrants need to flourish is that good men and women do nothing.
Let me officially announce operation Paul Revere, a $100,000 cash first place winner
to be judged by yours truly, Alex Jones.
The film can be three minutes, it can be up to two hours.
It can be fiction, nonfiction, documentary, drama.
It's got to promote liberty and freedom and expose tyranny and oppression.
And it's not just people in the US that can enter, it's folks worldwide.
The rules, the details are at infowars.com forward slash contest.
You have to read the rules and officially sign up for this because it's a $100,000 prize
first place, $10,000 second place, $5,000 third place.
But just as I did last year with a reporter contest, we are going to crowdsource from
the pool of incredible talent out there and hire several official crews to be directors
and writers and camera people in infowars.com produced major films and documentaries that
will be put in movie theaters and on cable and I've got all the connections to get it
done.
So we're going to really give the new world order hell.
This is extremely exciting.
I've made over 20 films, one of them alone has reached more than 40 million people on
YouTube and Google Video.
The Obama deception, Endgame, Father of Public, Road to Tyranny.
Films are the most effective thing I do, but they're very time consuming.
And so I want to turn the power of we the people loose here and your art, your research,
your ideas are unstoppable.
We're officially kicking the contest off this Friday and you've got a little more than three
months until April 30th, just a little more than three months to produce your documentary
or your film and get it out and it will absolutely reach tens of millions of people.
Our normal contest get about 500 entries.
That's what $10,000 prizes.
This is 10 times that 100,000 for first place.
That's one of the biggest contest out there.
In fact, it's the biggest next to Doritos that has $100,000.
This is huge, ladies and gentlemen, $115,000 in cash prizes and a shot to have your film
produced and financed by Infowars.com.
Edit it, upload it to YouTube and one other alternate public video site and send your
entry to Paul Revere at Infowars.com.
The animating contest of liberty that Thomas Jefferson talked about is happening right
now.
The modern battlefield is in the mind more than ever.
We use truth, the globalists use lies and deception.
The corruption and oppression and high tech police state is in our face, but the controllers
are scared.
They intended to use the Internet to dominate and control humanity and surveillance, but
we've turned their system against them.
This is a historic crossroads that we have reached and I ask you to ride in the year
2013, just as one of the founders of this republic did back in 1775.
I'm calling you to arms in the Infowar because the pen and the video camera is mightier than
the sword.
Let's go in there and rescue humanity and awaken them and set brush fires in the minds
of men and women everywhere.
Be part of this contest, you've got three months, put your hat in the ring.
Be part of the solution to the corruption and oppression.
Be part of the resistance to tyranny.
We're looking for the Paul Revere's that will drive a stake for the New World Order's wicked
heart.
All right, we're going to break and when we come back, I'll give you more details of this
and then I get into some of the other news.
But again, I'm even shaken up right now by how fast this is moving.
If you're a new listener and you're going, what is this all about?
Read history, read about tyranny.
That's what it's all about.
Okay, now, there will probably be 1000 entries to this, this will probably reach 100 million
people.
This will be the best 115,000 ever spent.
All of you win by entering the contest.
Get involved now, infowars.com has it red linked at the top.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not going to want to miss this exciting message.
Here's why.
Our solar generators provide life saving electrical power and unlike gas generators, solar generators
run quietly, emit no fumes and produce electricity from the sun.
So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part, every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't
sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of
each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait, they go fast.
Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
Digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of toxins.
That bears repeating.
And ProEM-1 daily probiotic cleanse is the key to digestive health.
ProEM-1 is a powerful liquid probiotic, strong enough to cleanse, gentle enough to use every
day.
ProEM-1 is dairy, wheat and soy free, contains all natural and certified organic ingredients,
contains no preservatives or animal products, supports a healthy digestive and immune system,
supports weight loss, improves absorption of food nutrients, aids in controlling yeast
infections, is never freeze dried, and uses three groups of live viable beneficial microbes
to cleanse and remove toxins.
Order ProEM-1 daily probiotic cleanse at teraganix.com, spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X.com, teraganix.com.
Or call toll free, 866-369-3678, that's 866-369-3678.
ProEM-1, the raw probiotic.
We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration.
An authorized Berkey dealer for over six years and serving thousands of satisfied customers,
the Berkey Guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration systems.
The Berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable black purification
elements that purify water by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria, cysts and parasites to
non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides.
Order the Berkey light system today, complete with two black Berkey elements for only $231
and the Berkey Guy will ship your order free of charge.
With the purchase of a Berkey light, the Berkey Guy is also offering a set of fluoride and
arsenic filters for only $39.99.
That's over 30% off the retail price.
Call the Berkey Guy at 1-877-886-3653, that's 1-877-886-3653 or order online at goberky.com.
That's goberky.com today.
Your own personal Jesus, someone to hear your prayers, someone who cares.
Your own personal Jesus.
Monday through Friday, 11 a.m. to 2 p.m. central.
Again, any historian would look at what's happening and would say, my gosh, we're going
into total fascism.
But it's really eugenics, eugenicism, I've got to come up with a word for this.
It's a technocratic hell.
And everything, once you study it, is a psych warfare program to get you to submit to them.
And to get you to take on the idea that you're guilty.
I mean, look at these headlines up at infowars.com, you're a radio listener.
Airport terror announcements now being played in hotels.
And the article by Paul Watson and myself, we wrote this article together this morning.
Paul's already written three articles today, I don't tell him to do that.
He's passionate and works about 16 hours a day, because he understands how bad it is.
And when he's very clean cut, his family are very nice, well-spoken people that look even
aristocratic almost.
And they go out in London and walk down the street, the police walk over and ask who you
are, line up, you're a terrorist.
It's when you look handsome or smart, you're the enemy, okay?
It's when you care, the enemy senses it.
If you look like a zombie, that's how I know how to infiltrate things, cuz I can pull it
off.
I can actually get in the mode of a low IQ and gonna, and then the system doesn't even
notice you.
They hate you when you're strong.
And people like Watson and his brothers will be out with their wives or girlfriend, depending
on which one.
And it's just always the police come over and line up, gonna ask you some questions
that happened to me when I was in London.
And this is how they operate.
And they told me in England, they said, don't be here at the tube station, out on the street
at the entrance.
Don't ask people questions here.
Move along or we'll have you thrown out.
They do that to people that are born in England.
England's not a free country anymore.
Paul Watson knows that.
So he sits in his house, 16 hours a day conservatively, some days 18, fighting the New World Order
at a computer.
Because he understands and he doesn't like being a slave.
He doesn't like that it's getting worse every minute.
He doesn't like the oxygen is leaving the room.
He knows, it's like the old swashbuckler archeologist movies that came out in the 30s, 40s and 50s
that Indiana Jones Raiders of the Lost Ark is based on.
Where you're in the temple and the water's coming in rising up, you've got to get out
of your debt or the walls are coming in on you or sands pouring in.
We got to get out of this.
And I'll be driving home looking at the trees, looking at the moon, the beauty of the world,
loving my wife, my children.
I don't want to die.
I mean, I know there's a probability they'll kill me or put me in prison.
I mean, I wish I wasn't right.
I wish I wasn't having to be up here launching a huge contest with hundreds of films to defeat
the enemy.
I wish I didn't have to be so effective because you know how dangerous that is?
I destroyed Piers Morgan, the proofs of the pudding.
They won't have me on any other shows.
They're scared to death.
Because they know I'll shake people out of their coma, not because I'm anybody special,
but because I am primitive.
It's a primitive response.
They don't want you in your normal response to being oppressed to go, I'm not your slave.
They want you to just go along with it, comply.
Now is the time to get involved.
Now is the time to take on the globalists.
Now is the time to decide for what you serve, evil or good.
And by the way, if we defend liberty, all the prosperity will come back.
That's the thing.
All of you that are part of the power structure and think this is going to be a beautiful
dark ride and you've got these visions of yourself with all these powers of the state,
you're going to wish later you'd not been part of this.
Everybody be part of this new film contest at infoawars.com, $115,000.
You are listening to GCN, visit GCNlive.com today.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as stress, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and
other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network and now live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
I want to look at the mass shootings in this country that have slightly increased the last
20 years.
I say slightly increased because they're still incredibly rare, but it's one of the only
violent crime statistics going up.
In fact, we can reload those statistics from FBI.gov that Melissa Melton collated in that
slide show when Armistice Ben Fuchs joins us.
Because I was listening to his show, I think it was Tuesday or Wednesday.
And I actually sat in the car because I used to get ready at home.
I sat in the car as I was driving into the office and I only got here about 40 minutes
before airtime, but I sat there for about 10 minutes wanting to listen to what he was
saying.
Cuz I've interviewed so many brain surgeons, endocrinologists, different scientists, that
I knew everything he was saying was true, it was just reminding me of it all.
But he was putting it together so concisely and I said, can you come on Friday, I'll talk
about this when we come back.
I said, can you send me something on drug interactions with SSRIs or SRIs and mass murdering
and killing?
That's what he sent me, all these documents and articles and inserts as a pharmacist,
a compounding pharmacist, one of the most successful in Colorado, he was a mainline
pharmacist before that.
That guy looks 20 years younger than he is, but I got some other questions about allergies.
I wanna ask him after that, cuz I've been on longevity steadily, but only a few of the
products.
I've never been a big supplement person, I'm just not in the habit for about a year and
I've lost about 25, 30 pounds.
It was about 40, but I gained some back cuz I never remember to do it all.
And my muscle levels gone up, standing there naked in my bathroom, I look a lot better
than I used to.
But the muscle weighs a couple times more than fat, so there's been that conversion.
But what do I do with supplements?
By the way, a university study on the M4's health supplements here that just came out
from Yahoo Finance, just about how amazing they are.
This is groundbreaking stuff, I wouldn't be promoting it.
And my mountain juniper, they call it cedar allergy, that plagues half of Austin on average,
has gotten so bad living here for 20 something years, since high school, 22 years.
And most plants pop during the spring or summer.
This thing goes off in the winter, December, January, February.
It's so bad this year that I'm talking about going to Seattle or Miami Beach or somewhere
for those months to do the show next year, because it's a living hell.
So I wanna ask him, are there supplements?
What can I do?
And I've just gotta get religious, cuz every time I do what he says, it works.
Look at Aaron, lost 95 pounds without going into one of those clinics and taking speed.
My wife's had dramatic response, my mother, my dad, if I will just follow this, then I'll
have a great response.
So I'm gonna come back and get into the shootings and how he recommends people are able to phase
off of serotonin reuptake inhibitors, cuz going right off of them, the inserts tell
you, that'll make even go more daffy duck where he bounces around and shoots off into
the atmosphere or over the horizon.
So I'm no medical doctor, the medical doctors we've had on, and the psychologists, psychiatrists
have said that are awake, do not go off East cold turkey.
Whatever you do, I'm not giving that advice, that's what they say.
I'm not giving any medical advice here, I'm just going off the research and what I would
do.
So we're gonna talk about the mass shootings, how to get off of it, and then natural things
that the, by the way, the FDA wants to ban, that in the placebo studies I've seen five,
six, seven, eight, ten times more effective in some cases.
And it's not just melatonin, so also good news for people that are depressed or whatever.
So this, we're all about solutions here, so that's why he's gonna be joining us.
And also, we're gonna do some midair refueling, when you buy the quality, longevity products
discounted at the lowest price available at mfowarshealth.com or mfowarestore.com.
You get stuff like free shipping when you sign up for auto ship, you can sign up and
pay 10 bucks, get discounts to be a distributor, get distributor prices, wholesale prices.
When you do that, it funds mfowars operation, so we can have $100,000 contest, people to
make films to wake up America, operation Paul Revere.
So the funding that comes in lets us continue and expand and do more aggressive stuff in
the face of the new world order.
Because if I'm gonna get killed fighting these people, which I hope doesn't happen, knock
on wood, pray to Jesus, I'm gonna go all the way.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support.
And it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action.
Tyranny is here.
The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality.
It really says that the state is God.
The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most oppressive police states
on earth.
This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being
expanded nationwide.
This documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all
powerful shadow state.
Police state four chronicles the sickening depth to which our republic has fallen.
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship, body scammers, sound cameras,
citizen spies, stage terror, and cameras on every street corner.
It's only the beginning of the new world order's hellish plan.
The police state isn't coming.
It's here.
Secure your copy today at infowars.com or see it online in the highest quality at prisonplanet.tv.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At E Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my E Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on E Foods Direct.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable, long-term, storeable, long-term,
long-term, storeable, long-term, storeable.
of the New World Order are spreading across the planet.
Every form of tyranny is exploding into huge flames
and it's generating all that is good.
The general public is under scientific conditioning,
completely programmed. It's up to us not to laugh at them
or to even get angry with them. It's up to us to shake them out of their trance.
To shake them out of the spell. To awaken
the brush fires in the minds of men and women everywhere. That's why we've launched
Operation Awaken the Sleeping Giant
where you can get 11 prisonplanet.tv memberships
for the price of one, $5.95 a month. That's less than $0.59
per person per month. You can create a username and passcode, give it
to up to 10 more people. And that many can be simultaneously
logged on to see the nightly news, to see all my films, to hear the show.
We're having a huge effect already. But quite frankly, Operation Awaken the Sleeping Giant
is nothing compared to Operation Paul Revere
launched about 25 minutes ago, last hour
at prisonplanet.com and at infowars.com
Operation Paul Revere, Operation Paul Revere
to just absolutely turn loose, tens of thousands
they have tens of thousands of entries for the Doritos contest
$100,000 for a stupid Doritos MSG ad.
Okay, this is $100,000 first place cash.
So you've got to jump through more stuff with the Doritos. It's got to air, it's got to get certain ratings
on the Super Bowl, sometimes it doesn't so you don't get all the money. This is just $100,000
I judge it. You've got three months to produce
the film. It can be three minutes long or two hours long. Three minutes to two hours
that's the area. It can be fiction, non-fiction. It's got to expose tyranny, promote
liberty. The rules are up at infowars.com. And all of you
will win by exposing the globalist. We're launching this right now.
All of us will win by resisting. Thousands of films are going to get made. It's going to flood
YouTube and one other online free video site.
Pick the other. Pick whichever one you want.
And just flood the internet. We all win. It's a giant rush.
It's Operation Paul Revere. Ride out as Paul Revere. I mean one example
of a film is you could dress up like Paul Revere and actually ride around in the city at night
warning people that tyranny is happening and handing out from horseback documents
about the new world order takeover. I'm not saying that'll be the winner. It's just there's unlimited
ideas. I'm actually planning to do that. I just if I get the time. I've got a thousand
ideas. I know how to bring these people down. I know how to turn you loose. You know
how to turn yourself loose. Operation Paul Revere.
Operation Paul Revere. Operation Paul Revere.
Operation Paul Revere. Launch. Dropped. And again taking
the capital that comes in. What's the best thing we can do? Launch a news program. Make
films. Come out with a magazine. Make viral reports.
I mean I get 15 million listeners conservatively
every week and that's growing. That's an old number. 140 stations.
Gaining a couple new ones a week. In fact I've got news stations I'm supposed to plug today. The week's gone by.
I mean it's incredible. We're having an effect. And with good cheer
I stand against the enemy. If they kill me or set me up or whatever
take care of my family. Keep the Infowars operation going. We've got a plan for that.
But don't. But understand that's a sign of victory against the enemy.
I hope that doesn't happen. The reason they have it is because they don't want to underline and highlight everything
I've said. The point is that this is a fight. This is the fight I was born for.
This is the fight you were born for. You're not meant to just watch TV and drink
beer all day and have a good time and then get euthanized at some government facility.
You're not meant to be some bureaucrat feeding on people all day. You're not meant
to live like this. You're not meant to put your kids on Prozac
and Ritalin. We're not meant to live like this. And this is the animating
contest for liberty. I'm not happy about the tyranny getting so obvious
because I know how dark it is. But you know what? If that's the case, good. It's now out in the open.
Okay.
We're going to go now for the balance of the hour to one of my favorite guests
and one of our listeners' favorite guest. He is
pharmacist Ben Fuchs. He was a mainline pharmacist for many years
until he saw what it was doing to people. And he's developed many
different products, different vitamin and mineral
systems, skin systems, you name it. He's the host of the nationally syndicated radio program
on GCN, The Bright Side. The Bright Side, again, is on GCN the hour before
I am. Fuchs is a registered pharmacist, nutritionist, cosmetic chemist,
and founder of the Ocono Comp Pharmacy and Rocky
Mountain Natural Laboratories. He's very successful pharmacist Ben.com
BrightSideBen.com. And I'll just recap this if you just joined us. I'm
driving in Tuesday morning. And I get ready at home. So it's
about 10 o'clock I leave. It's about 10.30 to get to the office.
I got to get in and do the show. I couldn't. I had to keep listening because he was covering what
serotonin reuptake inhibitors do to the brain. What SRIs do.
Serotonin, you know, just the basic systems.
He was breaking it down. And so I called him. I had Richard call him and I said,
I want to get you on about what you were breaking down because I've had all these brain surgeons and scientists on.
They said the same thing. You say it's so concise. Send me the documentation
on that. I mean, I already know it, but send it to me. So he sent me this giant stack
of inserts and documents and even mainstream news about
placebos doing better than Prozac for you. And then many natural things
really helping people that are depressed. So this is about
solutions. And this is how people can safely from the research
get off serotonin reuptake inhibitors and the natural things out there the FDA
is trying to block you from getting. Then I'm going to ask him about things that help with allergies.
But again, I also have this report and I'll show TV viewers a document
cam shot. Yahoo Finance, Alabama
International or AL International announces results
of Younggeviti clinical research studies performed by Clemson University
Institute of Nutraceutical Research. Unbelievable
findings and scientific double blind studies. And yes,
we'll also do some pitching here to fund the operation. It's a win win. I promote
what I believe in. I like government that takes your money at gunpoint that uses it against you and gives it
MSNBC or state run media out of Qatar coming in and
buying Al Gore's network to brainwash us. We're here saying, hey,
we believe in this. These products are incredible. Infowarshealth.com and he's going to go through
many of the things he formulated available at Infowarshealth.com that
have had unbelievable responses out there. Okay, so we're going to go over this
also talk about what he would do for, say, cedar allergy or really mountain
juniper, but they call it cedar allergy. I'm going to pick his brain about that.
And again, Ben joins us and I've got some of the questions. I said, send me
questions that I should ask so I can understand this better and for people. So let's
talk about the shootings. Let's talk about what SSRIs are doing
and other psychotropics and antipsychotics that roughly 20% of the country is on.
And then let's talk about, from his research, what has successfully
helped people get off these and actually helped people not be depressed
in this Orwellian system. What the FDA doesn't want you to know about.
Okay, so pharmacist Ben joins us right now. Thank you
for coming on. Thank you for having me, Alex. It's a pleasure. Okay, we're going to break
in about four minutes, so start getting into these chemicals, what they're doing, the inserts
say they make you mass murder. Why? The answer is give big pharma
more money, more access to kids to stop mass shootings always connected to these
drugs. Well, the most important thing, Alex, for people to recognize is that far
from the happy, bliss-inducing, joy-inducing neurotransmitter
hormone substance that serotonin is portrayed to be by the mainstream
media and by mainstream medical professionals, it turns out that serotonin
is a hormone of vigilance. It's a hormone of awareness. It's a hormone
that's designed to keep us on our toes, so to speak. It's a daytime
hormone that's designed to keep us able to handle the ups and downs and the
vicissitudes of day-to-day life. So when you start to monkey around with
this serotonin system, what you're monkeying around with is the awareness
system, and the end result of too much serotonin is hyper-awareness,
hyper-vigilance, paranoia, and this sense that
this hyper-focused sense that people have when they're freaking out.
Artificial schizophrenia. It's like a type of schizophrenia. In fact,
LSD is very similar to serotonin. It's in the same
class. Same class, basically the same substance. Basically,
it's the same molecule, and if you want to know what the effects of
too much serotonin are, the kind of effects that you get when you start to manipulate the serotonin
clearing system, which is how these SSRI drugs are,
think of the last time you saw somebody on some kind of LSD trip.
LSD was actually researched, was discovered when they were
researching ways to manipulate this serotonin system. So
serotonin is a neurotransmitter
that is involved with the vigilance response. Now, you obviously need to have this
vigilance response, but you've got to be very, very careful with it. In addition,
serotonin is largely produced by stress
cells in the digestive system. Your digestive system is always
on the alert for poisons and for toxins, and you have these stress cells,
cells that are literally similar to adrenal cells, that produce
serotonin, just waiting for you to eat some kind of poison or some kind of toxin.
Is that why Prozac is linked to diabetes? Prozac is linked
to diabetes for other reasons. We can get into that in a moment. That's
a very important point, but that's why Prozac is used as an appetite
medicine. Prozac and serotonin has an effect on the digestive system
that is much bigger than the effect that it has on the brain. In fact, 90%
plus of the serotonin in your body is actually produced by these stress cells
in the digestive system. So this feeling of butterflies in your stomach,
the feeling of nervousness that you have before you have a date or if you have stage fright,
these are all serotonin mediated. They are the alert response
that's produced by serotonin in these digestive stress cells.
In the brain, serotonin is involved in the wakefulness
response, and if you want to know what serotonin really does, think about melatonin,
which is the exact opposite of serotonin, and we all know that when you take
melatonin, you feel groggy, you feel sleepy, you feel relaxed. Well, serotonin does
the exact opposite. Melatonin is the antagonistic.
Alright, we've got to go to break, but from my research, because you're the big pharmacist and the expert,
other experts have told me, after you've been on these drugs a while, though, it burns you out,
and they put you usually on more, then you're in a hyper awake form
of sleep. You're in a dream state or daydreaming state,
but hyper awake, having a hallucination, and that's why people then go and use
a meat cleaver to chop up their one year old baby and drink the blood when the woman
is a Sunday schoolteacher. We'll be right back. Stay with us.
Wake up people in your area and support our operation
as we move to the next level. We need your help to spread the
word like never before. They wish to hide themselves during this
tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and
their program of global eugenics dehumanization and
ultimate extermination. The war is here. It's an info
war. The spirit of 1776
versus the mindset of 1984.
Hi there. My name is Frank Bates. What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds
could get me in a lot of trouble. I just created a free video presentation
at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are. Incompetent line
crooks that are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills
criminally high. Some have called this a conspiracy. Others
have called it a cover up and you will be shocked to find out how deep the
conspiracy goes. My video at 123coverup.com
exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them and how you
can beat them too. Watch the controversial video that thousands of other
smart patriots have already seen in the last three months. Go to
123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power
bill and protect your home. Go watch my video now at 123coverup.com
before they force me to shut it down. Again
that's 123coverup.com.
23coverup.com.
1-800-686-2237.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care
and is highly effective for water purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune
system support and it is also a perfect choice for your
emergency preparedness. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones
a fighting chance. That's SupernaturalSilver.com
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
And it's just incredible I forgot to tell you the Communist Party USA
who I've caught on video in New York some of their
reported members that's in my film Martial Law
just saying get out of here. And they went on to say you know we're going to
kill you like Stalin did and I've told this story and it's no exaggeration
let me just be conservative. 20 times I can remember or more.
I've had communists come up and tell me that when they take over I'm dead. I mean their religion
is how they're going to kill us. And so again that's
also at NewAmerican.com but up at drugsreport.com
communists cheer on Obama's gun grab
and there it is right there and we syndicate some of their
better reports and even had Bob Dacy one of their writers in studio last week
a fellow Austinite and it's got links to all of it
and to the official peoplesworld.org saying take our guns
Unbelievable information up at drugsreport.com
easiest place to find it because I think this is already scrolled off our featured news
from this morning. Which is a problem with Infowars. It's not a problem but
we're going to redesign Prison Planet as a test with a big official company
and then redesign some things and if that works then we're going to go to Infowars with a redesign
still the basic look that's popular. But if you go to the top of Infowars.com which we can punch you up
you'll see two links here. Breaking News that's the total
RSS news feed and I think I'm going to change that red link to the
top stories because the stories we write are the stuff that we think is most important
probably twenty or thirty of them a day depending on how many we put out go in this
and every five or six hours on average the top six or seven stories scroll
through
well I just noticed that the top story area
or he must have just written a new article about that
Infowars launches Operation Paul Revere
Kissinger predicts nuclear war with Iran, Sheriff refuses to
enforce unconstitutional executive orders in Arizona County
Airport terror announcements now being played in hotels
TSA conducts random checks at Austin train station
population control advocacy group, humans equal locust
Illinois citizens still being arrested for filming police in their own yard
for filming cops while they put a smart meter on their house without a
warrant, communist cheer on Obama's gun grab
that already has scrolled off the front page, Feinstein declares war on mill of rights
calls for American citizens to be disarmed or registered, urgent
big agri group trying to ban raw sales of milk in South Carolina
private sales, Muslim brotherhood propped up by the government
man who brought down Acorn tells all
the client sheriffs, just dozens and dozens and dozens and dozens of them now
standing up all over this great land from the north to the south to the east to the west
they're trying to say owning guns is a southern thing and trying to play us off against each other
New Yorkers and everybody else are coming together and saying how dare you bash people
in the south, we're all Americans, we're not hyphenated like you want us to be
we're not going to have a race war like you want, you're not getting our guns and I've seen so many
black folks and veterans mainly all over YouTube, I'm not even looking for it
I see like 20 really strong
smart, super well spoken, ought to have a radio show, black guys
just all over YouTube going on, we're not socialists, we're not globalists
we're not turning our guns in, we know what's going on, we know what's happening
we know the fraud, we know about eugenics, I mean it's exciting
it's exciting, okay I'm going to shut up and go back to our guest, Ben Fuchs
I'm glad Drudge linked to that because I saw that article this morning, I wanted to talk about it
look at all these stacks, I mean there's hundreds of articles, it's all insane
I'm going to cover a lot of special stuff tonight on the nightly news, we've got the reporters doing the news
but I'm going to have a special report on a couple things, Ben Fuchs
like this is your radio show now because I'm actually going to turn off my microphone and walk out of the room
because this gets me so angry and so excited that I'll start cutting into you
in the rest of this segment, get into the tryptophan
and the fact that they don't, you know what's in meat, they don't want us
getting that, explain to somebody on Prozac, I know you're not their doctor or pharmacist
but what you would do personally, I say Prozac, the whole class of dozens
of what is it 30 or 40 of these on the market or more right now, some numbers are over
70 but they're not quite in the same class, well you're the pharmacist, break down
what's not in our body, how they know this, why it says on the insert
could make you cause mass murder, have schizophrenic
mania, I've known women on it in college that were
every woman I knew on it was a nymphomaniac, I don't want to get into details here but I didn't like
that, I want the real woman, I want the real personality, not like some biological
android, what's, why does this, obviously they want more crazy
people so they want to put you on something that makes you crazy, what are things out there
naturally that would actually help people because of the deficiencies in this
toxic system, you have the floor, break it down. Well there's so many things, there's so
many ways and we'll talk about that in a second but I want people on SSRIs to understand this
the chemical imbalance theory of depression, the idea
that depression is caused by a lack of serotonin and that you build your
serotonin, you're not depressed, number one it's simplistic and naive and number two it's
never been shown to be the case, in fact drugs
that block serotonin have been shown to have anti-depressant activity just
as well as drugs that increase serotonin so please do not be fooled
by the simplistic idea that all you do is raise your serotonin levels
and you're not depressed anymore, that is drug company propaganda
that is marketing and advertising information that has never been
shown to be the case, that's first of all, what has been shown to
be the case is that elevations in serotonin, super high levels of serotonin
such as the kind that are caused by artificially manipulating
the serotonin system are associated with agitation, with restlessness
with diarrhea, with hallucinations, with fast heartbeat
serotonin itself, the very word serotonin
means sero for blood, tonin for tightening
that's because serotonin's classic effect is blood clotting
and hypertension, let me say that again, serotonin's classic
effect on the body is blood clotting and hypertension and it's in the
very name serotonin, now blood clotting and hypertension are two
iconic signs of the body's stress response
and given the fact that 80 million or more Americans are hypertensive
and some of the best selling drugs on the planet are blood thinning
drugs and among the most toxic drugs, so clearly blood clotting and hypertension
are big problems in this country, it seems to me that anybody who's considering
taking a drug that would manipulate serotonin levels, that would up
serotonin levels, that would increase the amount of this neurotransmitter
that's associated with blood clotting and hypertension would want to think twice
especially considering that this chemical imbalance theory has never been shown
to be the case, now what we do know is that serotonin is a hormone of
awareness, it's a hormone of vigilance, it is a summertime hormone
it is a daytime hormone, it is associated with
the sun and it's associated with light, which is why the best way to get
your serotonin is to make sure you're getting some sunlight and not only that
take your sunglasses off and make sure you're looking at the sun
the rays from the sun, the photonic energy from the sun will go through
your eyes, it'll go into your brain and it will help up-regulate
serotonin production, in addition Alex as you mentioned there's wonderful
wonderful nutritional strategies that you can use to up-regulate your
serotonin system, earlier we talked about how digestive
stress cells are called interochromatin cells, they're the largest
producers of serotonin in the body, one of the best ways that you can
make sure that your serotonin system is running cleanly is to eliminate
problem foods number one, and that means any kind of foods that the body will perceive
as a toxin, that is processed foods, that is things like excitotoxins
MSG for example, artificial flavors, and secondly
make sure you're addressing something called H. pylori
H. pylori is a bacteria that overgrows in the digestive tract
as we get older and as our digestive system becomes more compromised
as our acid production in our digestive system and our stomach starts to become compromised
this bacteria overgrows and that is a big time stressor on
the serotonin system, the digestive serotonin system, so addressing
your digestive system by clearing out H. pylori using things like apple cider
vinegar for example, digestive enzymes for example, probiotics
unbelievably important for supporting digestive health and supporting
the serotonin, the digestive serotonin system, then there's the supplements
that you could take, you mentioned 5-HTP and tryptophan, well
in order to understand the importance of tryptophan and 5-HTP when it comes
to serotonin, we have to understand a little bit about how biochemistry works
in the body, the body is always taking chemical A, turning it into chemical B
turning it into chemical C, turning it into chemical D, sort of like tinker toys
imagine when you were a kid you used to play with tinker toys, you stick a little piece in the tinker toy
and you create some kind of little constructive piece and then you put another
piece on and it's a different constructive unit that you've created
you put another piece on and you've created a different constructive unit and this is how chemicals
work in the body, well serotonin starts
off with tryptophan, tryptophan gets one piece stuck on and it becomes
5-HTP or 5-hydroxytryptophan, you stick
another piece on it and it becomes serotonin, but it all starts
from tryptophan, so you say well gosh tryptophan must be important stuff and you better
believe it's important stuff, not only is tryptophan critical for
making serotonin, but tryptophan is an essential
amino acid which means it must come in from the diet, you have
to be eating tryptophan and tryptophan is found exclusively
in high protein foods, you could find a little bit perhaps
in broccoli and asparagus and you'll find some in soy, but most
especially it's found in dairy and it's found in meat and it's especially
found in high concentrations in whey protein, in fact for anybody who's dealing
with SSRIs or wants to get off of SSRIs
the first thing you want to think about is getting yourself on some good whey
protein, a good whey protein supplement, if you can't handle it from a digestive standpoint
make sure you take it with digestive enzymes and a little bit of apple cider vinegar
just briefly tell us about that new product, tryptophan will boost your serotonin levels
but there's another way that you can boost your serotonin levels and that's by taking the
direct precursor to serotonin which is this stuff 5-HTP
now 5-HTP is unbelievably important and helpful
for people who are dealing with depression, anxiety, it's a wonderful sleep aid
it's a wonderful anti-apatite or appetite suppressant, it'll help you
lose weight, it's crazy cheap, it's like 10 or 15 bucks
for a 3 month supply, you take about 100 milligrams or 200
milligrams a night and that too will boost your serotonin, now when it comes to
making serotonin in the brain, it's not just protein, even though serotonin
comes from tryptophan, it's not just protein foods that help you
build serotonin, you actually have to have carbohydrate
with your protein, so you want to make sure that you're getting carbohydrates but you
want to make sure it's not super fast burning carbohydrates like
processed foods and soda pop and desserts, you want to make sure it's a carbohydrate that's got a lot of
fiber in it, especially vegetable carbohydrates, there's a big big
problem and there's an important relationship between sugar intake and serotonin
when you eat sugar, this is perceived biochemically by the body
as a major stress, sugar is very very explosive stuff
if you ever put a marshmallow in a fire and you see the marshmallow go poof
you can see how explosive sugar is, well in the body that same kind of
explosivity, that same kind of explosive reaction occurs
and so when you eat sugar, especially fast burning sugars, dessert kinds of
sugars, soda pop kinds of sugars, the body's stress response
is triggered and this stress response involves serotonin
in fact the hormone insulin and the hormone serotonin work
hand in hand and today we have a big problem, maybe the biggest
health crisis of all is something called insulin resistance and this is
when the body stops listening to insulin and going hand in hand with
insulin resistance is serotonin resistance and just like insulin
resistance will keep the body from listening to insulin, serotonin resistance will keep the
body from listening to serotonin, of course then you're going to go to the doctor and he's going to give you
an SSRI drug and all you really need to do is
reset this insulin system by reducing your intake of fast burning sugars
so you want to make sure you're having some carbohydrate with your protein, you want to make sure it's
fibery carbohydrate, you want to make sure you're getting enough protein, especially tryptophan
containing protein and you want to make sure that you're getting 5 HTP, now in addition
to all of this, there are co-factors that the brain uses, the body
uses to help make serotonin, chief among these is vitamin
C and the B complex, especially vitamin B6 and to a little bit
lesser extent minerals like zinc and magnesium, and that's why you need to take the Beyond Tangy Tangerine
and infowarshealth.com, I mean it's simple, my children act like demons
and I let them have processed sugar but when we are on the job and only feed them organic
and healthy food, they're little angels and everything's great, if I'm on the road
and I'm dumb enough to eat a piece of cake or something, I feel like I have a hangover the next day
going over this and people go to infowarshealth.com, there's many of the products, you and
others and Dr. Wallach have formulated and this is no joke folks
what would you, again we're not giving them the advice, they should, because it's
very dangerous to go off the serotonin reuptake inhibitors and we have a report
here, we're going to show people in a moment, what would you do
if you were say a 35 year old man or woman who's been
on psychotropics for say 6 years, they've got you on 3 of them
because the others didn't work and you don't know
who you are anymore and you're kind of eating a regular McDonald's
diet, what would be just the brief process that Ben Fuchs, and again my dad's
a dentist and oral surgeon, the people he respects more than anybody aren't
even doctors of people, it's pharmacists because he knows especially long time
master pharmacist, you guys kill people if you make a mistake and so
you guys really went to school to actually know what the drugs do, you know
I don't know 20, 30 times what doctors do, so that's why you're the
guy to talk to on this, what are the dangers of going off the serotonin
reuptake inhibitors or other anti-psychotic classes?
Well first of all we have to understand how serotonin reuptake inhibitors work, when the brain
secretes serotonin it immediately sucks that serotonin back up again
so the serotonin will get released and then it will get uptaken
it will get sucked back up again into the
nerves so that it doesn't have too much of an effect, this is called reuptake and it's a
standard process that occurs in the body or in the brain
reuptake inhibitors inhibit that
process so the serotonin stays in the system
a major chemical imbalance, that serotonin is artificially
kept active, so you get off your serotonin reuptake inhibitors and because
this uptake mechanism has been shut down, now you've got all of this
serotonin that has left the nerve cells, you run into
a major, major risk of serotonin depletion because the serotonin
is not getting taken up back into the cell, so you want to make
sure if you're going to get off of serotonin reuptake inhibitors that you
wean yourself off of them very slowly and you build your
serotonin levels back up by number one, making sure you're getting out in
the sun, make sure you get 10 or 15 minutes of sun 3 or 4 days a week
you don't want to burn, but you want to make sure that you're getting some sun
yeah the ultimate prozac is climbing mountains, I'm telling you right now
absolutely, ultimate prozac is the great outdoors, nature and the divine force, that's the prozac
oh my god, I want more of it!
right, you get out in the sun, don't we all feel better when we're out in the sun?
are you kidding, if I had my way all I'd do is climb mountains
with a demon in the sky that's hell-bent on our destruction
we've been bamboozled and entranced and we believe this nonsense
and then as you point out, when we don't have the vitamins and minerals, we do get sunburned
well that's another thing, if you want to prevent yourself from getting sunburned, make sure you're getting nutrients
that get stored in your skin to protect you from the sun, carotenes, flavonoids
vitamin c, zinc, vitamin e, they literally get deposited in your skin
to protect you from the sun, and let me tell you something, skin cancer rates
are increasing dramatically, despite the fact that
how do you like that? the sun is actually protective against skin cancer
the sun is protective against skin cancer, and people are using sunscreens
like they're going out of style, and skin cancer rates are increasing by 100%
aluminum based, we're going to come back, I want to talk about
again, somebody on these drugs, because I've got a schedule here from
ssrstories.com, and it talks about warning, going off this
is a big deal, I mean folks, you're on a LSD molecule
so we're going to come back, and we're extremists
we're saying LSD is bad to give to kids, especially
they're going to have a bad trip, and almost all these shooters and mothers
that kill their kids, they're on it, why don't we send them to jail?
is only compounding the problem
dangerous weather is always a threat to local grids
a solar power generator provides
powerful backup insurance and peace of mind
one of my oldest sponsors
you can get more information at www.mysolarbackup.com
that's mysolarbackup.com, remember, the government doesn't own the sun
go to mysolarbackup.com, or call 1-877-327-0365
you land in
Buenos Aires, then are shuttled to Santa Rosa, where a nicely
furnished cabin with all amenities, wifi, executive food and wine
and laundry service awaits, after a good night's sleep
your adventure begins, you're on a golden stag
safari for big game, but it's not Africa
Argentina, one-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo
huger, bighorn rams, wild boar, and the biggest
stag deer in South America, all gold metal quality
all the action you can handle
land rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages
hunting guides, ground transportation included, and more
all more affordable than you can imagine
all starts at goldenstagsafaris.com
the big game hunting ranch, goldenstagsafaris.com
Is this the year you finally get serious about your family's drinking water?
If so, keep listening for a special offer from Big Berkey Water Filters
Did you know that over 60% of municipal water is fluoridated?
Berkey Water Filters distinguish themselves from many other filtration systems with the capability to significantly reduce
dangerous chlorine, fluoride, arsenic, and disinfection byproducts from municipal water
such as black berkey and PF line of filters. Then there's affordability
At only 1.7 cents per gallon, Berkey Water Filters purify treated and untreated water
even stagnant pond water. Stop and think how much money you could save by simply reducing
buying bottled water and using water filtered by your Berkey Water Filter
No need to be constantly replacing expensive filters with a Berkey. A single set of filters can last for 5-10 years
Choose the best size Berkey for your needs at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com
And right now, all GCN listeners get 5% off all ceramic filter systems
Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY. That's 877-99-BER-KEY
Or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com
Free shipping on every order over $50. Big Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean water
We don't need no
education
We don't need
no thought control
Again, ladies and gentlemen, I don't have a dairy, I don't sell milk
I don't sell eggs, I don't sell beef steak
There's a lot of contaminants in the beef and stuff now, as you know
There's some downsides to a bunch of meat, and even though I love every piece of it
Because of the industrial system, we've got high quality whey available
Obviously, so I guess we do sell that in the way at Infowarshealth.com
It's a great place to get it and support the broadcast, become a distributor
Sign up at Infowarshealth.com to get free shipping
There's over 400 products linked on there, total
And by the way, the root beer belly probiotic
Is one of the most amazing mixes of healthy bacteria that they've ever come out with
I'm using this myself, that's available, tastes great
Kids love it, they can put it in water and stir it up
Tastes just like root beer, well I guess it is root beer, without the sugar and stuff
Also, if you're a radio listener and people complain, they go, hey man, give us the phone number
And so I will also give you that number
888-636-9277 for customer service
If you're already a preferred member to get discounts, you can just order right off the site
888-636-9277
Or new customer product orders 888-789-9277
888-789-9277
There's an international order area there as well
For people, Catherine at Infowars.com
And we have a whole team there of people, some of them pharmacists and others, when they answer the phone
Others are just trained by them to answer your questions, Infowarshealth.com
This is a revolution though, because I'll tell you this, Beyond Tangy Tangerine
Polymers Plus, the essential fatty acids, all of it
What it's giving me is more energy
Something magic to give us energy, no, we're designed for the minerals
The trace elements, the things we need, the government says we need 40-something vitamins and minerals
We need 90, and it's all available at Infowarshealth.com
Okay, so continuing, basically you're saying get out in the sunshine
While you wean yourself off, there's different regimens online
Doctors say it takes about two months generally, depending on the type
Obviously consult one of the physicians, the problem is these psychologists aren't really physicians
They'll tell you, stay on it, or their answer is more of it, well this isn't working
We'll stack them, that'll fix it, so we're not telling you what to do
I'm saying get out, exercise fresh air
Pray to God, if you don't believe in that, meditate, all the studies show it works
For whatever reason, praying helps, there are no atheists and foxholes
Ben, why do the studies show, I've got them right here, that the
Praying helps? Well, relaxation response
That's the reason why people have religion in the first place, is this idea that there's something
That can help them, that can take control over their lives
I'm not a particular religious person, but I'm a very spiritual person, and there's a lot of
A lot of good that can be had by people
When you pray, what are you focusing on? The great void, the great unknown, the universe
You're forgetting all this, you're ah
The magic of the body, the amazingness of nature, the cosmos
There's a hundred trillion cells in your body, and each one of them has 18 feet
Of DNA, if you added all the DNA in your body, it would go 300 billion miles
You have a coordinated, tightly choreographed
System that is beyond belief, just in a tiny cell of which you have a hundred trillion
It's unbelievable, Alex, we are the most unbelievable
We're the most unbelievable creatures, we should be only focusing on that
Let alone the cosmos that is trillions upon trillions
Look, one piece of human DNA as you know, three billion long
One piece, we are incredible
Incredible, Alex, you know what a cell is? A cell is a tiny, we talk about cells so glibly
But what is this thing? It's a tiny little animal that if you took it out of your body
And put it in a petri dish, it would walk to food, it would run away from poison
It excretes, it reproduces, it has a skeletal system, and it's one one hundredth
No, no, we're just like jellyfish, we are a colony creature
You know about that, don't you? The fact that our tissues make up a colony
We are a colony, that's right, we're a hundred trillion cell colony, that's exactly right
With DNA that resonates from signals from space
Proven, antennas, spiritual antennas, we'll be back
Thank you for listening to GCN
Visit GCNlive.com today
Or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog
Buy the one to two month sample package
And enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now
Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps
For all your cleaning needs, this is an amazing deal
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
See them on the web at FiveStarSoap.com
Or call 800-340-7091
For a free catalog
Coast to Coast
Direct from Austin, you're listening to the Alex Jones
Broadcasting Network
Big Brother
Mainstream Media
You want answers? Well, so does he
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones
I promise you this, unless I get run over by a car
The next couple of weeks we'll get Ben back to take an hour or two of calls
On allergies, on getting off serotonin reuptake inhibitors, on weight loss, everything
And again, we're doing a few minutes in for marshaling here, but really this is all hey, go eat more eggs
Folks, drink more milk, I mean healthy milk
It's really more sunlight
Now we do have SleepEase that does have the
Chemicals, the 5-HTP in it
That then I guess gets converted over to the tryptophan
And other things that the EPA took off the market with a fake scare a few decades ago
But the precursor of it, SleepEase, available at InfowarsHealth.com
Right now, there in the huge catalog
But Ben, you've agreed to stay another 20 minutes, what I'm going to do is we're going to come back in the next
Segment, I'm going to throw it to you to cover areas of this in general
Then I'm going to come back in the final segment, we're in overdrive right now
The reason I get so excited about all this is the truth is laying around all
In front of us, and it really makes me mad at the power structure, because you're a nice guy
You say, well, most doctors and people don't know this, and that's actually true, because I know a lot of
Doctors, my dad knows a lot of them, but a lot of them in the power
Structure, they do know, and it's very cold blooded that
Double blind studies, sugar pills, better than Prozac, and actually makes, I mean
What's happening in Harris and Kleibold and all these guys who are on these drugs
When they go crazy and have that same million mile stare, you know, crazy
Man look on their face, what's happening to them
When they're playing murder simulator video games and they're on four or five drugs
And an amphetamine drug on top of it usually, and they go and kill everybody
I mean, they're highly suggestible
Violence and paranoia are part of the hypervigilant response
Vigilance is important, you know, you've got to be aware, but this hypervigilant
Response is akin to paranoia, what we call paranoia can be defined as hypervigilance
When you start messing around with serotonin, pharmacologically manipulating
Its levels, keeping serotonin activity high artificially
You run the risk of this kind of paranoia hypervigilance, which is where
Rage comes from and rageful behavior comes from, you can't mess around
With your brain chemistry artificially and not expect to create
Problems, and this whole idea of chemical imbalance, manipulating the brain
Alex, do you think there's a test for serotonin, do you think you go to a psychiatrist and he
Does a test to see how high your serotonin level goes, they just give it to you
They just give them to you, that's exactly right, they give them to you like they're M&M's or like they're candy
The fact of the matter is the history of psychiatry is not very pretty, the history of medicine
In general is not very pretty, the inventor of the lobotomy as you know a hundred years ago did thousands
Thousands where he would go before a carnival and take a mentally
Retarded person and jam an ice pick in their brain in front of people
That's how they do, that's how they used to cure depression, they would hack your brain out
Or electroconvulsive therapy where they shock you into being happy, this is the
History of psychiatry, but Alex the question is, why are we complicit
Why do we participate, why do we listen to anything they tell us
When like you say, the information is right there in plain sight
Perhaps hidden in plain sight, but it's in plain sight, I sent you a stack of information
It took me all of 15 or 20 minutes to gather that information
It's everywhere, the fact of the matter is if you do your research you will see
Serotonin is a sunlight, daylight, awareness, vigilance, hormone
This is another very important point, serotonin absorbs
Light, serotonin contains, serotonin contains tryptophan
Or a tryptophan like shape, tryptophan itself contains like chlorophyll
Which is the ultimate light absorbing substance, gets its light absorbing power
From tryptophan, so when you eat tryptophan, not only do you upregulate
Serotonin, but you help your body utilize light, Alex we are
Photosynthetic beings, we absorb light from the sun
That sunlight gets turned into batteries, it gets turned into biochemistry
It gets turned into physical matter, most especially serotonin
In fact, by the way, tryptophan is a part of our visual pigment
We actually see via the activity of tryptophan, we receive light from the sun in our eyes
Via the activity of tryptophan, by the way I'm showing people images
Of public lobotomies, if you even misbehave
They just take you down and jam an ice pick up through the eyelid
And right into your brain, into the cerebral cortex and just randomly
Punching holes into your brain with pleasure
Come back and continue to break this down with pharmacist Ben Fuchs, InfowarsHealth.com
You will wake up people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level
We need your help to spread the word like never before
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness
You are the response to the globalist technocrats
And their program of global eugenics dehumanization
Ultimate extermination, the war is here, it's an Infowar
The spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984
Are you still a traditional smoker?
Now experience a new lifestyle and try vaping with e-cigarettes by LASIG
Imagine no ashes, stains, nasty smell or coughing and hacking
With LASIG e-cigarettes revolutionary microelectronic technology, rechargeable battery and unique replaceable cartridge
You'll get all the benefits and satisfaction of smoking without the hazards
Choose your taste from a wide variety of our new American made vaporie at e-liquids at LASIG.com
And LASIG smokes the competition by serving thousands of worldwide customers with real people customer service
Fast, free, same day shipping and a 30 day warranty and satisfaction guarantee
So are you ready for a new vaping lifestyle?
Then call 870-518-4307
That's 870-518-4307
Or visit LASIG.com
Spelled L-E-C-I-G.com
LASIG e-cigarettes for today's modern smoker
Injuries, slow healing, aches and pains, constipation, weakness, fatigue are all common the older one gets
The progressive deterioration of the body that occurs almost universally the older one gets can partly to significantly be prevented with conscientious attention to nutrition
If the Hanza men can play rugby in their 90s then it is possible for everyone in North America to experience a more youthful life as well
One key ingredient to warding off aging and reversing some of it is the type and quality of protein consumed
All protein foods or supplements you currently consume are heat damaged destroying 50 to 75% of your ability to utilize the body building amino acids
One World Way is not heat damaged and allows your body to utilize 100% of the amino acids
This feat no one else has achieved
The results to your health can be amazing
Call 888-988-3325
That's 888-988-3325
Or visit Oneworldway.com
The Genesis Communications Radio Network proudly presents the Alex Jones Show
Because there's a war on for your mind
We're back live, pharmacist Ben Fuchs, compounding pharmacist is our guest
We're doing one more segment with him here on this Friday edition and I'll be back this Sunday
4 to 6 p.m. Central live in studio we ran a best of with some new stuff that had there but also some tidbits of best of last Sunday 4 to 6
About once a month it's a rebroadcast, about three times a month it's live
One of the hardest working guys in media because I know there's no future if we don't turn this around
I'm going to shoot a couple of reports that are going to be on the nightly news tonight of extreme import
And that's 7 o'clock central, prisonplanet.tv, you can get 11 memberships for $5.95 a month and share them
I mean nobody offers that, that just pays for the bandwidth
Our goal is to get the word out, we have the $115,000 contest we're able to do because you're supporting us
For people to make films, thousand films I guess will be made, it will reach I'd guess 50 to 100 million people
That's my goal is 100 million, I'd be happy with 50 million
There will be some great films made, great resistance to tyranny and the winner gets $100,000, second place $10,000
Operation of Paul Revere, third place $5,000 and then it shot that pool of not just the winners but others
To come here and be financed by infowars.com, producing it to make a flotilla of films
Because I could make some really good films and I have obviously mega viral films
But we want to go to the next level and just expand the team in the face of this, it's all in
It's a total commitment against the new world order and we couldn't have done it without your support
If you support us in a win win, buying pro pure water filters discounted with promo code water at infowarsstore.com
Or going to infowarshealth.com and getting the best supplements that we've assembled all in one spot via Younggebity
Discounted, infowarshealth.com, this is how we do it
And by the way I'm not being a bad guy here because I'm against Genesis, Genesis is great
Most radio networks and stations take any advertising, Genesis has a lot of standards
But I'm approached all the time by supplement companies and they'll say
We'll pay you $100,000 to endorse this product and I go see the claims and I can't prove it
And I go sorry I'm not going to do that and then they come back and go we'll pay you $500,000 right now
These are things you hear nationwide not just on Genesis and I go I'm sorry I just can't prove these things
And so no, I have to do money bombs or sell memberships or whatever but everything I do is about getting the word out
If it's a t-shirt it's about defending the second amendment or property rights
If it's a film it's about exposing agenda 21
Everything we do is a win win win win win and Infowarshealth is just amazing
So get your beyond tangy tangerine, your polymers plus that bears my name on it, I like it so much
All the different supplements are available there, the essential fatty acids, everything
Infowarshealth.com and know you're supporting us
Now Ben I'm going to give you the rest of this segment about 10 minutes to get into other facets
What you would do, why allergies are increasing, how people should detox
Other things about what Prozac and other drugs are doing to people
What you would do with a child who's obviously bouncing off the walls
It's usually they admit what they've been eating
You've got the floor for the balance of this segment
Alex there's two great movements in the body
You have the movement towards stress and vigilance and awareness and fear
And you have the relaxation response
Growth and repair and anti-aging and healing all occur when the body is relaxed
Anything that exacerbates or exaggerates the stress response
Serotonin for example, prescription drugs for example, sugar and processed food for example
Anything that exacerbates the stress response, this fear response is going to shut down growth and repair
And this is why it seems to me like there's this almost this insidious conspiracy
To keep us from being able to grow, to keep us sick, to keep us from being able to repair
To accelerate the aging process and this is why it's so, so, so important
To avoid interacting with prescription drugs at all times
With the exception perhaps of pain pills if you're in pain
Antibiotics obviously although these days we hear about the problems with antibiotic resistance
Anybody who understands anything about antibiotics could have seen this one coming
But still there's times when you need antibiotics perhaps aside from antibiotics and pain pills and perhaps chemotherapy
Any prescription drugs need to be avoided like the plague
Literally like the plague
If you're on an SSRI drug, if you're considering an SSRI drug please consider the alternatives
Number one, get yourself out in the sun
Number two, make sure you're practicing deep breathing techniques
Number three, make sure you're getting enough salt for your adrenal glands
This is another hideous idea that we have to avoid salt
The fact of the matter is salt is very important for helping the adrenal glands
And keeping your body from going into this fight or flight response
Make sure that you're using a nutritional supplement program
Especially the B complex which is not only important for making serotonin
But it's important for the stress response and it's important for mental health as well
Make sure you're focusing on digestive wellness
The immune system is the digestive system in many ways
In fact 80-90% of your immune system is located in the digestive tract
You talk about allergies, the number one cause of allergies
Whether it's to cedarwood or whether it's to juniper or whether it's to pollen or whether it's to anything else
The number one cause is a stressed out immune system
Especially considering the kind of foods that we're eating
If you're dealing with H. pylori bacteria
This is one of the main reasons why the body goes into a stress response
Address your H. pylori, that means get on probiotics
That means eat fermented foods
That means make sure that you're staying away from anything that has a negative effect on the digestive system
And use apple cider vinegar and digestive enzymes after your meals
If you have your gallbladder, keep it
Focus on fat absorption, that is the absorption of essential fatty acids
And the absorption of fatty vitamins
If somebody tries to talk you into having your gallbladder removed
Don't do it unless you have cancer in there, you need your gallbladder
80 million Americans are dealing with fatty liver disease
If you go to a doctor today he'll tell you
Oh it's just a normal part of aging
No it's not a normal part of aging
In fact they call it non-alcoholic fatty liver disease
They have to distinguish it from the kind of fatty liver disease that you used to have to drink
A pint of Jack Daniels to get
A pint of Jack Daniels every day to get
Today we're all getting that kind of disease
Focus on liver wellness by eliminating processed foods
Make sure you're eating less calories and you're getting more nutrients
And this is one of the major reasons why a nutritional supplement program is so important
Use liquid nutrients and use liquid foods as much as possible
It will remove the load off of your digestive tract
Give yourself a food holiday periodically
Practice intermittent fasting
In fact one of the most anabolic building strategies you could ever use
Is to practice intermittent fasting
Where you take a food holiday, you take a day off from food once a month
Once every couple of weeks it will actually stimulate the production of building hormones
Do everything you can do to turn on the building response
The body is a healing system, it's a regenerating system
You are witness to this healing and regenerating system every time you cut yourself
You can see how the skin heals
Well that same healing system that takes place in the skin
Takes place in the bones, takes place in the digestive tract
Takes place in the nervous system, takes place in the liver and throughout the body
Access this healing response that is your birth right
Nobody has to have a degenerative disease
In fact we know that there is a 1200 different disease states
Well really there is only one disease state and that is the disease of degeneration
And given that the body is a healing and regenerating system
Nobody has to deal with this degenerative process
However we have to participate
We have to take a role in our health
And that means not listening to the medical model
We have more doctors in this country per capita than any other country in the world
Than any other country in the history of the world
We spend more money per capita on health
Yet we are the sickest culture ever in the history of mankind
Clearly the modern medical model has failed us
Ambulatory medicine, not heroic medicine where you get stitched up after you get hit by a car
But ambulatory medicine, this idea that you can go to the doctor for your blood pressure
You can go to the doctor for your depression
You can go to the doctor for whatever kind of illness you have
Ambulatory medicine is not the answer
We are the answer, the divine force is the answer
And it works through simple things like deep breathing
Simple things like getting out in the sun
Simple things like eating whole food
Simple things like getting on a nutritional supplement program
And simple things like spirituality and praying as well
And truly health is a multidimensional process that works spiritually, mentally, emotionally and physically
All the dimensions have to be addressed
Spirituality is your business
Mentality means thinking correct thoughts
Every time you think a thought, Alex, it gets turned into biochemistry
Every time you feel a feeling, it gets turned into biochemistry
So making sure you're thinking clearly
You're not thinking fear thoughts
You're thinking powerful thoughts
Making sure you're addressing the emotional aspects of reality of your life
And making sure that you're focusing on physical well-being
Through the correct foods, through sunlight, through oxygen
And don't forget about a good exercise program
The body thrives under conditions of small amounts of stress
Stress is not a four-letter word
Small amounts of stress actually turn on this building process
The body likes small amounts of stress
And long, luscious, long periods of rest
And this combination of stress and rest
With appropriate nutrition and nutritional strategies
Along with mental and emotional strategies
Is the key to wellness and the key to health
And nobody, nobody, nobody has to deal with degenerative disease
They're all reversible, including cancer, FYI
Amazing information
In fact, let's do one more segment and come back with this
Younggevity news that I've got
Here it is
This is out of Yahoo Finance
AEL International announces results of Younggevity clinical research studies
Performed by Clemson University Institute of Neuromedical Research
Have you seen this?
I love it, Alex
I used to, you know, medical professionals, they need to see paperwork
Fine, there's the paperwork
I've been seeing it for 20 years
The paperwork I get is letters
That's my paperwork
Letters from people who tried to be on tangy tangerines
So now there's credentialed letters
There's credentialed information from Clemson University
And I love it and that's some powerful stuff, Alex
And they're the best
And that's what we carry at infowarshealth.com
And you support the broadcast
So we can launch Operation Paul Revere, $115,000 in cash prizes
$100,000 first place
I mean, there'll be a thousand entries
It'll reach tens upon tens of millions of people
ProLiberty Films, fiction, non-fiction, short, long
Go read the rules right now, launch today
infowars.com, prisonplanet.com
A devastating blow exposing the globalist agenda
Whether it's the gun grabbing, all of it, you make the film
I'll judge it, you'll win
We'll be right back
People will wake up, that's the key
Hello, I'm Alex Jones
Myself, my family, the infowars.com team
Want to relay to you and your families
That we are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front
Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats
But we can't do that without your help
By getting the films, bumper stickers and t-shirts at infowars.com
You will wake up people in your area and support our operation
As we move to the next level
We need your help to spread the word like never before
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle
Between the forces of freedom and darkness
You are the response to the globalist technocrats
And their program of global eugenics dehumanization
And ultimate extermination
The war is here, it's an infowar
The spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984
Are you still a traditional smoker?
Now experience a new lifestyle
And try vaping with e-cigarettes by LASIG
Imagine, no ashes, stains, nasty smell or coughing and hacking
With LASIG e-cigarettes revolutionary micro electronic technology
Rechargeable battery and unique replaceable cartridge
You'll get all the benefits and satisfaction of smoking
Without the hazards
Choose your taste from a wide variety of our new American made
Vapory at e-liquids at LASIG.com
And LASIG smokes the competition by serving thousands of worldwide customers
With real people customer service
Fast, free, same day shipping
And a 30 day warranty and satisfaction guarantee
So are you ready for a new vaping lifestyle?
Then call 870-518-4307
That's 870-518-4307
Or visit LASIG.com
Spelled L-E-C-I-G.com
LASIG e-cigarettes for today's modern smoker
hempusa.org has a newly designed website
And a new and improved detoxification product
Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with
Vitamins, minerals, iodine and probiotics
And we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder
Absolutely free micro plant powder only at hempusa.org
Call 908-691-2608
That's 908-691-2608
And see what our powder, seeds and oil can do for you
Only at hempusa.org
Only this offer ends January 31st
Hi this is Ted Anderson
Have you ever wondered why banks, stockbrokers, investment advisors
Won't talk about gold IRAs?
They've been available since 1986
Yet the financial industry won't recognize the value of gold for your retirement
Gold has outperformed paper investments yet no word about IRAs
If you would like to have gold for your retirement
Call 800-686-2237
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns
Secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237
Looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves
How did we ever survive?
From natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy
And the devastating summer drought
To the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything
At eFoods Direct we hear from customers every day
That are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
By having a supply of food on hand
After Hurricane Sandy
Danny from New York City wrote
Almost all the grocery stores are closed
But I managed to get my eFoods just in time
To be able to help my sister and niece
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
Than one day too late
I can warn you but I can't feed you
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done
Call 800-409-5633 today
Or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex
And build your food supply
It's the best tasting non-GMO
Long-term storeable food on the planet
Call 800-409-5633
Or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex
You can bet your life on eFoods Direct
Yeah the Communist Party USA
Says they want us to turn our guns in
You know they're not going to be turning theirs in
No, no, they keep theirs, you turn yours in
They're real nice people
Oh boy, it doesn't matter, communists have killed
What about seven, eight times worldwide what Hitler did?
Wow, look at that, we ought to put their official logo
In that article we've got linked on Drudge at the top
That one that says CPUSA
And maybe we should slap that right up there
At the top of that article because it really says it all
And hey, they're working with Obama
There he is right there
Oh, we're in a lot of trouble right now
Oh, this is a good image right here
That actually ought to be added right there
That's the one right there
I'm going to have that added to the article
In closing, pharmacist Ben Fuchs is here with us
And this information is just amazing
And he looks 20 years younger than he actually is
Infowarshealth.com
I'm going to get this press release added up there to that site
I'm also going to get it added to Infowars.com
Briefly tell us about the announcement by the
Clinical research studies performed by Clemson University
And what they found about Beyond Tangy Tangerine
And some of the other products at Infowarshealth.com
Let me tell you something, Alex
People always want to know if they want one thing that they could do
Just to see how well this stuff works
And I'm telling you, if you try the Beyond Tangy Tangerine
There's no way you will not become a believer in nutrition
And it's because of this unbelievable concentration of nutrients
In a liquid format
The digestive system, the system that's designed
By nature to absorb nutrients over time
Becomes so overwhelmed that no matter what we're eating
No matter what we're taking
Especially in terms of nutritional supplements that come in pills
And the nutritional value of foods
We don't get the benefit of these things
Because our digestive system starts to break down
When you get your nutrients in a liquid format
Whether you're talking about soups or smoothies
Or vegetable juices
Or the Beyond Tangy Tangerine
You give your body nutrients with no work
That's why when you're sick you want the chicken soup
Exactly
You hit the nail on the head
When you're sick you want the Jewish penicillin
You want the chicken soup
Because you're getting the protein and you're getting the immune factors
And you're getting the sugars
The complex sugars
And you're getting that chemical that's so key
That's in the meat
I'm not sure which one that is
But you're getting lots of great protein in the meat
And you're getting it in a liquid format
You know the one that's in Turkey, it keeps escaping
You're talking about tryptophan
That's the famous tryptophan that we're talking about
And that's why they talk about tryptophan as being a sleepy kind of substance
Because it's so relaxing
That's another story
See how that's the real Prozac right there
That's your natural Prozac
5-HTP and tryptophan
Not that you're sleepy, you've finally gotten relaxed
You're relaxed, exactly
But back to your question about this Clemson study
What they found was
And exactly what I've been saying for years
Since I started using the young Japanese products back in the late 90's
When you take your nutrients in a liquid fashion
You notice results
And you notice them quickly
And the kind of results you get are global results
They're non-specific results
You lose weight
You have more energy
You feel better
You're not sleeping as much
You're not sick as much
That just affect the entire body
And that's why people lose weight without even trying
Do you know, Alex, that's the number one thing people say
When they're on the Beyond Tangy Tangerine
They lost weight and it wasn't even hard
And that is the beauty of a nutritional supplement program
You get healthy
And it doesn't require a lot of work
Because you know what?
It's your birthright
It's our birthright
This healing system is built into every one of the 100 trillion cells of the body
And let nobody tell you
That you have to take a drug
Or you have to have surgery
Or you have to have some doctor's interference
In order for you to be able to access this healing power
Armistice, Ben Fuchs
Thanks for spending an hour and a half with us today
Or almost that much time
And we'll talk to you very, very soon
Thank you for all you do
Thank you, my pleasure, Alex
Alright, folks, that's it for the live segment of the transmission
The in-studio interview with Dr. Jerome Corsi
Halfway in the first hour is coming up
You have your station tuned in and saying, I don't understand
It's been four hours, some days were three hours
Some days were three and a half hours
We sent out four hours
And for, I don't know, 15 years or so
14 years I did three hours
And for a couple years I did
I did four hours
But with the nightly news and the stuff
It just sometimes burned me out too bad
But now that I'm back
I've gotten on vitamins and minerals
I have more energy
So I'm kind of leaning towards four hours
Just officially again
789-9277
888-789-9277
Or 888-636-9277
And get others to go
And sign up as distributors
To get discounts at infowarshealth.com
It is a revolution
Information is power, the people perish
We're on the march, the empire's on the run, Alex Jones at the GCN Radio Network