big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
ladies and gentlemen it is Tuesday the 22nd day of January 2013 I am your host
Alex Jones we're going to be live here for the next three hours and we do have
a guest who's going to be joining us a little bit later in the broadcast in
fact several guests I'll tell you about that information coming up in the second
segment here today more about why Max Keiser is going to be joining us and
also Lloyd Chapman popping in Obama's considering shutting down the federal
Small Business Bureau just amazing information I mean why even have it
there they already don't give the contracts of small businesses anyways
we're going to quick update on that continued destruction of our economy
while telling the public the government's doing everything it can to get
the economy going the name of the game is economic domination that's how we're
being dominated but the globalists want to back that up with a physical
domination sometimes I take off for three or four days and the so-called
vacation turns into more work than just you know staying at home but I was able
to take off three days and go down to Big Bend where I hadn't been in decades
down on the Texas Mexico border in south west Texas very romantic scenery that
the desert speaks to a man's soul I guess just as the sea does and I just
had a lot of epiphanies clarification it's good to slow down sometimes and
and every time I do slow down I realize how much I do need to take a pit stop
just because then I'm more focused and and more clear and it's the same for
everybody but I feel completely rejuvenated and it's probably the high
mountain air and hiking up mountains and getting in the hot springs the natural
hot springs there by the Rio Grande and watching the Mexican ranchers ride
around on their horses look like right across the border look like something
right out of a Western just very romantic scenery and of course public
school educated people will think romantic means just like you take your
wife and do something romantic no I mean romantic of you for some people out
there who I know don't know what I mean by it cuz sometimes I get emails when
talking about something being romantic romantic the romantic novels or people
in ships and storms or astronauts going to the moon is romantic or beautiful
scenery or things that stir the heart and the soul that's romantic and just
very very good for the soul also there's no Wi-Fi there and cell phones don't
work anywhere but up close to the top of mountains I'd have to get up on a high
up on a mountain and sit there and transmit with my cell phones the two
videos I did shoot while I was there to the town 30 miles away at night with the
little blinking lights far away line of sight just amazing technology I'm gonna
attempt to get into all of the news when we come back and it's just more of the
same more confirmation of just how much trouble we're in but more facets of the
enemy as more detail is filled in as it gets closer and closer back to
in many cases the tyranny is not close anymore it's sitting on top of us
spitting in our faces it is all over even mainstream news that Western
governments are really running the al-qaeda groups in Africa who are
blowing up chemical plants and taking hostages and things like that
the african invasion was shut up four years ago even before Obama was put into
office four and a half years ago that's why he's the black face so they can sell
that so the left won't say anything cuz I mean he's black it must be okay and
they just use that as an emotional cover for what they're doing but it's pretty
amazing headline London Independent terror in North Africa our Westerners
pulling the strings and the French the US and others are already in place there
but now they're invading and mash we'll be right back stay with us
the new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness get
serious and make a stand with supernatural silver this is a
breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver can be taken orally
every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds
supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective
for water purification it is the number one choice for thousands of people for
immune system support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency
preparedness go to supernatural silver calm today and give yourself and your
loved ones a fighting chance that's supernatural silver calm check out our
new low prices and like us on Facebook if you want an American company with
American products made by Americans here is the cow bed soap company Alex and his
staff have used these pure soap products for years these all-natural soaps are
made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth friendly
and safe see them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for
a free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are
twice as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year
supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs this is an amazing deal you can
save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
see them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free
catalog you prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms but if you don't have
a home security system then you're missing a critical weapon in your
arsenal for home protection when you're sleeping or away from home who's
watching out for intruders check out simply safe it's a new do-it-yourself
home security system that is completely wireless go to get simply safe calm
simply safe is independent and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if
the grid goes down you're protected it's completely customizable so you can use
it in your home business boat trailer storage unit or shed get simply safe
calm simply safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20
minutes so there's no need to let a stranger into your home if you move or
need to relocate you can take the system with you wherever you go you aren't
always at home but simply safe will stand guard protecting your property 24
hours a day seven days a week again that's get simply safe calm
we now take you live to the Central Texas command center in the heart of the
resistance you are listening to the Alex Jones show
ladies and gentlemen I am your host Alex Jones I am a defender of Liberty I am
very upset about the tyrants that are taking over our planet and I am very
disgusted by their open attacks on all of our basic liberties not just the
Second Amendment and that's why I'm on air to try to set brush fires in the
minds of men and women everywhere to defend their freedoms that were hard
fought and hard won by our forebears now remember the United States
geographically is really a small country and we've only been five percent of the
world's population roughly in the last hundred years those numbers have stayed
about steady we're currently about five and a half percent of the world's
population but we had half of the world's wealth half of the world's
wealth and now we're losing that wealth why did five percent of the world's
population have half the wealth because we kicked the royalty out we kicked the
monopolies out we kicked the power combines out who always take over and
always seek to make everyone else poor and dependent and then incredible
poverty always follows that is what these oligarchs do that's what they set
up in the Mesoamerican kingdoms in Central and South America and southern
North America the Aztecs the Toltecs the whole Mayan culture that's what the
ancient Babylonians establishment it's what the Egyptians established it's what
the Romans established it's what every other culture establishes a form of
feudalism it is not an accident that they're trying to make us poor this is a
designed global engineered program all right I have got so much news that I
want to cover here today since I was out Friday Sunday and Monday and I want to
just thank Paul Joseph Watson and of course Mike Adams Rappaport and others
and the crew they all did a great job driving back from Big Ben yesterday when
I was able to get internet I tuned into the iPhone app and listened to large
portions of of Friday's transmission and just amazing information with Mike
Adams on that broadcast and obviously I called in on Thursdays or or Friday show
myself but there is just so much to cover and so let me just go over some of
the some of the headlines that we're going to be talking about here today
Nobel Prize nominee Obama asked military leaders if they will fire on US citizens
shot claim purported to come from one of America's foremost military heroes and
Paul then links to the army training manual from 2010 where they have begun
to openly train to take on American gun owners and confiscate our firearms
trainings predates that but now it's public and so I mean my point is why
even go with the claim even though we're tracking down this individual to get
them on I mean it's all right there out in the open already that's what Homeland
Security is as a system to wage war against American gun owners so we're
going to be going over that report also Obama's inaugural address Second
Amendment is obsolete he says that when the times change so must we I guess
we're going back to ancient Rome where slaves were disarmed so we've got that
report CNN communist Network trying to shove gun control down our throats we're
going to go over some of that new push and some more good news CBS news
reporting Missouri sheriff's sheriff's whole bunch of them pledge not to enforce
Obama's gun control law saying they're unconstitutional that's also being
reported by NBC
we now have
Texas sheriff's coming out and saying the same thing so it is spreading you
see the sheriff is a constitutional office
and sheriff's are elected representatives and sheriff's in an
emergency are the head honcho in the county they can actually declare
martial law but instead you've got the federal government trying to dissolve
sheriff's through the states trying to offer money if the counties and if the
cities will get together
and either get rid of the sheriff outright or if they can't do that make
them unelected and a creature of the system we're going to be going over that
report today and then coming up after I've had a chance to get into the Second
Amendment attack the latest developments there in the economy we're going to
cover the London Independent and several other mainstream articles terror in North
Africa our Westerners pulling strings and the Algerian Prime Minister has come
out and said basically these are white commandos commanding a bunch of jihadis
taking people hostage and blowing things up and then the West gets to go in and
invade the commandos pull out and the West then attacks empty facilities but
then gets to occupy in the name of defeating an enemy and and that's what
al-qaeda has always been it's a stimulant but the globalist have attack
or take the blame for an attack it's actually carried out by Western powers
the criminal elements that run us and and then you have the excuse to invade
and take over the region and every African country has either had a US
troops or NATO troops under Afrikan added to it or they've built up on the
borders of those countries and of course we told you an Obama deception at length
that there would be a major invasion of Africa to take over all of the natural
resources not already controlled by the West and it is neo-colonialism but
remember you don't get the stolen goods the stolen goods are used to be shipped
to China to be produced there under a monopoly deal where the West gets the
rare earths and gives it to China and then they use that to deindustrialize
the West so a lot of good old boys go well you know what let's go take it from
the Africans or let's go take the oil from the Muslims and that's actually
used to increase prices in fact if you go back to 1990 the real reason the UN
and the US was mad at Saddam who had worked for the quote United States and
attacking Iran and he was actually put into power by the CIA that's all
declassified congressional hearings on record he was actually a CIA trained
assassin in his when he was in his 20s and and then the US helped install a new
government he became the head of security then he helped run a Western
backed coup in 79 and then he was told go ahead and attack Iran and given
upwards of 40 billion dollars and and Saddam then wanted to become
independent kind of like Hosni Mubarak another puppet in Egypt and he actually
wanted to build up Iraq you say what you want about him but he did women got to
go to university they put rock and roll music on the radio Playboy in the stores
and not even saying that's a good thing but that's you know it was freedom
certainly I'm not saying you shouldn't be able to get Playboy or have rock and
roll my point is is that is that is that is that they westernized and they became
very wealthy and he stopped all the ethnic fighting that was going on and so
they set Saddam up and told him go ahead and invade quite we were not gonna get
involved you're our ally we don't get involved in inter-arab affairs that had
been his cues eight years before to attack Iran in the seven-year Iran Iraq
war so he went along with that so here's the problem with each article each each
each each little point I said I get to this later turns into a whole larger
story of what's happening and what's crazy is this is all publicly admitted
it's just not generally known just like a general public does not know the three
branches of government or does not know what sodium chloride is that's why most
surveys they say ban it it's of course salt or hydrogen dioxide most people in
surveys say ban that because it sounds scary it's it's water the people perish
for lack of knowledge the truth will set you free knowledge is power all those
maxims are so true and so central it's why I restate them so my point is
getting back to you don't get the goods of the spoils Saddam's big crime in 1990
and 1991 was he was paying off his 40 billion dollar debt and he was doing it
by flooding the market with oil and if you'll remember I mean gas was something
like what was gas prices pre pre-war it was something like 50 cents for just a
ridiculous number you could pull that number up I know it was way under a dollar
now yeah 60 cents double-check that though I know your memories right mines
right yeah I was like 60 65 cents pre Desert Shield then it jacked up to a
dollar fifty or something and again you know the good old boys are like get that
oil get them Arabs oil ever gonna get it oh you got it all right
Saddam was flooding the market in a free market with oil to pay off his debts
OPEC went completely ape it was all over the Wall Street Journal I was even
reading it at the time you know I was in high school and I remember watching the
news because I was into CNN and c-span and I mean I was following it and I
remember that I remember that gas was 55 60 65 cent spending on where you lived
and then shot way over a dollar fifty once the war or even once the Desert
Shield started but my point is now you pay you know close to four bucks in many
areas so let me explain something when our troops go and back up other groups
to take over and destabilize African countries and when all this happens
you're not going to get any of the goods you pay to get the bankers the resources
and then they all use it to leverage the market to consolidate and destroy the
market because they're in an act of economic scorched earth total takeover
so we have these articles where as we told you they're using al-qaeda to
attack all over Africa and then the US military and NATO and the French and the
rest of them go in there under the cover of African invading the whole place and
even the African leaders are going these are blonde haired blue-eyed men with
with English accents they are attacking no we do not want you you you are doing
it no oh no we're invading because al-qaeda took US citizens hostage and
the whole thing is a theater deal and that happened with the invasion of
Panama remember that that turned out that was all staged there were no
hostages at the University same deal this is purely manufactured everywhere
we'll be right back stay with us
looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves how did we ever survive from natural
disasters like hurricane sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family
hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that
have lost everything at e foods direct we hear from customers every day that
are fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand
after hurricane sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the grocery
stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to
help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too early than one
day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what
Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or
go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best
tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet
your life on e foods direct feeling like there are too many pressures and demands
on you losing sleep worrying about tests and schoolwork you can run the run
because your schedule is just too busy you may be under too much stress and it
may be affecting your mind get your mental edge back with new tropic mind
power from mind regard calm new tropic mind power is not a drug but a natural
supplement it's 12 powerful ingredients are natural and non-gmo plus it's
gluten-free wheat free and formulated by Americans for Americans by an NSF
certified laboratory new tropic mind power is available at mind regard calm
spelt m-i-n-d-r-e-g-a-r-d dot-com and comes with a 100% money-back guarantee
free your mind with new tropic mind power cognitive supplement from mind
regard calm mind regard clearly see tomorrow and yesterday today
hempusa.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification
product order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins minerals
iodine and probiotics and we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder
absolutely free micro plant powder only at hempusa.org call 908 691 2608 that's
908 691 2608 and see what our powder seeds and oil can do for you only at
hempusa.org only this offer ends January 31st hi this is Ted Anderson have you
ever wondered why banks stockbrokers investment advisors won't talk about
gold IRAs they've been available since 1986 yet the financial industry won't
recognize the value of gold for your retirement gold is outperformed paper
investments yet no word about IRAs if you would like to have gold for your
retirement call 800 686 2237 don't get left behind by rising inflation and low
returns call 800 686 2237 secure your future and call 1 800 686 2237 is this
the year you finally get serious about your family's drinking water if so keep
listening for a special offer from big Berkey water filters did you know that
over 60% of municipal water is fluoridated Berkey water filters
distinguish themselves from many other filtration systems with the capability
to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine fluoride arsenic and
disinfection byproducts from municipal water via the black Berkey and PF line
of filters then there's affordability it only 1.7 cents per gallon Berkey water
filters purified treated and untreated water even stagnant pond water stop and
think how much money you could save by simply reducing buying bottled water
and using water filtered by your Berkey water filter no need to be constantly
replacing expensive filters with a Berkey a single set of filters can last
for five to ten years choose the best size Berkey for your needs at big Berkey
water filters calm and right now all GCN listeners get 5% off all ceramic filter
systems just call 1 877 99 Berkey that's 877 99 B E R K E Y or visit big
Berkey water filters calm free shipping on every order over $50 big Berkey water
filters for the love of clean water ease the t-rex of political talk Alex Jones
on the GCN radio network
you know I could have just simplified everything I covered in the last segment
and said Shaddam Hussein's big crime was that he was over pumping oil in 1990 to
pay off his debts to the West and they were telling him OPEC and the West was
saying stop doing that you're making oil prices too low we want to gouge people
and he said no I'm gonna pay my debts off first he said well then forgive my
debts or cut them I want to be a sovereign country and they said no
you're going to be under globalist control again we're conquered by these
foreign international mega banks foreign is even the word global outside the law
mafias who brag that they've conquered us and they'll go put people like Saddam
in or Hazi Mubarak and then later set them up and bring them down to
destabilize the country to have a civil war to destroy its economy so they can
come in and buy it up for pennies on the dollar and it's in the IMF World Bank
documents that got released when Joseph stick let's quit the World Bank in 2002
now ten plus years ago hard to believe time is flying that that fast see that's
why I'm frustrated I know how cold-blooded the globalist are I mean
these are military financial conquerors these are hardcore systematic
mechanized corporate criminals who hate the free market and want a global
monopoly run by them and then I've got to sit there and watch Joe Biden on TV
going we can't let one more child die not one more and then that way when one
more gets killed by a gun see another one see it's your fault putting that
guilt on us well how about just never be born then never drive a car I never have
emotions well that's their goal for the general public is to turn us into
biological androids to turn us under the new freedom initiative into a bunch of
drugged out zombies and that's only in the interim phase while we're being
phased out as the establishment goes to robotics and automation and that's their
words whether that really works or not whether this plan actually will succeed
people think oh man you know you claim this is happening this is not my claim
this is the establishment all they talk about their hundred plus year plan that
they're following and let me tell you it leads to a very horrible place see I'm
not telling you what I think is going to happen I'm not fans think I'm super
smart and that man how does he keep knowing what's going to happen and then
my detractors think I'm up here like writing science fiction on the air
telling you what I imagine is going to happen because it's so fantastical and
it's neither one I've read hundreds of books and probably over a thousand
different white papers put out by the CFR put out by the Club of Rome you say
where are they what is the endgame.com has a bibliography on that film great
place to start watch my films I make a claim I show you the bill I show you the
document I go to the UT library and get the Club of Rome publication 1966
I show you where they say they're going to end the family
I show you where they say they're going to break down all of society and make us
basically drugged up brainwashed idiots before they release the control bio
plagues and wipe almost all of us out I show you the the training videos they
show kids in the UK about the planned Opelis and people watch it who aren't
children and think this is a satirical joke of a futuristic police state the
planned Opelis it's not it's an association with mainstream television
and newspapers and the British government putting out videos for kids
where mommy's the boss robots tell you what you can do daddy's a joke and no
one's allowed to go outside without government authorization and you never
get meat anymore and you live in giant compact cities and anybody else that
won't lives in these giant urban controlled slums or drones surveil
everyone you go well that's the 1970s judge dread judge dread is only writing
about what the globalist actually plan you see that's what you've got to get
folks is that it's not art that that life is then imitating it is life that
art is imitating and it's so frustrating that these globalist want to take us to
this ugly place are doing everything they can to hurt us and then I've got to
sit there and see Time magazine the gun fighters and on the cover of it it shows
Biden Bloomberg and shooting victim Giffords and you know what's interesting
is she was pro-gun before she got it she pretty much still is I don't know how
they gotta be part of this I guess she's been obviously injured shot in the head
but the point is is that we're now going to they're the gun fighters they know
there's that romantic idea of Americana and guns so they turn it around these
are the gun fighters they're trying to take your guns actually they are arming
themselves the government is they are buying a billion six bullets they are
buying the armored vehicles they are training to make war against us while
collapsing the society they are the gun fighters they're coming with the guns
they're wearing the black hats not Giffords the puppet but the other two
certainly Bloomberg is the chief leader for the foreign banks in Wall Street to
dominate and disarm us so we can be fully occupied these are conquerors we're
on the march the Empire's on the run Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers the prognosis for the
entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse the globalist model is
to shut down societies and starve Patriots out until they acquiesce to the
global takeover that's why we've assembled the most vital and important
preparedness items at info wars shop calm these are items that I did
research on that I personally use you've got the life straw so you can turn
fetid water into safe water anywhere you go the Ktor hand-crank generator to
charge up key equipment during power outages are out in the field strategic
relocation third edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein
thorough safe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any
radiological event and crank shortwave am-fm radios everything that we've
researched and found to be the best is available at info war shop calm and your
purchase makes our info war possible we're getting prepared are you in full
wars shop calm looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive
from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy in the devastating summer drought
to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to
those that have lost everything at e foods direct we hear from customers
every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm by having a supply of
food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the
grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be
able to help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too
early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the
warnings and do what Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six
three three today or go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your
food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term
storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct now that we
have moved into the winter season there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health at silver lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by
providing a full selection of silver based products our most popular silver
based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our 2 ounce nano silver
nasal applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps just released
is our 100% natural silver gel our new silver gel is not based on synthetic
gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface but
rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while
delivering the silver more effectively visit www.silverlungs.com and click on
our store page to find what silver based products are best for you
that's www.silverlungs.com
I was trained in firearms I carried a concealed weapon I made the
determination that if somebody was going to try to take me out I was going to
take them with me if I could have gotten 51 votes in the
Senate of the United States for an outright ban picking up every one of
them mr. and mrs. America turn them all in I would have done it defending the
Republic from enemies foreign and domestic it's Alex Jones
okay we're gonna get to a clip coming up in a little while of Obama saying
basically abolish the Second Amendment and the article on the text is up at
info Wars calm but if you're a radio listener I'm looking at the cover of
Time magazine the gun fighters kind of billionaire a vice president and a
shooting survivor stop the violence now imagine human violence has never stopped
if they really wanted to stop the violence Obama would have said
serotonin reuptake inhibitors and other psychotropics have been involved in 99
percent of these mass shootings and he would go on to say guns are good we've
seen a 49 percent the last 20 years FBI statistics from the local governments
very accurate numbers that's why they hide them
49 percent drop in crimes using guns 21 percent drop in the same period on
overall violent crime we've shown you those numbers at nauseum go to fbi.gov
and just go into it there's thousands of pages it'll blow you away all compiled
locally very accurate numbers murders muggings carjackings you name it I mean
imagine the level of this hoax imagine the level of what we're talking about
can they stop the violence and you notice they all keep saying we can never
have one more child shot I mean that's ridiculous never have one more child
dying a car wreck one more child drowned I mean the numbers like 15 something
times drowned every year would die from guns we're gonna ban swimming pools
gonna ban showers gonna ban people fall every day in every I mean it's more
probably every hour I mean the number is in the tens of thousands every year
falling and hitting their heads in the bathtub and dying but again they
emotionalize it they hype it they they stand on the graves of the children
Obama uses the children like human shields to sell his agenda and says I'll
get it done for you it is over the top that's why I get so angry but they're
targeting well-meaning dumbed-down Americans that like come on you care
about the kids right let's take the guns for them oh I guess you're right
but Bill Clinton came out over the weekend I thought we have a video clip
up at info wars calm saying don't trivialize the gun culture these people
are hard to beat and they're getting mobilized because we understand it's the
final straw it's the bellwether it's the canary in the coal mine it shows the
system is going for broke absolutely going for broke in a big way
on every front and of course they're going after our liberties on every front
and our forebears warned us about this over and over again and history has
shown in other nations what this means that's why it's such a big deal and
while they want to control the debate they're not controlling the debate and
this is how wars happen because we're committed to our cause they're committed
to theirs that's why I want to talk to those in the middle the police and
military and say to you you're being trained to take our guns that's now
public you're being trained that veterans and gun owners and George
Washington are bad guys that's public now as well think of how otherworldly and
ridiculous that is and how absurdist but it's really happening
because they have to demonize us ahead of this civil war they want to start and
that's what Homeland Security I saw an article yesterday Aaron Dykes covered it
so the dead David Ortiz on the news where they said Oh nationwide they're
gonna put gunshot detectors up for Homeland Security to detect shooters and
I went and looked it up and sure enough it's microphones see oh we're gonna spy
on you cuz of guns but we're listening to you as well oh
everybody's got to go get a psychiatric evaluation and the government will
decide if you're mentally ill and by the way it's mentally ill to want to own a
gun notice you hear that and gun owners are Nazis and gun owners are clan
members and gun owners help kill the kids at Sandy Hook and gun owners are
scum and gun owners are trash and gun owners are filth I mean you're seeing
Bob Shafer we defeated Hitler we can defeat the gun owners CBS news and a
normal informed person goes man that that that's discrediting not if we don't
resist it to say how dare you they will normalize the idea that we are criminals
inherently because we own guns I mean that tells you how bad these
people are that every FEMA training manual and I've got video of it in road
to tyranny it's online they go and tell police and police have called in you've
heard them yeah no we get sent to training especially the officers you
know the sergeant sent up where they sit around for three days they send them off
to these resorts and the feds come in and they sit there and badmouth America
and tell them how bad America is I mean there's the enemy right there
imagine a movie where you know the feds call in the cops and go the founding
fathers are bad guns are bad families are bad you can't trust people that talk
about wanting sovereignty they're the enemy we've got a train to take their
guns I mean right there folks use the bad guy right there is the foreign
operative I mean it's so over the top but that's how tyrannies are Joseph
Goebbels Nazi propaganda minister and I've read many of his writings said over
and over again and he admired Edward Bernays u.s. propagandists but admired
him but wanted to kill him it was declassified they had plans that when
they took the u.s. by having a occupy government like you don't just come have
the French stand down you don't just have the American stand down they were
going to have a deal with an American government with Senator Bush Prescott
Bush this came out in McCormick Dickstein hearings we can read the
congressional record they were gonna have him and others led by Smedley
Butler as the president the two-time Congressional Medal of Honor winner two
star general who had very high approval ratings they were gonna have him as the
new dictator and he said listen I'm not gonna do that and help stop it but it
was so incredible it would have brought the whole system down so they they shut
it down and nobody went to jail except German spies who were actually German
again this is history when you know this there's no going back that's how the
bankers have taken over is with collaborators but it's a corporate
takeover they've gotten very sophisticated the British Empire in the
last hundred years started losing militarily so they said we'll go into
the US we'll set up the CFR we'll take over their government not for the
British people the British corporate imperial model after World War one they
said we can't beat the Germans they've got all the science all the technology
they call it the German problem in their newspapers and Lord Milner said this was
in public newspapers he said we need to fund radicals in Germany help them
basically have a civil war which Germany had in the streets we'll put radicals in
and then we'll destroy them we'll give them weapons encourage them to attack
Europe after they wreck Europe we'll then take over this is all good go look
it up it was in the cover the front page of the Times of London I've read it the
online scans this was in all our newspapers at the time
just like they put Saddam in just like they create al-qaeda just like they're
trying to radicalize the militias and get us led by feds inside militias to
start an offensive fight they tried to start a civil war in 1993 and then again
in 95 but the police wouldn't go along with it so they couldn't fully carry it
out that's why they're trying to federalize see they they they know what
they're doing again I had family who were colonels and
people in the Confederacy but that doesn't mean that I was for the
Confederacy the Confederacy was a tyranny but so was Lincoln see see it's
not that one side was good one side was bad the south was wronged on tariffs
that ripped off the south and not the north tariffs on on on agricultural
goods not on finished goods not on industrial goods the taxes were wrong
there's a lot of stuff went on but the point and of course Lincoln was a tyrant
but he believed he was doing good the British came in and publicly financed
the south to to and of course the north went along with the manipulation and
and started the war with the south again the problem is it's all history if you
just knew history folks you'd understand how this works now Obama is different
he's not like Lincoln who was just trying to maintain control and went to
tyranny and then didn't and of course then Lincoln didn't want to abuse the
south with reconstruction so they killed him because they wanted the very same
interest one to loot the south the globalist want crime
the globalist want control the the globalist want chaos and they want a
civil war in this country and Ron Paul agrees with me it will cause a civil war
when they come for the guns it's guaranteed and they know that and the
only way to stop them is to go look we know you want to start a civil war we
know you're foreign occupiers we know what you're doing we know you're
illegitimate like the Vichy French again they didn't want to tell people in our
history books that the French see everybody says the French gave up in two
weeks there was only a few army groups that fought back in the French ninety
plus percent stood down and became the new Vichy French government run out of
Vichy France it was only the British that really fought a small expeditionary
group that then ran to Dunkirk and you had the famous evacuation and Hitler
still had a treaty with England that he thought they were going to follow to
divide up Europe with him that's how they set him up so Albert sphere of the
the vice Fuhrer the vice president flew over and parachuted in to meet with the
Lord who'd made the agreement with him that's why they locked him up in the
Tower of London never letting him talk to the media till he died
oh you didn't know about the treaty England had with Hitler see folks this
is all on the record but they won't put it on History Channel they put some of
it on there our government put Mao Zedong into power now declassified
John Birch society said that in the 50s declassified six years ago on History
Channel talking to the ancient CIA section chief about putting now in in
49 of course but you can't tell Americans that's the act like you're not
friends until the 70s when ambassador Bush is sent over to make the deal then
they use the Chinese slaves to leverage out the West and de-industrialize us
consolidating power again
and it's understanding all of this that will help us beat these globalist and so
that's why people are like come on Alex don't you want some sensible gun control
quotes you come part way yeah they always want us to give in something and
then we never give anything to them it they try to act reasonable all day these
are craven gangsters and their dupes who are coming after us and so I get
mobilized I get angry I get upset it is not my wish to be up here at the tip of
the spear it is not a very safe position to be in but there is no future if we
don't beat these people let's go to some of these clips and then I'm gonna
premiere an amazing special report put together by Aaron Dykes and crew
founding fathers battle globalists from the grave we're gonna premiere this
special report here on air that everyone needs to see it hasn't been uploaded to
YouTube and high res yet I'm gonna have it uploaded the Alex Jones channel as
soon as we can in high res there's a medium res version out there but I want
to promote the high res one because it's such an important report and make it the
featured video as soon as it's available but I've told you many times before this
new piers Morgan thing happened that every time I'm at the DNC covering an
event or every time I'm covering anarchist hired by the police every time
I'm at a so-called liberal event when the cameras off they'll come over and
grab me by the arm hoping I do something so the cops can arrest me I mean we've
caught the police working with the anarchists countless times and it's been
on record in Denver and other places they do this and they'll tell me they go
when we take over you're dead and I'll go so you you're here with the police
you'll see the cops watching ten feet away on little yeah you bet we are you
punk I've even had them punch me in the back and then I turn around and see the
cops waiting and then I know to control myself and Mike Hansen even caught some
of this on tape at the G it was the Forbes meeting I guess back in 99 here
in Austin but the point is is I've told you about this and you've also heard the
quote Democrats talk about how you know I want to kill this person I want to
kill that person Alec Baldwin and others I've actually been at the cocktail
parties of these people occasionally when I got invited into things when I
was against Bush not because I'm a socialist but because Bush was doing some
bad things they were so politically tribal that I would get invited in
Austin and New York and LA to cocktail parties with famous designers and
Hollywood folks and they they sit around talking about how they want to kill
conservatives and how disgusting the family is I mean this is what goes on
with these people
and so when I got there and in the day after I was on Piers Morgan they had
Piers Morgan and two of his guests talk about how how I need to be shot and
killed and how and how Piers Morgan will dress up in a uniform to do it I mean
only a criminal psychology would come up with that yes you'll wear a uniform he's
like yes I'll put on a uniform when I do it and you know it's the model you know
daughter of the ambassador Huntsman along with the Daily Beast writer and
Piers Morgan a Buzz Bissinger talking about you'll wear uniforms you do it
yeah yeah I mean folks when you know criminology it's like whoa whoa
fantasizing about dressing up in uniform see it's the state's their power they
they step into the state and then it gives them all this power
and then we found another clip that's up at infowars.com a Paul Watson article
Piers Morgan used machine guns to take out critics and and then we get the
weatherman videos and this was confirmed in federal court and many of them pled
guilty to this they're in meetings saying we're gonna take over put 50
million in camps kill 25 mil and they lick their stinking lips folks these are
these are psychopaths these are fantasy killers because they're weak
these people are sheltered sheltered it's been proven historically and Victor
Hugo wrote about it prosperity makes monsters adversity makes men he actually
said adversity makes men prosperity makes monsters I flip his quote and it's
true these people that's why cultures like Rome at the end where the Emperor's
were so decadent and disconnected from reality we're like kill him kill them
you know kill kill kill because they're just spoiled brats and to them it's real
sexy to talk about killing somebody that's why elites always get so decadent
and sick so here's Piers Piers Morgan the first time talking about how they
want to kill me and then we found a new clip how they want to kill all of us see
they want to kill you you have to understand they want to kill you in the
rape your wife not these people specifically individually but that's
where this leads that's what tyrants end up doing here it is but what do you need
a semi-automatic weapon for the only reason I think you need it is Pierce
challenge Alex Jones to a boxing match show up with a semi-automatic that you
got legally and pop them I'd love to see that and then Pierce goes goes y'all
wear my brother's uniform so again these guys are low-level minions they just
fantasize about you know shooting me but the higher level ones not not not these
little guys but history shows they want to burn cities loot take over let's go
out to break with this next Piers Morgan clip here he is talking about killing
all of us here it is Trini and in his like all of Britain's got talent they'll
do the respective kind of things that they're supposed to focus for you know
lots of us ranting about green credentials his love to sake jokes
Trini talking about what you guys are wearing how do you mark them how would
you scale them what I do is I've replaced the buzzers with a machine gun
and just take them all out and do the public a massive favor what I do is I've
replaced the buzzers with a machine gun and just take them all out and do the
public a massive favor there you go now now again Piers Morgan himself I was
saying not his guest but Piers Morgan mass death and he's dead serious and
he's biting his lip and he's getting excited and that's why physically when I
was around him I got very angry at a primitive level that's why I challenged
him I mean I you know I was like you think you're tough buddy I want to be
the champion of Liberty I'll stand against you I know who you are I know
who you are you you rapacious would-be mass murderer if you've ever wanted one
of our best-selling generators but we're waiting for an offer so crazy you
couldn't refuse then you're not gonna want to miss this exciting message
here's why our solar generators provide life-saving electrical power and unlike
gas generators solar generators run quietly emit no fumes and produce
electricity from the Sun so when the lights go out you'll always have the
power you need now here's the best part every year we accumulate a few solar
generators that we just can't sell as new we put them in a special spot in our
warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of each year we call them
scratch and dent units but they're really just like this each unit comes
with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe don't
wait they go fast go to scratch and dent solar calm that scratch and dent solar
calm for the craziest offer we've ever made go to scratch and dent solar calm
that scratch and dent solar calm in an emergency situation would you drink
contaminated water you could if you have the amazing life straw from my patriot
supply calm life straw is the most advanced personal water filter available
today it filters contaminated water from almost any source life straw is
lightweight and compact perfect for hiking camping or in an emergency like a
flood life straw is easy to clean comes with a one-year warranty and has been
used worldwide since 2005 get the amazing life straw personal water
filter at my patriot supply calm plus check out survival seat vault 20 seed
varieties for only 37 95 Tatler canning lids long-term storable foods as low as
69 95 and much more at my patriot supply calm enjoy stress-free shipping on all
orders over $49 call eight six six two two nine zero nine two seven or visit my
patriotsupply.com that's eight six six two two nine zero nine two seven my
patriotsupply.com for emergency preparedness self-reliance and food
independence weekend by GMOs stressed out about money and blasted by the
electric environment hi I'm pastor Jenny and that was the state I was in back in
2010 then I learned about RNA drops I learned that 97% of my DNA that
scientists have called junk is actually packed with millions of gene switches
that play a critical role in controlling how my cells organs and other tissues
behave I learned I don't have to put up with disease decay or decline like I've
been conditioned to believe I began taking RNA drops a 100% natural formula
designed to turn on those switches and provide me with amazing health and joy
learn more about RNA drops and order a free sample today visit RNA free sample
calm that's RNA free sample calm or call toll-free eight eight eight five seven
seven three seven oh three pay only shipping and handling for a free 30-day
supply of RNA drops get the information you need and the health you want at RNA
free sample calm
you
better get that through your head this world is ruled by violence
and a man's gonna do what a man's got to do
look here's the bottom line folks if you act like a nation of sheep if you act
like a nation cowering the government even if there's good people in government
they will be replaced by people looking to dominate sheep and that process has
been going on that's why great nations that had a lot of freedom it takes a
long time for them to get rid of the old culture of freedom the old culture of
being honorable and again if I could give a brain transplant or like a Vulcan
mind-meld with all Americans or all people in the world and just let them
see what I've seen like the new Star Trek movie that came
out if I could just say here here's what I just saw and have you see all the
quotes and all the things and them grab in my arm and hey what's going on we're
gonna kill you and we take over you know that the first time it happens you're
like man who are you I'm with them and we're taking over soon and I'll be our
time it's always some weird little wimp who would never face you except they've
got the cops there from the special unit not the general cops with the special
event unit ready to set you up their power is because they're a gang of
bullies lined up and then you go to the next event they come over and tell you
they're gonna kill you and I've even caught it on tape where the communists
are in New York and they say we're gonna kill you it's in my film martial law and
I'm like you're gonna kill me they're like yeah we're gonna we're gonna kill
all of you when we take over we're gonna kill you
and see it's not just folks when this is probably I don't want to exaggerate
probably 15 times I've had him tell me in person they're gonna kill me and then
and then now they get on the news and say they're going to kill me I hope his
kids don't get killed hope he didn't get that call some night and piers they cut
to piers and he goes yes and I'm like oh that body language didn't look good I
watch like that's really creepy that's a threat and I'm like I'm not sure but it
looked like it my kids who normally don't scare easier like they're gonna
kill us I'm like no no no no and then five minutes later yeah we ought to kill
Alex yeah we'll dress up in uniforms and do it people like oh it's just a joke
and then we cut to a chilling clip of him in England going the answer is just
to kill all the gun owners line them up and kill them with guns machine gun them
I mean look look look look look you don't have to believe me those of you
that haven't studied history if you knew history you'd know how right I was okay
you'd be having chills right now these are abusive hot tyrants you have cold
wars you have hot wars this is a flaming volcano of meanness of viciousness they
the journey is the destination for them that's like linen they in many towns
they killed 50% the NKVD documents were declassified a few decades ago they'd
say sir we've killed about half the population shit the other quarter to
gulag slave labor thousand miles away there's only a small percentage of
people left now and we need them to basically supply us with food and then
be our servants he'd say no kill them and they'd say why sir and he would he
wrote orders more blood and they would say and he'd say and if you won't do it
I'm gonna kill you and then he would go into these things on the ground flopping
Hitler did this to chewing at the carpet just murder them murder them that's who
they are this is GCN the Genesis communications radio network the new
year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness get serious and
make a stand with supernatural silver this is a breakthrough in silver
technology that is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or
ionic silver supernatural silver can be taken orally every day to help fight
bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds supernatural silver is also
exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water purification it is
the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness go to supernatural
silver calm today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance that
supernatural silver calm check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook
waging war on corruption Alex Jones on the GCM radio network big brother
mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does he he's
Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas Alex Jones
all right Alex Jones here back from an extremely re-energizing and reflective
trip to the high mountains high mountain desert of southwest Texas just never had
a place energized me like that absolute food for the soul I do intend to take
phone calls and we'll do that when max Kaiser's on with us in the third hour
today popping in for one segment I just had to
have him on he heads up the US Small Business Association Obama proposes to
close the Small Business Administration as predicted so they already illegally
don't do everything they can to not give government contracts to small businesses
and have a secret blacklist that he sued and exposed now they're just getting rid
of it period because they don't want anybody getting together and
communicating the giant screw job that's happening and here's an example not a
small business but big heavy industrial twenty two billion dollars was paid to
your taxpayer money to ship General Motors to South America China and Eastern
Europe and again it's not gonna help the Chinese and Eastern Europeans or the
Brazilians I'm not against them getting jobs because they ship it there to
actually lower the wages there and drag ours down it's a globalist plan it's
cold-blooded it's economic domination and see that's why they all push oh like
in World War Z the book how the great South African plan was that you know
just let the general public be killed and how cold-blooded and beautiful it
was and how not being human is so great and how being cold-blooded let me tell
you these globalists want you to be cold-blooded they actually are
hot-blooded and enjoy hurting people and they actually care about their kids
listen I'm not gonna lay over and die so a bunch of hunchback buck-toothed bug
eyed inbred New World Order trash can have their way okay you people are
cancer and I declare info war on you and set my full will and my name and my life
and my soul on the altar of God and God recognizes that God gave us all power
we're just not using our power against the New World Order and greater he that
is in me than he that is in the world and in the only reason we had all this
liberty and all this wealth was because we were evil compared to other countries
we were more god-fearing America was the best the West is the best what developed
here what happened is the greatest expression of human liberty with all its
warts and all its pot marks and all its problems and that's why the New World
Order seeks to expunge that and they send their horsemen their minions like
this piers morgan with his minions talking about shooting me here it is but
what do you need a semi-automatic weapon for the only reason I think you need it
is Pierce challenge Alex Jones to a boxing match show up with a
semi-automatic that you got legally and pop them I'd love to see that now a new
clip surfaced of him in England I guess while he was back visiting for two weeks
before all this happened and there he is sniveling about how line up the gun
owners and just machine gun us with a government gun you notice government gun
good citizen gun bad here it is theoretical situation you've got
Clarkson Trini and in his like all on Britain's got talent they all do the
respective kind of things that they're supposed to be famous for you know
lots of us ranting about green credentials there's lots of sake jokes
Trini talking about what you guys are wearing how do you mark them how would
you scale them and what would I do is I've replaced the buzzers with a machine
gun and just take them all out and do the public a massive favor what I'd do
is I've replaced the buzzers with a machine gun and just take them all out
and do the public a massive favor
always fantasizing about shooting people and since then I've saw some other
videos I forgot to give you guys where he's talking about shooting people and
by the way I've been around these guys they think you can't even touch a gun
unless you're in a uniform they see a guy they go but then they see government
and black Darth Vader outfit that's what you should get concerned about not
scared of the guy the fact that he's trying to scare you you know when
government starts dressing in black Darth Vader outfits you're not in a free
country or you're going the direction of tyranny we'll be back stay with us
sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and
laughing as you get sick and die start purifying your water with pro pure my
friends I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar
none is pro pure and it's available discounted at info wars com its filters
are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth there's no priming
required it's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up
to 95% easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity purify water from
lakes streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in beneficial
minerals which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that
leaches from the plastic probe here is the best gravity-fed filter out there
it's what my family uses info wars calm already has the lowest price on probe
here but if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10%
off and in full wars calm you can also call to order 8 8 8 2 5 3 3 1 3 9
millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other
illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a
revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution recent advances
in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily
to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while
powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as stress
death pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology
has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions the
Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook if you want an American
company with American products made by Americans here is the cow Ben soap
company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years these
all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut
oils that are earth-friendly and safe see them on the web at five star soap
calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog buy the one to two months sample
package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now or save
big with a one to two year supply of soaps or all your cleaning needs this
is an amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and you will love
the way real soap makes you feel see them on the web at five star soap calm
or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
ladies and gentlemen again thank you for joining us I am your host Alex Jones it
is already the 22nd day of January 2013 and the all-out assault on the
Constitution and Bill of Rights is accelerating there is obviously an
intensified attacks not just on the Second Amendment but moves to have the
government grab public and private pension funds we're going to be
covering some of that and also Obama proposes to close the Small Business
Administration as predicted this is a big deal and we're going to have the
head of the Small Business Association on to talk about the shutdown the called
shutdown of a Small Business Administration they're just getting rid
of small business this is absolute war on small business and just as another
proof of the program to de-industrialize and shut down this country also an
incredible video and article up at info wars calm Prince Harry's mental problem
murdering Afghans is like a video game and and and and Prince Harry is playing
with video games talking to the media about how war is just like video games
and again this is all done on purpose just to get you ha ha torture secret
arrest government growing the opium haha yeah video game kill people so no one's
gonna care when you're getting killed this is all being done by design we're
going to be breaking all of that down as well again Piers Morgan says use
machine guns to take out critics on top of saying I should be killed he wants to
kill me there's a new video Nobel Prize nominee says Obama is asking military
leaders if they will fire on US citizens that's up at prison planet.com all this
and a lot more but first I want to premiere here a special report put
together by Aaron Dykes and the rest of our great news crew this is the founding
fathers defending the Republic defending our country from the grave premiering
it here on the radio a high-res version is going up at info wars calm in the
next 20 minutes as well for all the radio listeners to see and get out to
folks here is this amazing special report the Second Amendment to the
Constitution a well-regulated militia being necessary to the security of a
free state the right of the people to keep and bear arms shall not be
infringed shall not be infringed shall not be infringed shall not be infringed
shall not be infringed the founding fathers agree armed citizens make good
government I asked her what is the militia it is the whole people who is
the militia are they not ourselves to disarm the people that is the best and
most effective way to enslave them George Mason Congress have no power to
disarm the militia their swords and every other terrible implement of the
soldier are the birthright of an American tench Cox 1788 the
Constitution preserves the advantage of being armed which Americans possess over
the people of almost every other nation where the governments are afraid to
trust the people with arms James Madison a federalist number 46 a free people
ought not only to be armed and disciplined but they should have
sufficient arms and ammunition to maintain a status of independence from
any who might attempt to abuse them which would include their own government
George Washington the founding fathers created the Bill of Rights enshrined
individual protections including the Second Amendment because they
understood that power inherently corrupts the Bill of Rights was set up
to try to discourage bad behavior from government try to further restrain it
and try to head off what they knew would eventually become misinterpretations of
the law and attempts to misconstrue the intent of the founders but their quotes
here cannot be more clear if the representatives of the people betray
their constituents there is then no recourse left but in the exertion of
that original right of self-defense which is paramount to all positive forms
of government Alexander Hamilton the Federalist number 28 are we at last
brought to such a humiliating and debasing degradation that we cannot be
trusted with arms for our own defense Patrick Henry the Constitution shall
never be construed to authorize Congress to prevent the people of the United
States who are peaceable citizens from keeping their own arms Samuel Adams the
right of citizens to bear arms is just one more guarantee against arbitrary
government one more safeguard against the tyranny which now appears remote in
America but which historically has proved to be always possible
Hubert Humphrey 1960 when governments fear the people there is Liberty when
the people fear the government there is tyranny the strongest reason for the
people to retain the right to keep and bear arms is as a last resort to protect
themselves against tyranny in government Thomas Jefferson the best we can hope
for concerning the people at large is that they be properly armed Alexander
Hamilton the very atmosphere of firearms anywhere and everywhere
restrains evil interference they deserve a place of honor with all that is good
George Washington arms discourage and keep the invader and plunderer in awe
and preserve order in the world as well as property forad mischief would ensue
were the law-abiding deprived of the use of them Thomas Paine to preserve Liberty
it is essential that the whole body of the people always possess arms and be
taught alike especially when young how to use them Richard Henry Lee 1778 a
free people claim their rights as derived from the laws of nature and not
as a gift of their chief magistrate Thomas Jefferson our Second Amendment
our free speech our gifts from God but the fact that they were pointed out
highlighted enumerated and strengthened in the Bill of Rights and Constitution
is our birthright you don't have to like guns you don't have to like the Second
Amendment to fight for it to stand up for it if we let it slip away we're
going to lose everything from free speech on down that light will be dimmed
if we allow them to encroach on the Second Amendment guard with jealous
attention the public liberty suspect everyone who approaches that jewel
unfortunately nothing will preserve it but downright force wherever you give up
that force you are ruined the great object is that every man be armed
everyone who is able might have a gun Patrick Henry dictators and disarmed
populations go together the most foolish mistake we can possibly make would be to
allow the subject races to possess arms history shows that all conquerors who
have allowed their subject races to carry arms have prepared their own
downfall by doing so Adolf Hitler April 1942 before standing army can rule the
people must be disarmed as they are in almost every kingdom in Europe Noah
Webster death solves all problems no man no problem Joseph Stalin in earlier
times it was easier to control 1 million people than to physically kill 1 million
people today it is infinitely easier to kill 1 million people than to control 1
million people Zignu Brzezinski if the opposition disarms well and good if it
refuses to disarm we shall disarm it ourselves Joseph Stalin one death is a
tragedy 1 million is a statistic Joseph Stalin to disarm the people is the best
and most effective way to enslave them George Mason and tyranny always follows
disarm populations it's the history of democide it's what naturally happens
when power is too concentrated in one man in one centralized government in one
tyrannical system as we now see worldwide we were supposed to set up
checks and balances in an attempt to create better government instead we let
our guard down and the corporations have taken over it is the duty of the Patriot
to protect his country from its government Thomas Paine the supreme
power in America cannot enforce unjust laws by the sword because the whole body
of the people are armed you know Webster 1787 ideas are more powerful than guns
we would not let our enemies have guns why should we let them have ideas Joseph
Stalin those now possessing weapons and ammunition are at once to turn them over
to the local police authority firearms and ammunition found in a Jews
possession will be forfeited to the government without compensation whoever
willfully or negligently violates the provisions will be punished with
imprisonment and a fine Nazi law regulations against Jews possession of
weapons 1938 political power grows out of the barrel of a gun chairman Mao
Zedong the only real power comes out of a long rifle Joseph Stalin those who
beat their swords into plowshares usually end up plowing for those who
didn't Ben Franklin if gun laws in fact worked the sponsors of this type of
legislation should have no difficulty drawing upon long lists of examples of
crime rates reduced by such legislation that they cannot do so after a century
and a half of trying but they must sweep under the rug the southern attempts at
gun control in the 1870 to 1910 period the northeastern attempts in the 1920 to
1939 period the attempts at both federal and state levels in 1965 through 1976
establishes the repeated complete and inevitable failure of gun laws to
control serious crime or in hatch and the right to keep and bear arms after a
shooting spree they always want to take guns away from the people who didn't do
it I sure as hell wouldn't want to live in a society where the only people
allowed guns are the police and military William S burrows they've undermined our
economic system they've instituted the Federal Reserve they bought out
politicians and now they're coming for the final restraint on their total power
that is firearms that is guns that is the Second Amendment and if you let them
do it they're going to encroach on our entire lives if you want the right to
control your own life to pursue life liberty and the pursuit of happiness you
must politically stand up for the Second Amendment and say no to these attempts
to use emotional strings the images of dead children okay folks that's only
part of the report there's like two three minutes left it just went up in
high def at the Alex Jones channel on YouTube it premiered last night on
infowars nightly news we just premiered it here on the radio for radio audiences
but the video just went up you can see at 21 views founding fathers battle gun
grabbers from the grave that's the best headline that I can come up with a very
powerful piece put together by our amazing crew your radio listener the
graphics the documentation the quotes make it ten times more powerful founding
fathers battle gun grabbers from the grave we're gonna have that video go up
at infowars calm and present planet calm the next ten minutes get it get it out
to everybody we're gonna tweet it out as well to everyone and make it the
featured video on the Alex Jones channel on YouTube when we come back we're gonna
get into clips of Obama's inauguration as supreme leader dear leader saying
it's time to turn in our guns stay with us
looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves how did we ever survive from natural
disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family
hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that
have lost everything at e foods direct we hear from customers every day that
are fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand
after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the grocery
stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to
help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too early than one
day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what
Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or
go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best
tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet
your life on e foods direct hello this is Ty Bollinger author of the
best-selling book cancer step outside the box I want you to know some very
important information in 1985 president Ronald Reagan requested that carnivora
be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the president could
obtain this world-class healer now 27 years later carnivore capsules are used
around the world to keep people healthy now you can protect yourself and your
loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that
instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single normal
cell if you want to stay healthy now's your chance to literally wake up your
critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body
call one eight six six Venus fly or order from carnivore calm that's car
ni vo ra calm that's one eight six six eight three six eight seven three five
one eight six six Venus fly or visit carnivore calm protect your immune
system it's the only one you've got gold it's like nothing else on earth from the
Romans through the Renaissance from the Industrial Age to the Space Age gold has
weathered the test of time for 6,000 years gold has remained the ultimate
store of wealth according to the World Gold Council in the u.s. mint demand is
at an all-time high the stage is being set for the re-emergence of gold as the
common-sense alternative to a fiat paper currency that gets weaker every day
Midas resources is proud to offer the hard-hitting report that arms you with
the truth you need to protect you and your family from the feds plans for your
hard-earned money don't gamble with your future call Midas resources today and
ask for your free copy of as good as gold call 1-800-686-2237 for the report
the Fed hopes you'll never see as good as gold can be yours by calling 800-686-2237
if you have ever thought about owning gold you must read this report
call Midas today at 800-686-2237 we all know that Berkey water
purification systems are the most trusted name in water filtration as an
authorized Berkey dealer for over six years in serving thousands of satisfied
customers the Berkey guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration
systems the Berkey light systems include a set of self sterilizing and
re-cleanable black purification elements that purify water by removing chlorine
pathogenic bacteria cyst and parasites to non-detectable levels and remove
harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides order the Berkey light system
today complete with two black Berkey elements for only two hundred and thirty
one dollars and the Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge with the
purchase of a Berkey light the Berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride
and arsenic filters for only $39.99 that's over 30% off the retail price
call the Berkey guy at one eight seven seven eight eight six three six five
three that's one eight seven seven eight eight six three six five three or order
online at go Berkey dot-com that's go Berkey dot-com today
Thank you for joining us we are going to get into
the design implosion of our economy and some people say well give us some
positiveness if people are destroying the economy by design I'm gonna explain
this to the next segment the good news is there's a way to fix it it'd be kind
of like if somebody kept stabbing your tires you came in everyday your tires
were stabbed should you just keep going and buying new tires no you should wait
out there till the person comes to stab holes in the tires admitting that
someone's doing it is positive it means that we can fix our economy and I'm
going to explain that coming up in the next segment and tie it into Phil
Mickelson warns of drastic changes because of state of federal tax
situation we've got Americans fleeing Hawaii fleeing California fleeing New
York fleeing other high tax zones to places like Texas so that is coming up
right now let's go to a clip from Obama's coronation yesterday on the
Second Amendment and more through it all we have never relinquished our
skepticism of central authority nor have we succumbed to the fiction that all
society's ills can be cured through government alone our celebration of
initiative and enterprise our insistence on hard work and personal responsibility
these are constants in our character we have always understood that when times
change so must we that fidelity to our founding principles requires new
responses to new challenges the preserving our individual freedoms
ultimately requires collective action for the American people can no more meet
the demands of today's world by acting alone than American soldiers could have
met the forces of fascism or communism with muskets and militia that's global
government no single person can train all the math and science teachers will
need to equip our children pause back it up back in about 20 seconds I want to
hear that musket part again they cut to the military shots of the military and
then they say militias and muskets the message is you can't protect us really
the muskets in the militia are to protect us from you the founders are
clear I just played clips that are on record of what they said and they try to
take the guns over and over again and now they've set up a paradigm where if
you don't give your guns up you're causing more children to die when the
government has made it gun free zones advertise it's a new thing to do go kill
kids and put people on drugs that on record gives them a compulsion to go out
and engage in mass murder while they advertise oh you're being given pills
that make you psychotic now we're going to push this let's go to this clip meet
the demands of today's world by acting alone than American soldiers could have
met the forces of fascism or communism with muskets and militias no single
person can train all the math and science teachers will need to equip our
children that's enough of it or build the roads and networks and research labs
that will bring new jobs and businesses to our shores it's more you didn't build
it garbage now more than ever we must do these things together as one nation
total communism that's enough now again if he came out and said we need to
collectively get behind the Bill of Rights and Constitution to empower
individualism you see because there is a collective of liberty but where the
individual is strong and makes the whole greater that's not their system the
collective is strong the individual needs to be weak it's the devil's
counterfeit and then meanwhile here's the key to all this we're going to come
back and break this down they're saying we know things are tough come together
and we'll get out of this and that's what they have the clergy response team
manuals say and we've seen clergy on TV talk about where they're told they're in
the crisis take the shot go to the FEMA camp do what you're told we'll get out
of this do what you're told we'll get you out of this collapsed mine do what
you're told the economy will come back turn your guns in things will get better
give us a third bailout grease and we'll turn the lights back on things only got
worse it's false hope it is a program where they implode things offer the
solution that's more government things implode more offer the solution more
government things implode more offer the solution more government things implode
more offer the solution more government and then they are exempt from the laws
and regulations and taxes so what happens they set up a system where you
can't operate and only they can it's called monopoly tyranny very cold blood
and they all write white papers and talk about it in agenda 21 and how they're
gonna shut everything off while going things are getting bad it's come
together behind me I'll fix them you see how cold-blooded that is while
they do everything they can to make it impossible to live or be have a farm or
a factory or to work in this country outside of the mega corporations that
are exempt we're on the march the Empire's on the run Alex Jones and the
GCN radio network the new year is a great time to take charge of your health
and wellness get serious and make a stand with supernatural silver this is a
breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver can be taken orally
every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds
supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective
for water purification it is the number one choice for thousands of people for
immune system support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency
preparedness go to supernatural silver calm today and give yourself and your
loved ones a fighting chance that's supernatural silver calm check out our
new low prices and like us on Facebook looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves
how did we ever survive from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the
devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous
economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at e foods direct
we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New
York City wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed but I managed to get
my e foods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece it is better to
be prepared ten years too early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't
feed you heed the warnings and do what Alex has done call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three today or go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and
build your food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term
storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four zero nine five six three
three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct
now that we have moved into the winter season there is an increased need to
support our immunity and health at silver lungs we are committed to meeting
your needs by providing a full selection of silver based products our most
popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our 2 ounce
nano silver nasal applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps just
released is our 100% natural silver gel our new silver gel is not based on
synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the
surface but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin
nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin
while delivering the silver more effectively visit www.silverlungs.com
and click on our store page to find what silver based products are best for you
that's www.silverlungs.com
crashing through the lies and disinformation it's Alex Jones on the
GCN radio network
alright we are back live ladies and gentlemen I'm going to get into just a
few data points of how the federal government which is the occupational
Vichy French government just like under the Nazis I'm not just saying that
that's who they are is trying to dismantle what's left of our country
it's been a soft corporate takeover by anti free market forces they know we're
waking up so now they want our guns they want free speech zones they admit the
NSA is spying on us they want for psychiatric reviews of everybody this is
what's being proposed all right out of a mix of Soviet Russia Nazi Germany I mean
if you know history it's incredible couple issues don't forget this
broadcast is listener supported be sure and support the radio sponsors you both
here locally and the national ads be sure and support our local stations I'm
gonna talk about them in a moment and also go to info wars store calm or info
war shop calm takes you the same place for our secure online shopping cart area
that has the best water filters at the lowest prices like pro pure 10% off
promo code water it's got the Pro Second Amendment t-shirts the info wars ball
caps great to meet like-minded people wearing these around it's got all 20
plus films I've made dozens and dozens of other films and books that I've read
that I think are the best out there the new documentary presentation strategic
relocation breaking down different areas of the country that are safer for
economic reasons military reasons you name it that new film is out along with
the book discounted hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of items that I
endorse that I believe in modify one the best supplement out there from all the
research my top researchers have done doctors and others the best seaweed from
an uncontaminated area in the Pacific off of New Zealand a lot of stuff like
that at info war store dot-com you can also call 888-253-3139 for any orders or
any questions 24 hours a day until five o'clock it is our crew answering the
phones the three great ladies over there and then after that it goes to Haitians
communications that I've been using for about 15 years 16 years a group of
telephone operators here in Austin Texas we could get about a third of the price
in India but our phones are here in Austin Texas as well nothing against
India it's just the point is we're pointing out that we're trying to have
as much stuff happen here in America as we can 888-253-3139 888-253-3139 to call
and this t-shirt sold out again but another truckload is coming it is an
ak-47 with the come and take it Texas flag and it says inside the ak-47 the
right to keep their arms shall not be infringed and on the back it has a
info wars dot-com and best-selling shirt ever even better than the Obama Joker
shirt that we had as a limited edition and my we're going to come back with
that soon not the old design because that was a limited edition haven't sold
that about two years a new Obama shirt is coming out but it's it's got a twist
to it so wait till that happens so all of this and more available at info war
store dot-com or 888-253-3139 or write to us at PO box one nine five four nine
Austin Texas seven eight seven six zero okay let's go ahead now and plug a
couple of our great stations and some of the stations in focus WRX came ninety
six point one FM Cape Coral Florida a hundred thousand watt monster of a
station has been airing the Alex Jones show for almost a year now this is
stations in focus check out their website at 96 rock dot-com and become
sponsors and support them bare minimum spread the word 96 k rock 96 k rock so
that's the letter K there so 96 k rock dot-com also when I have special thanks
to K LRG 880 a.m. Little Rock Arkansas a 50,000 watt mega station covering like
four states I've been up there and heard it sister station of WT AN also airs
Alex Jones their website can be found at K LR G dot tan talk network dot-com and
again we'll put that up on screen for everybody as well who's watching on TV
so 880 a.m. be sure and support both of those are all three of those fine
stations and a new affiliate already rolled in this week WSTP 1490 a.m. has
added our Sunday show live from 5 to 7 p.m. Eastern with a start date of the
27th WSTP 1490 a.m. and we've got more will also announce tomorrow so well over
140 a.m. and FM affiliates as of right now okay again it's hard for me to
get into a subject like this because I want to hit you with a thousand data
points but our guest is holding waiting to cover the latest incredible outrage
that the system is pushing but Obama is looking to get rid of the u.s. small
business administration and consolidated basically in under Homeland Security
just the overall Gestapo and he's selling it like hey you want to get rid
of federal agencies I will get rid of it now here's the issue you're supposed to
have him and our guests will give you all the numbers the majority of money
taxpayer money when it is federal dollars is supposed to go back to small
and local businesses so that at least the argument is if 30 40 percent of our
money is going to the feds it'll come back but that there's got to be a bid
competition to ensure that we don't get ripped off and then that way if we're
going to have a big government system at least our own tax money comes flowing
back to then build up of the economy now the problem with that always is big
government is going to end up having special interests mainly globalists come
in and pay them off and it's come out in the last few years he's filed dozens of
lawsuits dozens and dozens on the subject we'll get the actual numbers I
know it's a lot from him from our guest to to not let small businesses get any
of the money in fact most of them it turns out are foreigners and when the
public wakes up to this they go hey you're right there shouldn't be no bid
contracts for French companies no no this is even American companies that
aren't even allowed to bid in the case of what we saw in Iraq is is that they
spun it as oh yeah you know it's no bid contracts for national security but
turned out it was foreign companies the point is there's just so many angles to
all of this it makes my head spin and you've seen some of the most famous
actors and soccer players in France leaving because they have a 75% income
tax and then on top of that any money that you get to keep over a million
euros another 75% tax in fact some people pay over 80% but 75 is what most
of the high-income earners pay so what's 75 and then 75 on top of that you have
25% left and you take 75 from that not counting all the local taxes I'm you're
talking about not even 10% of your money you keep and and by the way Obama has
hired the big French top economists to help run international and domestic
systems that was in the news two weeks ago and they're calling her this genius
oh it's so genius to have everybody basically working for the government and
then that gives them total control over society well here's a new article out of
Yahoo Sports Phil Mickelson warns of drastic changes because of state federal
tax situation if you add up all the federal and you look at the disability
and the unemployment the Social Security and the state my tax rate is 62 63
percent he said so I've got to make some decisions on what I'm going to do there
are going to be some drastic changes for me because I happen to be in the zone
that has been targeted both federally and by the state and you know it doesn't
work for me now he added so I'm going to have to make some changes and is saying
he may leave and take his business out of California the great exodus so the
globalists say that they need a global government show that you can't escape
them but then they at the global level they're exempt just like EU bureaucrats
are totally exempt from federal EU taxes but they have the head of the EU
bureaucrats the head of the IMF what's the La Grande Lagarde I always
mispronounce it she comes out member and says the Greeks aren't paying enough
taxes on average over 60% and then Howard Dean comes out and says poor
people need to pay more well guess what they are now
payroll taxes kicked in how you like that 3.8% on top of the 10% you were
paying that's almost 14% right there okay that's enough I'm gonna go to our
guest here and he joins us and guys I had the article here it is press release
Obama proposes to close the Small Business Administration as predicted
October 31st 2012 that's when that first came out well now he's back with it that
he's been sworn in so they've been predicting it since then and now
they're moving ahead with it Lloyd Chapman a frequent guest I don't have
more time for him here today and I appreciate him joining us ASBL.com he
joins us he's a private group who's been successfully lobbying for millions of
small businesses and he's the biggest small business organization outside of
the Better Business Bureau and a few others in the Chamber of Commerce and
he's been exposing how they do everything they can to make sure small
businesses cannot get one dollar and it's and it's illegal what's happening
so now Obama wants no oversight and no group period to even dispense it okay so
Lloyd Chapman born and raised in Texas he began his career working of course
for Bob Bullock famous Democrat spent eight years the Texas Comptroller's
Office before moving to California to enter the computer industry and I'm not
going to go through how he launched successful technology firms and things
like that and how he was involved in congressional intervention and
investigations of f-22 stealth fighters and things like that he's gotten a lot
done how many lawsuits have you filed total oh probably about 40 40 so I said
dozens and dozens that was accurate okay I burn most the time here we got two
segments left run through what we're facing and what this means all right
well I like to I like to talk about the facts I'm trying to be persuasive so
according to the US Census Bureau small business in America responsible for over
90% of the net new jobs half the gross domestic product half the private sector
workforce and over 90% of all u.s. exporters so if you want to create jobs
you've got to do it through small businesses the Coppin Foundation at a
study a couple years ago that said small businesses have created 100% of the net
new job since 1980 that means fortune 1000 firms haven't created one net new
job in over 30 years so small businesses of a heart and soul of our nation's
economy there's one agency in Washington to help the small businesses that's the
Small Business Administration it's actually fairly small agency there's 28
million small businesses and Barack Obama is gonna try to close it which
would be economic suicide and I'm trying to stop him and I don't know why he
wants to close it I I guess the only reason he wants to close it is to cover
up the fraud and abuse that's going on during his administration I know if you
saw the story but the New York Times in a story of a couple of months ago if the
Obama ministration gave 900 over 900 million in US government small business
contracts to a Russian-owned international arms dealer called rose
born exports that's the type of thing that Barack Obama's doing and there's
been a number of federal investigation yes we did see that that was huge news
and that's only the tip of the iceberg absolutely the Inspector General for the
Small Business Administration that he appointed has stated every year of his
administration the number one challenge at the Small Business Administration is
the diversion of federal small business contracts to large corporations and
they've named it one of the largest challenges facing the entire country so
I think Obama's gonna try to close the SBA by combining it with probably the
Commerce Department and it's just an attempt on his part to cover up the
rampant fraud abuse and it's going to be devastating to our economy if he's
successful and I hope people will join us in fighting the Obama administration
to save the only agency to help the middle class and as usual mr. Chapman
there's all this spin that is involved at so many levels to this where Obama's
selling it like I'm gonna get rid of waste I'm gonna get rid of a bad agency
and I'm gonna cut government but really this is the agency that makes sure
federal funds actually go to real US companies and ie small ones absolutely
federal law says a minimum of twenty three percent of the total value of all
federal contract should go to small businesses I don't think there's a
better way to invest our tax dollars in then to reinvest back into the companies
that create all the jobs companies were most Americans work and he wants to get
rid of that he says he's gonna save three hundred million dollars a year in
the federal budget that's that's peanuts the Pentagon misplaces hundreds of
billions to put it into perspective he says he's gonna close the SBA to save
three hundred million a year it is gonna increase foreign aid by nine billion a
year that would be enough to do two things put an armed guard at every
school in America are run the SBA for a decade so his story about closing the
SBA to say three million a year is just ridiculous it's not believable and again
Lloyd Chapman joins us he is the head of the ASBL American Small Business League
really the only group out there kind of like Gunners of America that's that's
that's medium-sized and really fighting hard you know you're a nice guy and you
you're not a psychopath you're not a sociopath you're not a control freak so
you go I don't know why he's doing this well you know I mean you've helped break
it in the national news a few years ago where they create secret black lists for
small businesses where they're taking the majority the money and giving it not
just a mega corporations but foreign corporations he paid 22 billion of the
bailout money to General Motors to ship it to China vault Cadillac and and other
factories some others went to Brazil others Eastern Europe they're doing
everything they can we went from 25 million on food stamps to 49 million his
first four years they want us dependent they're globalists it's agenda 21
California knows when they raise taxes it's gonna kill the state I mean they
know what they're doing they want us bankrupt it's cold-blooded they want to
destroy this country they want to break us to bring us into collectivism they're
doing this period in fact what's the percentage I saw in the Wall Street
Journal in a report talking about you like a year ago how much of the small
business contracts actually goes to multinationals oh probably maybe half
and then total goes to big companies that's supposed to be going to small
ones right I mean I mean obviously if you're gonna have you know trillions of
dollars the federal government it better come back into America at least that
creates some jobs it gives them still control but I mean they're killing their
own golden goose here absolutely the Small Business Act is the most efficient
effective economic stimulus program in the history of America if Barack Obama
would simply quit giving federal small business contracts to fortune 500 firms
that not only are not creating jobs but shipping jobs overseas it would create
more jobs do more to boost the economy anything here President Bush ever spoke
of it's so simple he could do one executive order would take him five
minutes and just says a federal government would no longer report awards
to publicly traded companies or foreign-owned companies as small
business awards it would put as much as 200 billion a year an existing federal
infrastructure spinning back into the middle class but he's not going to do
that and he's going to destroy our economy there there's no logic behind
taking federal funds about largely going to the the middle class where most
people work and all the jobs are created and giving it to foreign-owned companies
that there's there's no way to justify totally illegal I mean again I kind of
bumbled it earlier we're going to break gonna come back and continue along this
but you know the point is the the no bid contracts came out in Iraq hundreds of
billions of dollars something was over a trillion total trillion seven like the
whole thing and still going but they're sitting there saying oh you know be
quiet we've got to have no bids for national security for American companies
it was foreign companies getting in a no bid I mean it's even worse but to the
general public oh we got to do it for national security for American companies
it's foreign companies I mean ladies and gentlemen the foreign companies come in
and lobby to take your tax money out of the country this is how we've been
occupied and conquered this is economic espionage if you've ever wanted one of
our best-selling generators but we're waiting for an offer so crazy you
couldn't refuse then you're not going to want to miss this exciting message
here's why our solar generators provide life-saving electrical power and unlike
gas generators solar generators run quietly emit no fumes and produce
electricity from the Sun so when the lights go out you'll always have the
power you need now here's the best part every year we accumulate a few solar
generators that we just can't sell as new we put them in a special spot in our
warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of each year we call them
scratch and dead units but they're really just like new each unit comes
with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe don't
wait they go fast go to scratch and then solar calm that scratch and then solar
calm for the craziest offer we've ever made go to scratch and then solar calm
that scratch and then solar calm
hey there Frank Bates here have you heard about the weird device that could
wipe out 280 million Americans this is really scary stuff defense experts warn
that this odd device poses the greatest threat we've ever known in fact just a
few weeks ago former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed
piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat I can't believe
that more people aren't talking about this it may be because the liberals and
the government are trying to cover it up that's why my friend just created a free
video at weird device calm that exposes this threat and blows the doors off the
conspiracy go watch the shocking video at weird device calm right now to
discover exactly what it is plus discover the number one way you and your
family can survive this deadly attack I'm not sure how long this video be
online so go to weird device calm before it's gone forever again that's weird
device calm don't throw away leftovers instead throw all your leftovers
vegetable peels eggshells coffee grounds pizza crusts and more into the Bokashi
if you love to garden and compost but don't like the hassle of turning a
compost bin or this smell then check out the EM Bokashi food waste recycling
system from tereganics finally a way to recycle all your food and plant waste
safely and effectively and stop using fertilizers the EM Bokashi food waste
recycling system rather than decomposition the Bokashi system uses
fermentation to break down waste so it takes less time to create nutrient-dense
humus for crops or gardens with no turning and no obnoxious odors to learn
more and order your Bokashi online visit tereganics.com and click on the orange
button that's tereganics.com spelled t-e-r-a-g-a-n-i-x.com or call eight six
six three six nine three six seven eight that's eight six six three six nine
three six seven eight recycle all your food wastes in about six weeks with the
Bokashi food waste recycling system from tereganics.com. Tereganics. Life's getting
better.
We got our guest a little bit into the next hour the Max Kaiser is joining us
on the economic front and a lot more
this video this is breaking news I haven't seen by pointed out TSA groped
attendees at Obama inauguration and and they searched them they groped their
genitals and they did the the full frisk because you're a criminal government is
God you are bad and then you see people like Saddam Hussein and others they can
stand around with everybody thousands of people firing machine guns in the air no
one shoots them but but our supposed free leaders and again the globalists
selected who could run they put the billions of dollars in to put who they
wanted in both guys basically wanted the same thing one just paid lip service to
you did build that the other didn't
Romney was a placeholder
and now we're seeing the fruits of it so I'm gonna do a report this week that
Obama why Obama really is a dictator that is his office has become a
manufactured synthetic presidency and the only word for that is dictatorship
and he's acting dictatorial with all these edicts again normally I say get
rid of the Department of Education get rid of all these groups because we
shouldn't have them running our local schools we should have taxes cut keep
the taxes in the state but I've got to say because the law plugs in to the
Small Business Administration it's designed to make sure the money does go
to the lowest bid contractor who has a good track record in the 50 states not
to foreign globalist so what will Obama's trying to shut this
administration down do you know when when you're talking about Obama there's
been a number of federal investigations during his administration and I'm just
reading these these reports and all the reports say that his administration is
diverting these federal funds and by law should be going to the middle class for
some of the biggest companies in the world you know Lockheed Boeing north north
of Raytheon Finn mechanic in Italy rose born in Russia companies and in South
Korea so it's just it's just a tragedy if you really want to know who Barack
Obama is he's he's a man in the middle of the worst economic downturn in 80
years when the statistics show irrefutably that small businesses create
between 99 percent of jobs he's doing everything he can to take that money and
divert it to the large businesses that most likely have created one job in 30
years and the law says he can't do that and remember the law he's breaking the
law to do that and the corporate whore media is barely starting to cover it I
want to warn everybody that works for the system you're not going to have a
country anymore if you don't stop things like this the reason we have you on five
or six times a year mr. Chapman is because what you're saying is a real
solution have the money go back to America it is a no-brainer it there
there's no logic I would love to have anybody in the country of Obama's
biggest supporter explain to me you know how it's good for America to take our
tax dollars that by law should be going to American companies and giving it to a
Russian-owned international arms dealer are some of the biggest companies in
Europe and Asia there there's no way to to to explain that by the way are you
are you familiar with Obama's Jobs Council I saw a story about that the
everyday tell folks about that oh well Obama's got a Jobs Council of all
fortune 500 firms now according to again the US Census Bureau and the Kauffman
Foundation it doesn't look like fortune 500 firms have created one job in 30
years and that's who Obama's Jobs Council the president was ahead of GE
GE is shipping more American jobs overseas the other company so it's
insane in a clear in the aggregate and then those are cut numbers is actually
worse we're losing jobs but in the aggregate not one new job from fortune
500 almost what is it 97% are made by the small businesses and then meanwhile
but see that's what he does oh we don't have 50 states anymore we have a
governor's council I appoint oh we don't have local counties anymore we have a
rural council I created that's what he does he creates a counterfeit that then
is represented by the globalist we'll be back stay with us you are listening to
GCN visit GCN live.com today sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks
adding poison to your water and laughing as you get sick and die start purifying
your water with pro pure my friends I've done a lot of research and the best
gravity filter out there bar none is pro pure and it's available discounted at
info wars.com its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth
there's no priming required it's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters can
reduce fluoride up to 95% easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity
purify water from lakes streams ponds and wells this filter system leaves in
beneficial minerals which is key save money by not buying bottled water and
avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic propure is the best gravity-fed filter
out there it's what my family uses info wars.com already has the lowest price on
propure but if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional
10% off and info wars.com you can also call to order 888-253-3139
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN radio network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
all right Max Keiser is coming up to the balance of the hour after the break Lloyd
Chapman is our guest right now with the ASBL.com American Small Business League
the globalists are getting rid of all the agencies not the bureaucrats but the
command structure in the mandate because these agencies are mandated by law if
Obama creates a new agency it's still illegal but somehow he can put new
people in who will just do whatever he says because bureaucrats have got
problems but a lot of them are like yeah in fact in all their studies are like
yeah this is supposed to go to local businesses US businesses small
businesses it's not happening and so they don't even like their own agencies
so just get rid of it because you know as bad as some bureaucrats are they're
basically committing suicide politically and economically there's some other
breaking news up at infowars.com that is so incredible so incredible video
photographer attacked by Metro security for taking pictures and filming yeah
more and more police are and and security people are beating people up
even on the street corners or arresting them for filming I mean government does
not want you filming and this is crazy we'll have to show some of that and talk
about it as well that's up at infowars.com let's go back to Lloyd Chapman
look we're almost out of time I know you wanted to comment on the Piers Morgan
thing give us a quick comment on that and then what we can do to help defeat
Obama getting rid of this agency and ignoring the law I love you on Piers
Morgan by the way I've watched it several times I loved it now you told us
that in the email you wanted to make a comment so go ahead what's your take on
it well here's what Piers Morgan doesn't understand FBI says about 20 children a
year killed in schools 1,500 a year killed by their parents and parents
more children are killed by lightning if you've got a child in school they're
more likely to die from a lightning strike than they are in school a
thousand kids a year commit suicide more kids are killed by bee stings then guns
in schools and about the same number of children are killed by dogs every year
as they are guns in schools guns in schools are not a problem children being
killed by guns in school is not in the top ten reasons children die three
thousand children a year die from head injuries riding their bicycles so when
you talk about these average over the last decade of 21 children you're being
killed in schools it's statistically insignificant it's not even in the top
ten reasons on the Piers Morgan show you mentioned 11,000 people in America killed
by gun violence ten times as many people in America die from the known side
effects of properly prescribed and properly taken pharmaceutical drugs ten
times as many people it's a total fear-mongering hoax manipulating our
hearts absolutely it's a tragedy that those 20 children got killed but again
they're more there they're 75 times more likely to be killed by their parents
they're twice as likely to get struck by lightning so it's it's actually
statistically insignificant and if anybody like Piers Morgan wants to worry
about saving children he needs to you know launch a program to protect them
from these prescription drugs here's the problem they all know this stuff they
want to disarm us why do they want to disarm us in your view well I think that
you know when you look at the home of security buying you know 1.8 billion
rounds of hollow point bullets and urban assault vehicles and surveillance drones
they got something in mind that we don't know about and they want to disarm us
and of course as you've talked about a million times disarming the people's the
first thing that dictators always have always sent throughout history and it's
the opposite the founding fathers one of the founding fathers wanted us to have
the firepower to overthrow the government if ever if the government
came oppressive a pierce morgan talks about why do you need assault rifle why
you need 30 shot clip well when the government stormtroopers start kicking
in your front door with automatic weapons with 30 shot clips you're gonna
want you know an assault rifle 30 shot clip to try to defend you and your
family so people need to understand assault rifles and 30 shot clips are
not for hunting they're not to protect your home there to make sure that the
American people have the ability to protect well said Lloyd Chapman will
talk to you again soon god bless you great job the new year is a great time
to take charge of your health and wellness get serious and make a stand
with supernatural silver this is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver
supernatural silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses
infections yeast and molds supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound
care and is highly effective for water purification it is the number one choice
for thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect
choice for your emergency preparedness go to supernatural silver calm today and
give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance that supernatural silver
calm check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook you prepare by
purchasing gold food and firearms but if you don't have a home security system
then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection when
you're sleeping or away from home who's watching out for intruders check out
simply safe it's a new do-it-yourself home security system that is completely
wireless go to get simply safe calm simply safe is independent and off the
grid it runs on battery power so even if the grid goes down you're protected it's
completely customizable so you can use it in your home business boat trailer
storage unit or shed get simply safe calm simply safe is also ridiculously
easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes so there's no need to let a
stranger into your home if you move or need to relocate you can take the system
with you wherever you go you aren't always at home but simply safe will
stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days a week again
that's get simply safe calm millions of people are going to get sick this winter
from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with
supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution
recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that
can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help
improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every
day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as
stress staff pneumonia colds flus and other harmful pathogens this new
technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at
several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions
the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver calm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver calm and like us on Facebook we now take you live to
the Central Texas command center in the heart of the resistance you're listening
to the Alex Jones show
Max Kaiser is a retired very successful stockbroker he also helped invent what
is used on many stock exchanges today he invented the virtual trading a Hollywood
Stock Exchange system and he's done shows with BBC RT press TV you name it
radio host TV host I was on his show that actually aired over the weekend and
that video is posted up at info Wars calm at least I gave it to the guys to
post this morning I didn't see it in the top story so I'm gonna have it reposted
up there an important interview we did on several subjects but max joins us
here today and we're gonna be talking to him in just a moment I wanted to plug if
you go to info Wars calm founding fathers battle gun grabbers from the
grave special report it just incredible video put together by Aaron Dykes and
crew that needs to go out to everybody this is powerful and is cyanide to the
globalist lies it is absolutely essential video founding fathers battle
gun grabbers from the grave top featured video at info wars calm and prison
planet calm you heard us air part of it last hour okay going to max Kaiser of
max Kaiser calm he joins us from London max so much is happening and I wanted to
get you on about the economy because you know they're buying urban assault
vehicles 1.6 billion bullets training the army for martial law that's all
declassified gearing up like it's the end of the world and you believe that by
the end of April we're gonna see the next phase and implosion we're already
in an implosion they just use more debt and welfare checks and you know the
government little credit cards to keep things going it's a consolidation
program but now we've seen a bunch of countries the biggest of which Germany
the key to the EU repatriating their gold saying saying in the news I saw in
the Financial Times we don't trust the US anymore so even the crux in running
Germany don't trust the crux over here so are we seeing that creeping towards
the exits that you've warned about then we'll get into the your take on the
Second Amendment what's coming up in the economy this African invasion or even
mainstream news is saying terror in North Africa our Westerners pulling the
strings of al-qaeda I mean even mainstream news now goes is is NATO in
the u.s. staging stuff to be able to invade duh duh look at Libya look at
Syria again joining us max Kaiser max so much is happening I hope that your bold
prediction is not true but unfortunately it looks like we're creeping towards the
eve of financial collapse we'll talk about what that collapse will look like
as well max Kaiser yeah well nice to be on again and thanks for coming on my
show and I think you describe it well creeping toward the exits and this is
what the German gold repatriation story is all about and as you point out the
central banks have lost trust in each other and they are taking their gold out
of banks in respective vaults around the world and they're bringing it all home
and they're doing this in a way that will precipitate and accelerate this
collapse that we've been talking about and to give you an idea for how this all
works in Britain for example the government says they have 300 tons of
gold here in Britain but my sources tell me that they have leased out or sold
over a thousand tons so we have a fractional gold standard around the
world that is keeping these central banks afloat and now that they all want
their gold back they find out that the gold's not there back when Germany took
900 tons from Britain back during the 2000 2001 period Gordon Brown to
satisfy Britain's dissatisfied Germany's demand for gold to be sent back in
Germany at that time he ended up having to sell 400 tons of Britain's gold so
Britain had to sell 400 tons and that's about over well over a trillion dollars
now that he gave away because the price of gold at that time was 250 dollars an
ounce now it's $1,700 an ounce and this is this is a problem going forward the
Netherlands want their gold Germany wants their gold China's buying gold but
these central banks that say that they have gold it's turned out that they
actually leased the gold which is a way for them to to put on their books that
they still own the gold when when the Fort Knox for example when they lease
the gold and they claim that that is as good as owning the gold itself but when
if you were to audit the Fort Knox you would find that most of the gold has
been leased and that means sold so when people come then to claim their gold
they find that it's not there the Bank of New York when Germany it says that
they want the gold over seven years well as a panic in the gold market builds
they're gonna want that gold a lot sooner and they're gonna be told that we
don't have the gold to give you because we sold it I want to stop you right
there because something I want to do when we're able to budget in hiring a
researcher or an archiver is when I have guests on like you I'm gonna have them
sit there and put the key points you say basically into a scroll at the bottom
like mainstream television but also put it on a computer so we can search a
database of when you've been on the radio slash TV show because max at
nauseum for about two years in almost every interview so there's probably 20
of these you have said that you'll know that it's about to collapse when they
start demanding gold from Britain and from the US and that they've leveraged
it at least ten to one in fractional reserve and that it's the fraud of the
silver and gold reserves that will finally bring them down and that they
want to have a controlled collapse without this happening but that if they
do go for the gold and silver this way that that's a signal that things are out
of control now now you've said that over and over and over again and my guests
through this all the time because we have guests on that are right they could
have guests on that were right on national TV here in mainstream news but
they don't want you to be right they don't want the slaves to know what they
know but max you're scaring me because you've said this over and over again
that this would be the sign and now it's not just Germany demanding the gold from
the US and England in places this is really scary so you've got the floor
till we got a break in five minutes break down how you knew this was coming
and what this signifies and how you think they'll satisfy at this time it
started really back in 2008 on March 17th of 2008 Stacy Herbert and I we were
making a documentary we were in Frankfurt Germany we were at the
boondis bank and we were talking to people at the boondis bank and this was
right when Bear Stearns was collapsing and gold shot up above a thousand
dollars an ounce and he ended up there at a very historic moment and I asked
you know I'd like to see the gold and the response from the boondis bank was
well you know most of it is in New York now that that film was later broadcast
Al Jazeera English and it was a shock to the people in Germany and another
journalist named Lars Scholl picked it picked up the ball and he's been
hammering journalists and bankers now every year for four years until the
point where boondis bank came out and said due to the popular pressure we are
we have have to admit that we have these huge gold positions held in the New York
Fed and we're going to now repatriate this gold we're taking the gold back and
then my sources tell me that the New York Fed said well we don't want you to
start a run on the gold market so we're gonna space this out over seven years
and but this was really going back to what we discovered in 2008 which is that
the gold that these banks say that they have they don't have and this set off a
fire you know a trigger now over the past four or five years what you have is
central banks and governments to keep the economies afloat have been
aggressively buying their own bonds they call it quantitative easing and you know
your other guests talk about this like Gerald Cilenti talks about this a lot
they buy their own bonds as a way to keep interest rates low or to keep bond
prices high now here's an amazing statistic the bond price in America has
not been as high as it is today in the 240 years that America has existed the
bond price the government bond price in the UK and Britain has not been as high
since 1694 when the Bank of England was created the bonds are where the dot-com
was in 2000 it's where the stock market was in 1987 it's where the real estate
market was in 2005 there it's a historic peak at a bubble peak now whether the
bonds collapse between now and April as I predicted on your show last year it
could happen I think it could happen I might be wrong but I won't be wrong by
much I could be wrong by a few weeks a few months but that's what we're going
to see we're going to see bonds collapse we're gonna see gold now panic buying in
the gold market taking gold a lot higher and of course it's all ties in to what
we launched on your show two years ago crash JP Morgan by silver the price of
silver was around 26 we at that time there was such a furor to buy silver it
moved up to be pulled back now to the low 30s but now we're seeing the price
of silver after this consolidation period now looks like it's going along
with gold you're going to see new highs and silver so silver will get over 50
60 70 dollars an ounce but that's that that those are individuals now who don't
trust the banking system they're not just governments and for individuals
they reach for silver because it's a lot easier to get it's cheaper and max the
public here going to break they're all buying survival goods shelters guns
they're voting with their purchases shelling they don't trust the system the
elites are all buying armored redoubts and getting bodyguards they don't trust
the system this looks like quite a mess we're going to enter well there's a good
point you're making there because it's the to contrast today with the 1930s
people say this is similar to 1930s there's a big difference between now
1930s in the 1930s there was a liquidity problem banks needed cash to keep their
business going for their deposits but today if that's not the problem the
problem is an insolvency issue these big to failed to too big to fail banks they
are technically insolvent they're zombie back they're being kept alive with this
money printing that they're the politicians tell us what we need to print
the money we don't want to repeat the mistakes of the 1930s that's false it's
not like the 1930s it's not a liquidity issue it's an insolvency issue and
they're keeping the banks alive with this cheap money and 0% interest rates
to keep their buddies afloat all right stay there stay there by the way kvue is
reporting CNN refuses to show live coverage very suspicious mass shooting
at Lone Star College in Houston we'll be back hello I'm Alex Jones myself my
family the info wars comm team want to relay to you and your families that we
are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front info wars comm
is leading the fight against the technocrats but we can't do that without
your help by getting the film's bumper stickers and t-shirts and info wars
comm you will wake up people in your area and support our operation as we
move to the next level we need your help to spread the word like never before
they wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of
freedom and darkness you are the response to the globalist technocrats
and their program of global eugenics dehumanization and ultimate
extermination the war is here it's an info war the spirit of 1776 versus the
mindset of 1984 it's time for a home security quiz answer this what
effective home security device is smaller than a coffee cup fakes out
burglars into thinking someone is home at your house while you're away plugs
into any wall outlet is recommended by many police departments and sells for
less than $35 yes it's fake TV this year about one in every 50 US homes will have
a break-in with burglars usually picking the easy target a dark house that looks
like no one is home fake TV is a small electronic security device that makes it
look like someone is home watching TV by simulating the light from a real TV it's
like a lamp on a timer but far more convincing and for only $34.95 fake TV
could be the difference between coming home to a secure house or one that's
been ransacked go to fake TV comm or call 1 8 7 7 5 fake TV that's 8 7 7 5 3
2 5 3 8 8 or go to fake TV comm fake TV the burglar deterrent quantitative
easing unemployment at depression levels Europe financial system falling apart
China getting out of US Treasuries at the end of 2008 the time of TARP the
national debt was at 11 trillion gold trading around $850 per ounce close to
2012 the national debt exceeded sixteen point four trillion gold double to
sixteen hundred dollars problems the 20 trillion threshold for the national debt
is inevitable politicians in Washington have a ferocious appetite for spending
its stimulus what's worse a printing press to finance a hundred years ago we
had a gold standard to limit this madness but now you have to adopt your
own gold standard don't be fooled with paper promises get Midas resources ten
reasons to buy gold free by calling 800 6 8 6 22 37 understanding the gold and
silver market may be the only insurance you could have to avoiding the next
economic crises call 1 800 6 8 6 22 37 and order your free copy again that's
800 6 8 6 22 37 you land in Buenos Aires then our shuttle to Santa Rosa where a
nicely furnished cabin with all amenities Wi-Fi executive food and wine
and laundry service awaits after a good night's sleep your adventure begins
you're on a golden stag safari for big game but it's not Africa it's Argentina
one-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo booger bighorn Rams wild boar
and the biggest stag deer in South America all gold medal quality all the
action you can handle land rovers top rental guns with scopes all food
beverages hunting guides ground transportation included and more all
more affordable than you can imagine the adventure of a lifetime starts at
golden stag safaris.com the big game hunting ranch golden stag safaris.com
obviously we have it recorded and we'll have it on the nightly news tonight I'll
follow special report for info Wars calm for all the radio listeners as this
develops at least three people shot at Lone Star College in Houston and and I
walked out there during the break and CNN's going we're not going to show live
feeds we'll show selective clips so now oh we're not gonna show live feeds but
who is is KHOU so we need to go to their website KHOU and KVUE has it so we've
now reached the point where CNN will not show you what's happening oh because we
might see other shooters in camo getting arrested and then we're told oh no the
five-year-olds saw that we never put that on the news oh you know go back to
sleep this is an operation Gladio we're not we're not staging something I tell
you Max Keiser people can debate you know whether a gun culture is a good
thing or a bad thing when anti-state folks don't like guns we know they're
here to protect us from tyranny but why is the government arming to the teeth
while rushing to disarm us is it because they don't want us to be armed during
the collapse I think that's a pretty fair statement the the bond when the
bond market collapses as we've talked about because it's a bubble it's in a
300 year high bubble and I look at what's happening in the markets to give
me a clue what the big money is doing and I know that JP Morgan over the past
couple of years has been developing huge positions monopoly like positions and
food copper industrial metals and in precious metals and they're doing so
because they know what's coming that hyperinflation is coming and they want
to be able to totally control that market for example JP Morgan Justin got
involved in launching an exchange-traded fund for copper so that means and they
and before they did so they bought something like 20% of the world's copper
supply so now the price of copper is going to start going up aggressively
higher because it's being manipulated higher because JP Morgan and the bankers
on Wall Street there will want to make have a new way to make money it's going
to be on commodities they've made all the money they possibly can over 30
years in the bond market because the bond market the interest rate under Paul
Volcker got 15 to 16 percent on the 10-year bond it hit this huge high on the
interest rate and during the past 30 years now gone down to zero during that
30-year period was the biggest bull market on Wall Street in history selling
bonds and bond related equities and stocks and options etc now that 30-year
period is over and we're going to answer into a period of commodity price
appreciation JP Morgan already knows it Goldman Sachs already knows it and
they're buying huge positions into these markets and as far as what's going you
know in in the US if the price of food gets to a certain level it causes
riots we know historically that when the price of food gets to around 40% of an
individual's income you look for a riot that's the point that got to in Egypt
before the Egyptians staged a riot revolution in their country and they
don't want us armed so that we can't protect ourselves but that might
actually cause total rioting or even the government gets taken down but the
tyrant's instinct is to disarm us so much they still don't care but
historically if they take the general public's guns that will make the
government even more unstable so in the u.s. the average American spends
something in the order of 12 to 15 percent of their income on food and
that's still you know it's not at 40% but as prices now begin to go up
because of the manipulation coming in the collapse of the bond market and the
loss of purchasing power from the dollar you're going to get to the point where
the food costs are going to be out of reach for a very very large percentage
of the population and so stay there stay there we gotta go to break but I've got
to play just a minute or so this is kho you and out there on dish Network and
the other cable we've got CNN says they won't show it live we're watching it
live they don't want you hearing the original eyewitness accounts this is
very suspicious turn it up and students are not right yeah correct so basically
uh this is live at 128 and soon as I heard the bullet the bullets flying
whatever the gun being you know fired off CNN will not let you see this you
know that was hit very suspicious so you ran right yeah I ran because uh
basically here's found that you know out of the ordinary you're gonna run so you
know that's just again why don't they want people to hear what happened live
get out the way because I don't want to be a you know victim or anything that's
a Brittany Mobley she's a student here at Lone Star College on the Northside
campus you can see there is still plenty of law enforcement activity here on the
scene they are allowing students to leave we're not sure how much
communication is going on to students other than they're being told that they
can leave but probably not come back today at are they supposed to get in the
fetal position as I can tell you look at me a higher death toll the road it's one
of the entrances off of Aldine Westfield there's another checkpoint all the way
down back here on the other side tell us how many dead point where we're told
that some vehicles potentially even all vehicles from students here on this
scene nobody's dead as they leave one officer did tell me I hope this
intimate mass shooting who are plenty well right back with Max Kaiser stay
with us stay with us at this point you can see this student mass shooting in
Texas public's not too big oh my gosh that's oh boy we're on the March the
Empire's on the run Alex Jones and the GCN radio network sick of the global
issue Genesis control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as you
get sick and die start purifying your water with pro pure my friends I've done
a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is pro pure
and it's available discounted at info Wars calm its filters are silver and
pregnant to prevent bacterial growth there's no priming required it's NSF 42
certified optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95% easy to set up
and use doesn't require electricity purify water from lakes streams ponds and
wells this filter system leaves in beneficial minerals which is key save
money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic
probe here is the best gravity-fed filter out there it's what my family
uses info wars calm already has the lowest price on pro pier but if you add
the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10% off and in full wars
calm you can also call to order eight eight eight two five three three one
three nine looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves how did we ever survive from
natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to
the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to
those that have lost everything at e foods direct we hear from customers
every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm by having a supply of
food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the
grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be
able to help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too
early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the
warnings and do what Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six
three three today or go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your
food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the
planet call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three or a foods direct
comm slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct if you want an American
company with American products made by Americans here is the cow Ben soap
company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years these
all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut
oils that are earth-friendly and safe see them on the web at five star soap
calm or call eight hundred three four zero seven zero nine one for a free
catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice
as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of
soaps for all your cleaning needs this is an amazing deal you can save
thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel see
them on the web at five star soap calm or call eight hundred three four zero
seven zero nine one for a free catalog
crashing through the lies and disinformation it's Alex Jones on the
GCN radio network
you know why they want only a few globalist controlled national news
networks because they want to be able to control the narrative and tell you what
they want we are showing KHOU 11 on screen right now for TV viewers at
info Wars calm and of course we're doing it via fair use of a news event here in
our state to document what's happening CNN during the break we've got it
recorded we're gonna have a report out on this said quote I just saw it again
we are not letting you see live feeds because of what you might see and it is
bodies laying on the ground with paramedics around them looks like from
helicopter with a shot where you can't even make out of their male or female I
mean you got shoot-em-up video games mass murder on TV in the 60s they'd show
kids naked running down rice paddy roads with their skin hanging off because
it was documentary that's why in old radio they would allow cussing only if
it was a real event that happened not because people wanted to hear cussing
but because you want to hear what really happened for documentary purposes that's
why when I was a kid I'd watch PBS and they'd have some you know thing about a
historical event that happened the 50s and there'd be cussing on it because
it's real so of course we should see whatever this is in 2013 see they tell
you can see all the simulated torture and murder and death you want in movies
you name it I just like Time Warner's putting out all these violent movies but
now saying nobody can advertise guns on any Time Warner magazine TV show cable
network you name it Max Keiser is our guest he always seems to come on when
there's a big news event this happened like three times the last three times he
was on Max Keiser syndicated TV host radio host you name it max Keiser calm
max what do you make of this new phenomenon because I've never seen them
do this where they say oh it's too hurtful what like a little girl has a
Hello Kitty bubble machine I actually bought these for my kids you pull the
trigger and you stick it it's not even meant to be a quote gun it's a thing to
hold and put bubbles a little pink Hello Kitty deal and the police came and
grabbed the little girl because a bubble things she had kids are being arrest for
nerf guns that are orange or being being detained I mean this is like mind
control where you can have all the drones killing people all day that's
beautiful but but but but you're gonna get grabbed for Hello Kitty bubble toys
yeah well the media companies I think are panicking because the the frequency
of these mass shootings is getting is increasing and people's pointing
fingers in many directions including the big media companies so in the case they
they are conglomerates and they own film divisions they own TV divisions and they
own print divisions and they have movies that are showing an enormous amount of
mass slaughters and they've been making billions of dollars with these movies
and they also own news content divisions and now they're I think they're
completely stupefied because they don't want to upset their franchise selling
gory films by upsetting people by showing the real news I mean if you go
back the old history of the past 20 years there's a great film that came out
a while ago called fish show that Robert Redford made that show the transition
from news to game shows that happened in the 1950s and now we're going through a
new transition where news has become and no news you're not allowed to see news
anymore you're only allowed to see simulated events and simulated news
because the real news would if you watch it and you're injured we can't it might
create a liability that we're then liable for only the controlled violence
that's completely insured are we able to show you so I see this as just another
symptom of a society the American society fueled with cheap money cheap
drugs and other than the rest of it it's just a break it's just a disintegrate
we're gonna go to a witness turn her up go ahead CNN doesn't want you to see
this here is for radio why don't you tell me what you saw no actually I
wasn't in the library was a friend in the lab that's right and they came she
came to our class 308 and to get somebody out of class and to tell them
that it was a lot of shooting going on well of course that scared us so what
what happened was that we all just cut off the lights we shut down all the
computers and the teacher told us is the closet just in case but to be quiet and
we was there for a while a long time and of course we started hearing the
helicopters but we finally got the internet on channel 11 and that's when
we found out what had actually happened I didn't hear the shooting but somebody
else did so because someone came into your classroom you hunkered down right
there in the classroom unbelievable that was the only way I will keep going back
to Max Kaiser while we run this video but let me just point out I've made the
point that why don't we just train people to line up back to back so one
bullet could kill three people because I mean that's the only step more
ridiculous than these these these colleges and public schools training
people to get in fetal positions and wait to be killed I mean if there's a
mass shooting people inside need to evacuate every time they knock the knock
the prison windows out toward is a prison to get out and and look overall
crime violent crimes going down FBI numbers but mass shootings are going up
because the media is advertising this and I want to point out what max is
talking about about fakeness presidents band pretended to punch up drugs here
for me turns out that was all fake Obama faked meeting with people faked videos
separate from the inauguration you know all recorded it's just again they the
establishment is going to everything being fake because real stuff might
get out of hand this shows the system is desperate you know I gotta say this max
is bad as things are right now the good news is I see panic and fear in the
establishment size they're power-grabbing right now and they're so
insulated I don't think this is going to go well for them I mean let me tell you
I'm not bragging about this I don't tell this story like I'm a big shot it's
actually pretty creepy and freaks me out and gives me anxiety I went to Big Bend
National Park on the Texas-Mexico border this weekend and there were people from
France there there were people from New York there California at some cases 80
percent of people if I stopped or something just you know to sit there and
take photos if I was in a congregated area would say Alex Jones Alex Jones and
it wasn't from really Piers Morgan I'd say how do you know about me I've been
listening for years listen when when when upwards of half or more of people
know who I am and say they agree no matter where I go now max I can go to
the hike and bike trail and in some cases everyone that comes by as a
listener I'm not bragging and saying I'm a big shot it's scary max because they
I mean that yeah I don't want to die they might come after me I don't know
how our numbers don't show we're this big yeah 15 million a week that the 15
million a week is not enough to have people from France knowing who you are
yeah and then the next table knows who you are and then the waitress knows who
you are and it's and then one and then somebody else comes over I mean what's
going on with that max well I've told you when I travel I've traveled in the
Mideast and around Europe and Asia and I people know me from the TV show and
almost invariably that people say and I watch Alex Jones and it's just the power
of the internet people watch your videos and the message resonates all over the
world and you're getting recognized all over and out I mean this is I mean the
establishment better be concerned well I think your message resonates outside of
America more than it does inside of America because people outside of
America have already been dealing with outright tyranny for decades for
generations and they know exactly what you're talking about it's only inside
America that your message falls on deaf ears in some cases because America has
been very quiet for decades now post World War two it's been a Shangri-La
it's been a happy town because we've benefited from winning that war and
we've had a 60-year run but that's coming to an end because a lot of the
trends that shape the good times are finishing and we're entering a new
period so it's it's funny that in your own country you're not as well
appreciated I think as you are it outside of your own country I can
anecdotally tell you that from traveling to these countries and hearing people
talk about you extremely with great fondness more so than I hear people from
the US well just to be clear I didn't even bring this up to say hey I'm really
big folks it's actually creepy because what I'm saying is is that the word is
getting out let me show people some of these headlines wrangle some of the
southern areas have cultures we have to overcome and CNS news even has video of
him saying this on the news I mean like like if you live in the south you're
just bad if you're a gun over you know you're a Nazi period lawmakers
introduced bills to ban high-capacity gun clips Texas sheriff's I will not
enforce law I consider unconstitutional same thing with Missouri sheriff's my
point is is look at this Sarkozy to move to London to avoid France's high taxes I
mean how far can these bureaucrats go till everything collapses this week in
Switzerland of course it's Davos and Davos is really the the primo of all the
new world order get-togethers I think it might even be more influential than the
Bilderberg meetings because here you have in the highest mountains Switzerland
really the cream of the cream coming together and cutting deals and doing
deals and so it's happening this week and this is where now we'll find out a
couple of weeks what they decided to do in Davos and we'll find out what
companies got bought and who's who's gonna go after home and a lot of news
will come out out of it but I think Davos is really in in Europe is is the
number one event of the year for these guys these tyrants like Tim Geithner who
just came out the news that in 2008 2007 he was selling information to Wall
Street about which way the Fed and the Treasury were going to move interest
rates he was alerting the back you know private conversations essentially
selling information because that he go to Davos and he'll get paid a lot of
money from the folks that's where they the bag man you speeches as a way to get
paid off I remember you on the show with bags of money the Geithner and they're
right there with their bank accounts you know he's already got caught cooking the
books for his own tax returns a few years ago so they take go to Davos
that's where they hand him the bag full of money you can stick it in one of the
private banks there and it's there now for the rest of his life that most is
where Tim Geithner gets the you know that 20 or 30 million dollars just
hand it to him in in precious metals or diamonds or cash and he stores it away
that's what they do in Davos that's what is there for that's what a new world
order gets paid today is payday for the new world order in Davos Switzerland
they worked all year they get their bonuses they get them today in Davos
this week in Davos Buffett gets his big satchel of cash Geithner gets his
satchel of cash everyone gets paid this week in Davos so let the party you know
let the parties flow I want to shift gears again ladies and gentlemen we're
obviously going to go into overdrive we're showing pictures here a live feed
from a helicopter that CNN says you're not allowed to see so we've entered a
new Orwellian level here where CNN and other cable news channels are saying
they're not going to show live feeds we have the KHOU feeds you can see it they
must have huge servers as this is being watched all over the country we have the
KHOU feed posted at infowars.com and prisonplanet.com right now but CIA
operative takes responsibility for Algerian gas plant attack in the video
Mo Qatar Bell Mo Qatar said to be the mastermind behind the terrorist attack
by the Islamic al Mujahideen brigade in the gas complex in Algeria takes credit
for the operation now let me show in the document cam viewers this a radio
listener should go to infowars.com this is confirming what the London
Independent was saying terror in northern Africa are Westerners pulling
the strings and it has the it has the Prime Minister Sayal telling reporters
that it's an English accent groups leading the Al Qaeda forces well we know
Al Qaeda works for the West they've given them Libya in Syria they've now
taken over Libya they're deploying into other areas and then using this as an
excuse for NATO through Afrikan to invade and and run raids into these
areas just absolutely amazing and US begins transporting French troops and
equipment into Mali with another staged event as a pretext I mean how unveiled
does this have to get where the West publicly runs Al Qaeda I mean does that
not add massive credibility to everybody that pointed out that government was
involved in 9-11 well Tony Blair you know he gave him credit for setting up
the collapse of Libya his relationship with Gaddafi he had him profited
handsomely from that he's a Davos guy Davos man Tony Blair he's cutting deals
all over the world and of course Mali is the the the collateral damage of Libya
because all those weapons suddenly found their way onto the street and into
Algeria and into Mali and so that there's a whole what they call the
Maghreb the North African region is now become you know controlled by those
folks that are at war with the banksters the Western interests that have been you
know screwing with them for a number of decades and the response from the US and
Britain seems to be completely wrong-headed they they don't understand
what the why the problem started they don't understand why the problem
continues and they have no idea how to end the problem so they're just going to
continue to foster continuation and spread of enemies you know when they go
they send drones into Pakistan or these places and just murder people
indiscriminately they're breeding problems and of course they don't have
the money to pay for all this so I have to borrow more money who are they
borrowing it from China China's now war with Japan who's who's allied with the
US so we're in World War three right now it's being fought in the currency pits
it's a currency war and it brings us back to the fundamental reality that
countries like Germany aren't repatriating their gold the Netherlands
is repatriating their gold because they don't trust that's anymore they want out
of Dodge they want their gold and they don't want to play this game anymore and
that's why gold is going to go to ten thousand dollars an ounce because the
gold is not in these walls to spend sold already to pay for these stupid
ridiculous how are they going to cover it now that these countries are all
demanding their gold out of the private Federal Reserve Geithner's over there
you know hanging out at Davos the public Bilderberg meeting I mean it's just
their craziness they're gonna cut them a check they're gonna cut them a check and
say okay you we owe you thirty billion dollars in gold here's a check for thirty
billion dollars and these countries will say wait a minute we want the gold and
they'll say sorry we don't have it the here's the check it you know sorry it's
tough luck and that's when they're going to that's when that's when all hell's
gonna break loose because then you're gonna realize that the gold has been
sold it's not there and you've got this reporter real fast talking to the police
she's getting the statements kind of find out what the latest and greatest
information may be as far as information we are going to bring that update to you
but just to sort of recap what we believe we do know at this point is the
before she was pulled away to get the latest information I did learn that the
person that they do have in custody they are unsure if that person is actually a
shooter or is actually a person who may have been involved in the altercation
that led to all of this at this point if this isn't stage you watch it's gonna be
gang related the ability of trying to get some of because 77% of the shootings
that call mass shootings are gang related which is still bad but it's to
adult shooting each other you know over the gangster culture that's so popular
also pushed I tell you max Kaiser is our guest this is just amazing max Kaiser
calm max we're gonna do a little bit of overdrive if you can do it because I've
been cutting you short here and I got so many questions when we come back what
will it look like as the countries say give us our money they say no that's
already happening what will that do will that create even more uncertainty with
the IO use and how long can the globalist pay off the Chinese the
Germans and others with bags of cash that is being devalued and what happens
once the dollar does lose its status I mean what type of bonker insanity these
dollars have been buying everybody off so far by the globalist I guess the
globalist will just move to another country and we'll get the blame for it I
think that's the answer but we're gonna find out you know there's max Kaiser
gonna be right in April or within a few months of that is it going to be the
next level of collapse and what will that signify I'm Alex Jones and this is
the end fall war if you've ever wanted one of our best-selling generators but
we're waiting for an offer so crazy you couldn't refuse then you're not gonna
want to miss this exciting message here's why our solar generators provide
life-saving electrical power and unlike gas generators solar generators run
quietly emit no fumes and produce electricity from the Sun so when the
lights go out you'll always have the power you need now here's the best part
every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as
new we put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily
at the end of each year we call them scratch and dead units but they're
really just like new each unit comes with a full factory warranty and
special bonuses you just won't believe don't wait they go fast go to scratch
and then solar calm that scratch and then solar calm for the craziest offer
we've ever made go to scratch and then solar calm that scratch and then solar
calm hi there my name is Frank Bates what I'm about to tell you in the next
60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble I just created a free video
presentation at 1 2 3 cover-up calm that exposes the electricity monopolies and
government agencies for what they really are incompetent line crooks that are
counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high
some have called this a conspiracy others have called it a cover-up and you
will be shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy goes my video at 1 2 3 cover
up calm exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them and how
you can beat them to watch the controversial video that thousands of
other smart Patriots have already seen in the last three months go to 1 2 3
cover-up calm and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and
protect your home go watch my video now at 1 2 3 cover-up calm before they force
me to shut it down again that's 1 2 3 cover-up calm injuries slow healing
aches and pains constipation weakness fatigue are all common the older one
gets the progressive deterioration of the body that occurs almost universally
the older one gets can partly to significantly be prevented with
conscientious attention to nutrition if the hundreds of men can play rugby in
their 90s then it is possible for everyone in North America to experience
a more youthful life as well one key ingredient to warning off aging and
reversing some of it is the type and quality of protein consumed all protein
foods or supplements you currently consume are heat damaged destroying 50
to 75% of your ability to utilize the bodybuilding amino acids one world way
is not heat damaged and allows your body to utilize 100% of the amino acids this
feat no one else has achieved the results to your health can be amazing
call 8 8 8 9 8 8 3 3 2 5 that's 8 8 8 9 8 8 3 3 2 5 or visit one world way
dot-com that's one world wh ey dot-com the Genesis communications radio network
proudly presents the Alex Jones show because there's a war on for your mind
you know a few months ago a listener if you're watching on TV sent us this Obama
snow globe and when we shake it up was our Christmas present it's totally and
completely filthy inside which I thought was fitting it's clouded and looks like
there's bacteria or sewage in it let me let me shake this up for everybody and
show the viewers a document cam shot there you go so thanks for the Christmas
present it turned out even better than we thought it came in the official
packaging and everything probably made in China and probably has like fetid
urine in it or something I don't know but there you go going back to Max
Kaiser of max Kaiser calm you can follow us on Twitter at real Alex Jones and
where is the best Twitter for you max there's several big ones out there well
just max Kaiser so it's Twitter forward slash max Kaiser okay you heard my
long-winded question before the break what is that what is the next stage of
collapse look like and what will happen well I'm just reading zero hedge they
got a story up right now Mervyn King Bank of England is talking about
rebalancing to avoid a currency war and that's that's a big that's it that's a
big moment because he acknowledges that we're in a currency war the UK pound is
gonna have to be revalued down sharply that means purchasing power in the UK
is going to collapse as you know I moved to London from Paris to observe and to
report on the collapse of the UK pound in the UK economy because it's one of
the most vulnerable economies in the world because they have so little gold
after Gordon Brown sold most of it back in 2001 so this is another shoe to drop
this is another chapter in the collapse of these paper money empires and of
course gold and silver are acting fantastically well so far this year and
it's just playing out exactly as we said it would over the past couple years and
2013 looks to be a continuation so looking into your crystal ball things
are right on schedule pretty much I say that the economy that growth needed to
pay the debt is a quantity that will never come to pass and I'll give you a
good example of how to determine that the the amount of debt in the world or
even in the u.s. with with its many many trillions of dollars of debt but to pay
that debt off it would of course be a subset of the tax being collected on
growth okay so how much tax and how much growth would be required to pay the debt
well all growth in the modern economy is tied to oil and if you were to burn a
trillion barrels of oil the approximately the same amount of barrels
of oil that have been burned so far in the last 100 years if you were to burn
another trillion barrels of oil you would not generate enough taxable income
to pay off the current debt doesn't give you an idea of how much debt there is so
in other words this debt is never going to be paid off jobs are never coming
back wages will continue to crash and the bond market collapse is coming and
gold and silver are gonna go a lot higher that there's just there's just no
way around it max we're in a little bit of overdrive here when we come back but
you know all I can say is this you look at how they've tried to destroy women
destroy the family how MTV has pushed gangster and jackass cultures on people
how it's been sold that men are supposed to be weak and stupid or thug like I
mean why would the system try to degenerate society I guess for the
casino gulag model that you talked about and it's all happening you said a moment
ago you talked about what's the endgame for the the elites I mean look what Glenn
Beck is doing he's trying to create it he's got two billion dollars he wants to
create his own village his own society down there in Texas the Koch brothers are
want to buy an island in Detroit and create their own you know their own
society you've got two or three examples now of these elites wanting to build
their own castles their own neo-feudal like it like they said that's the model
and then they're gonna call it libertarian globalism collapses things
then they exempt themselves from libertarian stay there we're gonna we're
gonna come back and talk about make libertarians visit GCN live.com today
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers the prognosis for the
entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse the globalist model is
to shut down societies and starve Patriots out until they acquiesce to the
global takeover that's why we've assembled the most vital and important
preparedness items at info wars shop.com these are items that I did research on
that I personally use you've got the life straw so you can turn fetid water
into safe water anywhere you go the Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key
equipment during power outages are out in the field strategic relocation third
edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein thorough safe
used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event
and crank shortwave AM FM radios everything that we've researched and
found to be the best is available at info war shop calm and your purchase
makes our info war possible we're getting prepared are you info wars shop
calm coast-to-coast direct from Austin you're listening to the Alex Jones
Broadcasting Network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones you see the globalist have exempted themselves from all the laws
regulations and rules that they've created and pushed so that only they can
operate and so they're gonna have city-states that are outside of the law
and given special licensure by the power structure so the elites can live in those
they're then gonna get the scared middle-class to pay exorbitant prices to
live within the castle walls and we actually covered that in a bunch of
recent reports we did last year breaking that down and again after they collapse
and suck everything together then like this big Bilderberg group member has
talked about the floating cities and all the rest of it then I'm gonna do a
special report on this then they exempt themselves and you've got to go live in
their system if you have any money I mean it they figured it all out that's
why they're getting rid of nation states with a global crime syndicate above it
who then will get their own private zones where they can operate however
they want and yeah can you imagine it's like zeitgeist living in Glenn Beck's
two billion dollar libertarian heaven in Texas and I knew they were looking at
stuff outside Austin I talked about the time to Glenn Beck was moving to Texas
before he did I said it could be Austin because they were looking at properties
here and I just hope he doesn't move and set up a bit I mean whatever it's a free
country I guess he can set up is is his utopia here I know I'm not gonna be
living in it but see if you're an insider you're gonna be able to get
deals as a stakeholder under general 21 to have lesser taxes to generate its own
power its own food so you live in kind of like the Glenn Beck gulag man I tell
you they've really thought all this out Max Kaiser I think you're gonna see one
of these whether it's the Koch brothers or Glenn Beck I think it's gonna be
another situation like the Hale-Bopp Comet cult or the Jim Jones
Yana cult they become very insular after 10 years people start going mad and then
there's mass suicide I mean that's where Glenn Beck is going we're gonna read
about him in 10 years as the guy who convinced you know a 2,000 people to
drink the Kool-Aid and commit suicide chasing his idea of whatever he's
mumbling on about because when you secede from society and you set yourself
up as in some way living according to an ethos that is completely divorced from
anything that we know and appreciate as a democratic system let's call it or an
American system or an egalitarian system you become prone to ego maniacal
dictator like psychopaths like Glenn Beck who rise up and realize that the
only way that he can escape facing the reality of his own shortcomings is to
convince everyone and himself to kill themselves and that's where he's headed
well I'm a January said it it's headed to sell real estate plan you know what's
incredible I was actually approached and I think oh my gosh I just remembered I
was approached by a bit successful businessman in Dallas about a month ago
actually for this plan I think Beck must have I know he was talking to Beck and
Beck I even know where it is oh my gosh see I don't even know about this you're
sort of talking about I've been out of town for three days four days I went and
looked it up and sure enough he's announcing it he's not saying where I
know where the idea came from oh my gosh I can't believe it it's a it's a it's a
shopping mall that's gone bankrupt outside Dallas that's breaking news
right there at least I know Beck is is looking at it oh my gosh can you imagine
going and living in a shut down shopping mall that has shops that then they're
gonna have stuff built around it where everybody moves which wouldn't be a bad
idea if it was his own incorporated city and I guess that's the plan wow I know
Glenn Beck's plan unless I'm wrong because I was called by a another
businessman who I know in the DFW area and he was telling me he was getting
together with other talk show host and then he'd recently met with Glenn Beck
well I understand that he's raised two billion dollars for this project so it
yeah it's a very well-funded real estate project they're going to live a
libertarian dream and as you as we were saying there's libertarianism and
there's fake libertarianism more segment can you do it yeah whatever man yeah
because I want to talk about this Peter Thiel the Bilderberg guy Glenn Beck now
says he is the leader of the libertarians while Ron Paul supporters
he said need to have the army used on him so that doesn't sound too libertarian
to me I will be right back my gosh I am flipping out because I actually know
about Glenn Beck's operation I forgot about this
hello I'm Alex Jones myself my family the infowars.com team want to relay to
you and your families that we are intensifying our efforts against the
globalist on every front infowars.com is leading the fight against the
technocrats but we can't do that without your help by getting the films bumper
stickers and t-shirts at infowars.com you will wake up people in your area and
support our operation as we move to the next level we need your help to spread
the word like never before they wish to hide themselves during this tectonic
battle between the forces of freedom and darkness you are the response to the
globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization and
ultimate extermination the war is here it's an infowar the spirit of 1776
versus the mindset of 1984 looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves how did we
ever survive from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating
summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our
hearts go out to those that have lost everything at e foods direct we hear
from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City
wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods
just in time to be able to help my sister and niece it is better to be
prepared ten years too early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't
feed you heed the warnings and do what Alex has done call 800 409 5633 today or
go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best
tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call 800 409 5633 or e
foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct we all know
that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration as an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years in serving
thousands of satisfied customers the Berkey guy offers amazing specials for
Berkey water filtration systems the Berkey light systems include a set of
self sterilizing and re cleanable black purification elements that purify water
by removing chlorine pathogenic bacteria cyst and parasites to
non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and
pesticides order the Berkey light system today complete with two black Berkey
elements for only two hundred and thirty one dollars and the Berkey guy will ship
your order free of charge with the purchase of a Berkey light the Berkey
guy is also offering a set of fluoride and arsenic filters for only thirty nine
ninety nine that's over thirty percent off the retail price call the Berkey guy
at one eight seven seven eight eight six three six five three that's one eight
seven seven eight eight six three six five three or order online at go Berkey
dot com that's go Berkey dot com today he's the t-rex of political talk Alex
Jones on the GCN radio network
well it's a terrible shooting but not as bad as it could have been and as I said
if it's not staged or some mentally ill Prozac head copycat er I've been saying
this for over an hour since it broke and then we had no information only because
it's usually only one of three things it's not hard to make these predictions
CNN who says they'll decide what we're allowed to see and and would not show
live feeds of it as we have been doing for TV viewers playing clubs for radio
listeners two students wounded in Houston College shooting officials not
servants believe two students were wounded in crossfire as two people shot
at each other at a Texas Community College Tuesday so gang related folks
it's gonna nip me because the culture is be a cool gangster you know all these
rappers and people that end up shooting each other just to prove their men it's
so horrible and there you go one of the shooters was also injured and is in
custody in the North Harris campus of Lone Star College spokesman Jed Young
said the other shooter fled the campus he said the police believe the danger
has been mitigated so hundreds of police SWAT teams you name it and meanwhile
listen it's gonna be gang related I mean like I said most what they call mass
shootings are rival gangs shooting each other at least three shot at Houston
Area Community College they use the New York numbers so what was it nine people
shot the shooter shot his estranged boss and then was walking away and the police
shot a whole bunch of people in New York got nine people and then also some
repair guy was on the bridge doing repair and they just came up and shot
him and then another veterans car broke down they just pulled up and shot him
and they and they count those as the shooting numbers they'll call it a
criminal event now I mean they count those nine people in mass shooting
numbers just just incredible yeah at least three shot at Houston Area
Community College but one of them is the shoe is one of the shooters reportedly
one of the alleged shooters and two of them are people shot in the crossfire
thank God it wasn't another goth devil worshipper because you got the gut it's
always the same goth devil worshipper in psychiatric care seeing psychiatrists
and psychologists on serotonin reuptake inhibitors
I mean it's amazing Harrison Kleibel were into devil worship God and I'm not
bashing folks like to wear black and all that you know there's different groups
of people like that it's just that that's the mo Wow guaranteed it's gonna
come out now gang-related and that's terrible news but thank God it's not 30
dead people because they would really go to town with that and I still believe
with all the hype we're seeing that they're gonna stay some false flags
that's why they're so confident max Kaiser thanks for holding into
overdrive here with us again TV host syndicated radio host max Kaiser max
Kaiser calm you just tuned in I'm Alex Jones of prison planet calm and prison
planet TV max for those just joining us I don't want to sit here just for the
sake of it and bash Glenn Beck and and and you mentioned Glenn Beck says he
has two billion dollars and is gonna build a libertarian utopia I know he's
been looking at land outside Austin as I talked to one of the people involved
let's leave it at that and I was horrified by it then it was actually
Dallas that he moved to and then I got a call by a nice businessman I know who's
a patriot and he said that hey you know there's this shopping mall that's
bankrupt and we can make it all guns Patriots stuff survival stuff and and
then maybe have a community around that because the worst real estate is is
North Dallas you know in Texas it's just plunging that's the worst area in Texas
overall good state and it may not be the same deal by but I know this guy's met
with Glenn Beck because he told me about that too and I've got a singing
suspicion that's where he got the idea because Beck doesn't ever have his own
ideas it's always somebody else's I'm gonna make a phone call after the show
today but it's the idea of Peter teal the big
Bilderberg guy teal feel or teal always get it wrong yep say it again
yeah yeah that Mike's so bad I can't understand a word coming out of it hold
on feel yeah yeah th yeah the of that Bilderberg guy is the one you know
pushing this but again they bankrupt things then make themselves exempt from
the very taxes and then go live in these command bases that's what the globalist
have said is their model so I guess Glenn Beck's is trying to copy that now
I've been ranting go ahead Max Keiser well first of all is a carpetbagger who
wants his Yankee down in Austin Texas I mean don't you Texans have more
self-respect to this I mean you got to run this guy out of town shouldn't
there be I mean y'all got the guns y'all got the the manpower why are you letting
this carpetbagger come down to Austin Texas and set up his libertarian utopian
paradise which is gonna nothing but a scam media scam in your backyard that's
an insult Alex I'm just speechless here it's just things are getting so
just help it's an insult how dare he go move into the Holy Land of Austin Texas
you know it's not gonna be weird anymore instead of saying keep it weird Austin
Texas it's gonna be like welcome to Glenn Beckville where everybody is
boring media Jack idiot you know he's really lowered the value of that town
tremendously if you let this carpetbagger into town and can't you do
something you got listeners down there isn't there something you can do Alex we
need you to stop this from happening well I don't I don't know if he's
moving to Austin I know he was looking at stuff here and pieces of land and
stuff all I know is that I found out from people that worked in around him
that indeed he did focus on everything we did have people watching it and when
we see he takes what we do and then spins it and then he kind of just walks
around in these weird you know blue jeans a little nerd outfit all creepy
and and and and weird and a lot of his followers are good people but a big
contingent of them are like into the wimpiness and into the whole and then
he always sabotages libertarians at key points so I feel like he's on my six and
it just is creepy knowing what I know about him that that he is constantly
worried about what I'm up to and I just you know his whole career is based on a
bad imitation of Alex Jones I mean before Glenn Beck came on Fox News I
mean there was Alex Jones and you know you brought to the to the media and to
the media world somebody who wore their heart on their sleeve in a very obvious
way and then Glenn Beck did this on Fox News where he would well up and get very
emotional over things and he's basically doing an Alex Jones impression so but he
would not cover the stories that Alex Jones covers because of course he
doesn't want to upset Fox News and his media masters and he's parlayed that
into this new two billion dollar fandango down in Austin Texas so what I'm
hearing he's going to build this utopian version of what I call fake libertarianism
which means fake libertarianism means he'll say well I'm going to borrow two
billion dollars at zero percent interest rate and if this works I'm going to keep
all the profits and if it goes bust then everyone in Texas is going to have to
absorb the losses and you say well why do you get to borrow two billion dollars
at 0% they'll say oh I'm a libertarian that's not what libertarianism is.
He supported the banker bailout. Well yeah that's not libertarianism that's not
even capitalism that's outright fascism he's a fascist you know he accuses you
being a fascist and yet he's the guy engaged in a two billion dollar fascist
enterprise combining the banks with the land speculators in Austin that's
fascism he's right there in your neighborhood. Well he's looking at Austin
he's also looking at North the North Dallas suburbs area where it's probably.
If you were so concerned he should check out Libya or Mali why doesn't Glenn Beck go
there to build his libertarian paradise that's where it's needed you know if he
really believes in the in the power of capitalism libertarianism why doesn't he
go to to Mali and show the people there what Glenn Beck can do. But let's
elaborate on this let's elaborate on this we've actually done news reports on this
we cover it in Endgame people think of globalism as getting rid of countries
they actually break countries into smaller pieces to control them they
create regions like London or the Vatican that are outside of law and can
do whatever they want Israel's a similar thing they build their own zones and
that's what they're actually saying Peter Thiel and others is that they're
going to establish this it's just amazing that we're actually like you
said we're going back to feudalism. It is going back to feudalism and I have been
saying that for a few years neo-feudalism and but this Peter Thiel
character of course he made his money with PayPal and PayPal of course was
that along with Visa and MasterCard shutting down WikiLeaks when when it
became and they also are extra judiciously shutting people down that
they don't want them to get their views like you know with the with copyright
and other issues they just shut them down and that's where Peter Thiel
comes from so he he made his bones engaging with the banksters directly
through PayPal that's that's where he comes from so now he's going to take
that experience and he's with the Bilderberg group now he's with these
folks and they're meeting and they're doing their deals where they're going to
try to create these little cul-de-sacs these little Disney asks fantasy worlds
where they're going to be surrounded by an army you've got media ideologues like
Glenn Beck at the center and within five or six years all the children are gonna
look like Glenn Beck but they'll all be inbreeding so some will have three arms
all right that's enough I don't want to get into a Beck bashing fest it's just
that you know it's just incredible and he is out to get me and you notice I'm
not out to get Rush Limbaugh I'm not out to get Michael Savage I'm not I don't
talk about what's the other one's name I don't listen to it what's his name the
guy on Fox News Sean Hannah Bill O'Reilly yeah what is they're not after
me so I'm not talking about him it's Glenn Beck is always look how he moved
up the road from me I mean it's like Sam I mean I need to get this guy out of my
life he's super creepy well he's a stalker he's talking you so I mean you
know you've got to deal with it in some way you just got to be enough people in
Austin that support Alex Jones to do whatever it needs to be done to keep
Glenn Beck out oh stop it he'll take that just a serious thing no no if he
wants to buy property and do something to become a libertarian that's great in
fact I want to think that he's becoming a better guy the problem is he's still
you know really making stuff up about us I mean I'm not a fascist folks I'm a
wild liberal in the Thomas Jefferson vein none of these names mean anything
I'm called a right-winger today because I oppose Obama I am a true
constitutionalist max I'd like to believe you're the same thing I mean a classical
liberal right I'm actually a closet Texan well you lived in France he lived
in New York he lived everywhere now you've moved to London to cover that
maybe when it all collapses you and I will both move into Glenn Beck's
neighborhood he won't be able to stop us we'll buy a cult compound right next
door to him you can't say no he's a libertarian maybe remember the Alamo
remember the Alamo remember the Alamo shows