Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is Thursday, the third day of the new year, 2013. And we are
going to be here, Lord willing, for the next three hours. We do have Dr. Jerome Corsi joining
us. They are going ahead with the North American Union NAPA superhighway program, despite telling
the public that first it didn't exist, and then the legislature shot it down twice.
It affects the entire nation, but begins down in Mexico through Texas up into Canada. They
even have the whole highway planned out with the highway markers for all the way into Canada.
But then when you talk about it, they say it doesn't exist. And that's part of the psychological
warfare tactic they use in general. The legislation is introduced and is passed out of committee
in Illinois to ban all semi-autos, even pump shotguns, pump rifles. I saw a comment on
infowars.com.
They said pump rifles. There's actually a lot of pump rifles. Now, the point is is that
it's everything but bolt action. And the NRA, of course, is responding to it. And it looks
like it's gonna pass very, very close today. And Obama is quoted as saying he wants to
quickly go for immigration reform, totally open borders, end of America, just not even
having a country.
No other country lets you do that. It's globalism, it's New World Order, and gun control. So
it's hammer down. And you notice that in mainline, quote, conservative circles, they're not even
discussing this. They're talking about tax increases in the fiscal cliff, which is important,
but the power to tax is the power to destroy.
But this pales in significance. And I didn't even get to it yesterday, cuz it's so well
known that Obama's one of the greatest liars in history. Just because we've gotten deeper
into the corruption, he's just a puppet. But the system is lying through their mouthpiece
where he said, I'll never raise your payroll taxes, I'll never raise this tax, that tax.
They're raising payroll taxes, you name it, a whole bunch of new taxes, fines, fees, regulations.
One of the crew members calculated on their paycheck what the new payroll tax is that
started. And it comes out to about 200, a little over $200 a month. So we're gonna do
a news piece on that. Or I guess whoever volunteers around here, we can black out their pay stub
and all that.
But government knows when you work for a company, they can just keep adding fees and regulations
and surcharges onto things. One of my crew members got pulled over literally two days
after his insurance expired, cuz he was gonna sell the truck, cuz he did, he did sell the
truck. The illegal aliens, of course, are released, they're allowed to not have insurance.
And I think he's gonna do a news piece on it, it's not a secret, but it was a $300 ticket.
It's all automated, turned out the cops had cameras that were scanning and reading it,
that's why they pulled him over. And then they said there's gonna be another surcharge
whenever you go to get your license of between 300 and $1,000 next time he renews it.
And then he got another $500 charge in the mail and it says you are convicted and they're
just starting to send him more and more bills. That's the new system where you're never out
of it. To be a US citizen is to be seen, you've seen those cartoons where the wolf looks at
the rabbit or looks at the chicken and then actually sees it as like a skinned piece of
meat on a spit and then starts drooling.
When government sees you, that's what they see is a meal and they see a mark. Americans
are now known as planetary chumps, we are now known as dinner. And all of us more and
more have to do whatever we can to get out of the system, sabotage the system, not go
along with it, because it's totally illegitimate.
You guys pull me the article Steve Watson did about checkpoints all over the highways.
By the way, now they're gang checkpoints where they search your vehicle. I mean, this country
is in martial law. It's what degree of it and we've got forced inoculation news as well
coming up.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east, but we are still in the eye of the perfect
storm. The most devastating economic conditions since the Great Depression, America's worst
drought in agricultural history, and now the economic results of the presidential election.
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply. I just doubled down and got even
more supplies from E Foods Direct and I recommend you do the same. It's time to get your own
supply from E Foods Direct. I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom
for food. I'm taking control of my future. And you're nuts if you don't do the same.
Go to efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex to find the specials and you can start with
a holiday gift pack that's normally $80 now under 50 bucks. Remember, I can warn you but
I can't feed you. Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex. Would you rather prepare
six months too early or one day too late? 409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com forward slash
Alex.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die? Start purifying your water with Pro Pure. My friends, I've done
a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none is Pro Pure and it's available
full discounted at info wars.com. Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial
growth. There's no priming required. It's NSF 42 certified optional fluoride filters
can reduce fluoride up to 95% easy to set up and use doesn't require electricity purify
water from lakes, streams, ponds and wells. This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals
which is key save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the
plastic probe here is the best gravity fed filter out there. It's what my family uses
info wars.com already has the lowest price on propure but if you add the promo code water
at checkout, you get an additional 10% off and info wars.com. You can also call to order
888-253-3139. Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and
other illnesses. Don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver, a revolutionary
new broad spectrum anti-bacterial solution. Recent advances in silver technology have
resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold
and food poisoning and help improve wound healing. Supernatural silver is safe enough
to consume everyday while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases
such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other harmful pathogens. This new technology
has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times
the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions. The Science Digest Journal says
silver is our mightiest germ fighter. It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder
of modern medicine. Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for
20% off. That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Up from the front lines of the information war, it's Alex Jones. A new world order. What
we are looking at is good and evil, right and wrong. A new world order. A new world
order. A new world order. A new world order. A new world order. Ladies and gentlemen, we
are live. It is Thursday, the third day of January, 2013. And we are going to be here
for the next three hours. Wow, where to begin? I have a personal story of here in our office
of just unmitigated, over the top oppression and tyranny going on with one of our crew
members who we're gonna keep anonymous at this point.
And I'm gonna tell that story calmly at the bottom of the hour. And I will tie it into
everything else that's happening. But you need to understand, ladies and gentlemen,
that the globalists are moving on every front. They are not just coming to confiscate the
guns. I am so busy working and spending time with my family and things that I never have
time to go out bird hunting or deer hunting.
I never even have time to really go to the shooting range, maybe two or three times a
year. I have time to go shooting now or I have people visit and they wanna shoot cuz
I live out in the country now. So I guess I'm shooting a little bit more than I used
to. Growing up, I shot every week and became a pretty good rifleman and even shot competitively
a little bit with rifles and handguns.
But that is a side issue rabbit trail. It's not that I'm freaked out about physically
Dianne Feinstein now introducing the bill today to confiscate most firearms. It's not
even the idea of going and laying them outside and the police come and inspect your house
without warrants.
That's what they're announcing. And they set up checkpoints on highways that are now searching
for firearms. That's now happening all over the country. They're even taking legal ones.
They don't care if the law says you could have a gun, they just take it right here in
Texas as well.
I mean, it's just martial law being phased in. It's that I know what comes with it and
it's going to be taxes increasing on everything. It's going to be VAT, it's going to be increased
sales taxes, it's gonna be increased taxes on energy. It is going to be increased payroll
taxes, that's already happening, surcharges, and it's designed. Some of the economists
say this will destroy the economy.
Well, that's the plan. I mean, they've got 100 plus million people on one form of welfare
or another. They wanna go up to 200 million. They've gone from 25 million on food stamps
to 49 million in four years. And they intend to double that. And they don't mince words
about it. This is your domestication. America has always been the target.
And we are to be fully brought down like Poland or Ukraine under Soviet occupation. And I've
studied history in depth, that is the plan. And people could say, cuz I've tried to psychoanalyze
myself. Is it a macho action that I am going to stay behind in this country and go toe
to toe with this?
And no, that is not why I'm doing it. It's not out of some hatred of the New World Order
and what they do. It's out of an absolute duty and commitment and pledge to fight these
people. I just wanna get it across to you, ladies and gentlemen, that they're hurting
innocents all over the world.
And they're doing things that when you're even mildly informed, are so over the top
that it boggles the mind. They give premature babies vaccines now in this country and kill
them. They know full well what they do. They give pregnant women vaccines and push them
and tell them in hospitals it's the law when they come in to get checkups, when there is
no law.
Guys, I sent you probably 50 IMs and it's clear there's a problem, you need to reload
that. Because I had the definitions in the history of gaslighting, it's a political term.
So if that's not in there, I need you to go get me just the top four or five up, the use
of gaslighting, the psychological term gaslighting, cuz I wanna cover gaslighting.
It's just one term to cover a game the globalists play, and they define it as gaslighting. And
it's when you walk in and you find your wife in bed with another man. And she says, there's
no man here and the guy gets up, dresses and walks out. They've psychologically found most
people will actually go, am I crazy?
That's not a guy right there. And because of denial, how we've been programmed through
television, gaslighting is more and more effective today than it's ever been. So I'm gonna go
over gaslighting today, because I read that term years ago, but I came back across it.
And I'm like, that's a great term for what I've been trying to describe. So many times
you learn something and you forget it, and they've got different terms for it. They've
got Stockholm syndrome, I mean, there's a lot of different learned helplessness.
But they've been building the Napa superhighway from Mexico into Texas and up in Oklahoma.
It's all over the news here. And they go on CNN over the years, I've played the clips
and go, Ron Paul isn't sane. There is no trans Texas corridor, Napa superhighway. When it's
all department transportation and publicly admitted and billboards up everywhere, then
they go, it doesn't exist.
And then they say, we're not gonna build it now. And then they sign an order and bring
it back in, even though the legislature said no, cuz they're having the states go and pay
for it with taxpayer money. And then the globalists get the tax money off the toll roads. Or it's
like CBS, NBC, ABC, all of them saying, Wayne LaPierre is a liar, there are no guns in Israel,
there are no armed teachers, there are no armed citizens, that is a lie.
The answer to mass shootings is not arming people. And the media went, whoa, LaPierre
has got egg on his face, man, that guy's a liar. I mean, it's an absolute fact in triplicate
that since the 80s, they've armed the teachers. And then when they go on field trips, they've
got M16s, and it's in Haaretz, Jerusalem Post, anybody can go type, Israeli teachers
armed, Israeli citizens armed.
It's a known fact, you can go read the Israeli laws on the Knesset website, and we've done
newscast on it showing you. But see, we can't reach but a few million people a day. And
even those listening on radio, once they've been gas lit, once they've been manipulated,
once everything's been fogged, they're like, well, he says they got guns, but I've never
been there.
And it's just incredible. Yeah, there's Fox News showing the teachers with the armed teachers
guards bolster school security in Israel. That's from December 30th. As bad as Fox News
is, at least they didn't try to hoax their audience. That's why they got more audiences
than all the cable news channels combined, because they at least tell enough of the truth
so people don't think they're total operatives and actually watch them.
That's part of the hoax, though, with MSNBC and CNN, whose top shows have a half million
viewers a piece. I mean, there's big shows in Chicago and Dallas and New York that per
hour have over a half million listeners on one radio station. I mean, I can look at the
numbers on affiliates we've got. Some of our bigger affiliates, we have 110,000 listeners
an hour.
And that's right off the dash, instant meter computers, 100% people are listening. But
it doesn't matter, they get up there in these big giant glistening sets, and they tell you
authoritatively, you need to turn your guns in. And people just, well, my gosh, I mean,
Piers Morgan, he has that snot-nosed accent and he's such a big audience.
Even around here, when I told my crew that they've officially set me up for the seventh
with Piers Morgan, people are incredible. And of course, they're thinking it'll be a
big news event because we'll have an argument or something. And that is how Piers Morgan
actually does have an audience. His actual show doesn't have an audience. The derivative
of it does get picked up and put on a lot of other channels.
That's why he's number one on CNN, is that he at least knows to have enough controversy
and people he disagrees with on to try to get some viewers. So I mean, it's a good move
by the Pentagon that on record runs CNN. That's come out Washington Post even, that it's run
by the Department of Defense and is basically a PSYOP operation out of Atlanta, New York
and Los Angeles and DC.
Well, not just a PSYOP, it's far beyond that. But still, there's the, my gosh, Piers Morgan,
you're gonna be on there? I mean, it's almost not worth it to go down to the satellite uplink
and do the interview. Seriously, and I'm not just saying that. Well, I turn down every
week offers, don't even call people back, I should, some other might be something good
comes along.
Reality TV shows, Discovery Channel, History Channel, BBC, and they send emails back going,
we're a huge show. Now, I did wanna go on BBC Radio last week, but I was out that day
and missed it. Because it was that World Service show that's on everywhere and it's live, that
I would have done. But I don't like tape stuff cuz they can manipulate it.
The point is, I'm not up here bragging, hey, I don't need them. It's that they are a hoax.
But in a way, I probably should go participate just because the general lemmings see it and
think, man, you've really arrived. I mean, my goodness, you were on The View. And The
View actually, I did get a big response out of, I've been on Fox, CNN, MSNBC, Discovery
Channel, History Channel, you name it, I've been on it, A&E, 60 Minutes, Extra Hard Copy,
you name it, I've been on it in 17 years.
And it just doesn't do anything, because you've got a bunch of zombies watching it. Now, when
we come back, but again, doesn't matter, it still creates the illusion that they're in
charge and that everybody believes them. So you've gotta understand, folks, it's a total
facade.
You ever seen those Hollywood facades to a tour of the studios where it looks like a
house but it's just the front with boards propping it up behind it? It's a facade.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east, but we are still in the eye of the perfect
storm. The most devastating economic conditions since the Great Depression, America's worst
drought in agricultural history, and now the economic results of the presidential election.
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply. I just doubled down and got even
more supplies from E Foods Direct, and I recommend you do the same. It's time to get your own
supply from E Foods Direct. I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom
for food. I'm taking control of my future, and you're nuts if you don't do the same.
Go to efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex to find the specials, and you can start with
a holiday gift pack that's normally $80, now under 50 bucks. Remember, I can warn you,
that I can't feed you. Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex. Would
you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late? Or 95633 or efoodsdirect.com
forward slash Alex.
Would it save you time to get the best quality water filters and the best quality storable
foods from one company? You bet it would, and now you can. Add Big Berkey Water Filters
dot com. Big Berkey Water Filter products and great tasting, long lasting, storable
wise foods are both now available on one website. Big Berkey Water Filters dot com. Wise foods
ready to eat meals are packed in airtight nitrogen pouches and come with a 25 year shelf
life. Big Berkey Water Filters are powerful enough to purify treated, untreated, or even
stagnant pond water. Combine Berkey Water Filters with Wise Foods for an unbeatable
preparedness combination. Get free shipping on every order over $50. And GCN listeners
receive 5% off all ceramic filter systems. Visit Big Berkey Water Filters dot com or
call 877-99-BERKEY. That's 877-99-BERKEY or go to Big Berkey Water Filters dot com.
hempusa.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine and probiotics
and we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder absolutely free. Micro plant powder
only at hempusa.org. Call 908-691-2608. That's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder, seeds
and oil can do for you. Only at hempusa.org. This offer ends January 31st. Hi, this is
Ted Anderson. Have you ever wondered why banks, stockbrokers, investment advisors want to
talk about gold IRAs? They've been available since 1986 yet the financial industry won't
recognize the value of gold for your retirement. Gold is outperformed paper investments yet
no word about IRAs. If you would like to have gold for your retirement call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns call 800-686-2237. Secure
your future and call 1-800-686-2237. Big business has discovered the preparedness market and
that makes it difficult to know where to go and who to trust. MyPatriotSupply.com is owned
and operated by patriots just like you. Has the best prices on storeable food, non-GMO
seeds, water filtration devices, home canning equipment, survival and self-reliance books
and more. MyPatriotSupply.com has old fashioned values and the absolute best customer service
in the industry. Look for the deal of the day, unique affordable survival supplies that
fit anyone's budget. Get same day shipping on all orders and free shipping on orders
over $49. Call 866-229-0927, 866-229-0927 or visit MyPatriotSupply.com for emergency
preparedness, self-reliance and food independence. Shop with a name you know and a name you can
trust. Before it's time to survive, it's time to prepare. MyPatriotSupply.com.
Here's USA Today, Huffington Post, Bloomberg, Wall Street Journal. We can punch it up for
TV viewers that are watching on prisonplanet.tv or just type in tax increase on 77% and literally
dozens of articles will pop up. 77% of Americans to have their taxes increased and it'll just
be added on to your paycheck or taken out if you actually file your own taxes.
And we've got this clip of Obama here. That's just on payroll taxes right there. There's
a bunch of other taxes and the Obama surcharge on investments and 401Ks and that's just the
beginning. All totals like 14, 15 new taxes, but they call them surcharges and fees so
they're not. It's not global government that's being set up, it's global governance. Let's
go ahead and play Obama four years ago back during the campaign as saying, I pledge to
never raise your taxes. Here it is.
I can make a firm pledge under my plan. No family making less than $250,000 a year will
see any form of tax increase. Not your income tax, not your payroll tax, not your capital
gains taxes, not any of your taxes.
Okay, so capital gains went up in Obamacare and payroll taxes went up. I mean, he broke
every single pledge and that's all he does. And a lot of Obama people over the first three
years really woke up to him, his approval rating went down. But once it was the left
versus right, rah, rah, Obama, Romney, you're a racist if you don't like Obama, the yuppies
and trendies, everybody said, well, hey, Obama's gonna win.
And then when Obama won, which was fraud, it was fraud to begin with, the whole fix
was in. Just like with the Republicans and the tax increases right now, it was rigged
from who was in the race to the fact that Obama clearly didn't win. They didn't care,
he was the guy who could create the most division, so they put him in.
And people are like, hey, my guy won, just you're angry about it. And I'm like, do you
understand Paul Ryan and Mitt Romney work for the very same foreign banks? And literally
when Mitt Romney was governor, he supported abortion, of government abortion funding,
open borders, takings, all semi-auto, handguns and rifles, carbon taxes.
And they go, sure, you lost, I won. And it's like, listen, this is dangerous, okay? They're
gonna destroy the economy. Right, right, you're just a racist. And it used to be a white person
calling in or on the street telling me this or commenting or newscasters. And see they
play along like they're part of the power structure, they're winning.
And now all over the country, in fact, guys, will you guys print me the article? I had
it on the nightly news last night, but I think it's on the other side. You can either jog
over there and then try to find it or just print me, teachers fired for not taking vaccines.
And there's another one, nurses fired. Suddenly all over the country, there's no law, and
they'd actually lost lawsuits before and it's racketeering when they make you do this.
But they just count on ignorance and they don't care if they lose lawsuits cuz it's
all government funded. It's about medical tyranny and forcing you to take shots. And
they're training police under the state's Model Health Emergency Powers Act to forcibly
inoculate you.
And that's what TSA putting their hands on you about, and that's what highway checkpoints
are all about, is they're getting you ready to put their hands on you. And I'm gonna get
into Feinstein's bill to physically confiscate your guns being introduced today. We told
you yesterday, Illinois was gonna introduce a bill, according to the NRA, they've done
it.
It's out of committee, set to pass today. Looks like it may pass right now to make all
people in Illinois turn their semi-autos in and pump everything that bolt action is gonna
be turned in. And they've got your void card, they know where to come get your gun, so they're
coming. It'll be on the news, the trucks and the police and people resisting being killed.
And it'll be patriotism to kill American gun owners, and they deserve it. They did Sandy
Hook and they're all Klan members anyways. Remember when that month ago they were calling
us Klan members and murderers?
You're like, that makes no sense, why are they just saying that? Cuz they're demonizing
us. Okay, see, you never saw demonization like that before, did you? See, they're taking
all the safeties off politically. They're announcing all of it. Here it is, nurses fired
for refusing flu shot all over the country. And now they're telling people that have children,
you're not gonna get your kid if you don't take the shot to my crew, to my crew.
Now we're recording them and stuff and not letting them know that it's my guy and they're
just to document all this nightmare, to get them. But the point is, is that I'm gonna,
it's just this country, folks. I've got mainstream news announcing checkpoints nationwide at
permanent highway checkpoints. Like you've had 100 miles into the border, nationwide
you're gonna drive up to police checkpoints, they're gonna search you, TSA is gonna be
there, it's been announced.
I've got those articles here. It's martial law, folks. And they're gonna set up machine
gun nest. You're gonna be under machine gun point when you pull up to these. We're going
under Fallujah control.
Here on the march, the empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company. Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These
all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are
earth friendly and safe. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for
a free catalog. Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as
good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs. This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel. See them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east, but we are still in the eye of the perfect
storm. The most devastating economic condition since the Great Depression. America's worst
drought in agricultural history. And now the economic results of the presidential election.
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply. I just doubled down and got even
more supplies from E Foods Direct and I recommend you do the same. It's time to get your own
supply from E Foods Direct. I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom
for food. I'm taking control of my future and you're nuts if you don't do the same.
Go to efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex to find the specials and you can start with
a holiday gift pack that's normally $80 now under 50 bucks. Remember, I can warn you but
I can't feed you. Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex. Would you rather prepare
six months too early or one day too late? 409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com forward slash
Alex. Alex Jones here with a very important announcement for truth seekers. We've carried
a lot of amazing films and books over the years on the online video bookstore at Infowars.com.
And out of all the titles we've carried, one stands out because it is just so chillingly
convincing and that's Dreams from My Real Father by Joel Gilbert, available at Infowars.com.
This film exposes the fraud that Obama is like nothing I've seen. If you want to know
who Obama's real daddy is, this is the film for you. Don't forget, your purchase supports
our broadcast and our growing media network. You'll also find it at Infowarshop.com. None
dare call a conspiracy by Gary Allen, the book that woke me up. We're also carrying
Behind the Green Mask UN Agenda 21 by Rosa Corey. This book is coffin nails to the globalist
takeover. The Greater Good, the most professional and up-to-date film I've ever seen exposing
the scourge that is vaccines. These titles and a lot more are all available at Infowarshop.com.
The Alex Jones Show. Some people say a man is made out of mud. A poor man's made out
of muscle and blood. Muscle and blood and skin and bones. A mind that's weak and a back
that's strong. You load 16 tons, what do you get? Another day older and deeper in depth.
St. Peter, don't you call me cause I can't go. I owe my soul to the company store. Monday
through Friday, from 12 noon to 3 p.m. Central, we're live back Sundays 4 to 6 p.m. And of
course don't forget ladies and gentlemen that we also have Infowars Nightly News 7 o'clock
Central every single evening.
Every single evening at 7 o'clock Central and one membership to Infowarsnews.com helps
us pay for the bandwidth and expand the TV and filmmaking operations. And one membership
then gets an additional 10 people. So really it's a total of 11, the banners on Infowars.com
and prisonplanet.com. They say that it is get one membership and share it with 10 people.
That's technically 11 memberships. The same username and passcodes can be logged in simultaneously
from 11 different computers with the same username and passcode. That is less than 59
cents per person per month.
You've absolutely got to go get a prisonplanet.tv membership or buy five or six of them and
support us. And then put the username and passcode you create that's for the site. Simple
names so people can remember it and go give them maybe cards to your boss or your employees
or your church.
I mean, you could go get three memberships that would be like, I guess $17, $18 a month.
And that would be 30 plus memberships. And then go out and get friends and family to
tune in every night. We put archives up in high def, all the films, ebooks, a bunch of
other documentaries.
We've been authorized to post up there. I mean, it really is a first class site now,
the new film, strategic relocation, special documentaries, all of it. This is the future
of the real medium. This is the real cutting edge. And we are continuing, I mean in perpetuity
that you can go get a monthly membership for 595 and 11 people can use it simultaneously.
And I'll tell you, most people aren't gonna tune in at the same time at seven o'clock
every night when the show goes on and then re-airs over and over again.
So I mean, you can probably get 20, 30 people. I mean, in fact, I think it's safe to give
like 20 people your username and passcode. Again, don't have the same username and passcode
as we say on the site. You have for other things, make it a unique one. And then email
it to friends and family.
Say, hey, here's my username and passcode. You can use it. They just go enter into the
username and passcode. Boom, they're in prisonplanet.tv or in fullwarsnews.com. We'll get them there.
And this is a really powerful initiative. If you've already got a membership, share
it with other people. If you wanna really support us, go get a couple more memberships
and print them up on cards, the username and passcode you create that's simple.
And then go give it to people, prisonplanet.tv. And I see that people are using this, people
are doing this and it is very, very exciting to see tons of people tuning in when the transmission
premieres every single evening at seven o'clock central standard time. And then of course,
there's archives a few hours later in HD. You can watch it when you want, how you want,
where you want.
And we're just adding more and more features to it all the time, a big redesign of the
site. Okay, getting back into the news, let me just cover some of what's coming up here.
Obama to quickly go for immigration reform, that means total open borders. And this is
out of the weekly standard, and gun control. So every time we do the document cam, it's
just right here. This is the spot right here, it's right here, we can show the TV viewers,
there you go, it's right there.
Obama to quickly go for immigration reform and gun control, White House pledges action
this month. And it just continues to go over all of that draconian Illinois gun ban advances
to Senate floor. Effort to apply Chicago's disastrous gun policy across entire state
accelerates.
It hasn't been disastrous, it's been a mafia takeover, it's worked absolutely well, the
drug war is a big success. Record prison populations, the country converting to a prison culture,
largest prison population in world history. Giant mega banks laundering all the drug money,
the police totally corrupted in many areas, I mean, it's absolutely worked like a charm.
And continuing here with the news, deputy police chief calls for permanent DWI checkpoint
in Texas. And they're doing this all over the country, they have these individuals under
federal grants. Every day I tune into local radio news and they're going, I think it's
the right thing to do to have checkpoints on the highways and just search everyone.
And Clinton called for this and signed an executive order, but obviously was unconstitutional
so it never got implemented. And they said, we're gonna set up hardened checkpoints on
the highways and we're gonna pull everybody over and search them. So to get everybody
ready up to 100 miles inside the border, they put these up to basically harass citizens
and dig through your car without a warrant claiming their constitution free zones.
More than half the population lives within 100 miles of a border or coastline. I think
it's like 70 plus percent if you pull up the numbers. So the point here is that they're
already doing it though. And under Clinton, I filmed this and have it in my film, Police
Day 2000. You can see I-35 at night backed up 20 miles from Kyle in South Austin, in
the suburbs, all the way to Georgetown, 20 miles traffic, 3 miles an hour, just to see
if they could do it.
And people sat there, and if you exited anywhere on the 20 miles, they said that was probable
cause to pull you over and search your vehicle on top of it. I mean you see 20 miles of traffic,
and we went and drove down the country roads, got out to the end of the checkpoint. Awesome
police remember this, and they tried and then the legislature said that's illegal, don't
do it anymore.
And the police now servile minions of the feds, at least the police chiefs. You've heard
it in Arkansas and Oklahoma and California and Michigan, Marines help run DWI checkpoints.
And it's in the newspapers in California and places and Marines with nine millimeter Berettas
on their hip and heavy machine guns in the backs of Humvees aiming at people.
There's a bank robbery outside Denver, so they shut down 50 something square miles and
dozens of roads and streets and have cops out with M-16s aiming them at everybody. Just
an act of domination, an act of piracy, an act of total control.
And now all over the country, they're pulling people over with the same glove. It's totally
illegal to search you without a warrant. They don't care, they just say women, get up against
the car. And then they take their hand and go in your body. They go in men's rectum,
they go in women's hind end, they go in the women's sexual organ.
And the women get sick and they get infections, they do it to multiple people. And they go
to the doctor and they just go shut up, shut up and get used to it. We'll use the same
glove and we're gonna stick our hands in you and you're gonna take it.
Just amazing, ladies and gentlemen. And so here's the article, deputy police chief, he's
been doing this like every day for six months, calls for permanent DWI checkpoints in Texas,
hardened points. And this is what Homeland Security is already announcing, they bought
thousands of these armored pillboxes that are like these armored 18-wheeler trailers.
And they just set them up, they've already done tests in Tennessee and other areas. We've
shown you newscast video, showing some of it now, and they just search you.
And by the way, folks, it's getting to the point, they're hiring cops, where you even
lip them. They just get you out and just go taser time, or they just roundhouse with a
big old punch, break your jaw, charge you with assaulting them, even though it's on
video. You videotape them, they club your head in, take you to jail, and it's just they're
gonna stomp your guts out, America.
They're gonna take your guns unless you wake up. I mean, I'm laying out what's really going
on here. I'm telling you where the end of the road goes, okay? I'm telling you where
the end of the road goes, okay? And the state police for two weeks, when they showed these
police just randomly, I'm gonna pull you over, happened to Darren McBreen's girlfriend.
She's driving all the way out of West Texas to come here and see him. She's on the same
road, cops pull him over, and they go, I saw you not use a turn signal. And she said, I've
been on the same lane for over 100 miles, he goes, let me just see your eyes.
This is just a DWI, just apologize, just randomly checking here. It's a joke, I mean, cops pull
me over, know who I am and ask if I'm drinking or if I have drugs or guns. And I just go,
number one, I don't use products that your bosses ship in. Number two, I'm not dumb enough
to be drinking and driving.
And number three, I just don't even know what to say anymore. You know full well that you're
implying guns are illegal. It's gone, it's gone. We have the biggest prison population,
we have the highest cancer rate, they're killing us. We're being killed, okay? And I've got
all their White House science, our book, Eco Science, where they talk about how they kill
us with cancer and kill us with stuff in the water.
I mean, it just sterilizes our sperm counts down 87 to 89% and the women are dying. Highest
rate of breast cancer in the world and our kids are the most brain damaged in the world
from all the shots. And I'm a bad guy, I'm a mad dog for being upset about it. Let me
continue here. A deputy police chief in South Texas, South Texas is the second biggest city
in Texas.
What is it, like 5 million people, wants to set up permanent DWI checkpoints in order
to save lives. Well, I mean, how do I put cameras in our house? They're already proposing
that in Houston. It saves lives, raising the possibility that Texans would be forced to
show their papers, submit to breathalyzer tests, and even mandated to have blood drawn
whenever they drive down the street.
Yeah, the feds started this 15 years ago in Phoenix, and now they've done it everywhere.
And first they go, well, it's a holiday, no refusal to take blood. Listen, one of my graphics
crew was out, and I happen to know she doesn't even drink. And they're out before New Year's,
it was after Christmas, and they're driving home and she's a designated driver going out
to eat.
And they get them out and they go, we're arresting you all, we can smell alcohol. And they go,
well, I haven't been drinking, I'm a designated driver. They said, well, do a bunch of sobriety
tests. She did one and said, look, I've not been drinking, I told you. They said, that's
it, you're DWI too. They wanna stick needles in you, and I'm gonna get to the forced inoculations
in a moment.
And it goes on, San Antonio Deputy Police Chief Antonio Trevino appeared Monday in Austin
before the Texas House Criminal Jurisprudence Committee. The San Antonio Express News reports
he urged legislators to allow law officers to stop drivers and do routine sobriety tests
near so-called drinking and driving hot spots, which is just everywhere.
Again, they let you go drinking the bars, humans have always done it. Texting and driving
is five times more dangerous than MIT studies, that isn't what matters. It's all about getting
you into the system, but if you're an illegal alien, they let you go. He says local data
could be used to identify areas where such behavior is prevalent.
Okay, let me explain to you, they're already doing these illegally. Here's the next story,
Steve Watson, infowars.com, prisonplanet.com. Texas cops cite gangs as justification for
unconstitutional checkpoints. They set up highway checkpoints across South Texas, and
then just search your car, they admit it in the articles, the McKellen Monitor, and make
you take your shirt off on the side of the road and take photos of your tattoos.
And then the argument is, well, it's the Mexican drug gangs that are government trained and
ship guns to and launders the drug money for, well, COVID Wells Fargo on record. I mean,
it's all a joke. You made the drugs illegal, just like they made alcohol illegal, cuz you're
criminals, cuz you want a cut of it, and you've destroyed Mexico.
And now they're gonna declare martial law. I had a state senator on two years ago who
said they've already declared martial law on the border. Now it's coming all the way
up to San Antonio, almost 200 miles from the border. I mean, I've seen Border Patrol vehicles
pulling people over in Austin, and it's citizens. I've talked to people who've had TSA, we even
got photos of it, big black armored vehicles that say TSA.
And they'll come up and rouse women in a parking lot and ask them what they're doing. I mean,
it's just a bunch of goons like North Korea. And they go on to break down how they're doing
and that's out of the McAllen monitor. I mean, ladies and gentlemen, this is just unbelievable.
Now let me move along to this report right here. Nurses fired for refusing shot, KTXS.
This is all over the country. Hospital employees had filed appeals citing religious reasons.
Six nurses and other employees at hospital in Indiana are out of jobs refusing the flu
shot. I just feel like it's a toxin. Well, it says it on the insert, it can kill you.
And I don't want it in my body, she told the station. There are side effects. Says that
in the insert, I can show you. CDC saying it can kill you. There are no guarantees that
it's even going to protect you.
The flu shot has never been guessed a year early of what it's actually gonna be. And
it lowers your immunity by 50% each time you take it and gives you Alzheimer's. But that's
mainline studies. Now let me tell you the story, okay? And we're not ready to give out
the info yet because we wanna not play that card right now cuz I'm probably gonna help
him litigate.
One of my crew members wife had a two pound six ounce baby last week. The baby has brain
swelling, the baby has blood going cuz 300 heart beats per minute out of its ventricles
into the lungs, the baby is in critical condition. What's going on at the hospital? And I warned
him too cuz it's a city affiliated when I said don't go near your life.
You gotta go where rich people go if you're gonna go to a hospital because they don't
feed on them yet. If you go to a big mainline mega hospital, folks, they see you as an animal.
Or you better show up in diamond rings and top hats because you have a birth plan or
whatever, you say on there no vaccines.
And the nurses try to pressure you do it, you go, no, I know there's no law, stop saying
there is. They're in there telling him, we're not gonna give you your baby. We're gonna
take your baby, which is in a lot of trouble. I want you to pray for the baby girl, we're
just gonna leave it at that.
This is a great guy and great lady, friends of mine, just really good people. And they
are in there day one going, you as parents must take the shots or you can't have your
kid, hepatitis, flu, you name it. No law, but they're telling them it is. You understand
how criminal that is, but they just do it cuz they're backed up by the police and their
ignorance and their evil.
And they're in there saying basically that, well, I'm gonna break it down after break.
But you remember just four years ago, everybody knew you don't give a pregnant woman a vaccine
as the insert says and cause a miscarriage or brain damage the child. And it's just well
known for decades. And I got crew here who have wives who are nurses, where they're pregnant.
And the hospital's like, okay, you don't have to take the shot cuz you're pregnant cuz the
doctors still know that.
But now they've come out in the news and said, no, if you're pregnant, you need extra shots.
Folks, they wanna just see if they can kill us right out in the open. And they're there,
imagine when a mother is in these desperate straits. They forced her to take the shots
outside of law, saying we'll take your baby. It's unbelievable.
Injuries, slow healing, aches and pains, constipation, weakness, fatigue are all common the older
one gets. The progressive deterioration of the body that occurs almost universally the
older one gets can partly to significantly be prevented with conscientious attention
to nutrition. If the Hanza men can play rugby in their 90s, then it is possible for everyone
in North America to experience a more youthful life as well. One key ingredient to warding
off aging and reversing some of it is the type and quality of protein consumed. All
protein foods or supplements you currently consume are heat damage, destroying 50 to
75% of your ability to utilize the bodybuilding amino acids. One world way is not heat damage
and allows your body to utilize 100% of the amino acids. This feat no one else has achieved.
The results to your health can be amazing. Call 888-988-3325. That's 888-988-3325. Or
visit Oneworldway.com. That's Oneworldway.com.
We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration. As an authorized Berkey dealer for over six years and serving thousands of
satisfied customers, the Berkey Guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration
systems. The Berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable
black purification elements that purify water by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria,
cysts and parasites to non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides
and pesticides. Order the Berkey light system today complete with two black Berkey elements
for only $231 and the Berkey Guy will ship your order free of charge. With the purchase
of a Berkey light, the Berkey Guy is also offering a set of fluoride and arsenic filters
for only $39.99. That's over 30% off the retail price. Call the Berkey Guy at 1-877-886-3653.
That's 1-877-886-3653. Or order online at GoBerkey.com. That's GoBerkey.com today.
Digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of toxins. That bears repeating.
Digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of toxins. And ProEM-1 daily probiotic
cleanse is the key to digestive health. ProEM-1 is a powerful liquid probiotic, strong enough
to cleanse, gentle enough to use every day. ProEM-1 is dairy, wheat and soy free, contains
all natural and certified organic ingredients, contains no preservatives or animal products,
supports a healthy digestive and immune system, supports weight loss, improves absorption
of food nutrients, aids in controlling yeast infections, is never freeze dried and uses
three groups of live, viable beneficial microbes to cleanse and remove toxins. Order ProEM-1
daily probiotic cleanse at Tereganics.com. Spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X.com. Tereganics.com.
Your call toll free, 866-369-3678. That's 866-369-3678. ProEM-1, the raw probiotic.
Let me break down how evil, how criminal, how wicked the TSA, the hospital workers,
the police, the whole system, they gang up like gangs and say, we're going to drag you
off in a room and stick our hands down your pants. We're the state police. And we'll show
some video of that for TV viewers. We're going to pull women over and we're going to get
these good looking women out.
That's why this was, it's always the same. And we're going to take the same glove and
we're going to stick it inside your body. That's America, folks. And the sycophantic
fetish of worshiping government is so incredible that people are like, it's the right thing
to do. It's for our safety. And they're showing the video now and they go to the next woman.
It's even more incredible. Now same glove, it's on record, here they go. That's on top
of all this.
Now let's expand on this. One of my crew members, probably the sweetest person that works up
here. In fact, no doubt the sweetest person that works up here. They're so excited about
having a baby. And of course, the system pushed to have ultrasounds over and over again. And
I was like warning them that it's study show that causes this.
But the point is, that goes on. There's a medical mafia. And then they're in there for
like a week now. And they come in and they go, you're not going to get your baby unless
you take shots. And this is somebody that works here and is smart. And they go, there's
no law.
They're like, yeah, there is. Well, show me the insert. There is no insert. Well, I want
the one without mercury. Just see what they go. There is no mercury. It's all just, you're
like, well, yes, there is. It's all just savage lying. And it's called gaslighting. That's
one term used in psychology.
And it made me physically ill when he was up here with tears in his eyes yesterday.
And I just said, go in there, record it. And we'll save a lot of people's children when
we put all this out. I said, record it. Get them to all say it again. Record on your iPhone.
And we'll get them.
You gotta get aggressive with these people, okay? They will tell parents, it's the law,
your kids gotta take vaccines. They shoot them up from Alabama to California now without
parental consent. And when people sued in California, they got the legislature to pass
a law to shoot your kids up and not even tell you, saying the state is the parent.
I mean, that's crook. They're like, we got a law to do it. Really, you got a law to do
it, huh? Your law is a tyranny. Your law is a fraud. And I've got all the Supreme Court
cases, but everybody knows that. I mean, these people are a cult of yes men. And these mega
corporations that are eugenicist, they go out and they hire people who will do what
they're told.
They give you psychological profiles now to get a job at McDonald's. And those profiles
on record are set to make sure you'll go along with it. Gaslighting is a form of psychological
abuse in which false information is presented with the intent of making a victim doubt his
or her own memory, perception, and sanity.
That's where they go. They'll say, you have to take the shots as mommy and daddy. And
so does the baby. Instances may range simply from the denial by an abuser that previous
abuse incidents have occurred, up to the staging of bizarre events by the abuser with the intention
of disorienting the victim. And see, the globalist brag, Cass Sunseat at the White House says,
they want to disorient us.
All this is like, our bill says we're gonna take your guns, but we're not going to. We're
building the trans Texas corridor, but it doesn't exist. And they play these mind games
with people, and that's why people are disoriented. And you watch cartoons and TV. That's why
cartoons don't make sense and are all disjointed.
It's on major studies. The kids brains are already wired wrong. They're brain damaged.
The general public's in a trance, folks. They've got military control grade systems that have
been proven in torture camps by the Chinese, the communist Russians, the Nazis in our government,
and they're using it on you. The police are pulling you over, putting their hands up your
rear end. This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health. At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver based products. Our most popular silver based products are
the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two ounce nano silver nasal applicators as well
as our all natural silver soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver
gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver
at the surface. But rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the
silver more effectively. Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver
based products are best for you. That's www.silverlungs.com.
If you just joined us, it makes me physically ill because I empathize. I've told the story
of
I live out in the country, I can watch these geckos hunt like tigers or lions sitting there
by the light coming out and eating mosquitoes, little fat pink things, a little lizards and
skinks and others.
Some of them are like a foot and a half long, some of these lizards, it's like Wild Kingdom
out in the Texas Hill Country.
And undoubtedly a couple times a year, especially when it gets cold, they come in the house
and I'll be in the bathroom at night and I feel a crunch.
And I turn the light on and there's a little smash gecko, his guts and brain smashed down
and it hurts.
Because it's a pointless death and it's a cute little creature and I empathize with
it cuz I love life.
Now I have proper instincts, I understand to go out and shoot a deer that's a prey animal,
butcher it and then eat it, that is a natural progression.
If you don't, you get overpopulations of them and they're running out in front of cars everywhere
and starving to death, this is just happening in Austin.
You're like, where is this going?
What are you talking about before Dr. Corsi comes on to get into the Trans Texas corridor,
the attack on the Second Amendment, just unprecedented stuff happening, but we have a normalcy bias,
even I do now, to just accept it.
Warrantless checkpoints where they stick their hands inside your body, it's all being set
up.
Then the cops pull you over and just laugh at you cuz they're in the uniform, they're
in the car, they got the power.
Doesn't matter they've already been implanted with cancer viruses in the flu shot, doesn't
matter they're gonna be in 10, 15 years dead of cancer, 45 years old, they'll never even
know what hit them.
So there's not even a, it's sad when you're looking at one of these zombies, cuz they're
just victims, but you can't get through to them, you can't get through.
You're not gonna get through to the zombies, 5% of our forebears said no to the corruption
and won, and there's way more than 5% of us really get what's going on, but I wanna say
something to mainline conservatives here.
It's time for you to realize that the left isn't the left, and the left isn't environmental
wackos or stupid or they don't know what they're doing.
They know taking guns makes crime go up, they wanna make you their slave.
And the reason I got off into empathy is that when I know somebody and their baby is in
critical condition fighting for their life.
And the nurses are there bullying them and telling the young mother, yeah, you gotta
take the shot or you don't get to have the baby, we'll take the baby.
That's like saying, come into somebody's door and saying, buy life insurance from me or
I'm gonna kidnap your kid.
I mean, it's the same thing, but it's, you're in a nurse uniform, well, I better do what
you say cuz the nurses have been forced to take it.
They're gonna now abuse you and force you to do it outside of law, assaulting you with
a deadly weapon proven to be hurting people.
It's amazing.
And they sit there with gaslighting and I'm telling you, gaslighting is a term used since
the 30s and there's other clinical names for it.
And it's in psychological warfare manuals that are declassified that I've gone and read
and training films that you can look on YouTube, army training psyop manuals of how when they
would take over a third world country, how they control people and round them up.
Our military has done that.
You go watch those psychological warfare videos, just type that in, army psychological warfare
videos, and you'll see them from the 50s and stuff.
And it's what they're setting up with the checkpoints and the tattletales and all this.
And they'll come to you and you're like, you just use the same glove to go in my hind end
and then in theirs, and they'll go, there's no glove.
And you're like, what do you mean there's no, cuz it never, it's a psych warfare technique.
There's no trans Texas corridor, Israelis don't own guns.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die?
Start purifying your water with ProPure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none
is ProPure and it's available discounted at infowars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified, optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%, easy to set
up and use, doesn't require electricity, purify water from lakes, streams, ponds, and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
ProPure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses, infowars.com already has the lowest price on ProPure.
Even if you add the promo code water at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the East, but we are still in the eye of the perfect
storm.
The most devastating economic conditions since the Great Depression, America's worst drought
in agricultural history, and now the economic results of the presidential election.
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply.
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from eFoods Direct, and I recommend you do
the same.
It's time to get your own supply from eFoods Direct.
I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food.
I'm taking control of my future, and you're nuts if you don't do the same.
Go to eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex to find the specials, and you can start with
a holiday gift pack that's normally $80, now under 50 bucks.
Remember, I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex.
Would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late?
409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com forward slash Alex.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
A prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at InfowarsShop.com.
These are items that I did research on, that I personally use.
You've got the LifeStraw, so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor Hand Crank Generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out
in the field.
Strategic Relocation, third edition by Joel Skousen.
When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein.
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Hand Crank Shortwave AM-FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at InfowarsShop.com
and your purchase makes our Infowar possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you?
InfowarsShop.com.
Big Brother, Mainstream Media, Government Cover-Ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
My friends, we are in extremely dark times.
The darkest of my 17 years on air.
And unfortunately, our worst analysis is coming true.
The worst case scenario is now unfolding.
You can probably tell I'm a lot more serious and focused on air.
I'm a lot more angry.
And it's because the globalist are hammer down.
They are going for broke right now.
As the big new Brzezinski has said in two council on foreign relations speeches, also
another one in Poland, and in his new book that I read a few months ago.
The globalist are in trouble, worldwide there's an awakening.
And so they are going to try to artificially trigger revolutions and put radical Muslims
in charge to destabilize the whole world.
And then use that threat to take our liberties, it's the old British game of divide and conquer.
Expanding on that, it is in the Illinois Senate, the NRA says it looks like it may pass.
The article is up at infowars.com.
It is a physical gun ban of all semi-automatics, revolvers, handguns.
You name it.
You can reach up infowars.com for viewers and people can actually see that article if
they're watching at prisonplanet.tv.
But gun ban bill advances to Senate floor.
Now notice they use the psychological warfare program of saying we never want your guns.
We don't wanna make you turn them in.
That's preposterous.
I've played Joe Biden saying it's ridiculous.
Nobody's gonna try to take your handguns.
Nobody's gonna try to take your shotgun.
He authored an even stronger assault weapons ban that called for them to physically be
turned in, that Dianne Feinstein originally turned in, that made you physically turn in
all semi-autos.
And we played the clip of her saying, I tried to get a bill where Mr. and Mrs. America have
to turn in their guns.
I'll play that clip later, but if you're a new listener, it was all over the news last
week.
But then they play this game of we're not doing that, we're not doing that, we're not
doing that.
Dianne Feinstein's introduced her bill that even mainline gun groups are going, it makes
you go in with your legally bought guns, and you go into the ATF and then they decide if
you can keep them, it's registration.
No, the bill actually says that and a forced buyback.
And she's in the New York Times with Cuomo saying we're gonna make you turn them in.
And now in Illinois, the area that this mafia controls, Rahm Emanuel and others, we're on
the radio in Chicago right now fighting him, a lot of good people up there are exposing
it.
They're saying, yeah, all state holders of guns, handguns, rifles, revolvers, pump shotguns
and pump rifles.
Yeah, I saw somebody on infowars.com comment and go, there's such a thing as pump rifles.
Yeah, you didn't know there were a lot of pump rifles?
Actually some pretty good firearms out there.
Lever action, you name it.
They basically are banning everything but bolt action and single shot.
And they've got the Floyd registration, they always use registration to then confiscate.
And they want the Chicago model of a total gun ban for citizens, which has made it the
murder capital of the world, 500 deaths last year, 512 they said.
And most of it's getting related.
The point is, this is the days of Al Capone, it's gangs killing each other, citizens have
a right to defend themselves.
And a lot of those deaths were citizens defending themselves.
Dr. Jerome, of course, is gonna join us for the balance of the hour and I appreciate him
coming on.
We're gonna get into this, we're gonna get into his article where Perry is still doing
public private partnerships, Trans Texas, Napa Super Highway in pieces.
And people say, I was on Man Cal yesterday and he said, well, why is it important if
it's in Texas?
He was asking a rhetorical question, he knew why, a really smart guy, Eric Muller.
And I said, Eric, there's 40 plus major interstate highways, another 40 other corollary roads
that they, in the official Department of Transportation documents, say they wanna take over, put taxes
on and fund the North American Union with.
And it's an artery right down to the Pacific side of Mexico with the biggest port now in
the hemisphere to bring in Chinese goods.
And it's an international corridor, like the Romans used roads to control things.
And I made the film Endgame, Blueprint for Global Enslavement, almost three hours long.
About 30 minutes of it is on this subject and it shows Bush giving speeches saying,
we've merged the North American Union with the EU, all the agreements.
I mean, we're already way down the hole here.
So all of that's going on, and that's what this is about.
We're already under a North American Union.
But the states twice voted it down.
Texas is the main funding artery to fund it all the way up into Canada.
They've got mile markers all the way to Canada.
It's marked for mile markers all the way for something like 2,000 miles.
But they just call it the I-35 shooter round outside Austin.
But it goes all the way to San Antonio, it's there.
And CNN, I've played the clubs, you've seen it, would say Ron Paul four years ago is insane.
There is no Texas superhighway, there is no trans Texas corridor.
We had billboards all over the state with a cowboy going, I like the trans Texas corridor
and paying tolls.
And they had ads going, yeah, it's trans Texas corridor, Texas is proud to be part of the
NAP superhighway system.
I'd go to movies and see ads before the movies going, Texas is a proud part of the North
American Union, appreciate all you're doing.
Meanwhile, we go, hey, we don't want this, it doesn't exist.
And that's a psychological warfare term called gaslighting, is a form of psychological abuse
in which false information is presented with the intent of making a victim doubt his or
her own memory, perception, and sanity.
Instances may range simply from the denial by an abuser that previous abuse incidents
ever occurred, or even the staging of bizarre events by the abuser with the intention of
disorienting the victim.
That's why they'll have school drills unannounced where they aim guns at kids.
It happened to my crew, who's got kids in public school.
They come and bang on the elementary and say, we're here to kill you, and the kids all cry
and get scared.
And the teachers go, following a manual, we're sorry we had to do this.
It's because of American gun owners.
In one manual in Michigan, the feds issued it was, we're sorry to do this.
This was due to homeschoolers and people against public education.
That's AP, if you think I'm joking, they go, sorry, we just blew up a car in the front
parking lot and came and said we were going to kill you.
And children literally urinate on themselves, teachers have had to go to funny farms over
it.
Literally, this has been in the news, have breakdowns where they marched people out saying
they're gonna kill them and mask, and don't tell them it's a drill.
That was in Minneapolis, St. Paul.
Okay, I'm ranting, we'll go to our guests.
I just wanna introduce this, cuz some stations just joined us in this hour.
That it is a psychological warfare program, and the police are being brainwashed too to
just accept this.
Now they're announcing checkpoints all over the country to stop gangs and look for illegal
guns.
The hammer's being dropped, and Dr. Corsi can break this down.
He, of course, has worked with the State Department and National Security in classified areas.
He has a Harvard PhD in political science.
He's worked for Fortune, top mega banks, you name it.
I'm not gonna go over his whole bio, he's, I don't know, three or four number one New
York Times bestsellers.
But this is the total takeover, and the Republicans, you notice, $1 of cuts for every $41 in tax
increases.
77% of Americans, massive tax increases, Obama lying about that.
They're announcing total open borders, total legalization.
They're going for our guns everywhere, it's on, checkpoints, everything.
Dr. Corsi, how bad is it?
It's even worse than I thought it would be.
What is your take?
Why is it moving so quickly?
I mean, it is like the dam is broken.
Well, I think it's a rush to the finish line.
I think the new world order sees an opportunity.
With the article I wrote in the World Net Daily WND just over the holidays, it's clear
that Governor Perry, with the trans Texas corridor, that it's back.
I mean, I researched it and found that now there's something like $20 billion in road
work underway throughout Texas on these public-private partnerships.
That's the key idea, the public-private partnership.
In other words, and typically three of the one, three of these deals I looked at in particular,
is State Highway 130 near San Antonio, extensions of I-35 around Dallas-Fort Worth, Cintra C-I-N-T-R-A
in Spain, which was the company that was going to do the full development of the trans Texas
corridor, the 4,000 miles that Governor Perry proposed before we exposed it and they had
to withdraw the plan in disgrace.
But Cintra's going to build these highways on 50-year leases, where, for instance, let's
say Cintra puts up $5 billion, the state of Texas subsidizes with a billion dollars, Cintra
builds the extension to the road, now they're doing it piece by piece, and Cintra gets to
run the toll road for 50 years on a 50-year lease, and Cintra in Spain collects the tolls
from the motorists driving in Texas.
And again, this was something that Governor Perry said he'd put an end to.
2009, there was a pledge to end the trans Texas corridor with Cintra.
Don't forget, you've seen the collapse where CNN just said it didn't even exist.
Right, exactly.
I mean, they're still denying that any of this planning exists or that Winnipeg up in
Canada has been declared by Prime Minister Harper to be an inland port, and they're building
the same infrastructure.
What's incredible is the meetings, the maps, all of it's 100% public, and then they first
announced it even in Time Magazine, and then when we don't like it, they go, you're crazy,
that doesn't exist.
Well, they deny it, they laugh about it.
If you remember up in Montebello in Canada, when they were asked, Harper and Bush at that
time, the president of Mexico, three of them meeting in the Security and Prosperity Partnership,
if there was going to be a NAFTA super highway that was going to combine three nations and
this continent, North America, into an international transportation system, and Harper laughed
at it and he said, oh yes, it may be interplanetary.
And then of course he comes out and announces that Winnipeg is going to be an inland port
and that the government of Canada is committed to building an international transportation
structure that ties into trade in China.
Well, it's all in the SPP documents.
We're going to be right back to get into this, but then I want to get into the guns with
you, and I want to get into the Middle East, Benghazi, because you're an expert on this.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the East, but we are still in the eye of the perfect
storm.
The most devastating economic condition since the Great Depression, America's worst drought
in agricultural history, and now the economic results of the presidential election.
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply.
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from E Foods Direct, and I recommend you do
the same.
It's time to get your own supply from E Foods Direct.
I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food.
I'm taking control of my future, and you're nuts if you don't do the same.
Go to efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex to find the specials, and you can start with
a holiday gift pack that's normally $80, now under 50 bucks.
Remember, I can warn you, but I can't feed you, call 800-409-5633, or efoodsdirect.com
forward slash Alex.
Would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late, 409-5633, or efoodsdirect.com
You land in Buenos Aires, then a shuttle to Santa Rosa, where a nicely furnished cabin
with all amenities, Wi-Fi, executive food and wine, and laundry service awaits.
After a good night's sleep, your adventure begins.
You're on a golden stag safari for big game, but it's not Africa, it's Argentina.
One-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo, huger, bighorn rams, wild boar, and the biggest
stag deer in South America, all gold medal quality, all the action you can handle, land
rovers, top rental guns with scopes, all food, beverages, hunting guides, ground transportation
included and more, all more affordable than you can imagine.
The adventure of a lifetime starts at goldenstagsafaris.com, the big game hunting ranch, goldenstagsafaris.com.
That's the sound of your door being kicked in by an intruder with a single kick.
That's the sound of the same door now protected by the door sentinel at mysafedoor.com.
Go to mysafedoor.com right now and watch the amazing video at mysafedoor.com.
You'll learn how to turn your home into a fortress with the door sentinel.
Sixteen kicks later and the door sentinel is still holding strong, mysafedoor.com.
That's mysafedoor.com.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson.
Have you ever wondered why banks, stock workers, investment advisors won't talk about gold
IRAs?
They've been available since 1986, yet the financial industry won't recognize the value
of gold for your retirement.
Gold is outperformed paper investments, yet no word about IRAs.
If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns, call 800-686-2237.
Secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
Hi there.
My name is Frank Bates.
What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble.
I just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are, incompetent, lying crooks
that are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high.
Some have called this a conspiracy, others have called it a coverup, and you will be
shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy goes.
My video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them
and how you can beat them too.
Watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patriots have already seen
in the last three months.
Go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect
your home.
Go watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down.
Again, that's 123coverup.com.
To be kind to Dr. Jerome Corsi, who's with us again, I'm your host, Alex Jones.
I've been right up front in this, going to the Campo board meetings, watching the takeover,
reading the SPP documents that Judicial Watch sued and got.
And I know Dr. Corsi's been on this even more than I have, but watching in Texas, they don't
even follow their agreements.
In fact, most of the new toll road stuff is built off existing toll roads on roads they're
not even supposed to put them on.
They break the law and do that.
Bush signed an executive order, I guess they say that makes it all right.
I guess they could sign an executive order saying the moon was made of cheese.
And then most of these new roads get paid for with taxpayer money, and then Central
just gets the money.
But I wanna get into that, and that's why I originally asked the guys to get you on
Dr. Corsi, and I appreciate you coming on.
But what about the overall, I'm gonna go back into it.
I know you're focused on this now, but what about the overall going after the guns?
I know you've been writing about that, and the Republicans selling out to massive tax
increases.
I mean, they're trying to collectivize this country, they know massive tax increases are
gonna shut the economy off.
But I guess that's the plan to get people on welfare.
Let's first deal with the guns.
I mean, I wrote an article also sent it in to your producers there on the shooting that
was the recent shooting in the elementary school in Sandy Hook.
And I interviewed some of the top psychiatrists in the world, Dr. David Healy, who was in
Great Britain, Peter Bragan, Harvard-trained, formerly full-time consultant to the National
Institute of Mental Health.
And they universally told me that these kids who are shooting in the schools, these incidences
are almost 90% linked with the medications prescribed to these kids by psychiatrists.
In other words, what happens is the school shootings, a kid, let's say, in school is
a little bit difficult to deal with and maybe has some problems at home.
So immediately, the doctors come in and they diagnose the kid as having some psychological
disorder or an attention deficit disorder.
They put him, get him psychiatric treatment and put him on forced medication, Ritalin
or Prozac or any number of other very powerful drugs.
And these are psychotropic drugs that they produce, especially in these adolescents,
a form of suicidal and violent outbursts.
So if you look at the incidents that have occurred and track down who these shooters
are, you're going to find that about 90%, especially the high-profile cases, these kids
were on medication prescribed by psychiatrists, on behavioral problems, which may or may not
have been real or may have just been an attempt to control a difficult kid in a school environment.
And by the way, I covered your article last week.
And when you say 90%, that these scientists, these doctors are being conservative, they
count the few gang-related shootings where three or four people shoot each other as in
that.
And in those cases, they're usually just drug dealers.
So that's why it goes down to 90.
If you look at the real mass shootings, it's always goth whites or Hispanics who are avowed
devil worshipers.
I mean, every case, they are into the occult, they are avowed devil worshipers, and they
are on psychotropic drugs.
I mean, it's more like 100%.
In fact, I can't find cases where the real mass shooters where it's like 10, 15, 20 people
and it's not gang-related aren't on these drugs.
Well, in fact, Dr. Bragan was particularly good.
He said a lot of these kids are just kids that in a normal environment, you go back
40, 50 years, first of all, you'd have God in the school, you'd have parents around that
could be involved.
The kid might need some attention, might be a lonely kid.
Now the school, which doesn't really want to deal with the kids in general, in particular,
they don't want to spend any teacher time, the teachers aren't trained.
So they get the psychiatrist involved, they prescribe these extremely powerful drugs.
They put them on suicide pills, the insert says cause you to commit mass murder and suicide.
And these pills are extremely dangerous, psychotropic effects, which produce the suicidal tendencies
of the violent tendencies.
The kids further withdraw, they withdraw into these video games, which are killing video
games in this created world of fantasy of killing and violence.
And then when these kids acted out in reality in a school, people are surprised.
I mean, there's no reason to be surprised.
Doctor, doctor, if you study Chinese style mind control and CIA, it's drugging with scenarios.
These video games were designed to create instinctive killing by the US military, non-thinking.
You put them on mind control drugs and put them on a Pentagon killing simulator.
What do you think you're going to get?
Well, and in fact, a lot of these video games were created by the military in order to increase
the percentage of soldiers in combat that would actually use lethal force.
It's one of the little, little appreciated secrets of combat going back to the...
Break this down, doctor, break it down on the other side, we'll be right back.
We're on the march, the empire's on the run, Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as stress, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and
other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die?
Start purifying your water with ProPure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none
is ProPure and it's available discounted at Infowars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified, optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%, easy to set
up and use, doesn't require electricity, purify water from lakes, streams, ponds and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals, which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
ProPure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on ProPure, but if you add the promo code
WATER at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at Infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
You prepare by purchasing gold, food and firearms, but if you don't have a home security system,
then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection.
When you're sleeping, who's watching out for intruders and spooks?
Check out SimpliSafe.
It's a new do it yourself home security system that is completely wireless.
Go to GetSimplySafe.com.
SimpliSafe is independent and off the grid.
It runs on battery power, so even if the grid goes down, you're protected.
It's completely customizable, so you can use it in your home, business, boat, trailer,
storage unit or shed.
SimpliSafe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes, so there's no
need to let a stranger into your home.
If you move or need to relocate, you can take this system with you wherever you go.
SimpliSafe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
Go to GetSimplySafe.com.
That's GetSimplySafe.com.
There's an old saying in Tennessee, I know it's in Texas, probably in Tennessee, that
says fool me once, shame on me.
Shame on you.
If you fool me, you can't get fooled again.
He aligns himself with the truth, and it's time for you to choose a side.
You're listening to Alex Jones.
You know, Dr. Corsi is probably more qualified to talk about Benghazi than anybody I probably
know.
And I should have gotten him on the last few months about that, it's just that it gets
lost in the shuffle, and I'm jumping in, chomping at the bit, wanting to back up everything
he says because it's so on target.
I wanna get into that and Hillary's feigned garbage and all this other stuff that's going
on and where he sees America in general going.
I mean, does he agree with my analysis that it is just runaway train right now?
Is there any way to stop the takeover?
Why do the globalists think it's their opportunity?
Is it a response to seeing an awakening happening?
They're trying to head us off at the pass.
I wanna get his take on that.
I wanna go back into the Napa superhighway because it ties in to this tactic now that
those of us that are awake go, this is ridiculous and discrediting that they announced there's
no global government being formed.
But in hundreds of financial papers, they brag how they're forming a world government
run by private banks.
So why are they doing that?
Well, cuz we're informed the general public folks doesn't know where their state capital
is.
You have to understand, people think of knowing things as work.
They never discover that knowing things is addictive and is what really being alive is.
And so you gotta understand, I mean, the general public is just not even dumb, they're ignorant.
And this tactic of just lying, I mean, at hospitals everywhere, everybody I know goes
into the hospital and they say, we're not gonna fix your broken leg till you take a
flu shot.
And they're like, but you have to render care and they go, we're not going to, get out.
I mean, it's totally illegal on so many fronts, I mean, I've had lawyers on, it's unbelievable.
That's what tyranny is, it's a willful criminal oppression.
And they're just doing it.
And now they're gonna set up armored checkpoints all over the highways to quote, check for
gang members.
It's just incredible.
Dr. Corsi, getting back to what you were gonna talk about with, for those that don't know,
the statistics from World War I, World War II, on troops wouldn't kill people up close.
So the Department of Defense developed, and you're right, this is something even foreign
governments really didn't pick up on for a while.
It's given the quote, United States the edge, murder simulators, killer simulators, tell
people about that.
Well, these original combat video games were developed by the military around the time
of Vietnam.
Because the little known secret is that in combat, most of the killing in person is done
by two or three percent of the troops.
A lot of troops will not use violence, lethal violence where they can actually see the enemy,
even when they're in danger themselves.
So in Vietnam, our troops exposed to these kinds of games were able to get the kill ratio
up to about 90%.
90% of the people in combat would be willing to use lethal force.
And that's where these games started, because psychologically, they engineered desensitization,
their desensitized process to where killing another human being or using lethal force
against another human being is no longer repugnant.
It becomes acceptable in the frame of behavior for the person to find for themselves.
That in combination with the type of psychotropic drugs that we are regularly handing out in
our schools is a formula for disaster.
These kids play these games, get programmed for violence, take the drugs, the drugs affect
their psychology, their thinking, they become suicidal and violent.
And then we wonder why we have the incidents of the schools.
And we wonder why the military has record suicide, and we wonder why the US, the number
one cause of death now is suicide.
Wasn't in the top 10, 50 years ago, in fact, folks, you can show ABC News, number one cause
of unnatural death, now suicide.
You're a nation on suicide mass murder pills, and the social engineers know this full well.
Of course they do.
And I want to skip to, with the time we've got, I've been writing again about the economics.
I have an article out today that Ben Bernanke, in the time he's been in the Fed, which started
in February 1, 2006, on December 12th, which is when they announced this QE4, another round
of buying our own debt.
That period of time, from 2006 to December 12th, 2012, Bernanke doubled the amount of
national debt.
We went from $8.13 trillion to $16.4 trillion.
And this is, again, another conscious process of destroying the United States.
The QE4, Quantitative Easing 4, which is the economist's term for it, means that we're
going to be buying monthly $85 billion of our own treasury securities and mortgage backed
securities, which keeps interest rates artificially low, but is essentially creating so much liquidity
that the dollar is becoming debased, and it's setting up the precondition for hyperinflation.
Hyperinflation is now an inevitability.
It's built into the system.
And again, the economists know this, because in the crisis of hyperinflation, crisis of
all these mountains of debt, the Americans will give up freedom, they'll move into an
international environment, they'll allow the-
And by the way, you worked in banking at the highest level, so again, you are uniquely
able to speak to this.
What's the timeframe?
How bad is it going to get?
Well, it's going to get, first of all, we're going to be at a point where we may double
again the national debt, not within, may not take us six years this time.
We may do it within three or four years.
Certainly, we're going to be over $20 trillion by 2014.
And when we get over $20 trillion, remember, our gross national product is under $16 trillion.
Unbelievable.
So by the end of 2014, which is in two years, when we're coming up with the next congressional
election, I expect us to be in another economic crisis of hyperinflation.
And this whole deal of fiscal cliff is a fiction.
We went over the fiscal cliff a long time ago.
This recent legislation did nothing to solve the fiscal crisis of the United States.
We actually have more spending in the bill that was just signed, just passed, in this
emergency fashion.
And the idea that people, again, lies were rampant.
Obama was saying that no middle class taxes were going to be increased.
77% of Americans who pay taxes are going to have an increase because of the phasing out
of the 2% relief that was granted on the FICA reductions on payroll taxes.
That's going back in.
Even though this lie was told, Obama will say, well, I didn't mean that.
But people are still going to get smaller take home pay, and they can judge for themselves
whether they were lied to.
The federal government lies to us regularly.
The Obama now lies boldly and doesn't even get called for it by the mainstream media.
And this whole idea of increasing our debt to a proportion that's unprecedented in the
history of the world, you know, buying our own debt, I mean, you have to get your mind
around the Treasury is issuing debt and we are buying it in the Federal Reserve.
It's so insane.
And at some point or other, you can't keep doing this.
You can't keep printing money.
This is just blatantly printing money.
And the liquidity may boost the stock market, but eventually, like the Weimar Republic,
you get into hyperinflation, and the authorities doing this, including Ben Bernanke, know that
it is inevitable that they're going to debase the dollar.
In fact, it's a plan to debase the dollar.
You can't look at it any other way.
Now I wrote, I mean, I've also got, I sent in the links, I just published a book on Obama's
plan to bankrupt the United States, and this goes to the Cloward-Piven theory, and I really
think it's critical people understand what the Cloward-
And we're gonna put your new book up, and we've been showing WorldNetDaily and the information.
In fact, I wanna get this book, I haven't read it yet, we've carried your other books,
but I know this is gonna be powerful because I know they're game playing as well, and what's
incredible is, and I know you know about this, you've written about it, they brag that they're
bankrupting us.
Communists don't bankrupt things on accident.
We always say communists are bad managers, and quote, things don't work.
Because of the incredible production of the last 100 years and science, even in a communist
system that wasn't run by devils, it'd be horrible and it would be unfair, but everything
wouldn't collapse.
They collapsed Ukraine and Poland on purpose.
This is not a secret.
They collapsed China and killed between 60 and 80 million people, they debate the numbers,
to radically transform forever.
They understand you've gotta break eggs to make an omelet.
It's about the control, and so the goal is going well.
More people in prison, more people on welfare, paying to ship General Motors to China.
I mean, this is a plan, and I've read the review of your book, I know it breaks down
where they say it's their plan.
So explain to people, California when they raise taxes over and over again, that's meant
to bankrupt the state.
I mean, explain this to people.
Concord and Piven were two sociologists at Columbia when Obama was there, when Brzezinski
was there.
And their whole idea was that to destroy capitalism, you create social welfare programs, all the
unemployment insurance, the Obama phones, the entire list of programs where the government
is paying checks to people.
And you build this system to the point where it is so huge, you've gotta raise the tax
base in order to pay these welfare payments, social welfare payments, entitlements, that
the system collapses because the taxes destroy the economic activity, the tax base decreases,
the system goes into bankruptcy.
And then the, Cloward and Piven, the sociologists said that this is the time when we really
have the opportunity to create a true socialist, read communist state, in which the principles
of social justice, meaning destroying private property, destroying the family, having government
control of every aspect of your life, having the bureaucrats make all decisions, including
death panels on health insurance, 100% government control of all the means of production.
This is what the communist dream has been, and the Cloward and Piven theory is a way
to make the Democratic Party essentially advocate the socialist themes, welfare.
We're trying to help you, we care about you, want unemployment insurance.
And then by putting the tax burden to these unreasonable levels, having debt go beyond
the ability to pay the debt off, the system goes into bankruptcy, collapses, and then
the ashes, out of the ashes is born a true socialist communist state.
That's the goal, that's Obama's-
And they're gonna look to the 90% that don't have jobs anymore from over taxation and say,
we gotta kill the old people, they're already saying this in slate and Soros outfits.
I mean, it's so diabolical, and remember doctor, they always said, there's no death panels
or like it's in the bill.
No, there's not, there's no NAFTA highway.
What do you make of them coming out and saying that Israelis don't own guns and they don't
arm teachers?
I mean, the level of lying, these people make the Politburo look honest.
In fact, the Democrats were gonna propose this legislation, in themselves own guns that
are protected by guns.
If you go into a federal building, you try to go into the US Congress, you're gonna go
through metal detectors, you're gonna go through all kinds of federal agencies with badges,
with guns, examining everything you've got before you get in that building.
Why don't you know where you're gonna go?
The bureaucrats that want these gun-free environments don't themselves operate in a gun-free environment
because they know how dangerous it would be.
Well, they're mafia, mafia always wants to disarm its slaves.
Here's my question, what is the general prognosis?
Am I right, and Larry Pratt saying this is the worst assault ever, Ron Paul, I mean,
I want your view on this and then your analysis.
How bad is it because they now look gleeful and are attacking on every front and the Republican
leadership is collapsing and just saying, yes, this is what we're gonna do because the
foreign banks are buying both sides.
The GOP is in disarray, the globalists and the socialists who, the far left, the bill
of errors crowd has stolen the leadership of the Democratic Party.
This is not the Democratic Party of Jack Kennedy or Hubert Humphrey or Harry Truman.
That party's dead.
This is the radical left, the socialists, read communists, hijacking the Democratic
Party and putting their agenda in the name of progressive.
I saw another slight article today calling to get rid of our free speech.
I mean, these people are monsters.
Diets are gonna be left and right, you get a Sandy Hook coming on immediately, the new
world order agenda jumps on this for gun legislation, the worst possible thing.
And then when the NRA tries to hold a press conference, they get ridiculed by the mainstream
media, there's demonstrations, the acting up, the agenda is not heard, the lies are
being told, yes, teachers are armed in Israel.
Yes, if you walk around Israel, there are automatic weapons being held by off duty military
in uniform.
It's a very militarized environment because it's the only way it's safe.
And in fact, if you do create these gun free zones, the truth is like Chicago, you're gonna
create a free killing zone.
And then they bring the military in as the answer.
See how they do it?
They take the citizens' guns, it becomes a crime system, then they bring in troops, which
is they're now doing.
Rely on the government to protect you, which is exactly, our founding fathers' advice is
do not rely on the government to do anything for you.
Let me ask you this, are they going to win?
I mean, how bad is it?
Well, it's gonna be, it's the closest to the globalist and the socialist communists left
winning, and they're using the Saul Alinsky agenda.
Obama is gonna, again, you've gotta read these two ebooks I wrote, the one on the Saul Alinsky,
the evil genius behind Obama, and Obama's plan to bankrupt the USA, the Cloward-Pippin
theory, cuz it explains what they're doing.
They're using the class warfare, resentment against the rich, we've gotta tax the rich.
Even with Obama getting this agreement on the fiscal cliff, he's already saying in videotape
presentations to his constituency, the Obama for America crowd, that he hasn't taxed, which
are still not paying their fair share.
They won't have-
Howard Dean came out and said the poorest people need to pay more taxes.
Well, in fact, the point is that the socialist agenda, nobody in the end owns any private
property.
Except the master bureaucrats who are exempt from all the rules.
And are protected by the military, do not themselves live in gun-free zones, don't give
up their weapons, but in fact-
No, no, they all have bodyguards, that's a status symbol of them.
Bodyguards, go into a federal building that you don't have to go through a metal detector
with badges and guns-
Michael Moore has five to six bodyguards every time I've seen him, it appears Morgan has
armed bodyguards, I mean, it's all on record.
Hypocrisy and the lying of the New World Order and this Bill Ayers left, that Obama left,
has never been greater.
They're lying about everything saying, although we don't have a NAFTA superhighway, there's
no public-private partnerships here.
Then you look and you find there's $20 billion of deals that Governor Perry has signed with
Central and Spain.
No, no, they bragged in the AP years ago, they said Perry's just going ahead in chunks.
I mean, it's not a secret, they just laugh at us and incredible, incredible, just stay
there Doc, we gotta get a break, I wanna come back and get more into just the economy.
I mean, is there any way to turn this around?
How bad is it gonna get?
And then we'll have the third hour with a bunch of special reports we're gonna premiere
here and a bunch of news and so much more, we just gotta get the word out.
These people are such authoritarians, ladies and gentlemen.
Big business has discovered the preparedness market and that makes it difficult to know
where to go and who to trust.
MyPatriotsSupply.com is owned and operated by patriots just like you, has the best prices
on storeable food, non-GMO seeds, water filtration devices, home canning equipment, survival
and self-reliance books and more.
MyPatriotsSupply.com has old fashioned values and the absolute best customer service in
the industry.
Look for the deal of the day, unique affordable survival supplies that fit anyone's budget.
Get same day shipping on all orders and free shipping on orders over $49.
Call 866-229-0927, 866-229-0927 or visit MyPatriotsSupply.com for emergency preparedness, self-reliance and
food independence.
Shop with a name you know and a name you can trust.
Before it's time to survive, it's time to prepare.
MyPatriotsSupply.com.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the President could obtain its world class healer.
Now 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of super bugs with 17 naturally
occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune
cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VENUSFLY or order from Carnivora.com, that's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A dot com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VENUSFLY or visit Carnivora.com.
Protect your immune system, it's the only one you've got.
Weakened by GMOs, stressed out about money and blasted by the electric environment.
Hi, I'm Pastor Ginny and that was the state I was in back in 2010.
Then I learned about RNA drops.
I learned that 97% of my DNA that scientists have called junk is actually packed with millions
of gene switches that play a critical role in controlling how my cells, organs and other
tissues behave.
I learned I don't have to put up with disease decay or decline like I've been conditioned
to believe.
I began taking RNA drops, a 100% natural formula designed to turn on those switches and provide
me with amazing health and joy.
Learn more about RNA drops and order a free sample today.
Visit RNAfreesample.com, that's RNAfreesample.com or call toll free 888-577-3703.
Pay only shipping and handling for a free 30 day supply of RNA drops.
Get the information you need and the health you want at RNAfreesample.com.
We've got an extremely powerful video piece we did to counter Mayor Bloomberg's piece
with all the different actors saying turn your guns in.
One of our listeners, again, I'm proud that our listeners are so active, put out a video
showing how each actor in there is in these movies involved in gratuitous mass murder
and shooting.
Which then anti-gunners who aren't even gun owners, cuz there's not just the predatory
anti-gunners who know they wanna disarm us and make us slaves.
There's folks who've never had guns and they think of guns like Hollywood that every time
a gun's out somebody's oozing someone and they're real scared of them.
And Hollywood helps do that.
And one of our listeners put out a video that's had millions of views cuz DrudgeReport.com
linked to it and then Fox News picked it up and all these other channels.
That's what I keep telling listeners, I'm nobody special folks and I've reached 15 million
people a week now one way or another, okay?
People like Dr. Corsi, who's well researched and smart, he reaches millions every week
in interviews and his books.
One of our listeners, cuz I went to his channel and saw that he listens to the show and some
of his videos, went and did something that's been seen by tens of millions now.
And we're gonna put a video out that hopefully will get seen by millions that really counters
Bloomberg.
It's up to you though.
And just thank God for Drudge, listen, I gotta say something Dr. Corsi, I'm not just kissing
the rumpus of DrudgeReport.com.
I've been tracking it, and more and more, it's WorldNet daily, it's Infowars, but we're
like Junior when it comes to really just every time Drudge is able to take our information
and others and his research and really force it out there.
And I see the system always demonizing Drudge, because they don't like it.
And I think it's a tale and an example, an allegory of the fact that we can win.
If we get aggressive now, so let me ask you solutions in this segment and five and in
the next hour, I know you've got to go.
What can we do to really beat these people?
Because even a lot of folks don't like socialism, but their jobs have been shipped overseas,
they're disabled.
And Obama's gonna give them money until he fully takes over, then he's gonna euthanize
you.
What can we do as solutions, Dr. Corsi?
Well, I think first of all, you're right about Drudge, Drudge is doing yeoman's work, and
so are you, Alex.
We're in the battle, we're doing it every day as well at WND.
The weapon we've got is the truth, and we've got to keep developing and presenting the
truth to the American people.
We've got the advantages of being able to communicate with millions of people through
the internet, we've got the ability to get the word out, and people are reading and paying
attention.
In the next few years, we're gonna have to learn how to even use social media more effectively,
how to use all these techniques of reaching people one by one in their homes, knowing
who our listeners are.
There's great advances coming, and the ability, I believe, to technologically reach people
and communicate with people individually, but in large numbers.
But the advantage we've got is the truth, and I think if we keep going back to it, I
mean, every one of the articles I write, Alex, I footnote, I've got all kinds, you can go
look at the original sources.
That's what made the Articles of the North American Union, going back to when I was writing
the late, great USA in 2005, 2006, so powerful, was I linked to their own documents, the government's
own documents.
If you look at the article I have on Bernanke increasing our debt, I linked to the Federal
Reserve minutes in which that is announced, which is a document that's boring, most people
don't want to read it, but when you see it, it's startling, because there, the Federal
Reserve is telling you they're going to buy $85 billion a month, it's staggering.
It's like, we're going to buy a trillion dollars of our own debt, and as if that's, you know,
buying your own debt is like having a, you know, a printing press in your basement, so
checks come in, don't worry about it, we'll just keep printing money and send out, pay
the bills.
Well, it's a globalist, they get real goods for that, and then we get handed the debt
when most of its derivatives stay there.
Again, we're bailing the bankers out, we're going to do five more minutes, I want to hear
more solutions.
You are listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company, Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Aging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network and now live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
What is your own course?
He's got to leave in about four or five minutes.
He's got another interview coming up and again, I've been covering the whole field here, throwing
stuff at him, but finishing up with solutions.
I guess the solution is the truth, as you said, and knowing what their plans are.
Bankrupting America.
How do you expect things to go?
Sure people are waking up, but the power structure is accelerating things in your gut.
How do you see things ending and in your gut, are you the most concerned you've ever been?
I'm the most concerned I've ever been.
And we're going to have a series of crises that are produced that the only solution offered
is more government control by both parties, Democrats and Republicans alike.
This is where the Tea Party has got to recognize that the Republican Party is not necessarily
a natural home for a conservative movement.
It's not only exposing the truth, which we've got to do, but it's exposing the hypocrisy
of the socialists, the communists, the Obamas.
Obama lives, he's talking about the rich don't pay their fair share.
Well, Obama's living a life that would make most kings and queens in history pale in comparison
to the privileges he gives himself and his family.
We've got to expose this.
Michael Moore does not live a carbon efficient life.
None of these people.
Michael Moore is protected by weapons as is Nancy Pelosi, as is Senator Feinstein and
Chuck Schumer.
All these people go into a federal building to work all day where you go through a metal
detector and there's guards all over the place to protect them.
The hypocrisy is what exposes the New World Order, the lies and the hypocrisy.
The crises are what I'm concerned about because the capability of producing, people got to
understand this power pivot theory, that the engineered bankruptcy that we're in, this
expansion of the entitlement programs is a plan.
It's a plan to cause capitalism to crumble so people will give up freedom.
And then they blame capitalism when we've left capitalism and this is crony fascist
socialism.
Removal of God from everywhere.
This is a major theme.
The school in which the kid who's on, you know, psychiatrically prescribed drugs, playing
all day video games at his home, comes into that school.
You couldn't even use the word God in that school without being arrested.
But then Obama would pray once it came time, they still give us the old thing every once
in a while like it's a treat they give us to then punch our buttons.
It's all masterfully done and you get back to that.
When you remove God, the devil comes in.
You know, it's funny all these killers, they're not atheists, they're devil worshipers.
Play the God theme like music on, you know, in Oregon to get our emotions going.
So we say, oh, isn't it horrible, we've got to get the guns out of the schools.
No, you've got to get armed guards in the schools.
You got to get these kids.
So the teachers in the teachers union who don't want to spend any time dealing with
problem children, can't just send them off to a psychiatrist and give them Ritalin or
Prozac or some other-
Well, look, I'll say this, it'd be better to put kids in a boot camp to get their butts
kicked than assault them with Prozac and Ritalin that literally destroys their hearts and brains
and organs.
And again, that's the problem.
When I did stuff wrong, I got my butt whipped, the coaches whipped my butt, they'd make me
run till I threw up.
And thank God they did, or I'd have probably been in prison.
These kids need discipline.
And the social engineers, Dr. Spock and all them, they bragged, they knew, they knew what
they were doing.
They knew exactly what they're doing.
This is no longer freedom, it's no longer producing character, it's about control.
Producing control.
So those in power, the teachers union, the socialists running the Democratic Party, they
control everyone.
And whenever they want more control or more power, they create a crisis, a bunch of people
are killed, people are starving, they bring out God, roll out God for 20 minutes.
Barack Obama's not gonna let God be on the horizon.
Watch how many times he refers to God in the second inaugural.
No, he says we are not a Christian nation.
God bless you, sir.
We'll talk to you again soon.
The battle for the republic is now.
Thank you, Dr. Corsi.
Thank you, Alex.
Keep up the fight.
I will, sir.
We'll be back with masses of key information.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarshop.com.
These are items that I did research on, that I personally use.
We've got the LifeStraw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor Handcrank Generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out
in the field.
Strategic Relocation, third edition by Joel Skousen.
When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein.
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Handcrank shortwave AM-FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com
and your purchase makes our Infowars possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you?
Infowarsshop.com.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other
harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as
you get sick and die?
Start purifying your water with ProPure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research and the best gravity filter out there bar none
is ProPure and it's available discounted at Infowars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required, it's NSF 42 certified.
Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%.
Easy to set up and use, doesn't require electricity.
Purify water from lakes, streams, ponds and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
ProPure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on ProPure but if you add the promo code WATER
at checkout, you get an additional 10% off at Infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Show.
Alright we've had listeners begging for this more than anything I've probably ever seen
and because I know at a sick level it's entertaining but it's also revealing and the incredible
thing is we sit here and talk about them and then they still call in but some of them have
a halfway valid point.
They go, look, I don't like Mitt Romney.
I know he's evil.
I know Obama's evil.
He's a lesser of two evils but those are people that have, in my view, a fallacy in their
understanding and they don't understand what we're saying but when you get real Obama supporters
calling in, they say you're racist, you're bad, basically the talking points but they
really believe it.
I mean, they're freaked out, they're mad, they think I'm trying to keep them from some
wonderful world under collectivism under the eugenicist because this isn't just collectivism.
It's eugenics run collectivism but see all collectivism in the last 200 years has been
eugenics run because the British government ran this big empire and they made a big study
on record with a whole bunch of different scientists.
That's why all the major sciences came out of eugenics the last 160 years.
We cover this in the film Endgame.
It's free online, Endgame, Blueprint for Global Enslavement and it's the key to understanding
what's happening that they wanted to domesticate people and basically create a false reality.
Create an artificial system where you can't think outside that box and never escape because
they want that control box so they can reduce your numbers and people say, well, they haven't
done a very good job of it.
There are different paths and different forces in the world.
That's the thing, the globalist aren't all powerful.
They will be if they get that global technocracy in place, which they're really pushing for.
They could easily fail, they failed before.
They admit they're behind, that's why they're working so hard right now.
And some of you will go, well, there are too many people, have you seen how dumb the general
public is?
Okay, but you need to understand something.
Yes, there's truth to some of the eugenics argument.
And I've never really talked about this on air, this is such a complex issue and I wanna
make a whole film about it.
But when you really look at it, they've been there sabotaging things all the way, doing
things that actually increase the population and increased the population's systems, forms
of their systems to where it was more destructive on the environment.
It's incredibly complex.
I shouldn't even have gotten off into all this because the point is, they're trying
to dumb people down and they want more dumb people than smart people until they get control
and then they're gonna wipe almost everybody out.
It's all divide and conquer.
It's all play nation states off against each other, races, religions off against each other.
It's all a destabilization program.
I forgot to get Corsi's take on Benghazi.
We sent him back up next week for 30 minutes just on Benghazi.
I forgot to get to that.
The point is, is that it all goes back to eugenics and the government is attacking and
going after smart people.
You have to understand that eugenics is sold to yuppies and to intelligentsia like, hey,
there's too many dumb people and they cost too much money.
Let's go ahead and abort all their kids and get rid of them.
It's the humane thing to do.
Let's tell people we're liberals, we're really eugenicists.
Okay, we'll do that.
No, I understand, act non-threatening, exactly, sneak up on them.
All right, let's do that.
Meanwhile, the entire system, as if that isn't bad enough, is really targeted at smart people
who aren't part of the power structure or a surplus of smart people.
Or a surplus of aggressive people who they use to project their force, but who they fear.
So like a cannon after a war, they decommission and spike and cut up into pieces and melt
down.
They do that to our military after they've used you, and now they're just going towards
robots and drones where you're not even needed.
And then they write books to the heads of the big computer companies, write books and
articles in Wired Magazine how they're doing it to you.
I mean, it's not my opinion is what's frustrating about this.
I would have rather gone in the last 100 years, truly industrialized the third world equitably
to try to build up a system, have technology export that actually built up the first world,
while empowering the third world.
Basically no federal welfare, only local welfare, cuz I've studied economic systems at work.
But those systems create high education, true education, not indoctrination.
Notice the more education we get, the dumber we get, the more ignorant.
Again I said I'd take Obama calls and I just go off into a trillion different issues.
I really want good things for humanity.
I really have studied history.
It's not hard, it's not like I have my opinion about what works and they have their opinion
about what works.
They don't want collectivism to empower you.
They want collectivism so they have you under their control paying your electric bill and
paying for your tiny house, your agenda 21 jail cell, so that they can dictate you're
gonna take shots that are gonna actuary when you die to kill you early.
And so they can fully control your life and use you and expend you as a cog because they
are a religion, the priest of power.
Their whole religion is about organizing groups of people.
And I don't like it, and I don't like them.
I mean these globalists are very, very sick people and it is the ultimate sin in the British
Commission on Population.
I'm gonna give the number out only for Obama supporters here in a moment and call in on
their Obama phones.
I'll just go ahead and give the number out now cuz I'll keep pontificating and the whole
hour will go by.
I got a bunch of news to get to and some incredible videos we're gonna premiere.
One of them is absolutely amazing.
I hope you're a prisonplanet.tv viewer, but for radio listeners, it'll be posted later
this afternoon at mfallwars.com and prisonplanet.com, I wanna get it out to everybody.
It's gonna be the featured video on the YouTube channel and it'll be in HD at prisonplanet.tv.
How am I gonna save the fluoride heads that have probably had 150 shots in their life?
Let's say an average 30-year-old inner city woman, black, white, Hispanic, probably had
150 shots on average, been drinking higher levels of fluoride.
They've done national studies where in the minority areas it's a lot higher cuz they're
putting it even higher in your area.
And that's how actuated out this is, folks.
And the people in the water district don't ask questions, they're just told to distribute
it this way.
That's why some have blown the whistle.
See, I was able five years ago to start beating the drum about how they're adding radioactive
isotopes in the so-called sodium fluoride from the phosphate mines.
It's toxic waste they'd have to store, so they make you pay for it.
Some cities, millions a year, like Austin.
And I knew in the studies that the stuff they buy out of Florida, the stuff they buy out
of Colorado, the stuff they buy out of Mongolia, China, is full of five or six different radioactive
isotopes.
I mean, you want kidney cancer, you want bladder cancer, baby, get ready.
I mean, in some studies, it gives you over 50 times chance of getting, and that's why
that's all off the chart.
So I just get up here, did reports, talked about it, read the ingredients.
Took me probably 30, 40 times talking about it to get suddenly local newscasts all over
the country.
You can look these up.
Would go and would stick a Geiger counter up against the pipes, and they would just
go off the chart.
And the government spun it, it must be radiation in the aquifer, which is true.
They're mining limestone for phosphates, where they then take the toxic waste derivative
and put it in our water.
It's the same thing that's in some of the aquifers, but in very low levels.
So see, their spin, I tried my hardest to make sure you wouldn't get killed, but I can't,
I can't help you.
Because they're just gonna hit you with a disinfo off.
The feds all come in, it turned out Rick Perry made it secret.
As soon as I started exposing it, signed an executive order, in fact, it was an executive
directive to keep the findings, cuz the state started investigating when I talked about
it.
They put an order on it, blocking it out, then folks blew the whistle inside.
See, there are good people in government corporations, they just don't have intelligence.
And by intelligence, I don't mean native electrochemical intelligence in their cerebral cortex.
I mean, they don't know.
They would never give people radioactive isotopes.
So they hear me, they go, this guy's crazy.
They go stick a Geiger counter up to it and to a bag of fluoride coming in out of China.
And it's 20, 30, 40, 50, 100 times.
I mean, it's pegging the meters.
It's Chernobyl.
And now you see the newscast, yeah, our water's radioactive in Austin.
We don't know why.
Don't worry about it.
Our water, all outside Austin.
So it's radioactive in Houston.
It's radioactive in San Antonio.
All over the country, radioactive, even when you're not even getting it from aquifers.
They're like, well, how is this happening?
We're getting it out of a lake.
They're adding it.
And it's on record, they're adding it.
I mean, if a cop pulls me over for no reason, if I said they're putting radiation in your
water, he'll go, I don't care, here's the ticket.
I mean, it's like, how do you, and it's the same thing with Obama supporters.
I get up here and criticize Obama.
They think I'm saying I'm for Mitt Romney.
No, the fix was in like a Don King boxing match, that that's the winner.
That's the puppet.
That's the guy.
That's what he's gonna do.
But then they still tear down liberty by having Romney claim he's for good things.
So that can be discredited through fraud, so he won't defend it.
So see, then it forces you to defend Romney when he's saying, no, small businesses did
build America.
But he's still a bad guy, but I'm forced to defend him.
And then you hear that, you go, you're defending Romney.
Listen, I'm not defending Romney when I tell you there's radiation being put in your water.
Radioactive isotopes.
See, this is what's so crazy about this, is can you grasp that in your brains if you're
an Obama supporter, or if you're a right winger or whatever?
Do you understand the fix is in?
Do you get that through your head?
The system wants to suck the energy out of you while they get ready to go to the next
wave robotic system.
They don't need us anymore.
They say you used to be cheap, life used to be cheap, now you're a negative.
And Brzezinski in a speech he gave a few months ago, you can pull it up, said, I saw it even
quoted in the news.
He said, he said 20 years ago, to paraphrase, we find the exact quote, he goes, it was easier
to just spend a million dollars or a billion dollars to brainwash people to follow what
you said.
Now it's just cheaper to kill them.
See, this is what I'm trying to get across to you, folks.
You're under attack.
800, I'll give the number out when we come back, 800-25-99231, Obama supporters.
Hello, I'm Alex Jones, myself, my family, the Infowars.com team want to relay to you
and your families that we are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every
front Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats, but we can't do that without
your help.
By getting the films, bumper stickers and T-shirts at Infowars.com, you will wake up
people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before.
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here.
It's an Infowar, the spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
Hey there, Frank Bates here.
Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out 280 million Americans?
This is really scary stuff.
Defense experts warn that this odd device poses the greatest threat we've ever known.
In fact, just a few weeks ago, former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed
piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat.
I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up.
That's why my friend just created a free video at weirddevice.com that exposes this threat
and blows the doors off the conspiracy.
Go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover exactly what it is plus
discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack.
I'm not sure how long this video will be online, so go to weirddevice.com before it's gone
forever.
Again, that's weirddevice.com.
On the average, Americans work between 45 to 50 years hoping to build up enough wealth
to retire and live out their golden years.
Unfortunately, with taxation, the rising cost of food, energy, housing, and medical, many
retirees are forced to live below the poverty line.
Is this a flaw-free enterprise or is our monetary unit we call the Federal Reserve Note forcing
us into perpetual debt, ensuring inflation and higher taxes?
These questions and more can be answered by reading G. Edward Griffin's book, The Creature
from Jekyll Island.
Congressman Ron Paul states it's what every American needs to know about central bank
power, a gripping adventure into the secret world of international banking cartel.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson.
I will give a silver dollar from the early 1900s to anyone who purchases this book.
Call 1-800-686-2237 and order a copy today.
It's critical that the public be made aware of the system.
Call and order your copy today at 1-800-686-2237.
That's 1-800-686-2237.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the bestselling book, Cancer Step Outside the
Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White
House at a time when only the President could obtain this world-class healer.
Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now, you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally
occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single
normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune
cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VenusFly or order from Carnivora.com, that's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A dot com.
That's 1-866-836-8735, 1-866-VenusFly or visit Carnivora.com.
Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
Don't worry, this show is documented.
I'm Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Yeah, if you type in radioactive isotopes found in water supplies, you'll see newscasts
all over the country.
And guys also type in, as I mentioned, it's been a while since I've covered this, type
in Rick Perry covered up radiation water or Rick Perry ordered radiation and water cover
up.
And again, my point is we're able to get a story out and go, by the way, they're putting
radiation and radioactive isotopes in your water.
We're able to get that out, but then they just give it a cover story.
I mean, we know where it's coming from and they have all these investigations.
Where's it coming from?
And they've got enough globalist managers out there that no newscast ever said, it's
in the bag of fluoride right here.
When it's in government studies and state studies and federal stuff, it's all known.
And see, that's an example.
You will take vaccines from government controlled hospitals with a government that's been caught
testing.
Everybody knows about syphilis in black people because it was a big deal and came out.
But there's like thousands of studies, thousands of things like that, black, white, you name
it.
I mean, Obama is a globalist New World Order eugenicist.
They all are.
The point is they're gonna use the leftist takeover of collectivism to get control of
you so they can put whatever they want in your body.
Obama supporters, 800-259-9231, they are feeling good right now.
They're celebrating everywhere.
The government's their friend.
They've got a big ego now.
They're under the dark wings of the New World Order.
And let's talk to Mac in New Hampshire who's an Obama supporter.
Some of these will be sarcastic.
Go ahead, Mac.
Hey, why not, Alex?
I mean, think about it.
You sell gold for the New World Order, so why can't I support Obama?
Okay, so I guess that's it.
I'm convicted.
I sell gold for the New World Order.
Who owns all the gold?
The Rothschilds, right?
They own a lot of it, but they're trying to drive down the price of it and hoard it.
They actually, openly, all the big mega banks and people wanna keep gold down, so while
they buy it, they're always bad mouthing it.
And I told people buy gold at 260 bucks an ounce, and then it doubled, tripled, quadrupled.
I personally believe in gold and silver.
I guess everything I do is bad, so that's why you support Obama.
I'm not saying everything you do is bad.
No, no, no, hold on, no, no, no, it's a moral equivalency.
You're saying I support Obama, I guess cuz you think he gives you something free, I guess
that's the message.
And then you're saying I'm immoral, I sell gold when I have a sponsor, Midas Resources
where I get my gold, who has great deals on it, so that when the fiat currency goes belly
up, people are prepared.
See, I sell things I believe in to fund my operation because I try to be a moral person.
So whatever I think's really hot, like Propure Water Filters discounted at info.store.com
or Midas Resources, Frank's or whatever, I promote the bullion.
Even though sponsorship wise, I could make more if I promoted the numismatics, and there
are some good deals on that.
It's just hard to really know what you're doing, I promote bullion.
Even though I have sponsors knocking my doors down to promote numismatics with 200% markups
that other talk show hosts promote all day.
Do you hear me do that?
No, you don't.
So why do you like Obama?
We've heard how I'm evil.
Okay, I'm bad.
Now, you tell us, you're in charge, aren't you?
You kind of feel good about this big government right now, don't you?
Well, I look at it this way.
One way or the other, I don't care.
What's Obama gonna do that any other president hasn't done already to us?
Exactly.
You're like, I'm old, I'm getting my government money and I'm just gonna laugh at it and that
gives me power over it.
Well, I mean, let's face it, every other president, right, has screwed up, am I right?
No, no, no, since they murdered Kennedy and they were good and bad and he wasn't perfect,
we've been run by foreign banks, so things are getting progressively worse.
The president's a puppet, see, I can't get that through to you, we're in a foreign takeover.
Do you know what they've done in Greece and places?
They're gonna do that here.
You understand, you're gonna end up not getting your money or social security down this road.
Let me ask you this, if you think any president was ever good, right, then how come you never
mentioned on your radio show that the Constitution was suspended in 1933 and no one's ever re-suspended
it?
How come you never mentioned that?
Well, sir, that's in my films, the Emergency Powers Act of 1933, and that's when they put
us under emergency and that every year they re-enact the emergency and that we've had
martial law since then as a beachhead and that they've been slowly turning the heat
up.
Back then we were about a number one at martial law on the Richter scale, now we're about
a seven and a half, I've written articles about it, so I guess you must have missed
that show.
Right, and do you ever tell anybody that we live under corporations or we don't live under
a government?
But wait a minute, I talk about this constantly, you must be missing the show, but wait a minute,
why do you like Obama just cuz you think you're gonna get more goodies, I mean, why do you
support Obama?
It's not.
Of course not, he's not gonna do anything more than any other president has ever done.
Are you kidding?
We'll be right back.
We're on the march, the empire's on the run, Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company, Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action.
Tyranny is here.
The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality.
It really says that the state is God.
The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most oppressive police states
on earth.
This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being
expanded nationwide.
This documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all
powerful shadow state.
Police state four chronicles the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen.
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship, body scanners, sound cameras,
citizen spies, stage terror and cameras on every street corner.
It's only the beginning of the new world order's hellish plan.
The police state isn't coming.
It's here.
Secure your copy today at infowars.com or see it online in the highest quality at prisonplanet.tv.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of
silver based products.
Our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions.
Our two ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well as our all natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and
leave the silver at the surface, but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the
natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the
skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver based products
are best for you.
That's www.silverlungs.com.
Rallying patriots worldwide in defense of human liberty.
It's Alex Jones.
Masses of key news, intel and information at info.wars.com and prisonplanet.com.
You're on the site.
Remember to send the links to articles on to friends and family to wake them up.
Texas man arrested for filming cop.
Officer says I need to see ID in case this ends up on YouTube and arrest him for filming.
That video is up at info.wars.com.
TSA denies using drone at Vikings Packers game.
Does not comment on roaming Viper agents.
Unbelievable.
Washington Free Beacon reports radiation leak at Iran's nuke site.
That is just some of the news.
I want to go back to the Obama supporters.
That's what I found.
They just have an arrogance and he's all right.
And they like how he talks and they like his baloney.
Will you queue up?
I've got to tell you this, the Obama clip where he pledged not to raise taxes on payroll
taxes or any other taxes on people below a quarter million dollars a year because there's
like 14 different new taxes, fines, fees, and was covering it yesterday, 14 different
ones out of the new Congress that he robo signed yesterday.
And 12 billion in cuts, I mean, that's a joke.
They want to bankrupt us.
They're not screwing up in Washington.
Let's go ahead, I mean, I should have played this for that Obama supporter.
I mean, do you like being lied to and they go, that's just the way I'll do it.
Well, why the Democrats get so upset about drones and killing and wars?
I got upset when Bush was doing it.
I'm upset now, cuz see, that's being done in my name and my tax money is going to do
that.
So I feel responsible.
So I mean, I feel bad about it.
I can't control some Prozac head who stole guns from mommy and goes and kills people.
The folks that put them on the drugs in the schools, the people that push all this and
know it's gonna happen, I don't like them.
They're the ones that help this happen.
But I'm not guilty for Adam Lanza because I want to protect my family and my Second
Amendment birthright.
Well, let me tell you something, I do share some of the blame for not doing enough to
stop these wars and things.
And then just to watch you Democrats who would get so upset about Bush, cuz it was just moral
power for you.
Now when Obama does it, you love it.
I see him defend it.
I put a video out showing kids Obama killed with drones and they were like, good, kill
them.
They were real Democrats.
I mean, you're just sick.
You think you're on a winning team when Obama is a front man for a guy putting fluoride
in your drinking water, putting cancer viruses in your vaccine.
You're like, I ain't been doing it a long time.
You are living in fantasy land.
I'm gonna move quickly here through Obama supporters 80025 at 99231.
We've got our answer to demand a plan that's gonna premiere here.
It's pretty powerful, audio and video, and it'll be posted in the next few hours in infowars.com
for the radio listeners.
Obama supporter listening on 90.1 FM in Austin, go ahead.
Wait, wait, wait, put them on hold.
I forgot we have a station owner or manager who wanted to say something about Obama.
I apologize, I'm out of control.
I'm doing stuff during the breaks is the problem.
Greg, I think his name is Lesher, operates 1540 AM, KYAH, yeah, 540, I'm so out of my
mind folks, operates 540.
You know what it is?
We gotta move this TV closer to me with the calls cuz I got good eyes.
But since we put it on a smaller monitor, I can't read, I mean, my eyes are going.
I've always had like 2015 vision and I can't read this.
Again, Greg operates 540 AM, KYAH, another one of our great affiliates across the United
States.
Greg, what is your take today, sir, on all this?
Okay, you're sitting down, I hope.
I am sitting down, sir.
Okay, when a forest fire gets going, the best way that they fight it is create a backfire
so they can burn up all the fuel.
And they've done that with this birth certificate malarkey, okay?
It doesn't matter where the man was born.
He could have been born on the high seas.
He understands this.
But in order to qualify to be a candidate for the United States President, or to be
the President, you have to have natural born citizens, both parents.
And even according to the United Nations laws, because his father was a British citizen,
he is a British citizen himself.
Yes, he's a dual citizen.
I knew that.
No, actually, I knew that.
It's never gotten attention.
And the laws, when he was born, said you had to have both parents be citizens who were
actually born here.
They've since, I believe, changed the law going from memory.
But no, he is illegitimate, and they used the whole thing about where is he really from
as a distraction.
Yeah, no, laws are not changed.
You have to be a natural born citizen, or your parents at least have to be naturalized
citizens before your- Both of them.
Yes, both of them.
It's in the Constitution, okay?
That's the way it is.
No, no, you're right.
But I believe at the time that was the law, and you're right, it's in the Constitution.
I think they claim they have a law that changed it, but you're right.
It's in the Constitution.
You can't do that without a constitutional convention.
Well, that's why they got this, the artificial birth certificate.
That's not the issue.
The issue isn't where he was born.
It doesn't matter.
As long as both your parents are citizens, you can be born on a high seas.
You can be born in space.
You are a natural born citizen.
What we're talking about here is a native born, and that has nothing to do with the
law.
You have to be a natural born citizen, and here's what's happened.
He has already served his four years.
Now, we're in a critical time period, very critical, because tomorrow, Congress sits
down and they go ahead with the election and accept it.
Now, here's the deal.
A quo warranto action has been started with the Attorney General, and people need to get
behind this and get overnight letters to their senators tonight, today, before the post office
closes.
What they need to do is they need to go to teamlaw.net.
There's a news flash, call to action.
Click on that.
Read the article.
We actually did the one who started this quo warranto action, and actually, Eric Madsen
there at team law has actually quo warrantoed judges numerous times and got them off the
bench.
They understand-
No, no, I'm aware of that.
And again, John McCain was born on a ship in the Panama Canal, but both his parents
were known to be US citizens.
So obviously, he's a citizen.
It's not where you're born.
It's that you have parents that are both born in the United States, and it's the same thing.
And you're right.
That's been looked into.
It was part of England when he was born.
And so his supposed dad, that makes him a British citizen.
And up till now, nobody's done, they've investigated what has been done, and nothing has been brought
into the proper venue until now.
And once this gets started, and once these people send these things to their senators
in Washington, because that's where they are right now, and overnight them, your listeners,
we could create truckloads of these, and the attorney general will be flooded with these.
The attorney general's job is basically done, okay?
Because even if he refuses to proceed with this, Zane Gray, who started this, becomes
the special prosecutor for the United States, and then it becomes the United States against
Barack Obama.
That's what the court document will read.
And it will begin the core warrantal action, and there is no way that Obama can get out
of it, because he cannot argue the fact that he's already said his father was from Kenya.
He's a Kenyan, okay?
Well, let me ask you this, are people waking up there in Delta, Utah, to what's going on?
Oh, absolutely.
We just had a two-hour program.
We had Eric Madsen with Team Lawn, and by the way, Eric Madsen will be on with Butch
Pot tonight on Call to Decision.
We had a two-hour meeting, and Zane Gray was on there.
We talked about this in great detail.
I will actually send you that two-hour program, if you wanna put it on your website, so people
can listen to this.
And I mean, it's just fantastic.
This is the time when we can stop the whole thing.
We can get this man out of office, because he will be going in there illegally, against
the Constitution.
He is not a citizen.
Well, I'll tell you what, I'll get your name and number.
We appreciate you carrying the show, and maybe we should get those guys on as well.
God bless you, and I appreciate you calling in.
I said I was gonna go to Obama supporters here, but I wanted to hear from one of the
station owners out there in Utah.
Now, let's go back to Karen, now in Texas, an Obama supporter.
Go ahead, ma'am, you're on the air.
Okay, well, it was the Republicans that put these toll roads into Austin, and we were
trying to fight that.
And when I originally voted for Obama, we thought that he would keep us out of a war,
okay?
And we thought that maybe he was better than McCain.
So now he ran against Mitt Romney.
Well, they wouldn't let us vote for Ron Paul, and we didn't know who else to vote for.
So what are we supposed to do?
No, no, see, this is a reasonable Obama supporter calling in.
No, I get it, the Republicans run horrible people, so you don't have a choice.
The point is Obama is really, really bad is my point, because he gets away with the wars,
he gets away with the torture, he gets away with everything.
And they don't use him to bring people together, they use him to create division, Karen, I
appreciate your call.
And look, we get obsessed with personalities.
My point is that the Obama supporters that cheerlead for Obama and who really think he's
like a movie star and go, and I'm like, listen, he's really bad, you just lost.
That's who we're talking about.
Those are people that are really dangerous because they're so stupid.
And that's who we're wanting to talk to, I'll be honest with you, we had one earlier.
Joe in Florida, you're on the air, go ahead.
Hello?
Yes, sir, go ahead.
Sorry about that.
First things first, I would just like everybody to research an AD psyop created called Mind
Wars, and how Infowars is a manifestation of that.
Number two- Now, sir, now, sir, obviously, I use the
term infowars.com to say the global issues information lies against us, we use truth
against them.
See, the word propaganda just means information to get something political done you want.
Black propaganda means lies, white propaganda means truth, gray propaganda means spin.
I use white propaganda, so I want to be clear about terms out there.
When I talk about violence lowering after gun ownership increases, and I have the FBI
statistics, that's white propaganda.
Okay, so I want to be specific about that, go ahead.
I understand that, and the message certainly use the term bear fruits.
The fruit that is bared from the message is certainly true, but what I'd like to point
out is that you have to be careful.
A lot of the times in the entertainment industry especially, 75% of the truth is reported with
15% careful- Listen, I agree with you, listen, we're taking
calls from Obama supporters, will you tell us, do you support Obama or was that a way
to get on the air?
No, I do have a point about Obama.
Now, you'd have to be completely unaware of the situation, what's really going on with
the politics.
Whether you're for or against Obama is irrelevant.
If you go by the fruits of what their actions bear, you'd have to be an idiot to support
them.
All we're seeing the government do is wars, and we're seeing corruption and robbery of
taxpayers.
Obama is merely, that's what you should focus more on, and I do agree with that.
Well, the globalist wanted Obama.
Why is that?
Well, if the globalists want to open borders, I can intellectually tell you why it's bad,
but I just automatically am against it.
If the globalists want our guns, I can tell you intellectually why I'm against it, but
they're against it, I'm against them.
You see, I'm pro-gun because they're anti-gun.
I'm pro-sovereignty because they're anti-sovereignty, and I have all my reasons for that.
They have their reasons.
I don't know what you're getting at, Joe, I appreciate your call.
I mean, these Obama supporters, just God bless them, you know Republicans are pretty dumbed
down as well, but at least they say they want smaller government and no collectivism ruins
people.
And the Republicans are just basically the other side of the system and they just move
forward as well.
But I mean, Democrats, I mean, it's about being part of a club.
It's about having the Obama sticker and people go, you're liberal, you're good.
No, you support a front guy, a pitchman for a globalist operation feeding us GMO and fluoride
and cancer viruses in the vaccines and radioactive isotopes in the water and launching wars all
over the place.
And I have Obama supporters, I go, listen, these wars are wrong in person.
They go, you're just sad you lost and I'm like, no, no, listen, they're expanding wars.
It's really bad.
Oh, yeah, you wish Romney would have been better and I'm like, you need to recognize
it's wrong what Obama's doing.
Can you at least do that?
They go, no, you're just trying to use that against him, but you don't like him.
I'm just like, man, and it's the helplessness of them.
Jamie in New Mexico, Obama supporter, go ahead, you're on the air.
Yes, first time caller, long time listener.
I am forced to support Obama because I am living off of welfare and food stamps.
It is real easy to get food stamps.
And depending on your employer, it's really easy to get unemployment benefits.
I'm making about $100 less than I was.
And right now it's a good thing because I'd probably be on the streets.
I'd probably be living with my mom or my brother.
You realize with 50 million people on food stamps, it destroys all the small businesses
because only the big businesses are designed to take the money and the cards.
And you understand in the end, you're going to get nothing.
I mean, you understand, have you heard my story of how you domesticate hogs, bald hogs?
The reason why, it's only for this month, because I am looking currently-
Listen, I'm not saying you're bad.
Listen, if people are really downing out the churches or state government, there should
be some form of safety net.
This isn't a safety net, this is a safety news, sir.
And again, you say you support Obama, he's only doing all this to get you dependent so
he can get the guns and then drop the hammer.
They've already done this in Europe and Mexico and everywhere else.
Just so long as you know, it's a trap.
I mean, look, there are calories in a butterscotch candy.
A small butterscotch candy probably has 50 calories, okay?
Do you agree with me on that?
Yes.
Now, a butterscotch candy is not bad in and of itself.
If a man opens a van door at a playground and tells a three-year-old his parents aren't
watching him, get in the car, I got butterscotch, should the child get in the car for the butterscotch
candy?
Negative.
But I mean, it's a free candy.
I see your point.
I was at the EBT, the food stamp place yesterday.
People purposefully have kids to get on welfare.
People purposefully quit their jobs to get on unemployment.
It's too easy.
That's why I'm not understanding.
No, I really respect you.
Listen, I respect you because when we open these phones up for Obama people, the really
arrogant ones call in and are very entertaining, but it's sad to hear real Obama supporters
calling and go, I don't have a job and I won't have food.
That's what they've done to America that 50 years ago could feed the whole world.
And now we can't even feed ourselves.
I'm going to skip this network break.
I'm bankrupting the network doing this.
God bless you, sir.
I appreciate your call.
I'm going to skip this network break because I've got to premiere this special report here
in a moment and finish up with your calls.
And briefly, there'll come a time when the country's so poor, people won't even be able
to support us with sponsorship.
You won't even be able, your dollar will be so worthless, you won't be able to even get
a water filtration system.
You won't be able to buy the magazine in bulk to give it out to people.
That's their plan.
The Bilderberg Group has bragged, Paul has an article out today that they want to make
us poor to control us.
Making you poor is a tool of total control.
And they've done everything they can to shut this country down.
Believe me, I know.
And it is very, very sad.
I just hope listeners will support the broadcast, A, by spreading the word about the AM and
FM stations you're listening to, Global Shortwave, Internet Streams, and Infowars.com, the video
streams at prisonplanet.tv.
I hope you'll send it out to your email list, your Facebook, your Twitter.
Get our stories out, folks, retweet the articles we send out at Real Alex Jones.
You have the power, but you have to get aggressive and vote with your dollars and your energy
to promote broadcasts like this, these oases of truth, so that we can get the information
out to checkmate the globalists.
And we're close.
I tell you, we're in the fight.
That's why they're coming down on us, okay?
But I mean, it's kind of like a bully starts beating you up, and you get a good lick in,
and they go, whoa, this guy can fight.
Now the real fight's about to start, okay?
So I mean, it's on, all right?
I mean, I'm here to tell you, this is it.
Every expert we talk to says their spotty sense, I just got a complete chill, is off
the chart right now.
Gosh, I got goosebumps on my face, look at that.
I mean, this is not a game, ladies and gentlemen.
This is gut check time, okay?
This is not theatrics here on the radio.
This is not a game.
And they're gonna bankrupt us forever, very soon, and put us under agenda 21.
They want you on welfare to make you go live in a 200 square foot house room.
They're already making welfare recipients take unlimited shots, like 50 a year.
All right, I'm gonna go to this special report, it's very powerful.
We're gonna give it a title in the next hour and put it up at infoawars.com.
Get it, Facebook it, put it out on Twitter, put it out on YouTube, talk it up, get it
out there.
Fight the COINTELPRO trying to block our videos, trying to distract people.
You cannot be stopped if you take action.
Little things turn into big things.
Small things can grow like a mustard seed.
Big things have small beginnings.
So this video is our answer to the demand a plan Hollywood Bloomberg turning the guns
video.
And it gets into false flag democide, you name it, put together by Melissa Melton and
the rest of our crew.
Here it is.
Northwoods.
Gulf of Tonkin.
Gladio.
Kent State.
Ruby Ridge.
Waco.
Oklahoma City.
The World Trade Center.
The Pentagon.
Shanksville.
Hurricane Katrina.
Fast and furious.
How many more?
How many more false flags?
How many more government buildings?
How many more innocent people?
How many more?
What has been the number one cause of unnatural death in history?
Democide or death by government has killed 290 million people on record.
Two hundred and ninety million people killed killed 290 million killed by government.
The government, the number one killer in history is democide, democide, democide death by government.
Look it up.
Go look it up.
In the 20th century, government murdered four times as many people as were killed in all
the international and domestic wars combined.
USSR, 61,911,000 people killed.
Hitler's Germany, nearly 21 million people killed.
Japan's imperialism, nearly 6 million people killed.
Western colonization killed over 50 million people.
Pol Pot's Cambodia, funded by the US government, 2 million people killed.
China's Communist Party, as many as 76 million people killed between 1949 and 1987.
And the list goes on and on.
So now you know the most dangerous thing to you and your family in the world is government.
Because mass murderers agree, gun control works.
Disarming citizens is democide.
Disarming people is democide.
How many people have died because of Fast and Furious?
No more false flags.
Enough.
It's enough.
Now is the time.
It's time.
It's time to realize that when the government takes your guns, people die.
It's time to realize the biggest threat to you and your family is government.
It's time to recognize government is the greatest killer of all time.
It's time.
Demand a plan.
Demand.
Demand a plan right now.
As a free human being.
As an American.
As an American citizen.
As a patriot.
For your children.
Demand to know why you and your children are forced into gun-free zones while government
officials, celebrities, and their children are protected by armed guards.
Demand they show you the word hunting in the Second Amendment.
Demand to know why the government shipped thousands of guns to Mexican drug cartels.
Demand our government stops blowing up federal buildings.
Demand that our troops stop protecting opium fields in Afghanistan and come home.
Demand the government stop this phony drug war.
Demand to know why the Department of Homeland Security bought more than 1.6 billion hollow
point bullets with our money.
Demand our government stop poisoning our food supply with genetically modified organisms.
Demand that President Obama stops killing innocent women and children all around the
world with his illegal drone attacks.
Demand an end to these unconstitutional wars.
Demand that the TSA stop groping our genitals at the airport.
Demand that the NSA stop illegally spying on all of us all the time.
Demand that toxic fluoride be removed from the water supply.
Demand our politicians uphold the Constitution and Bill of Rights as they swore to when they
took office.
It's time.
It's time for our leaders to act like leaders.
It's time for our leaders to read the Constitution.
It's time for our leaders to obey the Constitution.
The Constitution.
Because a well regulated militia with 10 round magazines wouldn't last very long.
Demand an end to citizen disarmament.
Government sponsored terror.
And democide.
Democide, death by government.
Right now.
We are sick and tired of our tyrannical government taking away our rights.
Stop stealing our rights.
Our rights.
How many more people does government have to kill?
Enough.
Enough already.
Enough of the people laying down and letting government kill them in mass after disarming
them as they've done throughout history over and over again.
Enough, enough to laying down and letting these criminals use us up like slaves.
All right, folks, the full video with all the documentation is going up at Infowars.com
the next 10 minutes.
Get it out to everyone you know.
Thank you for listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east, but we are still in the eye of the perfect
storm.
The most devastating economic conditions since the Great Depression.
America's worst drought in agricultural history.
And now the economic results of the presidential election.
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply.
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from Eastwood Direct and I recommend you do
the same.
It's time to get your own supply from E Foods Direct.
I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food.
I'm taking control of my future and you're nuts if you don't do the same.
Go to efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex to find the specials and you can start with
a holiday gift pack that's normally $80 now under 50 bucks.
Remember, I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex.
Would you rather prepare six months too early or one day too late?
Coast to Coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center and the heart of the resistance.
Rallying patriots worldwide.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Show.
When populations get decadent and decide it's cool to lay down a big government, everything
collapses and you get put in forced labor brigades and the people that were on the welfare
usually right in there in the forced labor.
Of course, people that actually work usually make better workers, so it's the former welfare
folks with their machine guns prodding us around like the Soviet Union.
Let's go to Jeannie who says she's a real Obama supporter.
She's a KLBJ 590 listener.
I guess she's listening on 90.1 though right now.
Jeannie, show up.
Tell me about how great Obama is.
Well, I mean, I'm not going to say how great, but Alex, I was a Ron Paul supporter.
When he came out of the president election, I had to, who else was I going to vote for?
Think about it.
To me, Romney, all the Republicans, I feel like he wanted to take women's rights away
and all this.
I could not-
Ma'am, ma'am, ma'am, ma'am, ma'am, ma'am, we're not even saying you should have voted
for Romney.
It's the endorsement of Obama and people feeling like they had a victory because he's in there
now and he's your president.
It was all rigged.
Okay, that's what I'm telling you is that it's rigged and it is wrong what they did
to Ron Paul.
It's probably why Romney overtly lost, but there's election fraud as well.
My point is, is that America is going in a socialist direction and socialism, ma'am,
is a nightmare.
I mean, France now has over 80% taxes with a 75% tax on everything above that.
You make over a million dollars, you pay 80% plus 75 on any money you keep.
I mean, should taxes be at 99% or 100%?
Alex, I wanna say something controversial and I don't care if it gets everyone mad,
but I'm gonna say to me, the reason this country is going to you know where is because of old
white men who are running the Senate and Congress who have been running it.
We have what, 1% of Mexicans and black people that are in the Congress Senate?
No, it's not, are you kidding?
It's all time record high.
There's like 20 women in the Senate alone.
White, old men running this country, the Senate and Congress-
All right, ma'am, ma'am, hold on, ma'am.
Are you really this ding-dang bad where it's just fun to, hold on, I know the Democrats
are all about race.
You sound like a white lady, I don't know who you are.
But the point is, it's like just fun to put down white people and I get that's fun.
I mean, that's the new trendy thing.
I get it.
Jumping off cliffs is fun too.
The point is, is that certainly, you know, ma'am, that Dianne Feinstein is a quote white
lady and she's saying turn our guns in.
So if she's white, if being white is bad, I guess she's a woman though, I must make
it okay.
Do you support us turning our guns in?
No, I don't, I don't.
I mean, I really don't, I'm against that.
But to me, that's my opinion as a 49 year old Mexican woman living in Texas, I feel
the reason this country is going to crap is because of all white men running it.
Let me be clear, okay, so why is Nigeria, that's all black people running that, why
is that going to hell?
Or let me ask you a question, why is Mexico, I guess Mexico is doing really good, cuz there's,
I bet I mean Mexico, I mean, is that the fault of all white men?
How many people are that are white, older men running the Congress and Senate?
Can you tell me why we are in this situation?
Well, Japan is in a total depression for about 15 years, and I mean, is that the fault of
all white men?
I wonder who, that's Steve, president, but- Well, ma'am, ma'am, I mean, listen, I'm asking
you something here, cuz you know white skin is only a lack of pigment.
Yeah, Alex, look, I'm being honest- But I mean, hold on, I understand, I got it,
is it racist to own guns?
Start putting him down also, if it was a Mexican president, and we were in this situation,
I have no problem saying, he's a problem- Hold on, ma'am, ma'am, ma'am, did you hear
me?
The president is a puppet, we're talking about how you're supporting a puppet.
Alex, we can agree to disagree- No, no, but say you like Obama, but you don't
like turning your guns in.
No, I'm not gonna- I'm gonna ask you a question, should we get rid of our Congress and put
in the Mexican Congress, would that make things better?
No, I think we should start all over- But wait a minute, you just said, maybe we
should go down to Mexico, that's kinda what the North American Union is, and bring all
those great people, cuz they're Hispanic, up here to run, they would do a better job.
I think she's actually right, folks, we gotta continue here, let's continue.
Hello, I'm Alex Jones, myself, my family, the Infowars.com team want to relay to you
and your families that we are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every
front.
Infowars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats, but we can't do that without
your help.
By getting the films, bumper stickers, and t-shirts at Infowars.com, you will wake up
people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before, they wish to hide themselves
during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here, it's an Infowar, the spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
Who wants to be disease-free, full of energy, and vibrant health?
Two reasons you may feel constantly tired and run down could be that your body's acid
level is high and your pH level is low.
How does acid enter your body?
A cup of coffee, a sandwich, tap water, stress, and cell phones, plus your own body produces
acid on a regular basis.
Alkavision plasma pH drops alkalize the water you drink and raise your pH level.
They promote more oxygen in your system, higher energy potential, and many other documented
health benefits.
And studies show viruses, bacteria, and toxins cannot survive in an alkaline high pH environment.
Alkavision plasma pH drops is the least expensive and the best pH level product you can buy.
Order Alkavision plasma pH drops for just $29.95 at alkavision.com, spelled A-L-K-A
vision dot com, or call 800-518-7615, that's 800-518-7615.
Raise your body, supercharge your health, with pH drops from alkavision.com.
We have witnessed two terrible storms in the east, but we are still in the eye of the perfect
storm.
The most devastating economic conditions since the Great Depression, America's worst drought
in agricultural history, and now the economic results of the presidential election.
This perfect storm is a huge threat to everyone's food supply.
I just doubled down and got even more supplies from E Foods Direct, and I recommend you do
the same.
It's time to get your own supply from E Foods Direct.
I know I won't be standing in a bread line trading my freedom for food.
I'm taking control of my future, and you're nuts if you don't do the same.
Go to efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex to find the specials, and you can start with
a holiday gift pack that's normally $80, now under $50.
Remember, I can warn you, but I can't feed you, call 800-409-5633, or efoodsdirect.com
forward slash Alex.
Would you rather prepare six months too early, or one day too late?
Call 800-409-5633, or efoodsdirect.com forward slash Alex.
The answer to 1984 is 1776.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Show.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you just joined us, you missed an incredible phone call.
The woman called in, and she said, I am a real Obama supporter, she was real.
And she said, there are too many white people in Congress, and that's why America's in trouble,
and that's why I support Obama.
She said she was Hispanic.
And I said, so Mexico, should we take the Mexican Congress, one of the most corrupt
governments in the world, and bring it up here?
Governments are corrupt, whether you're in Africa, or whether you're in Iran, or whether
you're in Israel, or whether you're in Russia.
You read the Bible, it talks about government being wicked, and wickedness in high places,
and the god of this world.
Now, whether you believe in a physical devil or not, the issue is, historically, most governments
are bad, and they tend to get worse, and worse, and worse the longer they're in.
And I gotta be honest with you, I mean, the ignorance of Obama supporters, we got David
Montana says he's an Obama supporter, I'm gonna continue to take Obama supporter calls
right now on this third day of January 2013, 800-259-9231.
Program note, there is a video we just premiered that is one of the most powerful short pieces
we've done in a long time, collaboration between the whole crew, but John Bount and Melissa
Melton kinda came up with it.
Or I think simultaneously, Bount said we should do a knockoff of the demand to plan Bloomberg
thing with all the stars saying turn your guns in.
And then others have the idea, but the point is, I also had the idea to show Hollywood
violence and them shooting people.
And then one of our listeners had that idea, and I never talked about it on air.
People just have the same thoughts when you're looking at hypocrisy.
So we put out a new video pointing out that government's been the biggest chiller in history,
and it shows all the statistics at the end.
We're gonna put an article up in the next ten minutes or so, they're putting it together
right now that shows from the University of Hawaii study, cuz I keep saying 260 plus million,
they corrected me, it was 290 plus million.
Sometimes I get factoids off, usually to the lower number, my mind tends to underestimate.
That's why people think I'm exaggerating sometimes, most of the time, I mean, I would literally
say over 95% of the time, I underestimate.
Or sometimes I flip numbers, it's almost like dyslexia.
But side issue, I just want you to know, if you hear me say something wrong sometimes,
earlier I said 1540, a station was calling in and it was 540.
The fact is, I'm not following a teleprompter, I'm not following a script here, I'm really
telling you what I think.
So you're gonna see some of that, but the point is, government non-military casualties
200, 290 plus million people killed last century, and so we say demand a plan to stop
government mass murder.
And the video will go up at infowars.com for everybody to see it, and I want you to send
it out on email, Twitter, Facebook, everywhere.
Get it out to local talk stations, get it out to everybody, and again, it's now live
on YouTube, Demand a Real Plan is what we call it.
Demand a Real Plan, Demand a Real Plan, and we're gonna have the statistics that we have
in it posted under it.
She's also writing another article that'll be done soon that basically goes with it.
But for Obama supporters, call in on your Obama phones, 800-259-9231, 800-259-9231.
Let's go ahead and talk to Dave in Montana.
Dave, go ahead, you're on the air.
Alex, I support Obama because I hate the Republicans so much because they hate the 10th Amendment.
They could have been in office, they could have ran away with the election.
All they had to do was back up the 17 states that exercised the 10th Amendment-
For marijuana.
Allowed their people to use medical cannabis and to use cannabis to hemp, rutialis part
of the cannabis for industry and jobs and- All right.
And liberty.
No, no, I hear you, I'm gonna go back to you, Dave, I'm gonna go back to you.
This is the best Obama supporter call we've gotten in the five or six shows or sections
of broadcasts that we've done cuz he actually has an issue.
That thing about, the Republicans wanna take women's rights, I mean, that's just a pure
political distraction.
The state's rights issue, and I've supported decriminalization, I've supported legalization,
I'm a libertarian.
And I know all you do is get low quality marijuana full of pesticides and let the corrupt mafia
and government get a percentage of it by making it illegal, just like in prohibition.
I'm not a big supporter of alcohol, I think it's more destructive than marijuana.
And I'm for drug decriminalization, but also I think the state shouldn't be involved in
alcohol.
It should be a local thing, a criminal thing.
You poison somebody with alcohol you sold, you're going to prison.
Now you poison somebody with alcohol, you just get a fine.
But side issue, the thing I'm trying to get at here is Obama tripled the raids in California
on medical cannabis.
Triple the raids, look it up, I've had all the activists gone.
So that's the bottom line on that front is that they did noises like they support.
He said he was against the NDAA, but he actually wrote it, and then said he wouldn't sign it
but did.
See Obama, I'll tell you what Obama does.
He gives you 15 pain pills to put you under, you pass out before he slits your throat.
The Republicans, they want to just stab you in the back a couple times.
But they don't give you any painkillers, and if you want to use that analogy.
And that's the thing about it, it's not, I want to hear from Obama supporters why you
think he's good.
I mean, if you say, I don't like him either, but at least he did this, but see you're even
really wrong about that.
But I at least understand you had a thought, you had a reason in your mind you thought
something was going on.
Let me explain something.
The globalists are gutting the economy, they're in control of that.
They're 85 billion of themselves every month, on top of the trillions they already stole.
And they're gonna pass on the inflation to us, I mean, it's both parties doing it.
That's why I said, Boehner's gonna sell us out on tax increases, 77% of households got
a tax increase, more than ten of them.
Okay, so do you want to tell me how bad the Republicans are?
The point is the Republicans represent the best people in this country.
They are the people that soak up the energy of the libertarians, conservatives, constitutionalists
who compared to the average Democrat are more productive, are more pro-human, pro-life,
real people.
Okay, I mean, the average Democrat I know is a helpless, disconnected from reality,
visibly weak, stupid person who thinks they're real smart.
The average Republican is a reactive, but hardworking person who's been conned as well,
but at least believes in private property and the Second Amendment and national sovereignty.
Sure, they've become territorially supportive of the Republicans, even though they don't
really like them.
It's kind of like a husband who doesn't really like their wife, but better not say something
to my wife, buddy, or I'll punch your lights out.
And the Democrats know they've taken over and they know the Republicans are bought off,
so they know that conservatives are gonna leave Republicans and the whole party's just
gonna die.
And then it's gonna be a giant Democratic Party dictatorship to split in two, and that's
actually been their plan, they're talking about that.
Cancer divides, and they're just gonna hammer us up one side and down the other.
When they legalize the 30 million illegals and let them bring in their families to have
anchor babies paid for and everything, it's gonna further bankrupt stuff, drive down wages,
they're exempt from all the laws.
Again, not that they're bad people, they're leaving a country brought down by globalism
as well.
It's that they're given this free ride.
Well, it's the same thing with any other group.
You've got some Hispanic Mexicans who work harder than anybody I've ever seen, who are
incredibly smart, know how to fix everything, politically know what's going on, and are
good people.
And they will not, cuz they're Christians, they're always Christians.
They won't go take welfare, they're too prideful, they understand it's bad.
And then you've got the other group, just like with whites or blacks, that wants the
free ride.
And it's just disgusting, and everybody's gonna have their future destroyed.
All I'm telling you is, the people running things are super bad news.
Let's go to Gordon in Canada, he is a Obama supporter, Gordon, go ahead.
I was gonna go back to the other guy, but he hung up, go ahead, Gordon.
Yeah, you mentioned that you believe the president is basically a puppet, is that correct?
My gosh, he's an absolute New World Order puppet, but he enjoys his work.
Okay, so we both agree on one thing, at least today, that the president is basically a puppet.
And really, as a puppet, would you agree that he's basically ineffectual as a president,
he's merely a puppet?
Yeah, just like John Boner, John Boehner, but the spectacle of him being the leader,
that's used to pacify people and to create a false debate.
I think that as a leader, Obama has been one of the most influential leaders that the United
States has ever seen.
Yeah, no, no, Kissinger said that, he said Obama's gonna bring in the New World Order.
Well, unfortunately, I probably would disagree with you there and say that it was probably
Franklin Delano Roosevelt that brought in the New World Order a long time ago.
Yeah, but a beachhead is not true domination.
See, this country had so much wealth and so much power and was so wild, it's taken them
80 years to get to this point.
So see, that's an argument about, they may have declared a federal emergency and set
up state police or a really federal police, I'm gonna skip this break and then go to the
bottom of the hour.
Go ahead and make your point, I'm gonna let you talk.
Mr. Jones, I just flew into Canada, a very small country of 32 million people.
I was relatively unaccosted at both security sides of the border.
I enjoy a job that is based on free market society and the only reason that I'm able
to enjoy the level of, or the standard of living that I do enjoy in the United States
is because we have a stable government and right now, the United States government is
one of the most stable governments in the Western Hemisphere and as long as the President
of the United States is in power right now, I will continue to enjoy that standard of
living.
When I was living under the previous administration's standard of living, it was atrocious.
The police state was far more worse than it is today.
I understand where you're coming from, I do believe that we've probably stepped over the
line in terms of personal liberty.
But the goal so far is to start labeling the president or to question the president as
integrity as a man.
You and I really don't have the luxury of knowing the person or the human being.
I disagree with that, you will know them by their fruits and the obsession over most Obama
supporters I talked to who are intelligent will say the things you're saying.
And then they'll say plus you don't know the man, you don't know what he's going through.
Listen, I've really watched Obama carefully and I've read his earlier writings and he
is just another narcissist wanting to dominate people and he's reading off teleprompters.
I'm saying what Obama signifies and the time we're entering, by the way, I know a lot of
folks have been in Canada lately, they say it was the worst security they ever went through.
Now they must have you profiled, that's part of the police state and they're leaving you
alone cuz your business, you go back and forth.
Canada just worst experience I ever had at the hands of the quote police, well, not the
worst but the worst as an adult, as a non teenager was there in Canada.
So I mean, just to say I'm doing great, I'm doing good.
All the financial metrics show the Republican and Democratic leadership are hand in glove
with this banking takeover.
And for certain people, the economy is doing better but overall worldwide, globalism is
designed to render us bankrupt.
And I mean, the globalist state they're using this to bankrupt us and Obama's trying to
get carbon taxes through worldwide that are designed to block development in the third
world clean development, cuz they don't want them ever becoming self sufficient.
They want them poor, or they can hand pick cherry pick who they want to come into the
armored compounds at the factories with the suicide nets, and then have forced abortions
inside.
I mean, I just know too much about the globalist, I mean, people tend to judge things by I mean,
I guess I could sit here and say, I know a lot of conservative talk show hosts, libertarian
talk shows, they go well, Alex, things are real bad, but at least, we're gonna get bigger
audiences during this.
And that's like saying, like if I own stock in a company that sold chemotherapy stuff
and one of my kids had cancer and I'm like, well, at least I'm making money off the chemotherapy
I just bought cuz I have stock in it.
I mean, it's super hyper predatory and I've read all these books and papers by the top
technocrats saying they're gonna set up a world government.
They're gonna make it all look sexy and make it look like the bad stuff they're fighting,
the good stuff they created, they're gonna shut the economies down.
And they're going to forcibly reduce population.
And then I talked to so called lefties and they go, well, there are old people do spend
too much money at end of life.
We are collectivist, let's get rid of them.
I mean, that money that gets spent goes into the system to begin with and funds people.
Is the medical system corrupt?
Yeah, because they're teamed up with government.
I mean, are there reforms?
Yes, not the ones we're doing, it's gonna double the cost of health care.
They talk about, see, it's gonna give you less care and charge you more for it.
It's like you're gonna live in a 250 square foot house and pay 90% or 80% of your money
in property tax.
Whereas you put that same amount of energy you expended into work could have lived in
a 3,000 square foot house.
I mean, it's just diabolical.
And I mean, look, they put cancer viruses and vaccines, I can show you all the documents
I have before many times.
These are bad people.
They're doing medical experiments on kids in New York right now, on record.
And people are like, but Obama, I got an Obama phone or people think the government made
the economy good when they're in.
And plus the economy is not good by most metrics.
Just because you're doing good, I mean, here I am a talk show host reaching millions of
people, have a big operation, you would call me successful.
I feel successful for waking people up.
I don't feel successful because I've got a new Ford pickup truck.
I don't feel successful because people pull chairs out for me because I'm, quote, a celebrity.
I mean, how do you gauge success?
Go ahead.
Success by the caliber of a person and the integrity of that person, not by his wallet.
Mr. Jones, I have no doubt that your view of a world government is as such as it is.
I've been listening to you for a number of years now.
And I respect your opinions and views.
However, I do disagree with you with regard to your sense of how quickly we're about to
go over any precipice.
When I travel around the world, one of the best countries that I'm always pleased to
come back to is the United States of America.
Yes, we have a very- But that's not the government.
That's not the government.
Everybody acts like the government made America.
Guns made America, buddy.
Whiskey made America.
Freebooting.
Pitching people's teeth in made this country.
Obama did not make this.
We made this country.
But when we begin to target one individual and blame him for our collective woes, and
incessantly, I mean, and constantly, I think we're really truly missing the target.
Let me ask you a question.
Do you think it's good to use taxpayer money to ship General Motors, Cadillac, and Volt
factories to China?
I understand that there are decisions that are being made in boardrooms all over the
United States of America that are being made by individuals who are actually being controlled
by individuals such as the big new Brzezinski, Henry Kissinger, and the likes of the law
class.
Exactly, and Obama is their golden child.
I appreciate your call.
It's, you know, tomorrow, we'll try to take more calls.
And I just, you can talk in circles with each other all day.
I mean, I don't even know what to say anymore.
I'm not saying Mitt Romney would have been better.
What is Cynthia McKinney, who's been so demonized with the corporate media say because she exposed
government slave rings and things, sex slave rings, white slave rings, and the public so
dumb they always send me emails saying, I see them printed out.
What about black slaves?
Sex slavery is called white slavery, folks.
The point is, is that she says Obama is the more effective evil.
He's not the lesser, he's not the greater, he's the more effective.
It's real simple, okay, folks?
If the globalists want your guns, you want guns.
If the globalists say don't buy gold, you want gold.
If the globalists say don't eat organic food, you want organic food.
If the globalists say it's good to radiate your food, it's bad to radiate your food.
And then you can go look at the reasons it's bad.
But in every case, if they say something's good, you better believe it's bad.
I mean, they call this modern world empowering women.
Women aren't empowered, they look like they've been run over.
They've been gaslighted into thinking they're ugly and they don't have any value when their
family and everything is waiting for them and worshiping them.
And they're running everything.
Women have always been the center of everything.
Women are running everything and they think they don't have anything, cuz the television
is there showing them this imaginary Hollywood world.
Let me tell you, that isn't what Hollywood's like.
You can't keep me far, I'm not bragging, I get invited, not in as much as I used to.
But I get invited to behind the scenes, huge world events, world concerts.
You know, sky boxes at Formula One with the top five world rock band and he constantly,
and it's not that I'm against those people, they're listeners.
They wanna, maybe I should go meet with them and stand around all fancy with bodyguards
and preen.
I mean, I guess that is success, but that is not what I'm into.
And not because I don't like status, I want status amongst thinkers.
I want status amongst strong men and women.
I want status amongst artists, not to be a peacock, but I want to influence them because
I have a vein of primal human liberty that I want to infect people with.
You understand, I don't just wanna have 15 children because I'm vain and like siring
children.
I want life, I wanna live forever.
I wanna hug them and train them and see the electricity in their eyes.
And I want their great, great grandchildren to be on Alpha Centuris, living to be 1,000
years old, doing things that the eye has not seen or ear has not heard.
I want to live, I want to produce, I want to let it all hang out.
I don't wanna run around in some primitive monkey behavior and sit up on the top of the
highest part of the tree like a chimpanzee with, I mean, you'll see arrogant chimpanzees
or baboons acting just like humans sitting up there cuz the top one will sit there just
lounge like a king, I'm in charge.
That doesn't do anything for me, spacecraft, mathematics, art, beauty, that into the next
level is what I want.
I wanna see you win, the globalists wanna see you fall, I mean, it's real simple.
The government is not your friend, it's cancer.
Get the video at Infowars.com, get it out to everybody, the gun grabber video is now
up there right now.
On the march, the empire's on the run, Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.