We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center, in the heart of the Resistance.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Show.
Aaron Dykes here for InfoWars.com.
Obviously, I'm outraged just about the use of executive orders themselves.
It's very abusive of constitutional powers.
The fact that he has bragged through his aides to the media, in Reuters, that he's going to act without Congress.
It's even more outrageous that he staged this press conference, exploiting children, bringing them on stage with him.
The same Obama who fake cried over the Sandy Hook shooting.
The same Obama who released the White House photo, showing him looking distraught.
The same Obama who lied about the entire bin Laden account, a staged photo of the Situation Room.
Supposedly watching the raid.
The same Obama administration lying about Benghazi.
But worse than that is the actual actions taken in those executive orders.
And Obama's not even done with 23 of them.
He's still going to ask Congress to reinstate the assault weapons ban and do even more.
Now remember the words of Obama's first chief of staff, Rahm Emanuel, now mayor of the murder capital of the world, who also wants gun control.
He said, never let a good crisis go to waste.
It's an opportunity to do something you couldn't do before.
You never want a serious crisis to go to waste.
And what I mean by that is it's an opportunity to do things that you think you could not do before.
Now it's on record the Obama administration has been pursuing gun control all along.
I did a top ten list of the actions of his previous administration.
Also, Senator Feinstein was amassing legislation to re-institute the assault weapons ban at the time of the election.
And they were waiting to use the appropriate crisis that became Sandy Hook.
So let's just remember they always wanted to exploit a good crisis and that's what we've seen now.
With that in mind, at least two of Obama's executive orders on gun control institute a brainwashing mentality.
Remember that Eric Holder, attorney general, said in 1995 he wants to brainwash the American public on guns the way they did with cigarettes.
Just really brainwash people into thinking about guns in a vastly different way.
And here inside those 23 executive orders are two political campaign propaganda points.
One to launch a national safe and responsible gun ownership campaign.
And another to have a national dialogue on mental health with Kathleen Sebelius, the head of Health and Human Services.
And Arn Duncan, the education secretary.
Now Obama, of course, has announced he's looking for ways to act without Congress,
without having to even ask for permission to infringe upon the uninfringable second amendment of the Bill of Rights to the Constitution.
With that said, look at how he's exploited health care in his executive orders.
Here it is in the weekly standard, Obama asked doctors to help deal with guns.
And he reminds them in several different executive orders, as many as seven executive orders can be put in this category,
where he reminds doctors that they're able to report on suspicious activity.
They're able to ask their patients if they own guns and if they have guns in their homes.
They're able to flag people for threats against, for violent threats, report them to authorities.
And what they're doing is building a mental health database flagging people for potentially unstable behavior.
Obviously we don't want crazed people going out in society and shooting up crowds of people.
At the same time, we want to maintain due process and we don't want to create a snitch culture where the entire Obamacare apparatus is used to spy upon Americans,
which is all dangerous for the sake that we've seen what they do with the terror watch list.
Once you get on it, it doesn't matter if you've ever done anything wrong, it's very difficult, if not impossible, to get off that list.
And we've been told more lists are coming. Rahm Emanuel said in this clip, no fly, no buy.
If you're on that no fly list, your access to the right to bear arms is canceled because you're not part of the American family.
He was at the Brady Center and said his number one priority was to get people on a no buy gun list, that you lose that right.
That was under the context of terrorism, but it's going to apply to mental health as well.
And we've seen Chuck Schumer in the Senate and others already trying to introduce that legislation.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is Thursday, the 17th day of January 2013. We're going to go to break and come back.
This is a full mobilization by the federal government under foreign control to absolutely go hysterical and attack the Second Amendment at every level, including extra judicially.
All of these everywhere, this is just one up at Infowars.com, are announcing that they're going to lean like the mafia on gun dealers, gun manufacturers, you name it.
We'll be right back. Stay with us.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal-Bend Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years. These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs.
This is an amazing deal. You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
The New Year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness. Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver. This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections, yeast and molds. Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness. Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com. Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of silver based products.
Our most popular silver based products are the 32 oz. Nano Silver Solutions, our 2 oz. Nano Silver Nasal Applicators as well as our All Natural Silver Soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface.
But rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.SilverLungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver based products are best for you.
That's www.SilverLungs.com.
You walk into this room at your own risk because it leads to the future.
Not a future that will be but one that might be.
This is not a new world. It is simply an extension of what began in the old one.
It has patterned itself after every dictator who has ever planted the ripping imprint of a boot on the pages of history since the beginning of time.
It has refinements, technological advances and a more sophisticated approach to the destruction of human freedom.
But like every one of the super states that preceded it, it has one iron rule.
Logic is an enemy and truth is a menace.
The answer to 1984 is 1776.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Show.
We are gold.
We are launch.
It is the 17th day of January 2013.
And while we're busy watching the globalists go after our guns, they are stealing $85 billion of taxpayer money a month and giving it to the six private mega crime syndicate banks who are offshore and tax free.
$85 billion a month for derivatives.
$85 billion they created.
Hey, instead of going to jail, you just get the taxpayer money and get to run everything.
Same thing in Europe.
And ladies and gentlemen, we've got some incredibly serious news to report here for you.
What we're facing is mafia tactics.
And I wrote an article this morning with Paul Joseph Watson that just went up at Infowars.com that goes over all of this.
Philadelphia mayor declares economic warfare on gun retailers.
But it isn't just this mayor.
There's a bunch of other mayors.
And there's a people like Chuck Schumer and people like Rahm Emanuel and Dianne Feinstein and Michael Moore and Nancy Pelosi and Joe Biden who've all been calling for what Bloomberg's done, suing gun manufacturers, suing gun dealers, suing gun shops.
Now they're just saying we're going to pull city investment funds out of any companies and we're going to harass gun shops and we're going to do all this.
I mean, it's mafia.
If you don't go along with us, it's called good old fashioned muscle.
You ever seen Martin Scorsese's Goodfellas based on a true story?
That is exactly how these big city crime machines work, Chicago, New York, Philadelphia, Los Angeles, San Francisco.
They are oily gangsters involved in all sorts of crimes, but they're above the law because they run the system and they want the people disarmed, period.
And we have President Obama in yesterday's speech, we have a video up at Infowars.com, we break all this down, titled President Obama responds to Alex Jones.
That's clearly what he's doing.
And others say, hey, there's no tyranny.
We're not coming after your guns.
The people that are saying that just want to make money.
Unbelievable.
Remember, this is the guy saying he would never come after our guns.
Here's that clip.
This will be difficult.
There will be pundits and politicians and special interest lobbyists publicly warning of a tyrannical all-out assault on liberty.
Not because that's true, but because they want to gin up fear or higher ratings or revenue for themselves.
And behind the scenes, they'll do everything they can to block any common sense reform and make sure nothing changes whatsoever.
You're a liar.
That's it.
The only way we will be able to...
The only way is for the, quote, supporters, conservatives to stand up and do the right thing.
And I'll get it done for you because you asked for it, little kids.
High five.
The most exploitive garbage I've ever seen.
Totally transparent.
Don't let a good crisis go to waste.
Now, we now have the 23 executive orders, and it is an unbelievable nightmare.
Natural News does an analysis.
Aaron Dykes does an analysis.
It's all up at infowars.com.
And our auxiliary site, if you can't get to infowars.com, prisonplanet.com.
And we've got a clip of this.
Mayor, we're going to play in a moment, but they're saying, listen, we're going to shut down your businesses one way or another.
Unless you do gun buybacks every year and a half, two years, which they've always done gun buybacks in the news worldwide before they then register, before they confiscate.
I mean, they've taken guns worldwide.
They've taken guns everywhere these big city crime bosses run things.
So we know their goal.
I mean, they've introduced bills to do it before.
They've said our goal is civilian abolition of firearms ownership.
That's the UN Unity or Treaty.
And those of us that are informed and actually read and know how the world works, we're going, hey, Lemmings, wake up.
They're coming with the guns.
Shut up, conspiracy theorist.
The government told me it's reasonable for the kids.
And we're like, hey, mobsters, we know you want our guns.
That's right, Mac.
We're going to get them.
That's what's so frustrating about this is they still play this game.
We just want some reasonable stuff.
And then just like the Obama health care plan, a bunch of these executive orders and the bills they've now introduced are nebulous.
It's like, yeah, it's up to the ATF discretion.
You come in and register them and we may do a forced buyback.
I know a big deal, though.
It says in Feinstein's bill, it's the chief one that they're trying to pass.
We've read it on air, written articles about it.
It's been national news.
It says, just as a footnote, and we may do a forced buyback too.
Never mind about that.
But this gives us that power.
We're like, hey, this bill has death panels, says it'll double the premiums and will bankrupt everything.
It's a takeover health care plan.
Shut up, conspiracy theorist.
Doesn't say that.
Yeah, here's a subsection right here.
No, it doesn't.
They pass it.
Well, of course there's death panels.
Of course we're going to double your premiums.
I promise no payroll tax will go up, no other capital gains tax.
Nothing will go up on anybody making under a quarter million a year.
Capital gains tax for everybody went up.
There's a total investment tax, almost 4% on top of everything else.
That's on after-earned money.
Unbelievable.
Totally unconstitutional.
Payroll tax, 3.8 on average.
I keep going here if you want me to.
Everybody knows you're getting your paychecks now.
I mean, people are real mad.
In the last three days, most people get paid every two weeks.
You got your first two weeks.
Most people got their first two weeks.
Some of them are going to be getting them today.
Oh, people are mad.
I'm already seeing it, people.
The tweets are going out.
People got their check this morning and they're like, what is this?
What is this?
Oh, and everybody.
All the major chains, all the big stores are announcing.
Nobody gets 40 hours anymore except the manager.
Everybody else gets 25 because Obamacare kicks in above 29 hours.
And that way, if you get a couple hours overtime, it doesn't go over 29.
Boom.
And people are like, what's going on?
What happened?
But see, they're going to say unemployment is going to go down because they'll count each new job as new people.
This is how the mafia operates.
So the average person is going to get two or three jobs now.
They're going to go, look, there's more people getting hired.
Just cook that number.
Real unemployment is above 20%.
Every major economist has said that for four years.
They say, hey, you know what, unemployment is down at eight something.
It's all about these are gangsters.
It's just like in Goodfellas where the mobsters are in the bar beating people up, not paying their $5,000 tabs for parties.
The owner says something, so the one out of control gangster beats him up.
This is based on a true story.
It's such a good gangster movie because they were all convicted of this in court when one of the major crime families got brought down.
A guy read the book back at the time when it came out like in 1990.
I was so impressed by Scorsese's movie.
I think it's his best movie.
But the point is that they go to the head gangster and go, we'll just take over my business so he won't keep robbing me.
So he goes, okay.
And then they take everything.
They leverage out the business with all this debt that they put on him and then take everything he's got on top of it.
I mean, they're gangsters, Joe Biden, Barack Obama, all these guys, if you watch how they act, their histories, what they do, the deaths around them, they're Goodfellas.
And they're going, oh, look, we got the kid right here, a nice little kid.
Hey, little Sammy, I'm going to take the guns for you, kid.
All right, go around the back there.
I got three dresses for you.
She goes and looks and sees guys getting ready to kill her.
No, I don't think I'll take the dresses.
No, no, don't be a conspiracy theorist.
They don't believe people to warn you about me.
You want to get in business with me.
I'm going to take care of you.
I mean, and then look, I'm up here.
Nobody else has got the nerve going.
Listen, criminal gangsters, I know you're a tyrant.
You're a scum.
And Obama is responding.
The Washington Times goes, I hate to quote, you know, the conspiracy nutball, Alex Jones,
but this is tyranny.
I got an article.
I mean, even the Washington Times can't come out and call this tyranny when it's staring
at you in your face.
People are like, I don't know if these are Goodfellas.
I don't know.
They might have.
Really, you don't know?
You don't know?
These are Goodfellas with nuclear weapons.
These are Goodfellas with the big red one.
These are Goodfellas that control our military, the drones, everything, and only a full understanding
they're pure criminals will stop them.
And by the way, that's already happened.
Congress has a 9% approval rating.
Obama needs this gun thing as a fight where he can restrict guns while making us, he's
on the offense.
See, he's been on the defense.
He's gone on offense now where we've got to go defend the Second Amendment while they
loot 85 billion a month, just one of the dozens of ways they're robbing us, while they pass
more regulations that shut us down, while they ship more jobs taxpayer paid for overseas,
while all this, while the total meltdown happens, while the federal regulations, home inspectors
roll out, power plants being shut down, massive layoffs, they're going to push for total amnesty.
Republicans are saying they're going to go for it because they're bought and paid for
by the same foreign banks, the real mafia dons.
Obama and people are just regional capos.
That's all they are.
They're capos.
You take the mafia analogy, that is not an analogy, that's what they are.
The command structure, National Security Council, all of it, they just happen to be a mafia
of perverts and scum and pedophiles.
I mean, they're just the worst of the worst of the worst.
The globalists don't let you in unless you are nasty.
Little parties with kids, women is always coming out devil worship ceremonies with Dominique
Strauss-Kahn and a bunch of hookers and a bunch of world leaders.
That's nothing.
That's like, okay, you go and have orgies with hookers, with 200 people, we might trust
you.
Okay, you rape a kid, we'll start to trust you.
Now, shoot that kid in the head.
It's like all gangs, they have initiations.
Go knock that old lady in the head, you're a made member of the Crips.
We've got a group of vicious criminals running this country, and I've got the nerve to tell
them they're criminals because I'm not going to be their slave.
They knew Texas would stand up to them, they've profiled America, they've tried to take over
Texas before, they know it ain't going to happen.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive?
From natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the
family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy.
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At eFoods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Weakened by GMOs, stressed out about money, and blasted by the electric environment.
Hi, I'm Pastor Ginny, and that was the state I was in back in 2010.
Then I learned about RNA drops.
I learned that 97% of my DNA that scientists have called junk is actually packed with millions
of gene switches that play a critical role in controlling how my cells, organs, and other
tissues behave.
I learned I don't have to put up with disease decay or decline like I've been conditioned
to believe.
I began taking RNA drops, a 100% natural formula designed to turn on those switches and provide
me with amazing health and joy.
Learn more about RNA drops and order a free sample today.
Visit RNAFreeSample.com.
That's RNAFreeSample.com or call toll-free, 888-577-3703.
Pay only shipping and handling for a free 30-day supply of RNA drops.
Get the information you need and the health you want at RNAFreeSample.com.
Plan a healthy garden easy and fast with OrganicaSeed.com.
Easy because OrganicaSeed.com offers one of the largest online selections of organic,
heirloom, non-hybrid, and untreated seeds, as well as tobacco and cotton seeds at low
prices.
Go to OrganicaSeed.com, spelled O-R-G-A-N-I-C-A, seed.com.
OrganicaSeed.com.
Remember, Organica Seed is healthy seed.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson.
Have you ever wondered why banks, stockbrokers, investment advisors won't talk about gold
IRAs?
They've been available since 1986, yet the financial industry won't recognize the value
of gold for your retirement.
Gold is outperformed paper investments, yet no word about IRAs.
If you would like to have gold for your retirement, call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns, call 800-686-2237.
Secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237.
Feeling like there are too many pressures and demands on you?
Losing sleep?
Worrying about tests and schoolwork?
You think you're on the run because your schedule is just too busy?
You may be under too much stress, and it may be affecting your mind.
Get your mental edge back with Neutropic Mind Power from mindregard.com.
Neutropic Mind Power is not a drug, but a natural supplement.
Its 12 powerful ingredients are natural and non-GMO, plus it's gluten-free, wheat-free,
and formulated by Americans for Americans by an NSF-certified laboratory.
Neutropic Mind Power is available at mindregard.com, spelled M-I-N-D-R-E-G-A-R-D dot com, and comes
with a 100% money-back guarantee.
Free your mind with Neutropic Mind Power, a cognitive supplement from mindregard.com.
Mind Regard.
You can clearly see tomorrow, and yesterday, today.
Cyrus Jones from 1810 to 1913, made his great-grandchildren believe you could live to a hundred and three.
I'm going to be honest with you, the whole radio crew, we just spontaneously locked hands
and prayed to God for guidance and protection in these times.
The globalists have dug our grave, they've dug America's grave.
They want us to be an example of a nanny state tyranny worldwide, not a beacon of freedom.
And they will wrap themselves around those little children.
They will use them as their front to sell evil.
And those of us that have discernment are completely freaked out by what's happening.
It is not fun to have to face down these gangsters, but it's what has to be done.
No king but King Jesus.
We are not going to bow down to these tyrants.
These are horrible people that know the vaccines are killing people.
Obama says, we haven't given any solutions to the killing, which they probably conducted.
The evidence is pretty damning, especially in Colorado.
We know they staged other mass shootings, Operation Gladio in Europe.
We know they staged Fast and Furious that killed thousands, so they're prime suspects.
But they know full well every one of the real mass shooters was through cultural copycatting,
where they put mass shootings in all these movies.
The last Tom Cruise movie had one in it, came out right on time.
The media hypes it constantly.
They do these drills everywhere in every town and city, getting it into everybody's mind.
Where when there are unstable people on serotonin reuptake inhibitors, that the insert says
makes you engage in homicidal mass murder activity.
I mean, we've shown you the inserts, they all say the same thing.
Paxil, Luvox, Prozac, I mean, I don't wanna get into any names, but I've had friends who
had a divorce or whatever.
And they said, okay, you're having trouble doing whatever, we're gonna put you on Xanax.
And they just turned into complete zombies.
I've known people put on Luvox and stuff who just are totally screwed up.
And I knew instantly, a few months ago, we had a cop killed in years, thank God, here
in Austin, that a guy for no reason just walked up and shot a cop in a Walmart.
They said the guy was walking around like a zombie with a gun, and in the first reports
he just shot a cop who responded in cold blood.
And it turned out he was on a bunch of Xanax, I mean, this is a no brainer.
And then Obama gets up there on television and says, hey, it's these gun owners, they're
the problem.
It's these gun manufacturers, these gun sellers, and we're gonna lean on them till they shut
down or stop selling semi-autos.
And then I'm watching CNN right before the show starts, we have it on to monitor enemy
transmissions.
And then another police chief on there going, we need to ban all the handguns, they're coming
for everything.
And they're gonna use the full weight of Homeland Security, now admitted, I had their manuals
years ago.
People are like, how did you know, Alex, that they were gonna use Homeland Security as an
anti-gun agency?
Because they've been training for it, they're just unveiling it now.
It's like in the old days, in World War I, World War II, they'd show a big ship being
built.
It'd be behind these big curtains in a giant dock, in a giant dry dock, and they'd pull
back the curtain with the press, with the film cameras rolling.
And then they'd cut these big ropes, and then all of a sudden, or they'd have explosives
detonate, and these big rocks would fall down, and the big ship would slide into the water.
I mean, they just pulled back, I mean, there's a big ship behind there, I've been behind
there.
They've done it over and over again, their blueprint, they're coming for our guns.
Uh-oh, here we go, boom, pull back the curtain, the ship's now gone on the water, it's on.
And Paul Watson is such a prodigious writer.
The mayor predicts Waco-style standoff in response to Obama gun confiscation.
It's not going to end well.
And that's the Gloversville mayor, Dayton King, yeah, they're gonna call us terrorists.
They've been telling police, we're going to get the guns, when they fight back, they're
terrorists.
And you go to the urban warfare drills, I've been to countless ones, this is a long-term
project to the globalist.
Getting units of police and military ready, most of them have been compartmentalized,
aren't part of it.
I've seen the footage in my police state films with guys that look like my farming relatives.
John Deere hats, overalls, they'll even have kids with them in the drills.
And they kill them, they practice killing farming people, okay?
And I mean, I'm no rocket scientist, but when the Army and the Marine Corps have been training
for at least 15 years that I know to take on Hank Williams Jr., cuz we can skin a buck,
we can run a trot line, we live back in the woods, you see, with the woman, the kid, and
the dogs and me, we say grace, we say amen.
And if you don't like it, well, we're not gonna go along with it.
You can't starve us out and you can't make us run, and that's the target of a foreign
banking takeover.
They're in New York, Chicago places, they see all the yuppies, all the soft scared people,
they're like, good, we got control of this.
But they see Americans going, we know you're criminals, we know you're globalist.
They're telling the cops there's no New World Order, nobody's coming for the guns, there's
no Federal Reserve.
Now there is a Federal Reserve, we are run by foreign banks, we are in a world government,
and those that don't accept it are terrorists.
And they got all these TV shows where the founding fathers are terrorists on television.
We got the sheriff coming up in Kentucky standing up to this.
We're on the march, the empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At eFoods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather a
life storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
A prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at InfowarsShop.com.
These are items that I did research on, that I personally use.
We've got the LifeStraw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor Hand Crank Generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out
in the field.
Strategic Relocation, third edition by Joel Skousen.
When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein.
Cerosafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Hand Crank Shortwave AM FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at InfowarsShop.com
and your purchase makes our Infowars possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you?
InfowarsShop.com.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other
harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
Visit SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
Well, a few days ago, it was very touching to our viewers and listeners.
We played some clips of a county meeting that Sheriff of Jackson County, Denny Payman, was
at.
He was at the public meeting and he said, look, I would be ashamed if our founders were
here who fought so hard and gave so much up so that we would have the birthright of the
Second Amendment.
I would be ashamed that we're even discussing this.
And that's absolutely right.
That's the perspective of an informed American.
But then you get all these globalist, all these corporate front men up there all over
television.
I was just back there during the break monitoring CNN and they're like saying again, we've got
to take the handguns too.
We got to take everything.
We've got mayors and we've got US senators like Chuck Schumer saying we'll just have
audits.
We'll just harass.
We'll just shut down outside of law gun shops unless you only sell single shots.
And we have clips of that.
We have all these articles up at Infowars.com right now, Philadelphia mayor declares economic
warfare on gun rights, financial terrorism, firearms sellers to be blackmailed into conforming
to gun control.
I mean, this is just Goodfellas mafia tactics.
They want a confrontation.
They've been training for it, especially since Obama got in.
They've been trying to federalize the police.
Police sent us the training manuals, Mayak on land security saying gun owners, veterans,
conservatives, libertarians, Ron Paul supporters that we were quote terrorist and the number
one terror threat.
Remember that three and a half years ago?
Well, now they're just going public with that and they want this confrontation.
Mayor Bloomberg told Obama yesterday, he said defy Congress executive orders make people
turn them in now.
And then here is another key report before we go to the sheriff.
This is also up at Infowars.com.
Mayor predicts Waco style standoff in response to Obama gun confiscation, expressing his
opinion to the New York SAFE Act, Gloversville Mayor Dayton King has just sensationally warned
that any federal gun confiscation program could lead to Waco style standoff in rural
areas of America.
And we're going to be going over that and I want to get that mayor on ASAP.
The point is, there are so many old veterans I know especially who understand tyranny,
and they are not giving up their birthright.
And again, most police chiefs and people are constitutionalist.
They're good men and women.
But a lot of them, the state police and others were gonna follow orders and it is going to
cause a civil war.
I had Ron Paul on last week, outgoing congressman.
He said, yeah, it's the line in the sand.
He said, undoubtedly, he knows they're gonna start raising taxes and things too.
There's gonna be tax rebellions.
And he said, when they come for the guns, it's going to kick off a war.
And they're gonna call us terrorist, okay?
Now me, I'm not here saying I'm offensively gonna do anything, I'm a radio talk show host.
I'm not trying to be macho, I don't want a war, but I'm telling you something.
They're gonna start it and we're gonna finish it.
That's where this is going.
I wanna take you now to Jackson County Sheriff Denny Payman.
He was the first sheriff, now it is dozens of them.
Rand Paul vows to torpedo Obama executive orders, so we're gonna fight peacefully.
They know we're gonna beat them peacefully.
That's why they're trying to say, we're just gonna go shut things down if we feel like
it.
Lawlessly, I mean, this government is crazy.
These so-called liberals are a bunch of authoritarian freaks.
I've studied history, they did this in Russia and Germany and folk.
The Germans did this to the Jews in their businesses, just outside of law started harassing
them.
And folks, I mean, this is not gonna go well.
Many more sheriffs vow not to enforce federal gun laws.
Oregon law enforcers lead national fight against Obama gun grab.
We've got Texas sheriffs doing it.
We've got congressmen from Texas saying they're gonna start impeachment.
I had Toth on yesterday, the state rep, and the legislature's racing, he's talking to
the attorney general.
They're gonna pass law saying you can't do that in Texas.
And that's constitutional.
So I'm gonna move now to Jackson County Sheriff Denny Payment.
I wanted to give him that briefing, I know he's probably aware of all this, and talk
to him because he's the first to go public.
And sir, why were you the first to stand up from the great state of Kentucky and all 50
states and say that you're not gonna be involved in gun confiscation?
Because it dealt with my county, it dealt with the people that I have swore to protect.
It was, when I first got word of a friend of mine came in and showed me what Obama would
say and what he had said, and he said, man, what would you say to that?
And I said, we're not gonna do it.
He said, would you say that public?
And I said, yeah, I believe that, we're gonna stand by that, I'm not gonna disarm my people
because they need these guns for protection because it is their second amendment right
to have guns and I'm not gonna have the government come in and tell us, no, you're not.
And so that's where it started.
Can you elaborate because it's very touching, it sounds like you're about to break down
but you controlled yourself.
When you talked about the founding fathers, it sounds like you know about that history
a little bit.
Can you repeat what you said to your constituents?
Yes, I stood there, and this is an emotional topic for me because of the price that other
people paid that we take for granted to flippantly talk about these issues when it's something
that really doesn't even deserve to be talked about, it should already be taken care of.
And it's something that I was, we were in this meeting and I said that I was embarrassed
to have to be at a meeting like that and I was ashamed if our forefathers were to be
able to see and to hear what we were talking about and what the government is doing now,
how would they feel knowing what the price that they paid that we could have this freedom
and how we were just letting the government, which they designed the constitution for us.
They designed the second amendment for us to protect us and we sit back and just let
them push back and mold that however they want.
That's like taking the Bible and let's just say either you believe it or you don't, but
let's say you take it and you mold it to suit you and that's usually what people do.
That's the same thing they're doing with the constitution.
They're just going to mold that, they're going to tweak that, they're going to use it other
than what it was meant for to suit their purposes, their desires for the direction that they
wanted to go.
I know you've seen the FBI crime statistics that are gathered from all communities, some
of the most accurate government statistics out there, 21% violent crime reduction the
last 16 years.
Most of that dropped since 2007 and then I saw the number at fbi.gov.
In the last 20 years, a 49% drop in crimes using firearms.
Anybody can go look these numbers up and what's amazing is that the mainstream media will
not talk about that and they don't want the big secret that is gun ownership has skyrocketed.
Violent crime has gone down because criminals are scared to death to home invade or car
jack now except in areas run by these big city mayors where they've taken the guns.
That's exactly right and that's what I've told people and that's what as we talk here,
I mean we're living in a rural area and sometimes just 30, 45 minutes before I can respond to
somebody on our north end of our county, but they're calling me and they're talking on
a cell phone and how can I disarm somebody when I tell them I'm 30 minutes away and there's
two guys kicking their front door at 2 o'clock in the morning and they just woke out of a
sleep and they're depending on me to get there while these guys are coming into their house.
I would much rather them have a handgun, a weapon of some kind, not necessarily a handgun,
it could be an AK-47, I really don't care, as long as they can protect what's theirs
and protect themselves.
What's happening right now is all they've done is just paint this a different color,
all they've done is to crack the door a little bit to see what they can push through later.
They've crammed these apples down our throat and now they won't go so now they're going
to paint them, they're going to put something else on them, some caramel and try to cram
them again and that's what the people, I can only speak for the people in my county and
the people I'm responsible for, half our county are better, packs guns daily.
We don't have shootings and stuff here, we had a shooting here not long ago where a guy
was stealing a guy's stuff and he shot him.
We've had guys, other people that were shot, but we don't have guys go kicking doors on
people they know are armed.
Well that's right, in fact, where I live in Austin, the only place that you see people
getting robbed is mainly the illegal immigrant communities because folks know they're likely
to not have guns and so the criminals feed on them.
Home invasions, I've seen the national crime maps, I know you've seen them, it's almost
non-existent carjackings, home invasions.
People don't walk up in Texas in most areas, try to rob somebody in a shopping market parking
lot because most folks are packing a gun in their purse, even if it's a woman.
And then I read about Chicago in New York, Chicago, 530 something deaths last year of
citizens being fed on and they have a total gun ban for the citizens in the city and wonder
why every criminal in the country goes there because it's their happy hunting ground.
Yeah, it's free, it's free food there, you know, it's a free lunch and that's like here
or anywhere else, you know, just like in the shooting inside the theater.
What if everybody was armed in there, do you think the guy would have come in?
No, you know, and if he would have come in, how many would he have got?
I'm pushing here to arm our teachers because if I'm sitting at the bottom of the hill,
which from our high school, and they call me and say, Denny, he's coming in the room,
I've got 30 seconds to get up there, get in the room, he's already killed 30 students.
But if I have a teacher up there, he walks through the door, he can take him out as he
walks through the door.
How many people are gonna be doing school shootings?
They're not because there's no glory and just getting shot walking in with the glory is
how many they left dead.
Well we need to profile these people.
I've done a study of it and I know police have as well.
Almost every shooter, Harris, Kleibold, the Batman guy was into the occult, the guy that
killed his mom with a hammer and then got the illegal AR-15 cuz he was a felon.
Why was he out of jail?
He was a devil worshiper.
Lanza was reportedly a Satanist, that's mainstream news.
They are goth.
I'm not saying all goths are bad, the point is they are goth, Satanist, into shoot them
up video games who were in the psychiatric system on psychotropic drugs in almost every
case.
I mean the drug insert, Sheriff, says it can make you do this.
Why didn't Obama mention not putting unstable people on Prozac?
Exactly, exactly.
They don't want it, just like if there is a shooting, just like the shooting in West
Virginia that was big, it was blown up, they don't talk about the shooting where a guy
came on and only shot two people and then they go back and check these guys as to why
they were doing it in the first place and find out that they were raised in these video
games that did desensitize them to that so when they're in that shooting mode they're
just playing another game.
It's incredible.
I want to bring up what the mayor was talking about.
I read you that headline here.
Mayor predicts Waco's call standoff in response to Obama gun confiscation.
I mean they knew when they put all these psychiatric drugs in schools and then made them victim
disarmament zones, there'd be shootings.
This stuff didn't go on until the 80s and 90s, even though overall crime's going down,
violent crime, this is going up because the media hypes it, there's mentally ill people,
there's these video game head Satanists.
This is really cool and fun for them to go and do this.
What do you think's going to happen, Sheriff?
And again, the sheriff from Jackson County, Kentucky, Denny Paiman joins us.
What do you think's going to happen if they give state police the order to, okay, we've
got undercover reports that this guy out here's got 15 guns and he's a veteran, he's refused
to turn them in.
What's going to happen when they go to try to take the guns?
And then let's say the first 100 people turn their guns in, if you've got 160 million gun
owners and 1% refuse to turn them in, that's 1,600,000 people that are going to fight back.
What do you think is going to happen there, Sheriff?
I think that they're going to have a civil war on their hands because I know people well
enough, they're going to go bury whatever guns they have, they're going to hide them,
they're going to put them, but they're going to put them with their easy access for them,
and they're going to come say, I searched my place, take whatever, but when it comes
right down to taking it from their hand, it will never happen.
These people will fight back because people will fight over a lot of things, but the number
one thing they will fight over is their firearm because they know that is their last, very
last line of defense.
If you've got a guy 60 years old that's a veteran, and he's crippled up from his service,
what he's done, and that's all his last line of defense, that's what he's going to do.
He's going to fight you for it.
So what do you think the social engineers are thinking?
I mean, Ron Paul, everybody said what you said, and then I told Piers Morgan, you're
going to start 1776 again, and he spun it like I'm saying I want that.
That's the last thing I want, but they're pushing and pushing, I guess they think they're
going to be able to initiate this, they're already saying Obama's going to be the new
Lincoln, and he'll crush the states, I mean I think these people are on megalomaniac power
trips.
Yes, what it is, it's a bully tactic, and what they're going to do is they're going
to bully first, you know, verbally, then they're going to try and stretch their muscle a little
bit to see, because they think, you know, they've got all these trained troops and stuff,
but I'll tell you what, there's more people trained here than what we have in our full
military.
In the United States, there's more people that are trained that shoot, casual shooters,
people that, you know, and they're going to fight back, and once, I'll tell you something,
once this started, I've looked at a lot of people here lately and talked to a lot of
people, they've got the look in their eye, I've had enough, they're not going to take
this too.
You know, everybody, our employment is down, I mean, up to where people aren't employed,
prices are high, people are thinking, you know what, what do I care?
When they go to try to take somebody's gun, they're going to have more than a civil war
on their hands.
It'll be so much worse than what it ever was before, because, you know, and here, if you've
got, say, just in any part of the United States that you come in and you isolate an area and
try to get the guns, the wars are not going to start there, but the American people will
come to you.
The support that I've got just over the United States from fellow officers, retired officers,
veterans, all these people that are coming together right now, they're all willing to
fight.
Wow, you've really done your homework.
Because what you're saying is absolutely historical, and here's the thing, we don't want this,
but they've taken our sovereignty, they say our military's under NATO UN control, they
tell Congress that's their face, Obama's shutting down power plants everywhere, power prices
are exploding.
To wreck America, he paid to ship General Motors to China, 22 billion, this is economic
warfare, to shut us down, to put us on welfare, to domesticate us.
And they brag and say that, and Americans know that, and they know everything's been
taken from us.
Obama said it five years ago in a secret meeting with his million dollar donors.
He said they're bitter clingers, but don't worry, I'll get them in the second term.
They call us bitter clingers, they hate us cuz we love God, they hate us, and they've
taken everything from us.
All we've got's our guns left in our Bibles, and now they're taking our churches, saying
the Catholic Church and others are gonna have to pay for abortions, these people are crazy.
Yes, they are, and there's not the same blood that runs through them as it runs through
the rest of the core of America, it's not the same blood.
They'll find out what that color of that blood is, cuz they've showed it before.
That's right, so again, Sheriff, it sounds like you've really done a lot of historical
research.
I know the police I've interviewed, except for maybe former Sheriff Richard Mack.
You are the most informed about history, cuz everything you're saying is exactly how it's
gonna go down.
Is there any way to stop it?
No, even biblically, they're looking into, a lot of stuff is gonna come to pass.
But even the stuff that came to pass, they didn't lay down.
And does it mean come to pass, does that mean in our generation or the next year?
We're only responsible to take care of ourselves and the next generation.
It's the next generation's responsibility to take it there.
Everybody's talking about these different things, the end times, all that kind of stuff.
It could have been end times in the 60s, but people fought back.
It could have been in the 70s or 80s, but now we're in 2000.
Only God knows the exact time that he will return.
Wow.
No, it's like Nineveh got 100 year reprieve, you're right.
God helps those that helps themselves, he gave us a brain.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, we could have, I mean, the whole, I mean, this could have all been over a thousand
years ago.
It could have been over 200 years ago, but he also gives in man the freedom, the freedom
and the desire to do what's right.
Well, I'm in, God bless you, Sheriff.
One more segment with you, Jackson County Sheriff, Denny Payman.
This is the kind of sheriff we need in every county in this country.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not going to want to miss this exciting message.
Here's why.
Our solar generators provide life saving electrical power and unlike gas generators, solar generators
run quietly, emit no fumes and produce electricity from the sun.
So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part.
Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of
each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait, they go fast.
Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
Big business has discovered the preparedness market and that makes it difficult to know
where to go and who to trust.
MyPatriotsSupply.com is owned and operated by patriots just like you, has the best prices
on storable food, non-GMO seeds, water filtration devices, home canning equipment, survival
and self-reliance books and more.
MyPatriotsSupply.com has old-fashioned values and the absolute best customer service in
the industry.
Look for the deal of the day, unique affordable survival supplies that fit anyone's budget.
Get same-day shipping on all orders and free shipping on orders over $49.
Call 866-229-0927, 866-229-0927.
Or visit MyPatriotsSupply.com for emergency preparedness, self-reliance and food independence.
Shop with a name you know and a name you can trust.
Before it's time to survive, it's time to prepare.
MyPatriotsSupply.com.
Is this the year you finally get serious about your family's drinking water?
If so, keep listening for a special offer from Big Berkey Water Filters.
Did you know that over 60% of municipal water is fluoridated?
Berkey Water Filters distinguish themselves from many other filtration systems with the
capability to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine, fluoride, arsenic and disinfection
by-products from municipal water via the black Berkey and PF line of filters.
Then there's affordability.
At only 1.7 cents per gallon, Berkey Water Filters purify treated and untreated water,
even stagnant pond water.
Stop and think how much money you could save by simply reducing buying bottled water and
using water filtered by your Berkey Water Filter.
No need to be constantly replacing expensive filters with a Berkey.
A single set of filters can last for 5 to 10 years.
Choose the best size Berkey for your needs at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
And right now, all GCN listeners get 5% off all ceramic filter systems.
Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY.
That's 877-99-BER-KEY or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
Free shipping on every order over $50.
Big Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean water.
Jackson County Sheriff hailing from Kentucky, Denny Payment is our guest.
You can hear his historical understanding of this.
I mean, when I look at the oily mafia types, the anti-gunners and their statements they're
making about, we'll just shut your gun shop down without a law.
We're just gonna, I mean, I'm gonna play some of these clips in the next hour.
I can't believe they're moving this fast.
Sheriff, what is your gut that their game plan is?
We know it's a full out assault, Homeland Security is now not for Al-Qaeda, it's for
the American people.
They're saying that it's for conservatives, libertarians.
What do you think in your gut is their full game plan and what they're planning?
What it is is that I feel is what they're doing now is they're gonna see what the American
people will tolerate.
They're kind of trying to crack the door a little bit, they're gonna throw some stuff
out.
They're throwing stuff out that we're gonna balk at, we're gonna balk and they're gonna
pull back and they'll say, okay, let's just try and find a medium here.
We'll give some, you give some and everybody's gonna be happy.
What the American people are gonna do is they're gonna give some and all they were gonna do
is they're setting the people up when they kick the door, they come in and take it all.
Because once you've been set up and you will compromise on the Second Amendment, if you
will compromise on any of that, then you've compromised on it all.
And that's what they're gambling, that we'll compromise.
If we don't compromise, they're not gonna know what to do then because they're gambling
that if we compromise, they can get the door cracked enough that they can get in that way.
But if we don't let them get in or let them get started, they're not gonna know what to
do next.
They also run the risk of being too over the top, I mean, I've got clips coming up, I'm
sure you're seeing this as well, I know you're busy.
But they're on CNBC, CNN, MSNBC saying, quote, our presidents beat Hitler, they can beat
the gun owners.
That's a Bob Shafer quote CBS, no, my grandfathers beat Hitler, not presidents and certainly
not Obama.
And they're saying it's like South Africa, that's embargoing the racist and gun owners
are Klan members.
I mean, it's so over the top to say gun owners killed those kids.
They're trying to put the guilt on us.
I say we get on the offensive and point out they're the ones that made schools victim
disarmament zones.
Because if we don't get on the offensive, we're gonna lose it.
Well, what I'm finding in these little tea party groups, liberal groups, patriot groups,
what I'm finding, I used to see back in the 70s, 60s, 70s, they're more of the redneck,
they're more of the working man, you know what I'm saying, where it was gonna be kind
of stereotyping, all these gun owners are all hillbillies.
What I'm seeing now is I'm seeing judges, I'm seeing legislators, I'm seeing educated
people.
The thing has changed dramatically, you still see a blend of people, but it's an upper,
I mean, you're talking people that are in places of power and control that can help
and can do something.
You just said it, we've got Congress people, we've got judges, we've got police chiefs,
sheriffs, it's a leadership core, just like leading up to 1775.
And the establishment better understand that, there's going to be organized at governmental
level resistance to this.
Yeah, but what they're betting that at that level it's gonna be taken care of, but it's
not.
It's still gonna take a cross of every American that packs a gun.
And just like for the people that don't pack a gun when this all comes down, they better
be standing close to somebody who does because they're gonna need protection too.
Well look at the economy, the derivatives, we're totally bankrupt by design, 50 million
people on food stamps, all these big cities run by these crime bosses are collapsing.
And then when everybody runs to the rural areas, I mean, we're not turning our guns
in so we can be gang raped.
Right, exactly.
You know, this is like they talk about the assault weapons and stuff.
I've got one, I've had one, I've had them for years, and I'm gonna continue to keep
them.
Why?
No, I don't go out and play with them.
It's probably been two years since I've even fired some of them, but you know, I keep them.
Why do I keep them?
I keep them for my protection, and that's what other people are keeping theirs for,
for protection.
You don't turn in your protection.
If you've got 50 people rushing your farmhouse or planning to loot you, you need an AR-15.
Do five more minutes with us if you can.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support, and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Anybody ask out there why the Republicans' leadership are going along with open borders,
gun control, all this stuff?
It's because most of the big guys are involved in insider trading, and that's come out, and
it's all illegal.
So they passed a law making it legal, which you can't really do, saying it's a law making
it illegal, but they just go get a ethics board to say it's okay.
I mean, it is incredible.
The Democrats are the kings of this, but they are a bunch of gangsters.
I've studied them.
We've put the evidence on here on air.
And criminals don't want people armed.
Good people want good people armed, cuz good people know criminals are gonna have weapons
regardless.
Might as well have the good guys with the guns.
Like the NRA has said, we have the amazing sheriff of Jackson County, Kentucky, Denny
payment, if you wanna find out more about it, jacksoncountykentucky.us, and go to the
sheriff's department.
But, sir, you were telling me, we've only got four minutes left, about the support you're
getting.
Talk about that, and then talk about some of the real solutions, cuz Obama said pro-gun
people have given no solutions, which is a lie.
We've given the only solution that's gonna work, because what it is, is that everybody,
all down through history, they figure out a way to, from bullying to attacks to whatever,
to take what they want.
And here's what's been happening here for so long.
But what Americans have forgotten is how to fight back.
We need to teach our teachers how to fight.
We need to teach some of our older students how to fight.
Somebody comes in your classroom, you know, everybody's taught now to run cover in the
corner.
It saves half the ammunition, and sometimes you can kill two or three with one shot.
You know, if they were to spread out and to fan out and talk to attack, how many people
would come into a classroom?
They would only make it through the one classroom.
We're gonna lose students anyway.
But the nanny state does not ever want, they don't even let you play dodgeball or tag.
They might as well have them line up back to back so one bullet could shoot through
three people.
Maybe that should be what Obama proposes.
Well, that's kind of making the way it sounds.
But you know, right now there's 18 states that have passed that they're arming their
teachers.
People are starting to figure out, you know what, I can't stand here anymore.
I need to fight back for myself and for the people I'm responsible for.
And that's what we're pushing here is to arm teachers to be able to protect our students.
You know, they talk about putting officers in the schools.
The government has offered that through different grants and stuff.
They can't afford that.
They don't have the money.
States can't afford that.
Our county can't afford that.
But I'll guarantee you, like crosswalkers, if you ask retired police to volunteer, say,
a week out of each month, you could get five or six, seven guys per county.
They'd all be able to do that as well.
But I agree arming the teachers is the way to go.
And that's got to make the gun grabbers mad that how many states would you say are moving
to do that right now?
Eighteen.
Wow, that's exciting.
So it's catching on quick.
David, we know we're playing actually playing catch up at this point because, you know,
he has moved in his direction.
Now we're having to basically counteract everything.
We should have not ever had to counteract.
We should have already been there.
My dad went to a rural school, but it was big and he would drive in 15 miles with his
mom who was a teacher to work.
But they would all bring their shotguns and stuff to go shoot at each other's houses and
dove hunt and quail hunt or deer hunt.
They would all bring their guns to school.
And it was a school with over a thousand people in it.
They never had one accident because they were a gun culture.
Right.
Well, you saw you see a pickup in the 60s and 70s, you saw you see a pickup parked in
the parking lot with a gun hanging on a rack so kids could go hunting after school.
It wasn't uncommon at all.
And I think it was because of the shootings and stuff there.
Well, I tell you, you are the way forward.
My friend, 1776 was a 5000 year leap for freedom there.
They're saying it's old.
They're wanting to go back to ancient tyranny where only government is armed.
Jackson County Sheriff Denny Payman, sir, we salute you for being a true American.
I know you're just doing your duty.
But in a world of universal deceit, telling the truth is a revolutionary act.
And you are a great example to everyone and I hope that you'll run for Congress or something
because I'll guarantee you we need you to join Rand Paul in the federal government to
protect our republic.
I appreciate that, sir, and I appreciate the opportunity to be able to visit with you today.
I'm saying right now you're drafted, buddy.
I don't know if that's what you want, but Kentucky, this guy's a statesman.
You draft him, you send him to Washington to protect the Bill of Rights.
Sheriff, we'll talk to you again.
God bless you.
Thank you, sir.
There he goes.
All right.
We'll be back with Lou Rockwell.
Amazing.
You may be arrested and or subject to other police action.
Tyranny is here.
The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality.
It really says that the state is God.
The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most impressive police states
on Earth.
This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being
expanded nationwide.
This documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all
powerful shadow state.
Police state four chronicles the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen.
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship, body scanners, sound cameras,
citizen spies, stage terror and cameras on every street corner.
It's only the beginning of the New World Order's hellish plan.
The police state isn't coming.
It's here.
Secure your copy today at infowars.com or see it online in the highest quality at prisonplanet.tv.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy.
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
a life storm by having a supply of food on hand after Hurricane Sandy.
Danny from New York City wrote, Almost all of the grocery stores are closed, but I managed
to get my e Foods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e Foods Direct.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network and now live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, we just concluded the first hour of you tuned in here and we
had Sheriff Denny payment on from Jackson County and he's got to be the most powerful,
just concise, calm speaker from, quote, law enforcement as a peace officer I've ever heard.
I mean, it was unbelievable if you listen to it.
He was just very calm, but you could hear it.
He said people have got it in their eyes.
They're ready.
This is going to be a new revolution.
And they're going to go and harass gun owners.
They're announcing hell on earth.
In fact, last night I couldn't go to bed researching these executive orders and it was everything
I knew they do.
But they are, I've got the mayor of Philadelphia saying we're just going to shut gun shops
down because outside of law, they're announcing you'll do what we say or else.
That's what Chuck Schumer is calling people.
That's in the news saying you will not sell guns or I will do something.
I mean, it's literally like the mafia coming into your shop and saying you'll do this or
else.
I've got clips coming up of Bob Schaefer saying that gun owners are like the Nazis in Germany.
He likens Obama taking on gun owners to defeating the Nazis.
That's a quote.
I've got that clip.
Morning Joe said, how dare the NRA point out that elites have bodyguards and he took his
glasses off and Mika Brzezinski went, I just am ashamed to be an American today.
Well, get out of our country, you witch.
And again, they just act like we're the weirdos and it's all affected.
Man, Alex screwed up getting in our face saying we want to take their guns.
Really?
I mean, Paul Revere wrote down the road saying get your guns and get ready to kill people.
George Washington signed death warrants.
I'm just saying don't try to take our guns or it'll cause a civil war, which they know
it will do.
But the truth is it was very effective when the NRA said, hey, Israel has guns in their
schools and it got rid of the mass shootings.
They went, no, that's not true.
Nobody in Israel is armed and lied.
And no, that's not effective, NRA is discredited.
That's a tactic when something really hits them hard, it's like you punch somebody and
they go, that didn't hurt.
Can you go out of the room, please, and they fall down on the ground.
They are so scared of us pointing out that Dianne Feinstein has a concealed carry and
five bodyguards, that Michael Moore has a concealed carry and bodyguards that have been
arrested carrying guns in airports.
That Chuck Schumer's been caught with bodyguards and then swore he'd never have them and turned
a gun in.
He got caught in a gun range with a semi-auto, all smiling, shooting it and bodyguards and
oh, okay, I've given it up now, remember that?
This is the end of these hypocrites and that's why they're like, did you see these ridiculous
hypocrites pointing out that David Gregory on NBC has bodyguards and guns?
Yeah, that's ridiculous, of course he has, he's a public figure.
Well, listen, you scum, the average person living in a working class neighborhood, my
dad going through college, through medical school would go because it was the best money
he could make.
And his dad had a heart attack and stuff and didn't have money to put him through college.
My dad would go, this is when I was born, he had his UT degree, but he was going to
dental school.
He would go and he would do, with his own company, spraying bug poison in the worst
neighborhoods of Dallas.
And you know what, he carried a 357 Magnum in his lunchbox, okay?
My dad drove around, bought his own poison, went and did it the whole nine yards.
I remember when I was like two years old, him getting home at like 10 o'clock at night
and I'd wake up and then wake him up once he went to bed and he'd get upset cuz he had
to get up at 5 AM or whatever.
Again, you scum, you elitist, my dad deserved going into the projects in South Dallas as
a roach man, they called him the roach man's here.
The roach man carried a 357 Magnum, he still got the 357 Magnum.
And this is what it comes down to here today.
And that's why they're freaking out.
But let me tell you, I've never seen such demonization.
The Philadelphia mayor says, take the guns, it's like apartheid.
We're gonna boycott, we're gonna protest, we're gonna shut them down.
They're saying Fox Sports, gun owners of the new Klan, we're mass murderers, we killed
those kids.
The government took the guns out of the schools, and government advertised schools as the place
to go and kill people.
This didn't exist till the media hyped it in the 80s.
Now joining us is the founder of the Von Mies Institute, the head of the Von Mies Institute,
former Ron Paul chief of staff, libertarian icon, Lou Rockwell of lourockwell.com.
I just gave him a basic briefing, I know he's already aware of this.
But the word is they're gonna try executive orders to use all of homeland security to
demonize guns, to harass gun shops and gun owners.
I've talked to several gun shop owners off record who are getting me the documents, ATF
coming in and saying, orders are about to come down, we know this happened last year.
You're gonna do what we say or else.
So at that point, we've got to move for impeachment.
I've entered public articles of impeachment that list with the law, so others can use
it.
Members of Congress are picking that up and others, and are saying we need to start impeachment
now.
Stockman of Texas and others.
Ron Paul is vowing to, quote, torpedo it, and he's talking about impeachment.
Ron Paul vows to torpedo Obama executive orders, new legislation with nullified gun control
dictates.
It's time to get on the offensive.
Lou Rockwell, is this not in your 47 years of fighting tyranny?
Is this the greatest assault you've ever seen?
I mean, I've never seen rhetoric like this.
Are we moving into DETHCON1?
Well, because there have been many periods in American history when the government has
massively expanded and stolen the people's liberties.
I mean, usually during wartime, the New Deal, the Great Society.
This is another one, and certainly this is an extraordinary moment.
All governments would like to be totalitarian.
They all would like to have total control, control every dime we have, everything we
do in our life, everything we think, everything we say, our businesses, our homes, our children.
So they want it all.
Whenever there's a chance, something like this Newton shooting and the horrible things
that happen there, they use it.
But of course, they don't care about so-called gun violence.
After all, Barack Obama is a leader of the world headquarters of gun violence in the
history of the world of the US government.
I mean, how many people, and he signs, of course, the kill orders, and the US government
employs millions of people to shoot other people.
I mean, that's their main deal in life.
Whether it's in Afghanistan, or Iraq, or Yemen, or Syria, or they hope Iran, and all these
other countries, they're shooting people.
And when they talk about what might be encouraging violence, is it video games, is it TV, Hollywood?
And I must say, I'm not a big fan of some of this stuff, although free speech does apply.
But how about the glorification of war, the glorification of cops, the glorification of
soldiers, the glorification of government gun violence?
So none of these people are anti-gun or anti-gun violence.
They're anti-private people owning guns.
And anybody who knows people who own guns, they are not pro-violence.
The last thing they want to do in their life is shoot somebody.
There are people, of course, who like to shoot people, they work for the government.
But private people with guns don't want to have to use them.
They only want to have to use them if their back is against the wall, like that homemaker
in Georgia the other day, who had, she was backed up into the attic where they're two
little nine-year-old twins, and then finally shot the guy and got him to run away and avoiding
rape and murder.
That's right, you notice that in these cases that happen, we hear about every week but
never make national news, every day, most days, the woman's on 9-1-1, okay, he's busting
down the front door, I'm going in the bathroom, then they're busting down the bathroom door,
and then 9-1-1's like, don't shoot them, and then the woman shoots them.
The gun owners always try to hold back, but we have guns because we're not going to be
victims.
No, that's right, it's like the old joke, and it may be actually a true story, about
a guy who called up 9-1-1 and said, I've got prowlers in the yard, and they said, oh, we'll
be out in 25 minutes or whatever.
And then he calls back and says, don't worry, I shot them, and of course the cops are there
in just a minute.
So they don't want us defending ourselves.
Government wants its monopoly.
The cops, aside from the few good guys like the sheriff you were talking to, most cops
don't want people exercising self-defense, they only want that to be a government monopoly.
They want to take away our guns for self-defense, and of course they want to take it for reasons
of tyranny, the same reasons that governments all over the world, and you had some great
photos of Hitler and Stalin and Mao and these guys using children in their propaganda exercises,
just like Barack Obama did recently, it was Hannah Arendt who said, any time politicians
start talking about your children, your country is on the road to totalitarianism.
Well, that's right, I haven't even mentioned-
Barack Obama says, the kids in Newtown are our kids, they're not his kids, he's got two
kids, nobody else's children are his children, but it's a totalitarian move, he wants to
be the chief minister, the chief religious figure, the chief protector, we're all supposed
to focus on him, we're supposed to give him our guns, give him our freedom, give him our
money, bow down, and he wants to be the pharaoh, but we don't have to allow it, and it's wonderful
to see, Alex, all the opposition that you're leading among the American people refusing
to have this happen to us.
Well, you're right, and what you're mentioning is DrudgeReport.com, it's in the middle column.
Yesterday I was sitting around with Kurt Nemo and we were looking at images of Hitler and
Stalin and Mao and everybody else in Saddam Hussein using children, so I just said, well,
let's just post it with Obama high-fying the kids.
And it's so amazing that he said, I'm gonna take the guns for you, kid, like he's the
good guy, he's the North Korean dear leader, he's the guardian of the society, he's the
Hugo Chavez, he's the Mao Tse Tung, I mean, this is right out of a textbook, and if you
don't turn your guns in, you're not for the children.
And that article is up at DrudgeReport.com showing Stalin, who said that he did all he
did for the children.
In fact, he was known as the Great Father Steele, he was known as the Man of Steele,
the Father of Steele.
Well, you know what, Barack Obama is not my father, I'm my father.
What did you think of, we're gonna break, but Bob Shafer's saying that our president
beat Hitler, I mean, our men beat Hitler, not the government, I'm sorry, go ahead.
Does it matter that Hitler was a big gun controller?
No, of course not, the facts don't matter.
And Shafer's just a spoke, he might as well be broadcasting for Radio Berlin or Radio
Moscow or Radio Havana or any of these other, I mean, he's just a representative of the
state media, giving out state propaganda, spreading the lies, and of course, as you
pointed out, we're living under such unbelievable intensive media attempts to control our minds
to make us all fear private guns and think that government guns are the way to save us.
Incredible, I want to hear where you think this is going, the man, Lou Rockwell is our
guest, we'll be right back.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive, from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought, to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy.
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e Foods Direct.
We all know that Berkey water purification systems are the most trusted name in water
filtration.
An authorized Berkey dealer for over six years and serving thousands of satisfied customers,
the Berkey Guy offers amazing specials for Berkey water filtration systems.
The Berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable black purification
elements that purify water by removing chlorine, pathogenic bacteria, cysts and parasites to
non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides.
Order the Berkey light system today complete with two black Berkey elements for only $231
and the Berkey guy will ship your order free of charge.
With the purchase of a Berkey light, the Berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride and
arsenic filters for only $39.99.
That's over 30% off the retail price.
Call the Berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653.
That's 1-877-886-3653 or order online at goberky.com.
That's goberky.com today.
Jim Newcomer from Mondays Resources, January 16, 2013.
Gold opened this morning at $1675.60.
One ounce gold coin can be purchased for $1718.29, $859.15 for a half ounce or $429.57 for a quarter
ounce.
That's $1718.29, $859.15 and $429.57.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson.
Have you ever wondered why bank stockbrokers and investment advisors won't talk about gold
IRAs?
Wait a sec.
Gold and silver is going up while Congress is trying to settle on the next debt increase
and there's no end to this madness.
That old 401K and IRA can be converted into physical gold without tax consequences.
I explained this in my book, 10 Reasons to Buy Gold.
Don't let time slip away.
Call for your free copy today, 800-686-2237.
Get away from that Washington spin and get honest answers about gold, 800-686-2237.
The book is free, 800-686-2237.
Hey there, Frank Bates here.
Have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out 280 million Americans?
This is really scary stuff.
Defense experts warn that this odd device poses the greatest threat we've ever known.
In fact, just a few weeks ago, former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed
piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat.
I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this.
It may be because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up.
That's why my friend just created a free video at weirddevice.com that exposes this threat
and blows the doors off the conspiracy.
Go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover exactly what it is plus
discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly attack.
I'm not sure how long this video will be online, so go to weirddevice.com before it's gone
forever.
And that's weirddevice.com.
This will be difficult.
There will be pundits and politicians and special interest lobbyists publicly warning
of a tyrannical all-out assault on liberty.
Not because that's true, but because they want to gin up fear or higher ratings or revenue
for themselves.
Did you hear that?
He is directly going after yours truly, obviously, from the Piers Morgan interview, pundits,
that here I am making money, shelling T-shirts, water filters, sponsors.
This is the government that takes your money and gives it to MSNBC.
You know they've been giving government money.
That's come out.
To push tyranny and then we're immoral and he goes on to say we've given no solutions
really get the kids off these drugs that have been linked to it directly, armed people in
the schools.
We shouldn't have big government training camps anyways.
Lou Rockwell of lourockwell.com, we've gotten to a point where they're having to respond
to us now.
I'll put you on the hot seat.
I want your real answer.
Do you think it was effective to get in Piers Morgan's face and go, look, this isn't about
child safety.
This is about tyranny and enslavement because if it wasn't effective, why then are they
responding to it?
Well, you know, Alan, you know, Alex, that I think was the biggest ratings that that
bird has ever had.
We know that his ratings are otherwise in the toilet and he probably, if he weren't
so politically correct and so useful to the regime as a propagandist, he probably would
have been sent back to England or some other place long before this because he doesn't
have viewers except when you're on.
Absolutely.
But I mean, isn't it effective?
I mean, you're gentlemanly, but you're also hard hitting.
They always call us kooks no matter what we do.
Isn't it effective to go ahead and get aggressive and back in their faces?
Sure.
You got to speak truth to power, right?
And this guy represents the state media.
I mean, he's no different from somebody who wrote for Pravda or, or, uh, was on, you know,
Moscow state television in the Soviet days.
He's nothing but a shill for the regime.
He's a professional liar.
He's paid to lie, uh, for the government.
Same with Bob Schieffer, all of these people.
So not only should we, should we speak the truth to them, but sure, I'm, I'm, uh, I'm
for dissing them because they don't deserve respect.
Uh, they're very bad people.
They're making vast amounts of money for doing evil.
Uh, so of course, of course we should speak the truth to them and we should be, uh, we
should be frank with them and, uh, we should tell them exactly, I mean, Piers Morgan is
a huge fan, for example, of drone warfare.
He's a huge fan of all the U S government wars and wars of the British empire.
He's for torture.
He's for all this stuff.
So we're supposed to think he's against violence.
I mean, this is a guy who's a champion of violence, but he wants to, he wants the state
to be violent.
And, and of course the state is violence.
The state is always the headquarters of violence.
I mean, how many babies we do, you know, we're talking about the horror in Newtown.
How many babies has the U S government killed in its, in its a career of mass murder?
I mean, I remember back when they were going after Iraq, which did nothing to us.
Madeleine Albright said a half a million dead children was worth it.
She said that on NBC news famously, and they said half a million dead kids.
Is that good?
She goes, yeah, it's good.
See, I mean, half a million kids that they were deliberately murdered by the U S through
its murder sanctions, anti-civilian murder sanctions, and also sanctions against food
against medicine designed to starve and sicken these children.
Half a million.
I mean, uh, has Saddam Hussein ever done anything that bad?
I don't know.
My guess is no.
I mean, the U S is, is really the murder state is the assassination state.
It's the drone state.
And we're supposed to think that Obama cares about violence.
He is violence.
Every morning he signs his death orders over his scrambled eggs.
This is the guy who likes this kind of thing.
Like by the way, everybody who prospers in government likes killing people or sending
other people to be killed.
They enjoy this.
It empowers them.
They feel very good about it.
They love guns.
And as you say, all the, uh, all the power leaders have, you know, Bloomberg and Obama
and, uh, I'm sure Piers Morgan, all these people have armed bodyguards.
CNN has gotten a bunch of armed bodyguards all in their studios.
How come that's okay?
But some little old lady, uh, in a bad area can't have a 22.
So that's, you know, it's, it's, but you know, they want to disarm us.
They want to control us.
They want to hurt us.
I'm also afraid by the way that they want to stimulate armed resistance in the sense
that they would love another Waco or two Waco was we have to remember was about gun control.
That's what the whole thing was about.
I totally agree.
They're trying to start a civil war.
How do we respond to that?
Well, I think we don't, we don't, uh, take the bait.
So I think we don't respond with violence.
Uh, and we just state our rights.
We, we buy guns, hold guns, join together with other people who believe in freedom,
uh, become, uh, go to the firing range, make use of them, talk up owning guns and really
spread the word.
I think most Americans, despite these little phony polls we're hearing and never forget
that these national polls are designed to tell you what to think, not to tell you what
other people think.
They're propaganda devices.
So when we hear that 189% of the American people, you know, a hundred percent agree
with Obama, you know, these are just, just laws.
Well that's come out, they've had polling agency heads admit they lie, uh, I mean, it's
just incredible.
It is to create a bandwagon.
Like 99% of people want to jump off a cliff.
Well, come on Martha, let's go jump off right now.
Lou Rockwell, long segment coming up.
I want to ask you what you think is coming in the future and how we counter these people.
We're going to pick your brain straight ahead.
We're on the march.
The empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
Recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be
used daily to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus and other
harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Bend Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Leading a frontal assault on the lives of the new world order, it's Alex Jones on the
GCN radio network.
Crank it up.
I'm going to do the gingham style.
There were a bunch of people who weren't going to turn their guns in and they could kick
some tyranny real good as well.
He never learned to read and write so well, but he could pull a trigger like he was ringing
a bell.
Go Johnny, go, go, go.
It's exactly what Lou Rockwell was just saying.
We're going to go to some clips with him as well.
You don't know who Lou Rockwell is.
He of course is a icon in the movement towards libertarianism.
You notice most real studies, university studies, people on the street is what I've seen.
Around 60% of Americans call themselves a libertarian.
They don't like either party and our movement is gaining steam.
I call it constitutionalist freedom lover, folks that just want to be left alone.
People that are into justice and that's why the power structure is going after us right
now is because when I see liberal women's magazines, because Austin's more quote liberal
than most cities in Texas, just because some of the Californian folks have come and taken
it over.
Not against Californians, but those kind of socialist types that call themselves liberals,
they're not really authoritarians.
Thomas Jefferson was a liberal.
But I want to get Lou Rockwell's historical take on this because he's seen a lot and really
has written about what he believed was coming and now unfortunately, it's unfolding.
Women's magazines becoming pro-gun just because no one would buy the magazine unless they
did it.
Women going out and learning how to shoot, gun ownership proliferating, gun sales proliferating,
self-defense classes proliferating.
People are really getting into becoming self-sufficient.
There is a rebellion against the nanny state, against all this, and people are really getting
into it.
And so the globalists are all out of salt because gun ownership is a beachhead against
the nanny state, against victim disarmament.
And that cultural area, one of the few areas of liberty really growing, was getting other
areas to grow.
It was becoming kind of a central part of a wheel with the spokes out from it.
And the establishment has said this.
And I mean, look at the prepper movement, look at the, all the liberals I know aren't
liberals now.
They've gone out and bought places in the countryside, they're getting self-sufficient.
You heard the sheriff, he said, I go to these liberty meetings now and it's judges and it's
state reps and it's doctors and it's lawyers and it's writers and it's former quote liberals.
They're still liberals, they've become real liberals.
And so the system is announcing a full out Homeland Security attack from hundreds of
angles, 23 executive orders, massive demonization, arresting people for toy guns.
Because if they can't shoot this down, they're going to lose.
They wanna collapse things and make us fully domesticated instead of collapsing things.
And then we get off the government heroin and become self-sufficient.
Lou Rockwell, your take on that and what you fear they're gonna try in the future and how
we turn the tide against these people.
Well, Alex, you're right.
I mean, there was one little boy tossed out of school for making a gun with his fingers.
I must say, during Obama's press conference, I kept hoping one of those little boys would
do that.
It didn't happen.
Of course, they're all brainwashed.
But I think my guess is that Obama has actually gone too far.
I think the government has gone too far, the whole government media complex.
I think it's taken a step too far by doing what they're doing.
And of course, this constant media propaganda and bombardment similar to what the old Soviet
days or something out of 1984 or Nazi Germany when they were demonizing somebody, I don't
think it's working.
Everybody was sort of taken aback.
Of course, we're horrified by the crime that took place, as we should be horrified by all.
For example, the little Muslim children killed in Afghanistan, very few Americans care about
that, of course.
The US government is killing children every day all over the world and nobody cares.
But I think by going after gun ownership like this, by being so openly a dictator, I don't
think, Alex, despite all you've done, I've done, Ron Paul, talk about executive orders
over the year.
Does the average American realize the president can just legislate by fiat like that, like
he's the pharaoh or the king?
I don't think so.
So this is waking people up.
Everybody's concerned.
Everybody's paying attention, both on the commissar side of the government and the big
media and so forth.
But the rest of the people and also more and more people are going to realizing that the
power elites, of course, all are themselves armed and have tax paid, tax applied, armed
bodyguards.
I think they stepped too far.
I think everybody's waking up.
I think they made a mistake.
I think it's all going to end in a black eye for the government.
They actually need two black eyes.
And I think it's a huge step forward.
It is connected to the entire liberty movement, as you point out.
And when people realize this, then they're going to take a look at other different areas
of government encroachment.
All the taxes they're increasing, the rotten Obamacare, which is also tied into gun control.
John Rappaport has pointed out that the doctors are going to be instructed to ask, how many
guns are in your home?
We can bet that the public school teachers are going to be asking children.
They already interrogate children on a whole range of things.
Do your parents have guns?
Are you scared of your parents' guns?
What kind of guns do your parents have?
So if anybody's concerned about what happened in Newtown, the answer to me is not to arm
the school teachers.
Although, of course, school teachers, like anybody else, have the right to be armed if
they want to.
Take your kids out of the public schools.
Succeed from the public schools.
That's the best thing you can do for your children, that you can do for your family.
Send them to private school or, best of all, homeschool them.
This doesn't happen in homeschools.
It just happens in government schools.
The old joke from when I was a boy and much older than that has come true.
That is, the head, the principals, the warden, the teachers of the guards, and the students
of the prisoners.
The public schools even look like prisons these days.
They're going to be looking more and more like prisons.
They're going to be more and more totalitarian with all kinds of cops, armed cops, resource
officers and so forth, to propagandize them against guns, against their parents.
Just like Stalin trying to use the children against the parents.
Get your children out of the public schools.
Don't pretend that you can reform the public schools because even if your children are
physically safe, they're not mentally safe in there because they're being indoctrinated
with lies, with evil, with everything designed to make them.
Never think critically.
Never think independently.
Bow down to the government.
Go off and kill if the government asks you to.
Give them all your money.
Let them run your life.
If you don't want your children indoctrinated in that kind of rotten stuff, bring them home.
Teach them yourself.
Well, and you're right.
And again, there are some public schools where there's good people in control.
So it's overall not completely out of control.
But in all the major cities, because I read the constant news and break it down, San Antonio
for three years now, they have Pentagon AI cameras in the bathrooms, in the hallways
and in the lunchrooms, quote, watching what the kids eat, and it even files how many calories
the AI knows.
That's a piece of fruit.
That's a piece of meat.
I mean, this is how high tech it is.
They're watching them.
They make them wear RFID.
And in California, even in Alabama and other areas, they're now giving inoculations without
parental consent.
That's a felony.
And so let me ask you this question, Lou Rockwell.
They counsel children, they have abortions, and you can't trust the public schools.
Yes, there are some good schoolteachers, of course.
Good principals, yes.
But they're targeted too.
They're not in control.
They're forced to go along with the federal curriculum.
What's being taught in all the public schools is damaging to your children, even if they
don't end up getting shot.
No, no, exactly.
But the issue is, I wanna ask you this, and I'm sure you know about this, but it went
up on infowars.com.
I haven't even played the clip yet.
We're gonna play it in a moment.
Let's get the Philadelphia mayor ready, please, and then we'll get to Bob Shafer and the rest
of it.
These are all some short clips, but they're important.
Philadelphia mayor declares economic warfare on gun retailers.
And they're saying, just like South Africa, we're gonna boycott you.
We're gonna shut you down.
We're gonna pull funding.
We're gonna have the police harass you.
They're literally like mafia, saying we're gonna put weight on you.
We're gonna lean on you.
And Chuck Schumer says he's calling stores, saying just don't sell it, or you're not gonna
like what happens.
And people say, well, that's not gonna happen.
I've talked to gun shop owners in Austin who were scared to go on air, where the ATF has
come in.
They're really rude to them.
They're mean.
I've been around them before at the gun show.
I've had ATF walk up and get my face like their god.
They look like criminals out of Central Casting.
And they're just coming in saying, yeah, get ready for some rule making.
You're gonna do what we tell you.
And as soon as we get these documents, I'm also talking to a gun shop in California cuz
they're telling them, there's gonna be new rules.
You're just not gonna sell these outside of law.
I mean, what do you do when the government goes full tyrant, full dictator?
Well, you mean as to what a poor gun store owner has to do?
Of course, they depend on having the federal firearms license, which itself was a horrendous
intervention like all the gun controls that were starting in 1934, in fact, the federal
government has been encroaching on gun rights.
So the government could take their livelihood in a second.
That by the way, is the position the government like to have us all.
They'd like you, Alex, to have a license and if you don't comply, they take your license.
So this is the way they're moving.
But I think, can you respond with violence when the ATF agents come into your store?
I don't think you can.
They're gonna murder you.
So I think- But can you believe we've gotten to the point?
Intellectually resist them.
I don't think the answer for a gun store owner is to resist physically, they'll kill you.
Exactly, but I don't think people understand, we're getting to the point now where they're
on the news.
I'm gonna play some clips of this, saying we're Nazis and that the president must wage
a war against gun owners like the presidents did before against Hitler.
And there's like this worship by the collectivist of Obama.
They're not just acting like they worship him.
They really get off on the power of the state.
They really get off on the idea that the president can do anything.
Well, government is always in competition with God.
They would like to displace God.
They look back to ancient Babylon or Egypt or whatever those regimes where the government
actually was God.
I mean, that's their ideal.
They don't like religion.
They don't like God.
That's why Obama made himself a religious figure at that new town, took over the parents'
grief and just tried to put all the attention on himself, on the alleged first responders,
of course, the no responders as usual, and onto the government and worship the government,
worship me as the God King.
Sure, of course, that's right.
The government would like to be God.
So they're always in competition.
They don't like religion.
That's the way they are.
In competition, we have to hate and fear the government.
The government is the worst.
The state is mankind's worst earthly enemy, always has been.
It's what tyrannizes us, taxes us, starts all these wars in cahoots, of course, with
big corporations.
And so we have to mentally toughen ourselves.
We have to educate ourselves.
We have to talk to others.
We have to withdraw our consent and refuse our consent and don't obey these people to
the extent we can safely get away with it.
They can't actually, because they are a minority and the oppressed of the vast majority, they
can't actually enforce this stuff on us if we refuse.
And again, why I think they've gone too far this time, I think the American people are
going to refuse if people like you and the rest of us keep counseling them about this
and about what the consequences are if we just go along and just salaam Obama.
So I actually think this is going to be a good development, as horrendous as all this
stuff is right now, as horrendous and talk about Obama accuses people like you of trying
to gin up fear.
That's all he does every day.
All the terrorists under the bed or Al-Qaeda's in Yemen or there's going to be a bombing,
there's going to be all these phony terrorist incidents here at home.
That's the government, the government lives by ginning up fear and therefore wanting people
to turn over their lives.
Think about this, our founding fathers and in history and common sense has shown fear
of big government.
That's what America is all about, keep it small, look at the prosperity.
Instead, they're like, there's people saying fear of the government and that the government
might want to do something bad.
No, we're just the biggest killers in history, trampling all your other rides, NDAA, Endo
Habeas Corpus, warrantless wiretapping, secret torture camps discovered.
Obama promised to never take our guns, but now we're lying because we say they want our
guns to oppress us.
I mean, it just is incredible that they're doing this.
Look at some of the mfoawards.com headlines.
Mayor predicts Waco-style standoff in response to Obama gun confiscation.
Gun permit forms question possible affiliation with anti-government organizations, that's
the new forms.
You see, the terrorists are those libertarians.
Mississippi governor vows to block Obama gun orders.
Philadelphia mayor declares economic warfare on gun retailers.
Just in a video, New York Democrats plan for gun confiscation.
There's video, I haven't even gotten to that.
Lou, let me play this clip of the Philadelphia mayor saying we're gonna go after the gun
shops, here it is.
Philadelphia was one of the first pension funds to divest from companies doing business
in South Africa.
We saw that movement go all across this country, in virtually every big city and other cities
in America, some states and other investment fund managers took action.
Cities, schools and other organizations can influence important societal change with their
investments.
Americans have economic power in how we choose to spend our money.
All right, let's stop right there.
It gets worse.
I must say, I think it's a great thing.
I hope government sells all its gun stocks.
It means that for those of us who wanna buy them, they'll be cheaper.
So why should government own stock anyway?
What the heck is the mayor of Philadelphia doing owning stock at the expense of the taxpayers?
That's an outrage.
Forget it, Mr. Mayor, but it's getting a reminder that government is a liar, is an oppressor,
and everything that comes out of their mouth is a lie or a threat.
You look at the bottom of your parking ticket there, threatening your life, put you in jail
and so forth.
This is government, it's thugs incorporated.
Don't compare it to the mafia.
They're far worse than the mafia.
You're right.
The mafia is not all bad.
I mean, they supply services people wanna have that are outlawed by the government.
They have an unfortunate means of enforcement being in the black market.
No, no, you're right.
They are historically better than the government.
But I mean, let's see, there's nothing worse.
Let's expand on this because you're absolutely right.
This is what Eisenhower warned about where at his time, 86% of all scientific funding
was government steered by DARPA.
Now it's over 92%, last time I checked, MIT put out a report last year bragging about
it, 92% directed by these kids.
And now they take our tax money, invest it, and now they're gonna use our money in the
market to try to wreck businesses that supply services we want.
I mean, these people are incredible.
Thanks for bringing this up because think of how much poorer we are as a society and
in terms of good inventions and new companies and so forth, that all this scientific and
engineering talent is taken out of the market producing goods and services for the people
and diverted into making bombs and poison gas and all kinds of weapons of mass destruction
and drones and just methods of killing people.
I mean, they're part of Murder Incorporated.
So the fact that these tens of maybe hundreds of thousands of smart engineers and scientists
are again taken out of the market where they could produce things and make our lives better
and themselves make a good living from it and put into this killing operation.
What an outrage.
What a disaster.
So the government doesn't only oppress us in terms of our rights and ideals, it makes
us much poorer.
We're much poorer because of the activities of the federal government.
All its wars, it's police state, it's spying, it's interventions, it's corporate state subsidization,
it's fascist economic system with the big banks and the big corporations.
It's taking the average Americans going like that to them.
I know an inventor, I know an engineer and inventor who's worth hundreds of millions
of dollars.
I'll just leave it at that.
And he talked about since the 70s, he's an old guy now, a lot of incredible inventions
that were made at big companies.
He was running as top technologist that they, the government would come like in Raiders
of the Lost Ark, take it under executive power.
Like you're not allowed to develop this and pay them and then go shelve it.
So, so they're also holding back our civilization.
That's right.
Alan, Alex, you're exactly right.
It is incredible.
Lou Rockwell.
Lourockwell.com is our guest.
Got a couple more clips with him in the next segment where they say that, you know, gun
owners are like Hitler.
We've got to defeat Hitler and more coming up.
Stay with us.
Thanks, gentlemen, for
We just can't sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse
and we discount them heavily at the end of each year.
We call them scratch and dent units,
but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty
and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait, they go fast.
Go to scratchanddentsolar.com,
that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made,
go to scratchanddentsolar.com,
that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
The adventure of a lifetime starts at goldandstagsafaris.com.
And the biggest stag deer in South America,
all gold metal quality,
all the action you can handle.
Land rovers, top rental guns with scopes,
all food, beverages, hunting guides,
ground transportation included and more,
all more affordable than you can imagine.
The adventure of a lifetime starts at goldandstagsafaris.com.
The big game hunting ranch, goldandstagsafaris.com.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger,
author of the bestselling book,
Cancer Step Outside the Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested
that carnivora be sent directly to the White House
at a time when only the president
could obtain this world-class healer.
Now, 27 years later,
carnivora capsules are used around the world
to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones
in this age of superbugs
with 17 naturally occurring compounds
that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only
without harming a single normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy,
now's your chance to literally wake up
your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders
that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-Venus-Fly or order from carnivora.com.
That's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A.com.
That's 1-866-836-8735,
1-866-Venus-Fly, or visit carnivora.com.
Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
We got two short segments left with Lou Rockwell,
and he and I are literally chomping at the bit,
you know, jumping over each other to fight for liberty
because it's so disgusting to watch mafia opportunists,
insider trading criminals use these little kids
and then sit there lecturing us
that we're bad in the pro-gun lobby.
It's never the Second Amendment.
It's never the individual.
It's that we're bad and we're Klan members.
We're murder enablers.
I'm going to play a Bob Shafer clip
where he talks about our presidents have defeated,
you know, Hitler and gotten the Civil Rights Act,
and we can defeat the gun lobby.
I mean, it's a whole new level of this.
I mean, is it just that I'm getting older and less,
you know, less where I can't put up with this anymore,
Lou Rockwell, or is it that it's getting worse?
You've been fighting these guys for four decades.
I mean, is it getting worse
or is it just that we're becoming more aware
of their disgusting activity?
Well, it's both.
They're getting worse and we're getting more outraged by it
and more dedicated to fighting it.
But my guess is nobody listening to this show
has ever bombed a party of children
collecting firewood in a rural area.
Obama has done that.
How many, he's actually killed a bunch of children,
and yet he's, personally,
he's authorized the drone strikes
that killed these children in a number of instances,
wedding parties and so forth.
So he's actually killed children
and he's lecturing us about killing children.
The hypocrisy has got a capital H
and it's all in neon letters.
Well, you're right.
And that's what's so incredible is that they just say,
oh, we bombed a wedding, killed 154 in one case.
And yeah, about 18 children died,
four or five others, you know, critically wounded.
But it's like, that's collateral damage, move forward.
But then, oh, these children, turn your guns in.
It's so fake.
It is fake, they couldn't care less.
But of course, as Rahm Emanuel says,
never let a good crisis go to waste.
And so they use any crisis to try to expand the government,
expand its income, expand its control,
and make us, they try to make us more obedient,
more kowtowing.
And again, I think if we do our job
and thousands and thousands of other people do their jobs,
this is not going to work this time.
They're not actually going to get away with it.
It's going to backfire.
It's already backfiring 10 million guns a month now
from up from 4 million.
Let's play a clip of Bob Shafer.
This is nothing, folks, compared to the longer thing
with Mika Brzezinski, where she goes,
I'm just ashamed to be an American right now.
I mean, what?
Because we have guns.
Well, get out and go to North Korea.
Here's a clip of Bob Shafer.
I want to get Lou Rockwell's response.
What happened in Newtown was probably
the worst day in this country's history since 9-11.
We found Osama bin Laden.
We tracked him down.
We changed the way that we dealt with that problem.
Surely, finding Osama bin Laden, surely
passing civil rights legislation,
as Lyndon Johnson was able to do, and before that,
surely defeating the Nazis was a much more formidable task
than taking on the gun lobby.
This is a turning point.
That's enough of that, idiot.
You're not even an idiot.
I mean, what a slimy little creature.
The government got in the way of beating Hitler
with all the bed-rigging and stealing.
It was my grandfather's and people that beat Hitler.
I mean, what do you say to that?
Well, Bob Shafer, of course, has gotten rich and powerful
off doing whatever the government told him to do.
So he's just like somebody on Nazi radio or Soviet radio
that he's just a shill.
There is one interesting thing, if you notice.
When he talks about the government, he says we.
So it's just a reminder of it's so important for us
to never say we when we mean the government.
The government is they.
It's a separate entity, lives off of us by force.
It's a parasitical entity that keeps a gun to our head,
speaking of guns.
I mean, everything the government does involves a gun.
You don't do what we say if you don't pay the taxes,
you don't pay this library bill or whatever.
Exactly.
We claim the right to kill you if you sufficiently
resist.
That's the government.
Do one more segment with us.
Five more minutes.
We've got to go to break.
Lourockwell.com.
You are listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
Sick of the globalist eugenicist control freaks
adding poison to your water and laughing as you get sick
and die?
Start purifying your water with Pro Pure.
My friends, I've done a lot of research.
And the best gravity filter out there, bar none,
is Pro Pure.
And it's available discounted at infowars.com.
Its filters are silver impregnated
to prevent bacterial growth.
There's no priming required.
It's NSF 42 certified.
Optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95%.
Easy to set up and use.
Doesn't require electricity.
Purify water from lakes, streams, ponds, and wells.
This filter system leaves in beneficial minerals,
which is key.
Save money by not buying bottled water
and avoid BPA that leaches from the plastic.
Pro Pure is the best gravity fed filter out there.
It's what my family uses.
Infowars.com already has the lowest price on Pro Pure.
But if you add the promo code WATER at checkout,
you get an additional 10% off at infowars.com.
You can also call to order 888-253-3139.
Waging war on corruption.
Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
OK, the whole clip is up on infowars.com.
It's also over at Newsbusters.
They're the ones that originally posted it.
And I can't play the whole thing.
Lou's got to go in five minutes.
And it's about a five minute clip.
They play the NRA ad.
First they go, this is pornography.
This is propaganda.
This is evil.
This discredits the NRA on the Morning Joe show.
And then they play the NRA going, hey, the government
people, they've got armed bodyguards.
Why don't we go to the NBA?
They've got armed bodyguards, why don't we?
And they take their glasses off and they go, he goes,
I can't believe this.
His poor children fight hard and had no choice.
And Mika goes, I'm just ashamed to be an American right now.
I'm ashamed.
And again, this is very effective.
That's why they go, this discredits.
Hoping we don't go down this line.
It is incredibly transparent.
I want to play part of this clip.
And again, you got to watch the whole thing.
It's unbelievable, the bad acting.
Again, they run from this.
Oh, don't say Israel has guns.
None of the citizens do over there.
You're a liar.
Of course, we pay to give the Israelis guns.
Again, because they're so scared of this thing that government
and bureaucrats and rich people have guns because they use class warfare.
The ultimate populism is the average person with a gun.
Let's play the clip and get Lou Rockwell's take.
Here it is.
That's a real ad.
Yeah, that's a real ad.
Political pornography.
That's one of the grossest things I've ever seen in my life.
It's like, oh my gosh, that's George Washington.
What's wrong with these people, Mika?
You have children that had no say in the decision
on whether their father was going to step forward.
Her father, by the way, writes books bragging about how he uplifted Paul Pothead.
The one for president, one of the most bone crushing.
Her father is an architect of mass murder.
The husband or wife can do to their family.
That woman is a pig.
And the second they make that decision, their children and their entire family
have targets on their backs.
Oh, my gosh, targets on their backs.
Oh, they want to hurt Obama's children.
No, you want our guns.
What's wrong with these people?
What's wrong?
I don't know what's wrong with a dead intern in your office.
On the anniversary of the Newtown murders and now putting out an ad
talking about the president's daughters?
They are out of step, out of the mainstream.
No, they pointed out he's got bodyguards and so does David Gregory.
And quite frankly, after seeing that, I think some of the people who run that thing
are sick.
I really do.
I think they are sick in the head.
And I'm serious.
I'm embarrassed right now.
I'm embarrassed for our country.
Well, get out of it and go to North Korea.
We're the only the state has guns.
Lou Rockwell, we got two minutes left.
You've got the floor.
Your take on that.
Well, obviously, Mika and Joe are themselves protected by armed bodyguards,
but they do feel, you know, they my guess is this really does upset them
because they don't like this sort of thing being made public.
That the power elite is, of course, got guns.
They all have carry permits.
I'm sure Mika and Joe have got carry permits.
Certainly, they've got armed bodyguards, just like they believe that the law is doesn't
apply to them.
It's only to be applied against us.
So this is the nature of their part.
They're part of the power elite or their spokesman for the power elite.
And of course, they're outraged that anybody would discuss their privileges and their special
rights and the fact that they can live differently than the rest of us.
So it's all the more important to point out not only that these people are doing bad things
politically, but they're they're personally ripping us off.
And they're all surrounded by guns.
Obama's surrounded by guns.
His children's school has got a bunch of armed guards.
And of course, they have armed guards all the time.
Bloomberg has got armed guards all around him.
And Obama just signed a bill giving himself and George W.
Bush armed guards for the rest of their lives 24 7.
So it's OK for them to have armed guards, but the people can't have armed guards.
So this is this is this is government.
It's a separate entity.
And it's an outrage to do anything but bow down and kiss their shoes.
I mean, that's that's what Mika is upset about.
And you're exactly right.
Her dad deliberately helped lure the Soviets into Afghanistan, causing many, many deaths.
He promoted mass murder in Vietnam and the coming of Pol Pot.
Pol Pot was put in his book and then the rest of the rest of them.
He brags.
He brags in his book.
I'm sure you know about how great Pol Pot did.
I mean, it's it's incredible.
You know, the U.S. government in the Vietnam War killed between four and six million people,
says the great military historian Martin Van Crevel.
Between four and six million people just in that one war.
They don't have their names on any wall in Washington.
So this is the government knee deep in blood,
killing people every day and lecturing us about the dangers of violence.
Well said, Lou Rockwell.
Thank you.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies
and starve patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital
and important preparedness items at Infowarshop.com.
These are items that I did research on that I personally use.
We've got the life straw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor hand crank generator to charge up key equipment
during power outages or out in the field.
Strategic relocation, third edition by Joel Skousen.
When disaster strikes by Matthew Stein.
Ferro safe used by Homeland Security
to protect yourself during any radiological event.
Hand crank shortwave AM FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at Infowarshop.com.
And your purchase makes our info war possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you?
Infowarsshop.com.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive?
From natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought
to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy.
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At eFoods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to
weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote,
almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storeable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or eFoodsDirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Now that we have moved into the winter season,
there is an increased need to support our immunity and health.
At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs
by providing a full selection of silver-based products.
Our most popular silver-based products are the 32-ounce Nano Silver Solutions.
Our 2-ounce Nano Silver Nasal Applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps.
Just released is our 100% natural silver gel.
Our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents
which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface.
But rather, we have formulated our silver gel
using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera
to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively.
Visit www.SilverLungs.com and click on our store page
to find what silver-based products are best for you.
That's www.SilverLungs.com
It's Alex Jones.
He's down there visiting friends in Austin, so we thought we'd have him come in.
And we are more and more every week going to have radio stations in focus.
In fact, radio station managers or owners that want to pop in for 15 minutes once a week or so,
we want to try to get our 140-plus affiliates, managers and owners,
you know, get their take on things
and also try to focus in on some of the things their stations are doing
because that is so, so incredibly important.
1530wckg.com is the website, 1530wckg.com.
And I do want to travel around to, especially our bigger stations, and give speeches.
And I've told the Dallas station I'm going to go up and do that.
I just have been so slammed with everything.
As everyone's seen, I barely have time to even see my family.
But we do want to do events with listeners as well
because it's important to get out there.
But the bare minimum I can do is promote our affiliates and some of the things they're doing.
Okay, I want to play just a few minutes of this.
And we're going to load the phones up for your take on what Obama did yesterday,
specifically on the Second Amendment and the all-out assault on our liberties.
And these mayors and people saying, we'll just shut down gun shows outside of law.
Austin tried to do it, but people beat it.
And where I live, this is happening.
And it was because of the backlash.
They had the votes to shut down the gun shows, even private ones, not on government property.
So they're really coming.
And it's because they know they're collapsing the economy.
And they know that they could end up losing control of the country.
But we are in the fight of the century.
We're in the fight of our lives.
The NRA has said that, I agree with them.
I said that before they said it.
This video is up on infowars.com.
And it's Obama Responds to Alex Jones.
It is in the featured news section.
It's the bottom story.
It is so important to click that featured story archive there at the bottom.
There's so many of the top stories scroll off the front page.
We've got to develop some other section like Drudge Report does,
where the really important stuff he keeps on top.
And then it's always changing in the middle and the bottom.
I just, it drives me crazy.
But the featured news archive is so important.
It's also red linked at the top, just breaking news.
That's the news feed.
Top Stories is the featured news archive.
Those two links are so important there on the top to be sure and go through that.
Let's play a few minutes of this 14-minute report.
I meant to play the whole thing today.
Maybe we'll play part of it tomorrow when Paul Watson is guest hosting the broadcast.
I think Mike Adams is gonna be a guest via Skype.
But the point is, and they got some big breaking news tomorrow.
Everybody's demanding we look at false flag at Newtown.
And it's Sandy.
Look, it's got all the signs of it.
It looks really bad, okay?
And I've just stayed out of it cuz I know they can crucify people with the information
if it's not 100% nailed down.
It's got all the earmarks.
We're gonna hear from some of the people that are saying this.
And it doesn't mean I agree with all of it.
There's a lot of signs.
I mean, we know they put them on the drugs.
We know we got the gun illegally.
We know they're blaming us for stuff we couldn't control.
We know they made them victim disarmament.
We know they made them victim disarmament zone.
But some of the other stuff, were the whole things a hoax?
No, they killed some real people there.
It does have the signs.
I mean, the Batman shooting in Aurora, I'll say that stage.
And even Larry Pratt has said it has all the marks.
I mean, they did Fast and Furious.
So they may have done this.
I mean, if they'll bomb a whole apartment building to get one, quote, terrorist and
kill 200 people, a bunch of them kids, of course they'll do this stuff.
But I don't know about Sandy Hook.
They're gonna look at that some tomorrow.
Watson is somewhat of a skeptic, but we're gonna look at it
cuz you're beating our doors down to do it.
That's all we've been doing is looking at it.
Believe me, that's all people are doing is it looks real bad.
But it's so over the top that I can't 100% prove it.
I mean, with 9-11, they were saying, we're gonna blow up building seven.
And then they blew it up.
And I have the news footage, and they call me a kook when I show CNN and BBC,
saying, get back, they're blowing it up.
And they go, what, are the cops involved?
I go, no, they told the cops get back, they're gonna blow it up, then told them shut up.
It was a CIA building, they blew it up.
I don't know why.
I talked to the head emergency manager who died a few weeks after he was on my show,
Barry Jennings.
I mean, this is scary, okay?
I'm not saying there aren't Muslim extremists.
I'm not saying, the point is there's criminal elements
in these mega banks, I mean, look how they're funding Al-Qaeda in Libya and Syria right now.
See, I'm already ranting.
Total free number to join us, 800-259-9231.
We'll take a few calls before our guest, 800-259-9231.
We probably wanna start getting the headset and everything ready
in the microphone for him coming in here.
That's always a good idea.
800-259-9231 to get some calls in today.
I'm tempted to do an hour of overdrive, but I'm here to meet with our guest after.
Maybe we'll just go into overdrive with the guests and take calls.
But I've also got to get a bunch of work done, a bunch of projects done.
That's why I'm taking off tomorrow.
A lot of times I take off now.
It's not even to take off, it's to get stuff done.
But part of this is actually taking off, be with family.
My children are growing up, I hardly even know them.
800-259-9231.
Let's go to part of the video.
And the whole thing's up on infowars.com.
Obama responds to Alex Jones and they are responding now.
Here it is.
There will be pundits and politicians and special interest lobbyists
publicly warning of a tyrannical all-out assault on liberty.
Alex Jones here for infowars.com with a special report.
Most people that watch television or even YouTube
know that last Monday I debated Piers Morgan and got in his face
and said, look, you're coming for our guns to enslave us.
America is becoming a police state tyranny.
Back off.
Hitler took the guns.
Stalin took the guns.
Mao took the guns.
Fidel Castro took the guns.
Hugo Chavez took the guns.
And I'm here to tell you, 1776 will commence again if you try to take our firearms.
Doesn't matter how many lemmings you get out there on the street
begging for them to have their guns taken.
We will not relinquish them.
Do you understand?
Two days later, Ron Paul came on my show, outgoing congressman, and he agreed.
He said, if they come to the guns, it's going to cause a civil war.
1776 part two.
Will you turn in your semi-autos?
Well, I might not even have anything to turn in for that purpose,
but I don't think the American people will.
I've always assumed that the line in the fan may well be drawn.
If the federal agent marches in unannounced and they say,
well, give me your gun and give me your gold.
I don't think that we'll do that.
You know, Tom, I think the American people will highly resent it and resist.
Now, as soon as I got off Piers Morgan, the White House released a press release
and said they were watching and responded to our petition, your petition,
to deport Piers Morgan for engaging in political subterfuge
and trying to overthrow our Bill of Rights and Constitution.
So we know they were watching.
It became the biggest story in the country
and the biggest story on Twitter for two days straight.
It's had like 15 million views online on YouTube alone.
So we know the White House is watching.
We also know that it's come out in Homeland Security documents
that myself and Matt Drudge have been basically investigated
and surveilled and are in secret documents concerning the TSA,
because we've been covering their out-of-control violations
of the Fourth Amendment and conditioning the public to basically be slaves.
But then today, I'm watching his speech while I'm live on the radio playing it.
And he talks about these pundits out there who just want to make money.
And they say that, you know, we're tyrants who want to enslave you.
This will be difficult.
There will be pundits and politicians and special interest lobbyists
publicly warning of a tyrannical all-out assault on liberty.
Not because that's true, but because they want to gin up fear
or higher ratings or revenue for themselves.
And behind the scenes, they'll do everything they can
to block any common-sense reform and make sure nothing changes whatsoever.
The only way we will be able to change is if their audience,
their constituents, their representatives,
their constituents, their membership says this time must be different.
It was incredible.
He was clearly going after pundits.
Talk radio host, chief among them myself.
And it's just really bizarre.
I mean, I've had the White House respond to this before
on their plans to shut down coal-powered plants and a few other issues.
But this is one of his big initiatives to disarm us.
And he said in the past he wanted to disarm us as a state senator.
Then as candidate Obama in 2008, he said,
I'll never try to take your guns.
That is a conspiracy theory.
And so now he's back with 23 executive orders and all the rest of it.
Dianne Feinstein's on record.
Mr. and Mrs. America, get ready, we're coming for your guns.
And now out of all these people out there, he's having to respond to me.
And why is that?
Because I tell it like it is and we have tens of millions of viewers and readers
and people that listen to the radio show.
It's over 15 million a week.
And their entire paper tiger facade corporate media,
the top shows on MSNBC have a million.
CNN, a half a million.
Piers Morgan's ratings doubled all week after I was on.
It's not that I'm something special, it's that people are sick
of these establishment mouthpieces reading off teleprompters.
So the good news is we're having an effect.
They're having to respond.
Now, again, you just saw that clip of the president where he's saying
these pundits and others, he's going after people implying we're crazy
to say that tyrants want our guns.
All of our founding fathers said that.
Federal court rulings have stated that.
We have a second amendment to protect ourselves from street thugs and government.
That's on record, but they're trying to act like that's crazy.
In closing, we know that Obama is deceptive.
We know he's lied about everything across the board.
I mean, he told poor people he wouldn't raise their taxes,
and that's who they targeted.
And I can make a firm pledge under my plan.
No family making less than $250,000 a year will see any form of tax increase.
Making less than $250,000 a year will see any form of tax increase,
not your income tax.
All right, we'll be back.
That's only five minutes of the 14 minute video.
It's powerful.
Obama responds to Alex Jones in full wars.com.
Get it out there.
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the best selling book,
Cancer Step Outside the Box.
I want you to know some very important information.
In 1985, President Ronald Reagan requested that Carnivora be sent directly to the White House
at a time when only the President could obtain its world-class healer.
Now, 27 years later, Carnivora capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy.
Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring
compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only without harming a single normal cell.
If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally wake up your critical immune cells
to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-VenusFly or order from Carnivora.com.
That's C-A-R-N-I-V-O-R-A dot com.
That's 1-866-836-8735.
1-866-VenusFly or visit Carnivora.com.
Protect your immune system.
It's the only one you've got.
We travel so much and having a fake TV.
Well, it gives added peace of mind.
Burglars look for houses that appear to be easy targets, but fake TV can fool even
professional burglars into thinking someone is home watching television.
As a recent widow living alone, it gives me great peace of mind to set my fake TV near a window
and know that passing motorists and pedestrians will think someone is home watching TV
when I'm actually away from home.
Fake TV easily plugs into any outlet just like a light on a timer.
And they're so easy to use.
You just plug them in and they're ready to go.
Plus, they're so affordable that we have one upstairs and downstairs.
Fake TV is only $34.95.
Order your fake TV by calling 877-5FAKETV or go to faketv.com.
That's 877-532-5388 or faketv.com.
Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
HempUSA.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine, and probiotics,
and we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder absolutely free.
Micro plant powder only at HempUSA.org.
Call 908-691-2608.
That's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder, seeds, and oil can do for you.
Only at HempUSA.org.
Calling this offer ends January 31st.
Hi there, my name is Frank Bates.
What I'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble.
I just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are, incompetent line crooks that
are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high.
Some have called this a conspiracy, others have called it a cover-up, and you will be
shocked to find out how deep the conspiracy goes.
My video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth and shows you the secret of how I beat them
and how you can beat them too.
Watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patriots have already seen
in the last three months.
Go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect
your home.
Go watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down.
Again, that's 123coverup.com.
Thank you, brother.
Wondering why is it going on?
Do you-
Well, we shouldn't be on the defensive.
They're trying to tell law abiding citizens who have gotten armed the last 20 years that
we're bad because violent crime with guns has dropped 49% FBI statistics gathered from
local communities.
Those are very accurate statistics because they're very diverse.
They're collated by a lot of different groups and double checked.
They're very upset that overall violent crime has dropped 21%.
And so they're telling us we killed kids.
I mean, if my neighbor came to my house and said, hey, you know, you kill kids.
I'd say, get off my porch, crazy man.
I mean, they're here telling us we're guilty.
So we've got to submit to them because he's up there high fiving the kids.
And I mean, it's just, it's unbelievable.
It's Jerry Springer level baloney.
And I appreciate your call, Jacob.
The reason they are doing this to answer your question is they're going to drop the economy.
The country's already fallen apart.
They're looting everything.
They're raising taxes.
They know less revenue is going to come in from that.
They want to bankrupt us.
They want to collectivize us.
They do this on purpose.
They're very bad people.
They told poor folks they were going to get a tax cut and they increase their taxes.
I mean, that's cold blooded even for dictators.
A lot of dictators want to be popular and really actually cut taxes to get more money
in so they can be the big shot.
These people are sicko eugenicist, okay?
They're not liberals, okay?
I'm a liberal.
I want you to live your life, be free, do what you want.
As long as you leave other people alone, libertarian.
They're not libertarians.
They're turds.
Let's go ahead and talk to Tom in Washington.
You're on the air.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
Hi, Alex.
Hey, buddy.
So far you've been doing a good job.
I just wanted to bring up something that came out on Monday, apparently, there was a bill
introduced that was originally called to amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1986 to allow
a credit against tax for surrendering to authority certain assault weapons.
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no.
I mean, I saw it.
They're trying to get all this stuff passed in the last few years.
Yeah, no, no.
I mean, we know their plan.
Yeah, that's it.
You're right.
They're trying the police.
That's why the cops are finally waking up because they're starting to get more and more
of them training in gun confiscation.
And the police, even if they're not moral, some of them, they know that is a very dangerous
job.
I mean, people are going to resist.
It's guaranteed.
Well, I just hope an article gets written up on this because it's pretty important.
It shows how the IRS is going to be used at least to kind of reimburse people for weapons
that are taken, whether they're voluntarily or not.
Yeah, wasn't that introduced like two years ago and again last year?
I mean, I'd forgotten about that, but I've never seen that like a year ago, right?
I don't know, but it was introduced this Monday.
It's HR 226.
HR, oh, I didn't know that.
226 and IRS for confiscated guns.
Holy Toledo.
I mean, you know what's amazing about why I should take more calls?
You guys always remind me of stuff I forgot about or things that I didn't know about.
HR 226 IRS bill, and that's the full bill number?
What's the title of the bill?
Well, they changed it here yesterday to support assault, firearms elimination and reduction
for our streets act.
So in other words, short for that is safer for our streets act.
Oh no, that's the safe act.
Okay, yeah.
So they put it in the safe act.
Oh wow.
No, the safe act is Obama's big omnibus nightmare like Obamacare.
Oh my goodness.
See, folks, everybody better be analyzing these bills right now.
Cuz I had heard about this, I guess they put it in by itself before, where they make you
turn your guns in, you get a tax deduction, and you're telling me it's been introduced
in the safe act.
Wow, what subsection is that?
I don't know, I just have a printout of information I tried to send you so I could get through
to you on air.
I found it on govcrack.us and I found it on thomas.look.gov.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that Library of Congress.
Okay, wow, okay, I'm gonna call Watson right now.
Or I can get a Don Salazar or one of my other writers on this.
This is big.
Anything else, sir?
January 14th.
Nope, that's it.
I mean, it's introduced January 14th, so that was Monday, HR 226.
Wow, yeah, there it is.
We just found it.
To amend Title 18 of the United States Code, provide a national standard in accordance
with non-residents of the state may carry concealed firearms in the state.
That's open to Congress.
I think that may be an old HR.
That's not the bill you're talking about, is it, sir?
I don't think so.
You got to make sure and get the 113th Congress.
Yeah, 113th Congress and you've got to get...
Okay, thank you.
We'll get it, sir.
Thank you.
We're on the march.
The empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support, and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Also call to order 888-253-3139.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
If that's the case, this is even worse than I thought, an IRS tax credit, because in the
Feinstein bill, she says, you gotta come in and re-register guns, and then we'll decide
if you can keep them, and we've got a forced buyback provision.
Well, in HR 226 of the 113th Congress in there to amend the Internal Revenue Code to allow
a credit against tax for surrendering to authority certain assault weapons.
Whoa, and that's for gun confiscation.
But they always first have it voluntary, and then you get the tax credit to create the
image of people turning their guns in.
They've done this in country after country.
I am very excited to have in studio the general manager of 1530 WCKG.
And Matt, it is so good to have you here with us.
Tell us a little bit about yourself.
Thank you for your hospitality.
The people here are wonderful.
Your staff has been amazing.
We just had some food.
You guys have been the greatest.
I've been all over.
I've talked to radio people.
I've talked to TV people.
I've been to their facilities.
They're not always the nicest folks in the world.
Everybody here is nice and a person first, and I think that's really important.
That's one of the reasons why I wanted to come here, because we have this radio station.
We put your show on, and 90% of the time, if you're a radio manager, you never meet
Rush, Hannity, Savage, those folks, and you don't ever know what's going on, and that's
why I came here.
I came here to meet you and to meet your staff and see what happens behind the scenes of
the Alex Jones Show and Info Wars, because we give a big part of our day to your show
Afternoon Drive.
How did you get into radio?
I was a kid with a dream out of high school.
I started working my way up, interned, did a lot of the things that a lot of the folks
around here are doing for you.
Ran and got coffee for a lot of the big shots, and it was music radio, and I saw where radio
was going, and I just worked my way up, and now I've gotten to the position to at least
be able to put on the things that are a little different than the average radio station,
the average media outlet, not the same old five shows from the same three companies.
And so on my station, we have Man Cal in the morning, and I spoke to him Monday and told
him I was coming to see you.
He gave me a call, and Alex Jones on In the Afternoon, and it really gives us unique information
to give to this audience in Chicago.
Well, I actually know just through strange things.
One guy who grew up around Rush Limbaugh and some other folks that know him pretty well,
he's actually a pretty nice guy and plays golf all day.
I mean, he's a real guy.
Some of these guys, Michael Savage is a real guy in a lot of ways.
He's pretty wild, I'm told.
But Man Cal, I've gotten to know him pretty well.
He's a really smart fellow.
He is, he is.
I've gone to church with him.
I've had Pico and Eaten Chips and Salsa with him, and we've spent some time together.
None of these places are in operation, though.
People don't realize.
None of these media places that you go to.
I recently did a whole junket a few months back.
My little boy was screened at the TSA.
And so I got calls from CNN, Inside Edition, Fox News.
My little boy was on your website.
He was the one in the wheelchair.
He was the one that got screened on.
Well, what a small world.
I was never even told that.
I didn't even know that.
So that happened.
He's five now.
That happened when he was three.
I was in a bad spot because we're going to Disney and we're going through the whole thing.
My wife's giving me the look like, don't blow this.
And I'm going, well, I can't.
I'm going to be honest with you.
I just didn't wrap which I'm the king of when I saw that video and how bummed out and scared
he looked because I don't know how my children are.
I mean, sometimes I have relatives come.
They haven't seen in a year.
My kids don't want to be next to them and one don't want to be hugged by them.
Imagine these weirdos and outfits in there.
Get away.
Get back.
Hold on.
That was you.
What a small world.
Yeah.
Well, sadly, I let it happen.
I let it happen because, you know, you go back in time and it's interesting to look
back now.
I let it happen.
And I put it online to share with my in-laws and my father.
They had never seen the video.
Monday morning, as soon as I put it on the Internet on our YouTube channel and shared
it with some friends and family, Fox, CNN, Inside Edition, you name it, and they all
wanted to talk about it.
And I thought, this is my chance.
This is my chance to make up for not having done anything about it except videotape it
when the thing happened.
And you know what?
I blew it.
I blew it because I didn't do what you did on Piers Morgan.
I didn't take the chance to go on and really break through and kind of, you know, wake
people up.
And I went on there and went on there with my suit and my tie on.
I stood in front of a green screen.
They put pictures of Chicago behind me and did their whole hocus pocus.
And then they used, you know, I was talking for 20 minutes.
They used a three second clip and they said, well, this is what it used to be like.
Now the TSA is better.
This is what it's like now.
And it was all steered government propaganda except Fox and friends who actually kind of
told the story a little bit.
But all of them were that way.
And so I wanted to see as a guy who runs, you know, I'm telling people how great our
station is and how great the hosts are.
And I'm standing behind the content.
I wanted to come and I wanted to see what's going on here because I saw what was going
on there.
And people don't know what they do.
Tell folks what they do.
And again, Matt Dubiel is here in studio.
He's a general manager at 1530wckg.com.
And every week we plug a couple of our affiliates.
We try to learn something about it, like if they have a podcast or they have an iPhone
app, we plug that.
Or if stations want me to cut liners for them, I'm trying to get all that done because I'm
running.
I'm not just a radio talk show host.
And since you're here now, you've gotten the tour.
I want you to tell me what you've seen.
But first, tell people what it's like behind the scenes at a big news operation.
I'll tell you and then get your take.
These are people on incredible power trips who think they're God.
They are people that are totally cold.
They are people that have a total agenda and know they're manipulating people.
Now, that's TV, that's CNN, that's MSNBC.
I mean, I've been there behind the scenes.
I've had Nightline here and we go to dinner with them.
They go, yeah, we know how it is, but you're on your side, we're on our side.
They're mercenaries.
Talk radio, though, has gotten the point in the economy where it's either a total standalone
station with a few guys overworked because of the economy.
And then trying to get real news out.
Or you've got some of the old line local news stations that still put out some real news.
But still, it's more real.
That's what's so great about talk radio is it brings in personalities.
I mean, Obama couldn't even read off a teleprompter the other day.
The whole thing was teleprompter.
I'm up here, there's no teleprompter here.
I mean, I'm here, this is what I think, this is what I do.
This is my passion.
And that's why I love talk radio.
And I'll tell you, talk radio people are not as arrogant.
I've met some of the biggest talk radio hosts in the country.
Usually they're like, don't tell anybody we're meeting because you're such a crazy
guy.
But that's fine.
The point is they're still real guys.
They actually know what I'm saying is true even if they won't go all the way.
Because they're reading all the same stuff.
They've lived a life.
That's what's so beautiful about talk radio is that it's not perfect, but it's long form.
It's real.
Look, you're not going to be good in talk radio if you're not real.
You're not going to be popular.
They got some guys that can wing it with a bunch of guests and cue cards and kind of
cobble through it and they sound great.
People don't want that in talk radio.
They want people that really, folks can connect.
Man, this guy's telling me what he really thinks.
This is a real person.
I'm ranting.
Go ahead.
No, it's intimate and you're 100% right.
And so I also did radio and I did radio in my hometown on WGN.
In fact, I did radio.
I'm calling into the radio show.
I'm doing the midday show on GN while I'm sitting in the CNN Bureau.
They have these bureaus when they don't have a full blown studio in your market in Chicago.
You go and they basically have a garage with a camera and a green screen.
And so I'm waiting for CNN to tape me and I'm doing an interview with WGN and the interview
with WGN was intimate and pure and the guy was coming after me.
He's a very liberal leaning talk show host that now does a show in Minnesota and a very
nice guy, but he was coming after me.
Oh, like I had something to gain.
And I said, well, listen, I'm not selling a book about the TSA.
I'm not trying to get you to do anything.
I'm just telling you what happened to me.
And the radio interview was so intimate and so pure.
He invited me to come down and do another segment.
The television interviews were the opposite.
And what they do is they bring you into a room.
I talked to the producer for 20 minutes from CNN.
She said that she was the producer.
She wasn't.
She was the person interviewing me.
They were taping it the whole time.
And I figured as much, but they had a green screen behind me.
So they put the fake skyline of Chicago behind you because they got to show the people that
are watching.
You can't be in Chicago.
If the skyline is not behind you, you couldn't possibly be in Chicago.
We got to show you Chicago behind him.
We got to play music underneath.
We've got to do this whole sort of facade to make them send the message we want.
And so the message from CNN was TSA used to be bad.
Now it's good.
We used to do this to kids, to elderly, so and so.
The rules changed today.
And now all hail the TSA.
That was the message.
And what I did, I brought somebody with me.
And he videotaped all the things behind the scenes.
And he videotaped all the things that I see here, except what I'm seeing here, the magazine
operation and the warehouse.
This is a full blown alternative media outlet to get info to the people.
Well, it's a military operation.
It's unbelievable.
We don't go around in uniforms and stuff, but we know we're about all there is against
the globalist and it's our responsibility.
And not that we're great either.
We're just saying God, we even had a prayer before the show and we don't usually do this,
but it's just coming.
We said, God, we're weak.
We don't do a perfect job.
Help us be strong because help us communicate because we understand.
That's why I work 18 hours a day most days now is because there's not any future if we
don't win this.
But I mean, you've seen the operation.
What else did you see?
I thought that it was going to be big.
I figured television.
I mean, now I know where Glenn Beck gets all of his ideas because I saw the television
studio.
I saw the set.
I see the radio area.
I was telling your guys and girls, you have such a great staff, positive, focused, driven.
They're all in sync.
They're all focused on what everything is happening here.
And I said, in radio, most broadcasting companies that have 10 stations in Chicago don't have
the tools and creativity that's at your disposal.
And every room, you see it from room to room.
You see the set for the TV for the nightly news.
You see the radio studios, the production facilities, the break room.
And these people that are working with you have these tools.
And I'm a little embarrassed, honestly, because I can't provide those tools to the people
that are working with me.
You've got the tool of your brain and the news articles and the analysis.
Exactly.
No, no, but we're just crawling.
We haven't even gotten to the walking stage yet because we're always busy fighting the
globalists.
But I can get somebody in here who is kind of a halfway libertarian but out of college
and doesn't even know if I'm for real.
Within six months, it's almost like they're in the video game, but it's real.
And the asteroids are coming in.
They start shooting at them.
People start going, whoa, look, this is real.
I mean, oh, my gosh, I thought you were making it up that they're got black kids in New York
killing them with pesticides and government tests.
I mean, here's the New York Daily News.
I never heard about this because what we do is I have a good memory, or at least I used
to.
We will take one article and go, OK, now we're going to show you 10 of the things that connect.
And that's what they hate.
They hate the connecting of the dots, not just Obama says he wants to get I don't want
to give you tyranny, but to me, OK, well, what's this, this, this and that?
That's something so-called reporters never do because they've been taught the last 50
years.
Don't have your own view.
Don't bring anything into it.
Only this report.
Well, that's not reporting.
That's regurgitating.
A real reporter is going in to find out what's behind it.
Muckraking.
That was the great journalism of 100 years ago.
And I found all these big meetings on record where Robert Barron said publicly, we got
to go buy up the media and shut this down.
Because used to it was 50000 Alex Jones is running around.
I mean, do you think the establishment like that?
No.
And what people don't realize is it's all a show.
And, you know, they treated me as though maybe I had something to sell because I was going
and saying, I wish I had protected my son.
I wish I hadn't had allowed that.
No, no, no.
That's how they put it back on you.
I mean, look, I'm like, yeah, you're right.
I'm selling something.
I sell what I believe in.
I'm selling freedom to fund myself.
I don't take the government line that many cases funding you.
They always use that thing.
Well, I mean, I'd say, hey, you're getting paid money.
Just sit here and see what you're doing.
They're getting paid big money.
They're getting paid six and seven figures as the news person.
In addition to that, they want more people to watch because the more people that watch,
the more the Pfizer can pay for their commercials.
The Prozac.
Exactly.
So they're trying to get ratings and more viewers to sell advertising.
And why are they doing that?
They're they're having me on to tell my story.
But I'm the bad guy because, you know, I'm looking back and I'm thinking, man, I let
that happen.
They know people are mad about TSA as well.
So they have you want to get people to listen and so they can then brainwash.
So they get.
So, oh, you're mad about this.
And then they try to knock you down while getting the audience.
And that's why I didn't let.
In fact, I wish I had been even meaner because I went in there, I had a chest cold and feel
good.
I was tired and he was so sniveling.
I just blew up at him.
And but then, you know, it turned out good because I think it really struck a chord.
Now you got state reps, congressmen and women, all these sheriffs coming out and saying
1776.
Yeah.
And listen, gangsters.
We know it's because you want to enslave us to the point of Obama's got to respond.
My only regret in the peers thing with you and CNN is that you didn't do more of the
British accent.
I would have really enjoyed just the back and forth of you doing the British voice with
him, because as I go back and I watch that stuff and we've got some of it on the radio
station website as well.
And it's just it really it really there's nothing he can say back.
There's no defense.
There's no retaliation.
There's no retort from him whatsoever.
By the way, I'm not just saying this because you've got us on one of our most important
stations.
You know, we're on Dallas, we're on outside San Diego, outside L.A., a bunch of other
big cities.
But the point is 50,000 watt.
We just got, you know, in places like what Fresno I mean, just new affiliates every week.
But you look like a TV anchorman and you sound awesome and you're a patriot.
I got Paul Watson sitting in and filling in tomorrow.
And Mike Adams is going to be guest hosting via Skype.
He's not going to be here.
But I mean, you're the type of guy that if you've got an ISDN line and or good Skype
for video, if you ever want to sit in, you know, once a month when I'm gone or got to
do stuff, I'd love to have you on the show.
I mean, I know you're busy running a radio station, you know, and that's God bless you
for saying that.
That's really nice of you.
This is my general manager suit.
And we all wear these costumes.
You know, we wear costumes when we go and I roller skate with my kids.
Now that I should wear the costume.
People take you more serious when you do.
You know, I did it specifically because I know that you dressed the way you did on on
CNN because you were just I don't you didn't need to put on airs.
You just needed to be you.
But that guy sitting next to you did.
He thought that he was better because he's and I wanted just to let people see that,
you know, this doesn't mean anything.
But guys, guys like this can sit next to and agree with some of the things that you're
saying without putting their costumes on.
I mean, I don't know what appears Morgan is honestly.
I know that he was on this reality show.
They introduced him to America.
Who gets a reality show when nobody in America knows you?
It doesn't happen.
He got fired for fake news.
He was at the top of a giant hacking operation.
I mean, they may indict him.
He literally came here to get away from all this.
He did.
But they introduced him into the media like he was God's dream America.
And then they put him on The Apprentice.
And you've seen The Apprentice.
Everybody on there is selling something or has something to promote.
And then all of a sudden, after The Apprentice, Piers got his CNN job and out was Larry King.
And finally, people sort of knew who he was.
But people don't know who this guy is.
Who gets a show on a big network like that when nobody knows who you are?
Fareed and Piers.
Fareed is part of the Bilderberg group.
These guys-
Fareed is really bad news.
But I mean, we've been in the media a long time.
You have to prove it.
Man, Kyle Muller is one of the best-
He's been on since he was 15.
Rush Limbaugh since he was 15.
They have a tough time.
They've had to work their way through the ranks.
These guys just all of a sudden, just a guy, Fareed?
Fareed's not good.
He's a plagiarist.
No, exactly.
I've been on air since 1995 and have had to crawl on my belly through just all sorts of
indignant things.
My first couple of years in radio, the general manager liked me, but he went to run the YMCA
and suddenly there were these new people that were like globalists.
And they're like, you scum, you're nobody.
We don't care if you have ratings and making us money.
You watch it or you're gone.
And I had to sit there and just to get the word out.
Okay, yes, sir.
I mean, all the groveling I've had to do just to even get here.
And it's not like, ooh, I'm a big shot.
It's cuz I wanted to get in the face of tyrants cuz nobody else was doing it.
Yeah, and you have to play their game when they're pulling the strings.
And if you don't, you get squashed unless you take matters into your own hands and build
your own thing.
Well, that's why I did this.
Plug the radio station.
Everybody in Chicago has got to tune in 1530wckg.com.
Yeah, 1530wckg.com.
It comes in around the airport in Chicago.
And our sponsor that made it possible in Chicago is royalvelvetnow.com.
They've been huge. They're from Austin.
And without them, I wouldn't be able to keep the lights on.
So thank you.
Plug them again.
Royalvelvetnow.com.
Great people, great supplement.
And we got to support the stuff to support Liberty.
If you ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not going to want to miss this exciting message.
Here's why.
Our solar generators provide life saving electrical power.
And unlike gas generators, solar generators run quietly,
emit no fumes and produce electricity from the sun.
So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now, here's the best part.
Every year, we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of each year.
We call them scratch and dead units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait.
They go fast.
Go to scratch indentsolar.com.
That's scratch indentsolar.com for the craziest offer we've ever made.
That's scratch indentsolar.com.
Digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of toxins that bears repeating.
Digestive health is the key to wellness and elimination of toxins.
And pro EM one daily probiotic cleanse is the key to digestive health.
Pro EM one is a powerful liquid probiotic,
strong enough to cleanse, gentle enough to use every day.
Pro EM one is dairy, wheat and soy free,
contains all natural and certified organic ingredients,
contains no preservatives or animal products,
supports a healthy digestive and immune system,
supports weight loss, improves absorption of food nutrients,
aids in controlling yeast infections, is never freeze dried,
and uses three groups of live viable beneficial microbes to cleanse and remove toxins.
Order pro EM one daily probiotic cleanse at teragonix.com, spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X.com,
teragonix.com, or call toll free 866-369-3678.
That's 866-369-3678.
Pro EM one, the raw probiotic.
Food storage, check.
Survival tools, check.
Weapons and water filters, check.
But what about a permanent source of cooking power that can run forever
without buying fuel or paying for maintenance?
Introducing Afterburner Stoves, home of the original,
patented Rocket Stove, the Kelly Kettle, and the Solo Stove.
Afterburner Stoves has what you need and now offers all GCN listeners
our complete preparedness package with the means to cook meals and sanitize water.
Whether you dig in or bug out, cook almost any meal with just a handful of sticks.
We already have the lowest online prices guaranteed,
but if you enter coupon code GCN at checkout, we'll knock off an additional 15%
and send you our amazing 6-hour solar rechargeable light bulb absolutely free.
All for only $249.
Visit afterburnerstoves.com or call 866-716-5214.
866-716-5214.
Afterburnerstoves.com.
Cook hot meals with just a handful of sticks.
Matt Dubiel is our guest and he's the general manager at 1530wckg.com
and it was his son in the wheelchair that they separated from him and scared him and all that.
I didn't even know that. I mean, what a small world.
And we're on his fine station at 1530wckg.com.
And don't you have like iPhone apps and stuff too or something?
Free app at 1530wckg.com. Free app.
You can get it in iTunes in the iPod store, the iTunes store.
It's an Android app too.
And, you know, it's, you can, all this stuff is at the website 1530wckg.com.
And I'll say this, stations that put true constitutional libertarian radio on.
You know, Glenn Beck's now the libertarian. Fine, I hope he actually becomes one
and doesn't support torture and secret arrest and all this.
People need to support libertarians and constitutionalists and need to support the stations,
the affiliates, the sponsors, sponsor these shows because that's how we're growing.
And because we've gone so far down this line, more people now realize, well,
Alex Jones was right to a great extent. We better put him on air to fight this.
And Matt was asking me during the break, he goes, are you planning on staying in the US?
Because he's obviously heard me talk about getting my family out.
When I say all this horrible stuff's happening,
every government wants to be a tyranny, as Lou Rockwell said.
This is just history, founding father stuff.
If you call it extremist, you have been brainwashed by the new socialist board.
This is what kept America great was keeping government small
and jealously guarding our liberties.
And I said, yes, I believe what I say is coming will happen if we don't fight back.
I mean, okay, so I'm here, I know how real this is, but they're not gonna get there.
I mean, it's always a fight, like that sheriff said in the first hour.
It's always a fight. It's not only evil people out there on the field.
Your comments on that?
Well, American people, everyday people, and I'm an everyday person, too.
I've just gotten to see behind some of the curtains,
and I know how the media business works. It doesn't make me better, just I know this.
And what I know is regular people, they need to take action.
They don't always know how to take action.
And listening to the program, going to infowars.com,
going to our radio station's website, those things are great.
But at the end of the day, the thing that makes it possible, the reason why
your show may not be on my station or somebody else's station is money,
because you gotta pay for it.
And the best way to make those things happen is for them to support
the advertisers that support these shows.
The globalists say they wanna make us poor, so nobody has money to protest them,
so they own everything.
People, you better support drugsreport.com, infowars.com, 1530wckg.com,
the radio station you're listening to right now.
Folks, support them, go support their sponsors, become a sponsor.
This is a war, and wars need money.
They absolutely do, and the reason why you are able to do the thing,
and there's nothing wrong with making money.
There is something wrong with making money at the expense of other people.
That's right, and we've taken the money and put it back in here.
And that's, you know what, media companies don't do this.
Huge broadcasting companies don't do and reinvest the way that you are.
And the reason why you can is because people will buy a video or a shirt,
or a water filter, or whatever it is.
They've gotta do that stuff within their means, be responsible.
Don't go crazy, but do it within your means, because if you do that,
and that's all you do, you will help.
You will help in some small way.
The next thing I'd recommend to people to do is forget about Obama versus,
what's his face, the Mormon guy.
Run for local office, help your local area, so that if things do get a little hinky,
there's somebody there that has a brain and can help things.
No, and that's happening, absolutely.
It is, and it's not easy.
And well-spoken folks, do your own YouTube videos to prove it.
Go to the local station and say, hey, I want to do one hour.
Just try me one, see how I do one time.
Put them on, pretty soon you might be doing the morning show.
Right.
I mean, so much of life is just getting your foot in the door.
Yes.
Get out there, use the web, stop putting weird pictures on Facebook
about something that doesn't matter.
Use it to share with people and connect with people.
Folks, you better get active or lose everything.
You act like sheep, you're going to get overrun.
We're going to do just a few more minutes of overdrive to talk to Alan
in Kentucky and a few others with our guests, stay with us, infowars.com.
Thank you for listening to GCN.
Visit GCNlive.com today.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans,
here is the Cal-Bend Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable
and coconut oils that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good
as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps
for all your cleaning needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Coast to Coast, direct from Austin.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Broadcasting Network.
All right, folks.
Yeah, see right there, you guys are running the refit over that.
I could tell I was here and do things, but that's good because we're into
overdrive and it's fun to have that type of stuff going on.
Let's jam in a few phone calls here.
Allen in Kentucky, you're on the air.
Go ahead.
Hey brother, how you doing?
Listen, of course this happens when we have a visitor.
Go ahead and kill it.
Well, what that is is you're running the rebroad.
You're running that the first five minutes of the show right now.
Just so you guys know, I'm just telling them I'm not actually getting on him here.
I'm telling him so they know what that is.
That's from when I played that clip of Aaron at the beginning of the show.
I'm going to go to 20 after now in overdrive.
I can't let the show in like this.
We had like a big IT crash yesterday.
This never happens, but how is it running our news station?
I know it's crazy, isn't it?
Your site, was Infowars down because of the traffic?
We thought it was traffic at first and a lot of it was traffic, but it was also a hack.
It's not even fair to say that I run a news organization.
I run an AM radio station, but we do not.
I mean, there's four people there at any given time.
That's the most amount.
You have an army of people.
In fact, back when I was an intern and Mancout came to town, we had a sports station across
the hall.
We used to call it a boyquarium because all the windows, you could see all the young interns
just buzzing around, making things happen.
And that's what it's like here for people that can't see.
There's just people everywhere doing stuff, all active all at once.
You come to our station and the morning show is fed in and the afternoon show is fed in
from Austin.
And so in between, we're doing what we can to support those shows, to get things up on
the web, and to get sponsors that get it.
It's one thing for Rush Limbaugh to get a bakery to sponsor that show.
It's not easy.
It's another thing for somebody to get a bakery in Main Street USA to sponsor a show that
is saying, hey, things are wrong.
It takes a special kind of advertiser to do that.
So-
Well, also what's happening is that people are intimidated by the system.
But I've actually noticed now that the tyranny is so out in the open, people are really starting
to actually go, you know what?
It's time to stand up against this.
Are you finding that?
It is, but it's almost like you got to put up a bat signal.
It's great to have a radio station.
The next thing that I want to do in Chicagoland is I want to get a couple of billboards in
really nice locations with either some of the artwork that you guys use promoting this
show, almost like a bat signal to kind of wake people up and go, hey, there's something
going on.
Check out this billboard.
Get a little conversation going about it in the market.
America's in trouble.
Find out why.
Exactly.
I want to turn America around.
It's on the radio now.
The Joker picture, some of that stuff even.
I mean, people, it takes things like that.
They're used to seeing regular advertisements.
They're used to seeing Subway or whatever it is.
I saw a billboard on my way to the airport to come see you, and it was blurry on purpose.
Blurry on purpose.
You can't read it.
And then as you get closer underneath, you say, I think it's time to get your eyes checked.
And it's like, wait a minute.
My eyes are fine.
You put up a billboard to make it look like my eyes are bad to then get my attention to
then get me to consider going to whatever vision center it is.
Well, that's like you might die of a heart attack.
Go get it checked right now.
They don't tell you that they're catching all these doctors putting stents in people
that don't need them.
Yeah.
So just like you guys take the things that they're doing and use them to get information.
I think that's the next thing that we need to do in Chicago is put up three or four billboards
in a few strategic places that really get people talking, shine the light on what's
going on.
And then what will happen is the guy that owns the bakery that will support this movement
and the show and the station, etc.
He'll find us and then we can talk and we can show him how great things.
Absolutely.
And again, the great part about live radio is one of our local affiliates, 590 AM.
They've got all that is an old fashioned big news thing with like 15 people in there.
You know, you'll hear him play the traffic wrong or somebody's live on air that doesn't
know it.
That's what makes it so real.
So, you know, the guys almost have a heart attack once a week when something screws up
and I'm like, hey, it's all right.
It's interesting.
And that's what makes it real.
Now, I promise to go to your call.
So be ready.
Allen in Kentucky.
We're going to go to you and we're going to go to everybody else that's holding with our
guests riding shotgun on the other site of this break.
It is 1530wckg.com, 1530wckg.com.
And wherever you are in the country, you can go get their free iPhone and Android app linked
on their site right now.
Stay with us.
Our operation as we move to the next level.
We need your help to spread the word like never before.
They wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness.
You are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination.
The war is here.
It's an info war.
The spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984.
You've come to expect winter specials from Herbal Healer Academy, and we're not going
to let you down.
Battle through cold and flu season with powerful natural and safe flu fighters.
Antivirals like olive leaf extract capsules and elderberry power.
Vitamin D3, 180 caps, only $9.
Beta glucans and an incredible immune system booster.
Our own four herb tea capsules and Respa 8, all specially priced during the winter sale
at herbalhealer.com.
Also exclusive homeopathic detoxes for lungs, kidneys, liver, whole body and lymph are on
sale.
Herbal Healer Academy offers correspondence courses to teach you how to handle your health
naturally.
And as always, new customers get a free 128 page catalog with your order.
Log on and save big now when you hit the winter specials at herbalhealer.com.
Healing the world with nature one person at a time since 1988.
Celebrating 25 years in service to the natural healthcare industry.
Who wants to be disease free, full of energy and vibrant health?
Two reasons you may feel constantly tired and run down could be that your body's acid
level is high and your pH level is low.
How does acid enter your body?
A cup of coffee, a sandwich, tap water, stress and cell phones.
Plus your own body produces acid on a regular basis.
Alkavision plasma pH drops alkalize the water you drink and raise your pH level.
They promote more oxygen in your system, higher energy potential and many other documented
health benefits.
And studies show viruses, bacteria and toxins cannot survive an alkaline high pH environment.
Alkavision plasma pH drops is the least expensive and the best pH level product you can buy.
Order Alkavision plasma pH drops for just $29.95 at alkavision.com, spelled A-L-K-A
vision.com or call 800-518-7615.
That's 800-518-7615.
Alkalize your body, supercharge your health with pH drops from alkavision.com.
Leading a frontal assault on the lies of the New World Order, it's Alex Jones on the GCN
Radio Network.
All right, Matt Dubiel is in studio.
He is the general manager of our Chicago affiliate.
And we're doing a few more segments here, taking your phone calls on this Thursday edition.
Ladies and gentlemen, we confirmed a bill has been introduced and added into the big
omnibus gun grab bill, saying that the IRS, the government will order all semi-autos turned
in.
They're now just saying all handguns on CNN, and that they will then give you a tax credit
for what they say it's worth.
I mean, whoa, the confiscation mechanism is now being put in.
I wanna go to some of your phone calls.
We've got the bill, Kurt Nemo's doing an article on it right now.
I mean, this is gonna be breaking news, cuz I went and looked, the gun sites don't even
have this information.
And we have confirmed it in the 113th Congress, introduced on Monday, and we're just learning
about it on Thursday from a caller.
Matt, where do you think all this is going?
It's scary because I think you're gonna have your insurance companies ask you if you have
a gun in the home.
You're gonna have doctors so and so, your pediatrician's gonna ask you if you have a
gun in the home.
And what happens when I got little kids, I got four little kids.
If somebody asked my kids a question, especially somebody in a position of authority, teacher,
doctor, somebody, they're honest children, they're going to answer.
And their answers could dictate the course of a path for that family that is very bad
or very good.
I mean, if this is creepy government, like in every other authoritarian system, sticking
its snout in there when they're the ones that disarm the schools and advertised it as giant
shooting zones.
I mean, this is absolutely totally off the charts, insane.
And they're announcing a Homeland Security program to demonize gun owners and harass
gun owners from 100 different angles.
This is what I've been saying on air was really set up for, because I had their manuals.
They're just unveiling what was already there, Matt.
If you don't have a gun in the house, you're marked to be a victim.
Like the newspaper display of all the houses that don't have guns.
If you have one, you're crazy.
So at some point, then you got to say, well, what do we say?
Do we have guns in the house?
Don't we have guns in the house?
Are people going to even talk about having guns anymore?
Are they going to be like the smokers that are in front of the office building that are
now-
No, no, that's what the Attorney General said.
He said, we have to make it look bad for the citizens to own guns.
And we have to literally brainwash them as the quote, but what you just said is key.
Think about this, folks.
Pinch yourselves.
The government is sitting here right now in everybody's face, attempting to tell you that
you're bad, you're dirty.
We're going to publish your name.
We're going to ask your kids questions.
This is outrageous.
Bullying is what we're seeing.
And the problem is we don't ask questions.
We don't ask questions about authority.
I took the little boy that was in the wheelchair video with the TSA, took him to the doctor.
We wanted to get a flu test just to see, we have to watch this.
And the first thing the doctor asked me was, did he get a flu shot?
And I said, no.
Well, why not?
Why not?
What do you mean why not?
Why did I know?
He just didn't.
Now let's talk about, does he have a fever?
Does he have this?
So when the doctors make me, and I started to sweat a little bit.
I don't know, did I do something wrong?
Am I going to?
So then what happens when they're asking, do you have a firearm in the house?
Do you have this?
No, no, no, they're making you a suspect for something that's not even illegal.
And listen, the flu shots have never been accurate for whatever the flu is.
They lower your immunity.
This is all a major government admissions.
The insert says it can kill you.
The insert says it can kill you, kill you.
But they go, hey, you're gonna take it or you're not taking your baby home.
Alex, four of us had the flu.
Four out of six of us had the flu three weeks ago.
We went to the doctor, they tested us, we had the flu.
We made it through in four days.
And you know what they said?
They said, well, you have flu A.
And I said, okay, well, what difference does it make?
They said, well, people that have been vaccinated typically have flu B.
And I went, oh, interesting.
So everybody that has been vaccinated has one kind of flu.
And everybody that hasn't been vaccinated is getting another kind of flu.
Well, let me put it to you this way.
Go ahead, sorry.
Well, there's various viruses out there.
There's thousands and thousands of flus.
How did they know which one to inoculate you for that year?
So and my point is, all four of us survived.
We made it through.
We had a fever.
We got sick for a few days.
We didn't send the kids to school.
We didn't go to the store.
We stayed away from people.
And then when it was over, we got back to our lives.
But see, that's that guilt thing that you're gonna make them sick.
Well, if they've had the vaccine, it says it can paralyze you and cause permanent narcolepsy,
Guillain-Barre.
I mean, this is all admitted.
And that's what's so frustrating to me is that it just gets worse and worse as a society.
Let's jam in some phone calls here.
Let's go ahead and talk to Alan in Kentucky.
Go ahead, Alan.
Yeah, Alex.
Yes, sir.
But you're quickly becoming the, well, you probably are the leader of the people that
woke up there in Kentucky for information.
I just wanted to bring something to your attention and your guests' attention.
I'd like to see people kick it around a little bit.
But there are some of us that are on psychotropic drugs.
You know, I've been on psychotropic drugs for 20 years.
I've had a gun that whole time.
I haven't shot anybody.
I haven't wanted a gun at anybody.
I haven't had a problem, which I'm proud that I didn't.
But if somebody doesn't step up and say, look, we've got to find a way to see whether these
people are competent or not, some kind of a real way of doing it, there's going to be
people that will not go that need help.
And there's going to be people that need help that will stop them.
And I just wanted to bring that to your attention.
Well, what's happening is we're already chemically imbalanced from all the additives in the food.
And so I'm not saying that out of the 60 million people on some type of psychotropic, it hasn't
actually helped somebody.
Most people can take LSD and not jump off cliffs, stab their wife.
But still, LSD is a very dangerous drug because some people are going to have a bad trip and
they're going to kill their neighbors.
And these are in that class.
And see, it's one thing if you maybe had a chemical issue and they put you on a drug
that actually helped you as an individual.
Different strokes for different folks.
I'm a libertarian.
You know, I say decriminalize all this stuff.
My issue is they put 67% of foster kids on psychotropics on average nationwide.
And the average is on seven drugs.
Now, these kids are bombed out of their brain.
And most of these mass shooters, it turns out the Batman guy was on five drugs that
they're now learning.
Five psychotropics.
Oh, this one made you crazy.
Let's put more, more, more, more.
So I'm not saying some people can drink whiskey and be nice.
Some people drink whiskey and they beat their wife.
Some people don't need to be drinking.
So what I'm saying is the drugs definitely are tied to the mass shootings.
Okay.
And so stop blaming my guns and inanimate object.
Start blaming high powered drugs on it.
Your comment on that?
Well, yeah, it's people have said before you take away the cars then.
Well, they could drive and they could have a problem.
They could stab it.
I mean, there's people that are on psychotropic drugs.
There's mothers.
Oh, these stories break my heart where the mother drives the car with the kids into the
lake.
We had that happen in Chicago a few years ago.
Or chops their arms off of the Mayclaver.
Always on it.
You can't, what are you going to do?
Take everything away.
Put everyone in a rubber room.
You can't do that.
What you can do is start at home.
Don't feed your kids garbage.
Don't drug your kids up and take care of a home court first and then worry about other
people.
And notice how exactly, notice how they're attacking the family right now.
The family is the only thing in church that is holding things together.
It's churches that go and bail people out of jail when they've been arrested for no
reason.
It's churches that were able with the whole Hurricane Sandy to hold things together.
FEMA said clothes for bad weather.
And it wasn't a joke.
I mean, it's families and churches.
And they're the things under attack.
What do all you yuppies think is going to happen when everything collapses?
That's the end of your martini parties.
It's the end of Sex and the City.
Because I know there's a lot of women out there.
I'm not blaming women.
A lot of women are awake who are like, oh, I don't want to hear negative.
Let's party.
Let's have fun.
The government's your friend.
No, it's not honey cake.
It's not your friend.
Comments on that.
My kids, I've fed them McDonald's.
We're human beings.
Every now and then we've given in and, oh, we go to McDonald's.
I've seen, I can tell when they eat that stuff.
Because later on, they're acting like they're not my kids.
No, no, we've been on the highway and fed a McDonald's and they act like demons that
day.
And I come home and I go, well, what do they have?
Oh, they have McDonald's.
Oh, so everyone else is putting that stuff in their kids all the time.
And then they go and they take them in and get them on ADHD meds or whatever.
So take a step back, lead your family.
And you're right, they want to tear up the family.
They don't want strong men leading their family.
And they don't want strong women with their strong men.
Who get that a strong family is a strong man.
They're teaching women a strong family is a man who's following you.
Yeah, an emasculated man that's carrying her purse and following her around.
You see it everywhere and these women are not happy.
Yeah, they're not.
And the kids aren't happy.
And because of that, folks are growing up with parents that are on the phone all the
time.
And we, you know what, we're human.
We try and put the iPhones away later and not text.
We're all guilty of it, but at least you can be conscious of it.
You got to because if you're not, then before you know it, it's going to spiral out of control.
Then you're going to be going, well, they should be doing this.
They should be doing that.
Well, wait a minute.
Let's get our home turf in order first.
Let's start at home.
Well, I'm really glad you came to visit me.
I'm impressed, man.
What a great general manager of our Chicago station.
Thank you, Alan.
We're not blaming anybody on psychotropics.
Okay, I just said you shouldn't put young devil worshipers on it because it's young
devil worshipers in every case on this that do it.
Let's talk to Josh in Wisconsin.
Josh, you're on the air.
Hi there, Mr. Jones.
Hey, buddy.
It's a pleasure to be on here with you.
I know you ain't got much time.
I had called you last month about a gun on, you know, Mr. Obama's thing and all this chaos,
but I called you last month about it.
And the day I got out of incarceration, I ended up, thank God, I ended up talking to
you that day.
And well, needless to say, I'm just hoping that I'd be able to get my gun back.
I don't know.
I've been pinpointed for the last month.
Yeah, what's happening is a lot of people are being arrested for petty things.
In some of these bills, they talk about we may just take your gun and never give it back
for no reason.
It's like these random investigations.
They're going to start persecuting gun owners like we're Al-Qaeda.
I appreciate your call, sir.
I don't actually remember your exact story.
Ladies and gentlemen, you need to visit the website 1530wckg.com.
It's got free iPhone apps where you can pick up all the great shows that are there, including
mine.
And we just appreciate you carrying the show live, Matt.
Very exciting.
We appreciate you doing the show.
You know, if you didn't do it, we'd have to choose from all the other garbage that's out
there.
That's the same, the same, the same right and left political Republican Democrat.
And it's nice to have an alternative to that.
Coming up next, we've got the Kentucky sheriff, the amazing patriot.
And he's warning of civil war.
If they try to take the guns, he's coming on.
And we've got the article up at info wars.com gun confiscation bill introduced in Congress.
IRS credit to citizens who allow government to confiscate their firearms.