big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
it's January 30th on this Wednesday edition 2013 we're gonna be live here
for the next three hours and we had him on last week and the hour went by very
quickly so I wanted to get him on for an hour today so you could question him Jim
Garo was talking about a quote retired military living legend saying that the
military brass that he knows has told them they're having a litmus test will
you fire on US citizens well the military's training for that and that's
in the news and General Boykin the former head of Special Forces he's been
talking about plans for a police state he's been talking about our government
giving al-qaeda terrorist weapons gee I wonder what general mr. Garo is talking
about but he has more to say today and he said the general not that we know
it's Boykin did not want to go public himself but wanted to go through Jim
Garo and I looked up Jim Garo he runs heavily in the big Christian circles as
general Boykin does the same circles but he will not reveal the source I'm smart
enough to know who it is and again people said well why are you revealing
it then you know 99% chance because the NSA and the government already knows I
don't live in a delusional world here ladies and gentlemen and I wasn't sworn
to secrecy I can just tell who it is so dr. James Garo PhD is gonna be joining
us and then always informative I want to get his take on the entire police state
and unconstitutional activities a constitutional advisor to the Congress
constitutional lawyer a top advisor policy advisor to Ron Paul when he was a
congressman and also running for president constitutional lawyer Bruce
fine will be joining us coming up and we will have open phones yet again first
time callers you know yesterday I said first time callers and a few of the
callers are like Alex it's good to talk to you again I called in last year no
this is first time callers your chance to call in with whatever issues you want
to raise questions comments news items that you want to talk about in fact I'll
just give the number out right now for first time callers it's 800-259-9231
800-259-9231 now obviously there is a lot of really
really wild news going on it just continues to confirm our worst concerns
about what's happening in the society I've got reports here where couple
facing 60 days in jail for rescuing injured baby deer the message is you
don't do anything you sit there in a catatonic state and go along with
whatever the system wants that report is up at info Wars calm I've got to do a
compilation of these in fact I'm going to go back and talk to my video crew
about this during the break and we've got to think of all the examples the
last month or two I mean there's got to be more than 20 where they say gun owners
are Nazis gun owners must be dealt with like Hitler was at CBS News gun owners
are the new clan got everyone in the south is just scum and has to be
overcome we're gonna get rid of the Constitution time to get rid of it the
founding fathers are bad now MSNBC as their people on saying quote Finney says
crazy crackers and again they want racial division in this country and I
saw that article out of
Newsweek last week piers pressure I've talked about so much where it says the
fight is not only brown and black against white now but our friends the
communist Chinese will help and so will piers Morgan it's globalism against the
evil southerners and Alex Jones let him prepare his flamethrower he's going down
I mean these are the revolutionaries and again they don't want people living in
peace they don't want it to be about ideas of liberty and freedom it's your
racist cuz you want to own guns and property you're like what's it have to
do with it shut up racist we're gonna arrest you for that Hello Kitty bubble
gun we're gonna we're gonna shut down Lego cuz Jabba the Hutt supposedly an
Arab and you're like that doesn't make sense
oh exactly what a Klansman would say it's purely designed at the lowest
common denominator and is amazing huge news on the economy we're gonna cover
first all this and more straight ahead looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves
how did we ever survive from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the
devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous
economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at e foods direct
we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New
York City wrote almost all of the grocery stores are closed but I managed
to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece it is
better to be prepared ten years too early than one day too late I can warn
you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what Alex has done call
eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or go to e foods direct.com slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term
storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four zero nine five six three
three or e foods direct.com slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct
introducing pro one all of your filtration in one system portable on the
go no more do you have two or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride
you have a system that cuts out the sodium fluoride and up to 95% of
hydrofluorosolic acid advanced manufacturing technology combines silver
impregnated white ceramic with new aqua medics advanced media for removal of
fluoride and other heavy metals all in one filter element it is the only one
that does it and out of the gates we have a discounted at 10% off with promo
code water this is the only system that in one unit helps reduce or remove
pesticides herbicides chloramines ammonia and chlorine hydrofluorosolic
acid the most common form of fluoride not covered by other fluoride filter
brands and sodium hexafluorosilicate get your pro pure with a new pro one
filters today at info war store comm or by calling 888-253-3139
millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other
illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a
revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution recent advances
in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily
to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help improve wound
healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while
powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as stress
staff pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology
has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions the
Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver comm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver comm and like us on Facebook
we are on the march the Empire is on the run Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
we are living on the edge of a designed controlled implosion they open three new
coal-powered plants a week in Communist China we are not allowed to open one new
one a year in fact just this week multiple coal-powered plants we covered
this on Monday were shut down more modern plants that are extremely clean
and a new one that had been built over the last five years has officially been
told they're not allowed to open on the Texas coast that was to supply Houston
Corpus Christi and surrounding areas we now have to buy our power from Mexico
that's on record who have completely dirty coal-burning plants but again
they're globalist owned you see everything is about shutting us down
with taxes and regulations and red tape so you can only operate in India and
China and Mexico and it doesn't build up those people it actually lowers their
standard of living on average as well don't look at it
China has a lower standard of living Mexico has a lower standard of living
India has a lower standard of living for the general population and they try to
cook those numbers but it's clear that's why just in 2011 something like 48,000
farmers committed suicide in India and it was some huge number last year as
well the official tallies aren't out yet statistics always come out six months to
a year later Mexico don't have to tell you about Mexico its economy just the
worst it's ever been close to 60,000 deaths the last five years this is the
incredible situation that the world is facing and the global ish use poverty as
a control mechanism let me just go over some of the headlines that we're going
to be covering today and then I'm gonna go to your calls because I'm shaking the
show up because I like taking your calls ahead of the two big guests we've got
joining us today I'll tell you about at the bottom of the hour they're also
linked up on the front page of info wars calm and prison planet calm if you want
to read more about the guests and some of the other issues we're gonna be
covering we've got more military and police drills terrorizing people first
it was Miami and then Houston with the army and now it's going on in Chicago
woman sues police over flash grenades SWAT raid to the wrong house police
state gone wild couple facing 60 days in jail for rescuing injured baby deer
Charlie Daniels says the nanny state politicos of this president will result
in chaos and bloodshed that's the plan who runs the world solid proof a core
group of wealthy elitist is pulling the strings I want to go over that article
later it's pretty powerful now you know you're no longer living in a free
country when I've got to get to that article because it just goes through is
just just the latest amazing trampling of Liberty
fluoridation ends in another major city after 51 years so some good news on that
front msnbc's Finney rips crazy crackers on the right for very hateful language
and again this is all about the so-called left who are really nothing
more than authoritarians absolutely going crazy and getting in everyone's
face and saying you're a racist you're bad if you don't accept higher taxes if
you don't turn your guns in if you don't take force inoculations they now call
racist for everything or everything and again it's a gang mentality and it's not
even so-called minorities who are really the majority in this country now who are
the ones pushing it it is the social engineers who want to divide Americans
against each other I mean I see Obama supporters walking around I talked to
them as I see their their button pins or their bumper stickers I talked to some
yesterday in a parking lot I was with my son and I said hey I see you have an
Obama sticker and they looked at me with a please look smiling the lady went
Alex Jones I went so you you feel like you're winning right now because you of
Obama she goes well he's better than Romney it was a older Hispanic lady with
her husband and I said really I mean he raised your payroll taxes he lied about
and he and he's very deceptive she's like ah whatever you're just mad you
lost and it's always the same thing it's like feeling like hey I won you know my
football team won or my guy won while he is a total globalist let me explain this
people they shut down over 200 power plants in the first four years of his
administration they're set to quote shut down massive numbers more some estimates
over a thousand that's about half of what we've got left now if you think the
economy is bad now and the GDP shrinking now folks you ain't seen nothing yet and
and let me tell you the social engineers it's all in agenda 21 it's all in the
big sociology papers that we covered you know last week with dr. Corsi in studio
there it is industry group 204 coal power plants to be closed in next five
years and what is that out of because that's a that's the environmental leader
and when did they come out with that report well that's September 20th 2012
they've already closed 200 plants what are they talking about I guess that's
just their their estimate on on what what more is going to be closed
regardless they've already shut down 200 they say they're shutting down 200 more
estimates I see as many as a thousand because see they say oh you can stay
open just do these things but then that bankrupts you which you've all seen the
clip or maybe you haven't in fact we're gonna play later the clip of the racist
stuff first but can you guys just pull up on YouTube the Obama we're gonna
bankrupt coal clip from five years ago thanks I don't want to just I'm getting
neurotic about I don't want to just say that and listeners go oh yeah right I
want to I want you to hear Obama saying you can have a coal-powered plant we're
gonna bankrupt you you know we've got enough clean burning coal that means
it's absolutely clean without even having all the expensive scrubbers to
run this country for over a hundred years and the studies they did in 1997
when Clinton laid off millions of acres in southern Utah and into one other
state of the only clean burning coal in the world other than a field in Mongolia
China that the Chinese developed and guess what the company that was given
the state rights to that a year before guess what happened to their stock in
the week after Clinton signed an executive order in 97 knocking it off
limits their stock doubled their stock doubled you see the real way the
globalist make money is they just shut down hundreds of plants not owned by
globalist and then that makes their profits go up because you've got to buy
it from them and they can gouge you I mean this is so elementary put rules on
where nobody can have a factory here in the u.s. it moves to China only globalist
insiders who made the deals when they put Mao into power and then officially
made the deal in 75 when Nixon went there 76 sent his minions earlier than
that
I guess Nixon went like 72 my point is is that even after that happened the
issue is ladies and gentlemen is that this is a full takeover and then they
can go and operate and and it's total and whenever Bush was in Republicans
were like I don't care if he tortures I don't care if there's secret arrest I
don't care what they do I'm feeling good my guys in and I'm like don't you
understand he's a globalist they had that same look of satisfaction shut up
liberal I'm like no no no he's a puppet it's an agenda we've got to get and now
the left is is I've got to say probably three times worse I mean they do not
care what Obama does they can he can raise their taxes he can go back on
promises and go after their guns he can do all of that and they don't care
because he's their guy and their winners through him reflected glory and it's the
creed of slaves it really gets to me we have the Obama cold video here he is in
2008 on television here it is so if somebody wants to build a coal-powered
plant they can it's just that it will bankrupt them because they're gonna be
charged a huge sum for all that greenhouse gas that's being emitted so
there you go
and so yeah they've shut 200 and something down they say they're gonna
shut down 200 more few months ago the numbers I've got is by some industry
analysts it's over a thousand because you won't be able to operate
and people like good I don't want those rich guys make money off coal folks and
then when I talk about this oh you must own coal stock or be with the coal
industry I've never gotten one red cent from anybody involved in any
petrochemicals coal distillates anything zero let me tell you though Austin is
the model of the Western world we get a UN awards were the official model city
of agenda 21 we even beat San Francisco out last year they'll look it up the
only other city was like one other Japanese cities our sister city they got
the Co award look it up
and our pro our our our power prices you can look this up have roughly doubled
the last four plus years and now they're set to double again we've got one power
plant that's very new just got upgraded about a decade ago the Fayetteville
plant one of the biggest in the state they're set to shut it down works
perfectly sitting right there city owns it incredibly valuable asset they want
it shut down
and the mayor said this is for the earth
a few months ago and again I've got all this news your calls I want to go to
first-time callers at 800 to 599 231 it just hurts it hurts to know this is
gonna absolutely put the brakes on the economy I mean I told you when when two
years ago when the carbon taxes that they're on corporations who don't get
waivers went in in California they went into a nose dive that's the plan when
they raise taxes they know what they're doing here's the news today Wall Street
Journal US economy unexpectedly contracts in fourth quarter as you get
the numbers months later unexpectedly mm-hmm it's like you walk up and shoot
somebody in the head and unexpectedly blood came out Rick Santelli responds to
negative GDP report we are now Europe and the plan Beijing air hasn't been
this bad since 54 yeah they have no air controls US debt headed towards 200% of
GDP even after fiscal cliff deal well that that's the hill it's designed to
bankrupt us and this is not an accident US banks and stress tests global shock
it's all by design we'll come back and cover all this and more looking back on
2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters like
Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships
brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost
everything at e foods direct we hear from customers every day that are
fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand after
Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the grocery stores are
closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my
sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too early than one
day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what
Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or
go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best
tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet
your life on e foods direct feeling like there are too many pressures and demands
on you losing sleep worrying about tests and schoolwork you can run the run
because your schedule is just too busy you may be under too much stress and it
may be affecting your mind get your mental edge back with new tropic mind
power from mind regard calm new tropic mind power is not a drug but a natural
supplement its 12 powerful ingredients are natural and non-gmo plus it's
gluten-free wheat free and formulated by Americans for Americans by an NSF
certified laboratory new tropic mind power is available at mind regard calm
spelled M I N D R e g a r d dot-com and comes with a 100% money-back guarantee
free your mind with new tropic mind power cognitive supplement from mind
regard calm mind regard clearly see tomorrow and yesterday today hemp usa
org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product
order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins minerals iodine and
probiotics and we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder absolutely free
micro plant powder only at hemp usa.org call nine oh eight six nine one two six
zero eight that's nine oh eight six nine one two six zero eight and see what our
powder seeds and oil can do for you only at hemp usa.org only this offer ends
January 31st hi this is Ted Anderson have you ever wondered why banks stock
workers investment advisors won't talk about gold IRAs they've been available
since 1986 yet the financial industry won't recognize the value of gold for
your retirement gold is outperform paper investments yet no word about IRAs if
you would like to have gold for your retirement call 800-686-2237 don't get
left behind by rising inflation and low returns call 800-686-2237 secure your
future and call 1-800-686-2237 is 2013 your year to achieve more more
vitality more health more well-being hi this is pastor Jenny for 25 years I
spent my life's work teaching others how to achieve more but in 2010 I got a
lesson of my own about RNA drops I learned that there are millions of gene
switches latent in every single cell of my body that are waiting for an
activator I learned by taking RNA drops I could begin to activate that power in
my cells and achieve the more that I desire I'd like to share what I
discovered with you and send you a free 30-day supply of RNA drops valued at 50
dollars for just the cost of shipping and handling go to RNA free sample calm
that's RNA free sample calm or call me toll-free at eight eight eight five
seven seven three seven oh three that's eight eight eight five seven seven three
seven oh three RNA free sample calm discover the more that's waiting for you
they came and took it all the way
the place is where
again if you're a new listener and you're like man this guy is like super
ultra negative if you go into the doctor and they say you've got a compound
fracture your bones sticking out of your leg we've got to do a surgery and fix
that it's not negative you're you're you're at the hospital you're getting
aid and the politicians are like we're gonna get you more welfare we're gonna
get you more food stamps and their own official policies that we've covered at
nauseum are to de-industrialize us under the treaty that we're signed on to
agenda 21 and the cover is it's for the environment
and it's so criminal that my own City Council is the model of this number four
years ago they are three and a half years ago they couldn't get the carbon
taxes ran through officially at the Copenhagen Denmark UN meeting because
all those documents were coming out how they were really planning to destroy
economies and carry out eugenics and how the third world had to have right at
double the cuts even the West did and now it was a death sentence not just a
death sentence for the economy death sentence for people and Schwarzenegger
said I will lead you can pull this up I will lead the move and a UN plan to
take over the cities and the states if the nation states will not do it they
were already doing that program it's called UN muneal ization standardized
tied to federal HUD funds in our country similar funds in Europe and other areas
and they come in with hey here's a 50 million dollars for your little town if
you agree to pass ordinances that all these people can't build on their
property you can only build on this property and then the maps are drawn
with a local boss all good old boys so they get to keep their land and the
globalists get to come in and do deals with them I mean it's very simple you
shut off power plants your power plants make more money
you shut off industry but only your industry gets to operate now you've got
a monopoly you shut off other people's real estate your real estate increases
in price that's how the globalist make their money and their control that's
their big secret and so as things shut down they say don't worry we got
welfare for you Oh food stamps went from 25 million to almost 50 million now
they're going to be a hundred million and it's the same in Europe the same all
over the world this is an exact program
and we've talked about it forever but people need to understand it's now gonna
get very very bad I'm gonna come back and go to your calls in a long segment
that's coming up but look at this US economy unexpectedly contracts in fourth
quarter I mean give me a break folks they knew that all the things they're
doing with contract the economy and wait until all the payroll taxes increasing
goes into place wait until all the thousands of major businesses who wrote
the health care law lower people down to 25 hours a week
instead of 40 so they get out of the Obamacare yeah it'll show an uptick in
employment because they're gonna count people working extra jobs as new jobs
but you're not gonna have as much money and it doesn't matter though you can
just get starry-eyed and go but I got Obama in he loves me he hates the rich
people US economy unexpectedly contracts in fourth quarter the average person's
getting hundreds of dollars more out of their paycheck every month taking out
other paychecks some estimates are as high as $200 for people making like
30,000 a year I mean this is just this is the difference between getting enough
groceries and then people love their servitude though because they've been
dumbed down and it just goes on here it just goes on here with the headlines US
debt headed towards 200% of GDP even after fiscal cliff deal think about that
think about how think about how crazy that is
the debt yearly will be 200% of GDP that means you're making let's say $50,000 a
year and your debt is $100,000 are you gonna be in a good position no you're
gonna be a debt slave who was put into this position and it makes me so angry
to now see our country's credit rating being devalued just like they've done to
European nations like Greece and when they're done that's where we're going to
be and they'll be up there promising more government more taxes to give to
people who had their factories and jobs shipped overseas and their jobs here
destroyed with red tape with the streets teeming with paramilitary police
checkpoints gun owners are terrorists and the government then hiring not just
putting the welfare folks on welfare now recruiting them as social workers spies
and enforcers we're on the march the Empire's on the run Alex Jones and the
GCN radio network the new year is a great time to take charge of your health
and wellness get serious and make a stand with supernatural silver this is a
breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver can be taken orally
every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds
supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective
for water purification it is the number one choice for thousands of people for
immune system support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency
preparedness go to supernatural silver calm today and give yourself and your
loved ones a fighting chance that's supernatural silver calm check out our
new low prices and like us on Facebook tyranny is here the grim future foretold
in 1984 has become reality it really says that the state is God the United
States is now recognized globally as one of the most impressive police states on
earth this film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA
camps now being expanded nationwide this documentary exposes how the continuity
of government program has established an all-powerful shadow state police state
four chronicles the sickening depth which our Republic has fallen prepare to
enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship body scammers sound cameras
citizen spies staged terror and cameras on every street corner it's only the
beginning of the New World Order's hellish plan the police state isn't
coming it's here secure your copy today info Wars calm or see it online in the
highest quality at prison planet TV looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves
how did we ever survive from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the
devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous
economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at e foods direct
we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's
storm by having a supply of food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New
York City wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed but I managed to get
my e foods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece it is better to
be prepared ten years too early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't
feed you heed the warnings and do what Alex has done call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three today or go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and
build your food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term
storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four zero nine five six three
three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct
we are on the march the Empire is on the run
Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
all right we're going to your phone calls again Alex Jones here if you just
joined us last night I listened to a little bit of the rebroadcast of the
show via the streams the audio streams at prison planet calm I clicked on them
and I was listening to my 15-minute rant towards the end of the third hour about
the plan to fully convert our society over to an automated technocratic
technocracy that's in the words of Zbigniew Brzezinski back in the 70s in
one of his books I read I forget all the titles of them I think was the
technotronic age point is is that they planned all this and you got to hand it
to them what they envisioned 30 40 50 years ago they did I mean I read stuff
Bertrand Russell wrote Nobel Prize winner was it for literature wrote in
the 30s and I mean it's what's happening now
take Aldous Huxley he wrote in 1932 brave new world and then of course he
gave a speech in 61 62 before he died at Berkeley it's online you can go listen
to it just type Aldous Huxley's Berkeley speech where he said this book is what I
believe would really happen being in the highest levels of scientific
intelligentsia growing up in London and of course his brother founded UNESCO at
the UN which is the real head of the UN
Julian Huxley and I cover it in the endgame it's just this is not my opinion
and I go back to this caller who was calling about how they're replacing
their Air Force base with drones in Arkansas and he just said yeah they're
getting rid of the I guess his army base it was a tens and he just hung up
sounding depressed and I realized if you just tune in and you hear all this you
need to think it's crazy because it is crazy but it's I'm not the one doing it
I know it sounds crazy reality is crazy truth is stranger than fiction has been
said a billion times
and I don't go over all this just to demoralize people I do it so people know
about it so that we're not compartmentalized and so we can see
through the wall next to us and then through the next wall and the next wall
and realize we're all in this together
man I don't care if you're some foolish cop running an illegal checkpoint I pull
up to and it's happened
I'm not even mad at you anymore
I'm mainly frustrated because I know the whole program basically I know how
you're programmed
I know you're compartmentalized and if I throw a fit and start yelling at you
it's because I'm sick of it
it'd be like if I was trying to get out of a burning house and I came to the
door and you're there going I'm not gonna let you out
I'm like do you see the fire and the smoke no I don't conspiracy theorist
I'm like listen all oh I just I don't even know what to say anymore
they're unplugging our power plants
they're shutting our entire industry down that they're writing books and laws
and white papers about it
they're evil they're evil
I want to stop them don't you care
people say what do we do and you know I guess that's the point we've reached is
there's so many criminals in so many positions of power and then so many yes
men and women beneath them
and I guess that's why they're so confident to now just be out in the open
with so much of this
I mean our country they are trying to hold us under the water and then
somebody else walks along says hey looks like you're trying to drown that person
oh no I'm trying to help get them out of the water sure looks like you're holding
their head under
and then I walk over and you'll pick up their notebook says here you plan to
drown them here today
you know you wrote you were going to oh no I'm not doing that you're and they're
holding them under
ok well I see you later Bob guess I'm have fun what you're doing
then later I walk back by there's a dead body floating
and I see Bob later he goes oh no he's not dead he's just relaxing
he's got gills
walk back by two days later there's buzzards over on the side of the water
eating the dead body
oh no he's not dead he's been liberated
I mean you have to be crazy to buy in to what these people are doing and
it just blows me away
to see them totally dismantling our entire country
and they're selling legalizing the illegal aliens as a way to fix the
economy
and again nothing against the people that are here I know most of these
people are hard-working smart folks who come from a great tyranny
the problem is when by the time they vote
over 90 percent in the polls and studies out there you look it up
vote for socialism because they see the government as their friend because it
told them they were their friend when they're really brought here to be brought
into the system inculcated and to get government services to be new dependents
and the illegals becoming citizens on average will vote to take our guns
and they will vote to collectivize and they will vote as long as they get a
goodie from the government
same thing with the domesticated American people
and conservatives and libertarians say well things will collapse
you're idiots they're not idiots the power structure is set up to consolidate
the control as we collapse and look I know I talk about this at nauseum but I
will not apologize for it
in closing and I'm going to your calls
so I'm listening to the show last night about 20 minutes of it or so just
dialing in on the iphone app singer of my smartphone laying in bed at 10 at
night or whatever it was
and I'm listening to the end of the third hour where I'm ranting about the
technocracy and I'm angry at myself because there's all these other points I
should have made and I could have if I was calm and I'm thinking about it all
but then I listen to the old guy calling in from Arkansas at the end of the call
signing just bummed out and that's not what I'm trying to do
I'm just trying to get you to become aware of what's going on
because here's the deal the arcade I'm pro technology
the problem is the architecture of the way technology is being rolled out
through federal and global regulations in concert with the dozen or so major
15 or so major technology companies is to put back door trojan horses in to
control and track everything we do
outside of law
and that's why there's new articles out about all the wireless devices and
computers have security flaws back doors no matter what company it is these are
built in
how that happened they're designed for the NSA for the police for Google to
break into your computer
Google got caught two years ago driving around with cars all over the world
hacking your computers but they weren't hacking them they had the keys
they are the NSA
and again they're building this whole technocracy to phase out humanity
we are obsolete and and and in the words of the global technocrats
well I say the tyrants are obsolete
and this is a huge power trip for them to be building this huge program to
have envisioned this huge program and their their response is you know if
you're reading this is in some of their books and white papers
you're thinking it's immoral
notice that no one's opposing us because they're dumb animals
and then they built a system to make people act like dumb animals from birth
the television the dumbing down the chemicals
it's so diabolical and it's all for full control and to put this into full
control
I mean again I talk about smart meters 10 years ago more than 10 years ago with
with engineers and people and I would have retired engineers on who who were
young who had left these companies
I mean while you heard the interviews warning about me text Mars
who's a engineer
Air Force officer scientist your best-selling books ever on robots
I guess the technology futurist for the Air Force before I became a space and
aeronautics professor at UT I read his book project lucid like in 95 when it
came out and it was about the smart meters and microchips and smart dust and
RFID and and and and then you know I later people a decade later breaking the
news
I mean this is all very old stuff and you warn people about this
and they go that's never going to happen you know my laptop isn't watching me and
I've had family years ago 10 years ago at my house they'd say why is your
laptop computer covered
why do you have a piece of tape over it into the built-in camera
when that when they were first starting to do that I'd say because they watch
you
oh yeah yeah they watch me now it's just all admitted you know it's public see
see how far we've come and I know I'm ranting I'll go to your calls
it's just that all this evil is already there
and denying it only gives it power and now that you're not in denial I don't
want you to get scared
I want you to get aggressive because we can educate people there can be a huge
turning against this a flipping
and it's starting to happen and people can just refuse this you know women are
standing up the smart meters because at an instinctive level they know it's
dangerous and bad and they know that all the new appliances dial into it and
they're wondering why every new appliance they buy has smart meter
wireless pickups in it and your TV does and your computer does and they admit
they're using it to track everything you do and even controlling your thermostat
and they're doing test women are sitting there in their houses watching the
thermostat change they call the power company and they go we're just doing
some tests but you gotta some tests to see if you go along with it
I mean it's so diabolical the government's watching you
they're molesting you at the airport they're controlling your your
thermostat
and folks this is just the beginning
show again the people at the other end of these computers are very bad
and their plan is to build an electronic present around you for your orderly
death and I know that sounds incredible but it's on record that they plan to do
this and I'm begging all of you to realize none of you are safe they're
already attacking you all
they're spraying stuff it's in the food it's in the water everybody's sick even
when they're taking vitamins and minerals to fight it
people like that are doing okay those that aren't are walking dead
the cancer rates are exploding this is real
let's go ahead and talk to DC in Ohio DC you're on the air
hey Alex how you doing today I'm doing all right brother
all right hey first-time caller and a first-time listener of the show
I'm an ex-navy during the first Gulf War when Papa Bush was even talking about
the New World Order at that time
I'm an ex-mortgage broker when the government was giving away loans to
everybody with bad credit so we all get in houses before the stock market crashed
and now a father of three
I'm a byproduct of the economic disaster of the middle class
I can't if I'm on food stamps I can't afford gas had to take public
transportation and now I'm just super concerned about everything that's going
on with the billions of dollars taken out of the Federal Reserve the army
tactics that are going on in Miami and in Houston and and it's got to stop we
gotta fight the fight
well I mean I just want all the bureaucrats everybody else to know I
mean they're all on a power trip just like the Obama supporters
it's so infantile it's like when you're three years old and you know you you
feel secure around your dad and your dad's talking to the neighbor and you're
standing there by your dad's leg and you you look over and lean your cheek up
against your dad and just oh my daddy's so tough my daddy's so strong
everybody who's had a father remembers that feeling that's the same feeling
government lovers get is they just look at you with this satisfied look
I see it in the cops beating up people with video cameras on the street or
going in people's houses without warrants the cops just have this
satisfied look
there's nothing you're gonna do I'm back and you know I got the people back at
the headquarters back in me and it's a satisfaction well I want you to know
something
the people running this are killing you and your family you dumb government
bureaucrats you're walking dead
they're eugenicist they're killing you I'm sorry go ahead
oh no I was going to say I've been pulled over so many times in the last
two years because of the scanners that they put on the police vehicles the
senior they could stand hundreds of license plates as they go down the
street and then anybody who has a warrant they pull over or anybody who
has priors they pull over you know ask you to a breathalyzer for for what you
know and again and again they act like it's not there when I pulled through the
border patrol checkpoint at alpine I went down to I'm gonna play this today
we've had it ready for a week but I've been so busy
I'll either air it today or or on the nightly news tonight but but the point
is I pulled the board patrol checkpoint they obviously know who I am they're all
looking I've been through there before other checkpoints and they're all about
to pull me over to the secondary search area where I always refuse and he goes
why are you videotaping me and I said you're videotaping me and they're like
no we're not and I'm like really what are all these video cameras and the guy
smiles it's like a mind game and and and yeah they've got these these these
robot cameras scanning us but you listen you know the secret of Patriots now
Patriots are now going to Mexico or buying Mexican cars with Mexican plates
I'm thinking about doing it I'm gonna be honest and you become God they don't
scan you they don't read you nothing I'm serious I'm thinking about changing my
name to like Juan Gonzalez and getting a Mexican car folks I'm sorry I'm not
joking I mean I may do this as an experiment legally change my name still
be Alex Jones in the air but legally have the name Juan Gonzalez and I'm
gonna get Mexican cars and I'm God I mean I will be God level at that point
until they fully bring the u.s. down and then close the trap on everybody they
brought in but what is that five ten years who knows I mean can you believe
that illegal aliens are God and I'm going I'm serious I've advised my crew
because you try to stay outside the system you know your license expires
you try to stay out of their grid they attack citizens with a savage hate but
let me tell you you get the Mexican plates God level they're now putting out
fake Mexican plates that people are using and the scanners don't touch him
and the cops leave you alone because they've been told that is that's there
to bring down the economy drive down the wages and vote to take the guns that's a
god leave a god alone well I declare myself an Olympian God I declare myself
Juan Gonzalez and I am God I mean I am God of the police now I can start
drinking and driving I can start not having insurance it's over what do you
think of that plan that's an awesome plan and I'm a lucky one because I can't
afford the smart TVs and the smart computers and all the smart technology
that's oh yeah ten years ago Mercedes had the thumb scanners get your car you
pay to be a slave sorry go ahead no that's all right and look what the
Superdome is named after Mercedes-Benz Superdome now and I'm concerned about
the Super Bowl coming up because both of those army drills were held one in
Houston eight ten leaves right to our interstate ten leads right to New
Orleans and the same with Miami are coming over from Florida the other road
coming right in there is is the interstate ten and they still have all
those housing there from Katrina Katrina that was a man-made disaster yeah hey
do you like the Juan Gonzalez show I love Casey I love and again all I gotta
do is Mexican cars everywhere I mean the parking lot out here has got a couple
one of the guys that has this big scientific company next door he's a white
guy I've talked to him he's not from Mexico got a brand new Mercedes Mexican
plates I'm telling you man it's the new diplomatic community I can become a god
yes this is Alex Jones with five good reasons you should consider buying a
solar power generator number one new climate legislation could easily double
or triple your electric bill number two our new energy czar wants to control how
much power your electric company allows you to have it's true total government
control of electricity in the name of smart grid technology is coming number
three in some areas of the country the power grid is dangerously overloaded and
now new socialist legislation is only compounding the problem number four
dangerous weather is always a threat to local grids every year thousands of
families lose their power from weather related on edges number five a solar
power generator provides powerful backup insurance and peace of mind folks I
really believe in the solar power generators offered by solution from
science one of my oldest sponsors you can get more information at www.my solar
backup calm that's my solar backup calm remember the government doesn't own the
Sun so go to my solar backup calm or call one eight seven seven three two
seven zero three six five time and time again you need to come here and help us
we need assistance please those we should be able to depend on let us down
federal and state and local officials saying help is on the way well the folks
here in Bell Harbor say show me don't depend on the government to save you
take action now so that you're prepared for the next disaster with my patriots
apply calm get the best prices on storable food non GMO seeds water
filtration devices home canning equipment survival and self-reliance
books and more at my patriots apply calm call eight six six two two nine zero nine
two seven we are hurting down here and we need immediately before it's time to
survive it's time to prepare my patriots apply calm my patriots apply calm it's
time for a home security quiz answer this what effective home security device
is smaller than a coffee cup fakes out burglars into thinking someone is home
at your house while you're away plugs into any wall outlet is recommended by
many police departments and sells for less than $35 yes it's fake TV this year
about one in every 50 u.s. homes will have a break-in with burglars usually
picking the easy target a dark house that looks like no one is home fake TV
is a small electronic security device that makes it look like someone is home
watching TV by simulating the light from a real TV it's like a lamp on a timer
but far more convincing and for only $34.95 fake TV could be the difference
between coming home to a secure house or one that's been ransacked go to fake TV
calm or call one eight seven seven five fake TV that's eight seven seven five
three two five three eight eight or go to fake TV calm fake TV the burglar
deterrent
I hurt myself today to see if I still feel I focus on the pain
the only thing that's real the needle tears the whole the old by the way if
you're not from Texas or a southwestern state we're not joking we're just
talking the illegals can drive without catalytic converters no inspections no
insurance no registration and are just left alone and I think that's good I
mean I I think citizens should have the book thrown at them and be stomped into
the ground I support the New World Order I think it's good they're shutting down
our power plants our GDP is contracting we're about to have double of the
deficit every year than money we even bring in hey what happened in Greece is
a great thing we're going there government loves us I think it's great
Obama raised taxes on poorest Americans and their payroll taxes and I think it's
good everybody's gonna get cut basically part-time now because he loves you in
the government cares about you so let's turn our guns in and trust them don't be
an extremist Thomas you're on the air you say you support Obama or did support
them you're a wlu v 1520 listener they're in Chicago go ahead Thomas good
morning Alex how's it going sir I'm pretty good I just realized I'm about to
become above the law I'm about to anyway sorry go ahead no no no problem I
definitely would listen to the one gun dollar so you know I think that'd be a
god-level radio show where we bow kind of like a Muslim out towards Mecca we
bow towards the radio we'd all be immune from all via all the speed traps and
traffic tickets and parking tickets yeah see we have a big ol fiesta why not
while I'm gonna go hey I think all Americans can do it that's the answer of
course I can't go to Mexico and be above the law or go there and have my kids
paid for with free free you know birth and stuff but but that's okay but but
would Mexico accept me though if I had fake ID to Mexico has consul matricula
Center set up to give fake IDs out would they accept my fake ID I don't think I
think they put me in a dirt-bottom jail but well that's not fair why can't I get
everything free down there well Alex the reason why I'm calling because I was a
former Obama supporter I even went to the inauguration 2008 now and now that
I look back at it was just years of disdain with President Bush and I didn't
know too much about the left-right paradigm at that point so kind of like
Chicago Bears versus Green Bay Packers I root for one team my children or my
teeth down and you know I can admit that to myself as a man that I got caught up
right in that trip now when you when you start to feel really be uh the onion
skin you start to get dig a little deeper you realize Democrat Republican
two sides of the same coin the good Jordan Maxwell quote and you know I was
doing a lot of awakening in the last six years with mostly with your help and
then you can't do it on your own the person might be individual like myself
needs to go reach for themselves do the research on their own and that's when
you truly start to become awakened because you feel like you're doing it
on your own you know just listen to what someone's dictating to that's when the
stuff really starts to open up and again we will say well are you saying vote for
Romney no no it's to realize it's all fixed at that level and then it's the
same globalist it's just the understanding that it's a scam and they
know where people are gonna wake up to that so they want to get everybody
dependent so even though you wake up you're still dependent on them so they
can run your life correct that's absolutely correct and like the
Democratic Party's like the biggest Ponzi's political Ponzi scheme because
you got all these 18 19 year olds coming out of high school they want you know
do-gooders just like I was a blue blood a blue-blooded liberal and then by time
you hit your 30s you figure it all out they don't need you anymore they got a
million more 18 year olds the big Democratic Ponzi scheme and I just want
to say to all the people that are smugging it up all you fake liberals out
there hugging each other the Beyonce's all the celebrities of the world up
there yucking it up with Obama you make me sick because there's nothing liberal
about you you're just control freaks fascist pigs and liberal closing that's
right god bless you great points
this is GCN the Genesis communications radio network if you want an American
company with American products made by Americans here is the Cal Ben soap
company Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years these
all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut
oils that are earth-friendly and safe see them on the web at five star soap
calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog buy the one to two months sample
package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what you're using now or save
big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs this
is an amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and you will love
the way real soap makes you feel see them on the web at five star soap calm
or call 800 340 7091 for a free catalog
waging war on corruption Alex Jones on the GCN radio network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
all right constitutional lawyer Bruce fine is gonna be joining us in the third
hour he just called us he's stuck in court fighting a constitutional law
issue on state secrets he will be on tomorrow that happens a lot of lawyers
and Congress people congressional advisor Ron Paul advisor Bruce fine we
are going to have a guest on that we had on last week because the time went so
quick so we can clear the phones out at that point and take calls people that
have questions for Jim Garrow who has that high-level military contact I quote
living legend from the military who says the military is training to confiscate
our firearms I mean that's the litmus test will you fire on Americans well
that's publicly in the training stuff now so but the fact that he's a
respectable guy and this individual wanted to conduit this info through him
he has some more info for us today as well and China in the New World Order
but right now let's go back to your calls rich in New Jersey you're on the
air thanks for holding and I welcome
with you since July of 2002 and I commend you for your great work sir you
better people just joined us I'm now Juan Gonzalez so I can be exempt from all
the taxes and regulations and drive and not be pulled over for no reason like a
US citizen four years away from the next inauguration of another selected
president of the United States but I think there's no time better than now to
call for a Patriot plan for presidential election reform I think you know we need
a comprehensive and look at the way elections are financed the whole primary
system and you've spoken to a lot of people over the years you probably have
a lot more ideas than I do you know what's your what's your take on it can
push off first off people need to have an awakening and realize whoever the
system pushes in the primaries from both big parties Republican and Democrat is
going to be a globalist when Goldman Sachs and JP Morgan were the biggest
contributors to both guys and most of Obama's policies were actually written
up by by Mitt Romney I mean giving a break Mitt Romney said some good things
but he was a globalist pawn and so we had to realize that we get 60% turnouts
for national elections on average about 8% local locals where you can still get
in and kind of block the federal system and do some good things we need to get
foreign money out of politics the globalist only want to pass campaign
finance to restrict the small individual on powering offshore globalist and we
need to get integrity in the vote again most of the country has fraudulent
electronic voting machines in place now and there's a lot of evidence I've had
top election fraud people on like Bev Harris clearly the fraud was against
Perry I mean I mean was against having one of those mental Romney Mitt Romney
I was thinking about Perry because he's saying let's give people back their
unspent tax money which is another fraud I'm gonna talk about later but all of
that is going on and really it's just realizing this system's bad news but but
but it's also hey don't shut down our power plants while China gets to have
three new ones a week hey don't let illegal aliens be above the law hey you
just point out the corruption and and say no to it and get good sheriff's
elected that won't enforce unconstitutional laws I mean I mean it's
a cornucopia of things but the biggest thing is recognizing fundamentally this
country's been usurped and taken over by foreign corporate interest in the spirit
of 1776 then Alex I would like to see you guys you know all the people all you
leaders in this movement you know draft a document to get this thing going that
we do need to get the money out of politics you know how about $500 per
American no more corporate financing of these campaigns and real real reform of
the primary like one or two one or two shots at it during the during the
election season we don't you know I'm in New Jersey Alex when the time came for
me to cast a vote in the primary the candidate was already selected our
illusion of democracy is a big joke here on the East Coast well you're right it's
an illusion almost everywhere now and the corruption is just getting more
intense but morally and culturally if we reject see their mainline Republicans
are saying we've accepted globalism we've accepted socialism Republicans
have to get with the program to get back in office well then they're just the
Democratic Party there's no point to even elect them but that itself is a
giant psyop hoax we'll be right back millions of people are going to get sick
this winter from colds flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect
yourself with supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum
antibacterial solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a
silver solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and
food poisoning and help improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe
enough to consume every day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of
many serious diseases such as stress death pneumonia colds flus and other
harmful pathogens this new technology has the ability to terminate entire
colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of
colloidal or ionic silver solutions the Science Digest Journal says silver is
our mightiest germ fighter it is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a
wonder of modern medicine go to supernatural silver calm today and use
the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off that's supernatural silver calm and like
us on Facebook the new year is a great time to take charge of your health and
wellness get serious and make a stand with supernatural silver this is a
breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver can be taken orally
every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds
supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective
for water purification it is the number one choice for thousands of people for
immune system support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency
preparedness go to supernatural silver calm today and give yourself and your
loved ones a fighting chance that's supernatural silver calm check out our
new low prices and like us on Facebook if you want an American company with
American products made by Americans here is the cow Ben soap company Alex and his
staff have used these pure soap products for years these all-natural soaps are
made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly
and safe see them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for
a free catalog buy the one to two months sample package and enjoy soaps that are
twice as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year
supply of soaps or all your cleaning needs this is an amazing deal you can
save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel
see them on the web at five star soap calm or call 800 340 7091 for a free
catalog
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones
well since he first joined us last week dr. James Garrow PhD his information has
gone viral just millions of views on YouTube of our interview and Gary
Francis interview with him on his news program so the good news is this
information is getting out to people so I wanted to getting back on also take
some phone calls as well again I'm Alex Jones your host if you just joined us
the question of course is Obama has posed the top brass as the litmus test
will you fire on US citizens that is the litmus test Obama is saying to the top
brass will you fire on US citizens and again we already have this in the new
army training manual from 2010 that I'll go over the numbers for so you can pull
it up at army.mil you've already seen the drills out there where the military
practice is shooting large crowds of Americans that's going on in the news
almost every day now the urban warfare training you saw the gun confiscation in
Katrina you saw ABC News where they said yeah if you don't turn them in we shoot
an American and the police chief says all the guns will be taken no one will
be allowed to be armed and they're they're they're they're training the
military to engage us under brigade homeland I mean that was in the Army
Times three and a half years ago I've had colonels on from the army admitting
you know they were doing gun confiscation drills in Arcadia Iowa that
they now run army checkpoints in California Tennessee but a top retired
general quote living military legend and there's been another military legend
wink-wink general Boykin former head of Special Forces has come out and said our
government's arming al-qaeda in Libya and Syria we're going into a police
state our country's in deep trouble he's also in the film behold a pale horse
that we sell with Charlie Daniels as the host of at info war store.com that's a
side issue but general Boykin is in that I'm guessing it's general Boykin our
guests will not say that's who told him this but this is a credible guy that's
why we have dr. Garrow back on but I wanted him to recap go over the basics
of the gear up towards despotism I mean who can deny that this is really out in
the open now with our guest and and now he can also make some other points that
he didn't get to last week and some new information and of course he also runs
pink pagoda girls.com he's been over in China since 1968 with English language
schools and some of his staff the government was trying to forcibly abort
their kids also kill already born babies and so he started a group in 2000 that
saved over 45,000 Chinese girls and I could certainly vouch for him because
even a member of my crew has adopted Chinese girls out of China and is well
aware of the pioneering work of pink pagoda girls the group he founded
because they they'll die if they're not adopted you understand they kill them
they kill them so just amazing and of course there's more people wanting to
adopt kids every year in this country than there are even abortions but they
never tell the young women at Planned Parenthood you know there's Christian
groups that will pay for your whole pregnancy pay for your medical bill and
depending on the group give you 20 to 50 thousand dollars after after you have
the baby for not killing it you see those billboards up everywhere abortion
you know need alternatives that's some of the Christian groups and then they
even try to get you a job afterwards Wow so you want to go have a have a have an
abortion that doubles your chances of cervical and uterine cancer going off
the left field as always do now major studies have shown per abortion or get
paid to have the baby and not have it killed oh but Planned Parenthood won't
tell you that because their goal is to kill their eugenicist Margaret Sanger
they want to quote kill the black weeds they were founded for that but moved on
to everybody else of course but oh doesn't matter they get somebody up on
MSNBC saying we gotta deal with the white crackers she gets some street
lingo going out there cuz you know you talk about getting the white crackers
that's cool that's liberal but oh hey let's not chop up the babies shut up
racist okay let's go to our guest pink pagoda girls a founder dr. James Garrow
PhD doc recap the Intel you've got the other info tell people what we're facing
here you've got the floor well as you know and I stated last week the
difficulty is that this is something more and more true either I was a little
doubt for myself I have to be honest with you but more and more of the
evidence coming forward since you know since we were putting it out to the
public and of course you've known this for quite a while but it's just so
scary about what is happening and as you see them marched down the roadway to
despotism it is to me it's just mind-boggling but you know this army
senior army officer retired who came forward and asked me if I would help him
put the word out he was quite frightful of what was going on in America where
things were going in terms of the fact that the military we're now going to be
asked to take action against the American public and for doing what for
rioting for no nothing like that it had to do with a scenario of would you in
fact fire on people who had been in possession of arms had refused to allow
confiscation of those arms or to lay down those arms which was it you know
the right to hold under the Constitution the Second Amendment you're well aware
of that but now would you as an officer order your troops to fire if the
commander-in-chief you know who you have taken an oath to actually obey as
commander would you obey that order so many have said no I think it's going to
come out fairly soon that many people are saying no I've had so many phone
calls Alex I gotta tell you between interviews and all of that I had so
many people phoning me current military and retired military saying thank you
thank you for bringing it up well we just want to thank you now listen have
you talked to the retired quote military legend since he wanted you to warn
people about this because again I can separately figure out who it is myself I
can separately you know research the information to know that it's already
being set up I mean it's publicly being set up have you talked to that
individual anymore yes I have yes I have it was a very short conversation he
called me and just said thank you and that was the extent of it so if you're
if you're going into did you ask him to come forward again no I didn't get that
chance in fact all he wanted to do was say thank you that's it so he just
wanted you to get the info out and he thinks he's going to be safe having you
do it instead of him coming out yes yeah very much he believes that what he's
done is quite brilliant from from what I know of this person and and what we
talked about how it was going to come out and why me and everything and to me
it seemed to be not not as if he was a coward in any way and people have said
that you know and sent me messages you know that oh he has to stand up he has
to come forward actually no he doesn't watch Alex where things go in the in the
near future and I think you'll appreciate that this man was right on
with what he did let's face it he was not a dull-witted somebody who is
unable to who are unable to strategize quite a brilliant map sure now expanding
on that I never implied he was a coward I have seen some people say that but
after you were on last week I began to think actually it makes sense because
Smedley Butler when he exposed the Nazi fascist plan working with the bushes
Prescott Bush at the time but he was just mid-level in it and a bunch of
other people to have a fascist takeover in the 30s he went to Congress first and
then that's how they rolled it up and I've been noticing now that did you see
former Senator Hagel say to Obama you can't trust the military you're not in
control of the Pentagon they're not doing what we say because I know the
military over and over again has actually stopped some of these wars a
lot of people say would lead to World War three possibly I mean does that tie
into what you're saying we should look for in the future well I was certainly
people are getting it aren't they if hey if this guy says you know this to Obama
by way of warning it's a good warning and you know the military folks got so
many of the rank and file phone me up and say you know what we would never
turn our guns you can't miss the office who said that to us we turn them on them
and that's the message that's kind of going out there Obama does not have the
support of the military at all he thinks he can command and control but the man's
living in la la land well he certainly is dr. James Garrow PhD joins us from
Toronto Canada right now run some of the largest English-speaking at training
schools in China and it's a 45,000 plus little Chinese girls that would have
been killed or used in medical experiments I'm not kidding it's very
macabre I want to talk some about how they kill those little girls before you
leave us so we can you know put a human face on this and not just have it be a
statistic but I've had countless military in fact I could I could scrub
the phone calls right now but we're gonna go to them later I'm so I'm not
going to and open the phones but we'll do that after we take some of these
calls and say military call in are you being trained to take our guns are you
being trained for for killing Americans and they'll call in and say yes indeed
we are but again I have the army training manual in fact I'll pull it up
here in a moment for radio and TV of yours I mean this is the new mission and
and we're hearing now we got to have troops on the streets and all of this
but I only see that serving to wake up the police and military oh amen that's
exactly what's happening that's the result there's been a total
miscalculation on the part of Obama and crew who don't have a military mindset
they don't understand what loyalty really is and the fact that the military
a lawyer to the American people they really are they believe in the role of
being a protector to the American public and they've torn an oath of Constitution
but listen who's behind the Constitution it is we the people nothing short of
that that's it so bottom line these people are understanding it there's a
huge as I said again I'm gonna say it it's a huge miscalculation and I mean
if if there were people who had bad intent looking to control through the
military the country this would be certainly a way to march toward that
but mr. Obama has thought that he would be the one that would be able to have
the loyalty of the troops and I'm sorry the troops are not stupid I want to find
out of the retired military legend the general talked about false flags is he
concerned from his sources about the globalist staging something show they
would buy this looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves how did we ever survive
from natural disasters like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought
to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to
those that have lost everything at e foods direct we hear from customers
every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm by having a supply of
food on hand after Hurricane Sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the
grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be
able to help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too
early than one day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the
warnings and do what Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six
three three today or go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your
food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term storable food on the
planet call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three or e foods direct
comm slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct don't throw away
leftovers instead throw all your leftovers vegetable peels eggshells
coffee grounds pizza crusts and more into the Bokashi if you love to garden
and compost but don't like the hassle of turning a compost bin or this smell then
check out the e and Bokashi food waste recycling system from tereganics finally
a way to recycle all your food and plant waste safely and effectively and stop
using fertilizers the e and Bokashi food waste recycling system rather than
decomposition the Bokashi system uses fermentation to break down waste so it
takes less time to create nutrient-dense humus for crops or gardens with no
turning and no obnoxious odors to learn more and order your Bokashi online
visit tereganics comm and click on the orange button that's tereganics comm
spelled t-e-r-a-g-a-n-i-x.com or call eight six six three six nine three six
seven eight that's eight six six three six nine three six seven eight recycle
all your food wastes in about six weeks with the Bokashi food waste recycling
system from tereganics comm tereganics life's getting better do you know how
much the dollar has lost in its value against other currencies in the last 90
days ever think about how inflation will change your life your savings your
retirement plans remember inflation in Zimbabwe Argentina the Weimar Republic
put another way who cares if your investments go up 10% but you lose 40%
of your purchasing power gold is the only monetary asset is no one else's
liability gold still buys the same amount of stuff it always did gold does
not require trust in a third party you can possess it in your hand you can take
it with you gold is real money gold is honest money my name is Daniel Larson
from Midas resources to find out how you can protect your savings and roll over
your IRA funds into precious metals accounts please call me at eight hundred
six eight six two two three seven extension one three four that's eight
hundred six eight six two two three seven extension one three four eight
hundred six eight six two two three seven extension one three four is this
the year you finally get serious about your family's drinking water if so keep
listening for a special offer from big Berkey water filters did you know that
over 60% of municipal water is fluoridated Berkey water filters
distinguish themselves from many other filtration systems with the capability
to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine fluoride arsenic and
disinfection byproducts from municipal water via the black Berkey and PF line
of filters then there's affordability it only 1.7 cents per gallon
Berkey water filters purify treated and untreated water even stagnant pond water
stop and think how much money you could save by simply reducing buying bottled
water and using water filtered by your Berkey water filter no need to be
constantly replacing expensive filters with a Berkey a single set of filters
can last for five to ten years choose the best size Berkey for your needs at
big Berkey water filters calm and right now all GCN listeners get 5% off all
ceramic filter systems just call one eight seven seven ninety nine Berkey
that's eight seven seven ninety nine B er ke y or visit big Berkey water
filters calm free shipping on every order over $50 big Berkey water filters
for the love of clean water stand tall and strong
we're going to your calls coming up the next segment dr. James Garrow PhD is our
guest and he's relaying whistleblower information to us which is obvious with
all the movements out in front of us and the training that's going on continuing
with talking to the military people that have been contacting you and other
information what else do you think is important to relay to people that we
didn't talk about last week or that people aren't aware of this week because
you know these reports that you're putting out that I'm putting out are
again really getting picked up online people are paying attention to it and
people are really concerned you know there's not much we can do about corrupt
politicians now or globalist selling us out but look at all the bullets sold out
in almost every place in the u.s. look at 10 million guns a month being sold
previous record 5 million last year I mean the system better know people don't
trust them anymore yes absolutely and I'm glad you've given me the opportunity
to do this there is a warning a real caution when people ask me you know what
is it that we can do to safeguard ourselves well I'm going to warn you
right now let me read something too and this is coming from the diagnostic and
statistical manual of mental disorders this is what the counselors
psychiatrists the doctors use to look at you as to whether you're crazy or not
I'm just throwing out a crazy word there but there it is and here's what I've put
online get ready for the new onslaught of insight we'll call it a insight from
Obamacare the new mental illness it will fight itself into DSM-5 since the late
nineties DSM-4 has been that manual of diagnostic of diagnostics so now we have
a new one coming out in May well we we have a precursor here of what's what's
going to be in it whatever it defines it'll allow the government to lock you
up for an indeterminate length of time label you as something which will result
in your inability to own or possess a firearm and allow the police unlimited
search and seizure of your domicile or your motor conveyance you will not be
allowed a security clearance a driver's license or pilot's license you'll not be
allowed to serve in the military or law enforcement you'll not be allowed to
work in government service schools daycare centers hospitals or medical
clinics you'll be restricted in your movements that be forced by law to carry
an implanted device on or in your person you will be restricted in your ability
to do financial transactions to buy or sell goods or services now my bottom
line is this you'll now know how it you felt under the Nazi regime but here's
how they're gonna do it Alex in the in the manual gsm-5 here's what we have
DSM-5 there's something called a general anxiety disorder GAO now I'm gonna ask
you a question I'm gonna play doctor for a second here Alex when you knew you
were gonna have be on the program we a little bit anxious the first time
because you really didn't know me yes I am always anxious when we're
interviewing a new guest and vetting their information okay Alex I'm you've
now given me authority to report on you because anxiety is a is a can be at the
extreme a mental illness and so now I've got to start writing out stuff I'm gonna
lead you and they go on and say do you ever get upset everybody gets angry well
that's mental illness well let me ask you something do you believe that a few
thousand years ago there was a guy who was killed he was he was murdered he
died his body was buried and then three days later he was brought to life again
do you believe that well I know that and I believe that it was Janet Reno said on
60 minutes that if you believe in Jesus Christ and that he's real and and his
second coming you are mentally ill and this has always been their plan they're
going to say we're mentally ill yeah I'm gonna take you through from I'm just
going check check you know down the list here but do you believe that there is a
spirit that inhabits you and it enables you to get guidance from another unseen
spirit God you do oh I just put another check mark here so there's a whole list
of things that are going to be asked of you all of it is to show that you are in
fact incapable joking in and it's not just me that gets angry and stuff
mainline people like Larry Pratt they call him insane and they say on the
Democratic websites you're insane you shouldn't have guns we're going to get
your guns you're insane because you don't want socialism and it's all about
how they control the narrative they decide what is they live in this is part
of their psychosis is that they're in charge and you need to be
institutionalized because you're non kampus mentis you're not in charge your
fact of your faculties it's obvious you believe in some guy who dies and comes
up gets up out of the grave and you know and you get a spirit guiding you hello
you know it's lunacy so that's that's how they're gonna do this to you all of
it to take your guns amazing absolutely amazing of course does this sound like
Nazi Germany sir it does stay there we're on the march the Empire's on the
run Alex Jones and the GCN radio network
you prepare by purchasing gold food and firearms but if you don't have a home
security system then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home
protection when you're sleeping or away from home who's watching out for
intruders check out simply safe it's a new do-it-yourself home security system
that is completely wireless go to get simply safe calm simply safe is
independent and off the grid it runs on battery power so even if the grid goes
down you're protected it's completely customizable so you can use it in your
home business boat trailer storage unit or shed get simply safe calm simply safe
is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes so there's
no need to let a stranger into your home if you move or need to relocate you can
take the system with you wherever you go you aren't always at home but simply
safe will stand guard protecting your property 24 hours a day seven days a
week again that's get simply safe calm Alex Jones here with a message to fellow
freedom lovers the prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs
from bad to worse the globalist model is to shut down societies and starve
patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover that's why we've
assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at info wars shop
calm these are items that I did research on but I personally use you've got the
life straw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go the K
tour hand-cranked generator to charge up key equipment during power outages are
out in the field strategic relocation third edition by
Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein there are safe used by
Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event and crank
shortwave AM FM radios everything that we've researched and found to be the
best is available at info war shop calm and your purchase makes our info war
possible we're getting prepared are you info wars shop calm looking back on
2012 we asked ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters like
hurricane sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships
brought on by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost
everything at e foods direct we hear from customers every day that are
fortunate enough to weather life storm by having a supply of food on hand after
hurricane sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost all the grocery stores are
closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able to help my
sister and niece it is better to be prepared ten years too early than one
day too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what
Alex has done call eight hundred four zero nine five six three three today or
go to e foods direct comm slash Alex and build your food supply it's the best
tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call eight hundred four
zero nine five six three three or e foods direct comm slash Alex you can bet
your life on e foods direct the matrix is everywhere it is all around us even
now in this very room you can see it when you look out your window or when
you turn on your television you can feel it when you go to work when you go to
church when you pay your tax it is the world that has been pulled over your
eyes to blind you from the truth that you are a slave like everyone else you
were born into bondage born into a prison that you cannot smell or taste
or touch a prison for your mind
the Alex Jones show because there is a war on for your mind
by the way in health news it's up on info Wars calm the video the interview
Dorian Yates six-time mr. Olympian one of the most famous bodybuilders in
history I guess only next to Schwarzenegger even I know that I don't
even follow about a bodybuilding has come out against fluoride and talked
about how deadly it is in the water supply and and that's good because then
people like that will get to the bodybuilders and then famous soccer
players have come out against fluoride and then people wake up there and then
a teenage girl in Mississippi spends three years exposing a deadly very toxic
chemical and Gatorade linked all sorts of problems cumulatively and and now
Gatorades pulling it out I mean there is an example of solutions and the
government is going to try to get more power and then sometimes you're gonna
get real tyrants in charge that want to go for it all and that's why we need to
say no warrantless checkpoints aren't to keep us safe it's to set up a police
state and now they're saying the warrantless checkpoints aren't for
al-qaeda now they're for gun owners and everything our guests was announcing I
had to really bite my tongue and not interrupt a bunch about how we're gonna
have more ankle bracelets that were found mentally ill how they can just
announce it now under these new federal edicts they're saying and the Soviets
and the Nazis did this Hitler the first people they killed had been grabbed and
ordered mentally ill by psychiatrist and and just like in China they said all
your kids got a clubfoot we're gonna kill your two-year-old they would take
them into the doctor's office and then say oh they died of a heart attack
there's actually documentaries on this they killed hundreds of thousands before
they even started arresting political dissidents and it's eugenics it's like
why are we seeing the same thing because Hitler didn't get it from Germany he got
it from England and from the United States that developed modern eugenics
and then he took it to an extreme level and quote discredited it so the Journal
of eugenics switched over to the Journal of population and things like that and I
covered that in our film in game blueprint for global enslavement
available at info war store comm so important to see that so important to
show it to your church now expanding here that we're going back to our guest
you know beyond tangy tangerine and some of the other amazing things that have
just basically every vitamin mineral trace element huge amounts of vitamin C
huge amounts of the B vitamins they did a big Clemson study that they've been
doing for several years you've got to go read this it's up at info wars comm from
yahoo finance and we'll punch this up and post it on top of it it's in the
health section of info wars comm video pharmacists exposes deadly
antidepressants but then under that is the yahoo finance international al
international announces results of Young Jevity clinical studies performed by
Clemson University yahoo finance they took cancer cells from human cancer in
the colon that's just exploding because of all the toxins and chemicals and of
course it mutates the cells and the the the the Young Jevity beyond tangy
tangerine it has some of the others as well you can go read the results in a
scientific study went in and did not hurt the healthy cells and killed the
unhealthy cancer cells now the reason I knew when I did this probably what was
gonna happen is Linus Pauling got a Nobel Prize for this folks I don't know
was it 40 years ago but it got suppressed so they're just redoing these
studies but they it is the best stuff out there that's why I promote it info
wars health comm you can sign up and get free shipping there at info wars health
comm on the 400 it's 300 and something they're adding a bunch more to me over
400 of the best products out there the polymers plus all of it the essential
oils it's all they're the best stuff I only promote the best and your purchase
then funds our radio show the news operation and what we're doing info wars
health comm we have any questions or comments or want to order right there on
the site at info wars health comm you can also call 888-789-9277 and when you
call that number we'll put it up on screen one more time and I'll plug that
for folks 888-789-9277 if you want to sign up to be a new customer and sound
to be a distributor and to get discounts or just order the products that's right
there in force health comm or to just be a distributor info wars team calm okay
that said look I got calls all over the map but our guests can obviously speak
to any of these but after these five or six callers because the the Genesis phone
board only takes six callers ours can take a hundred at a time but as soon as
you hear a caller hang up that's your chance to call in we're gonna only open
it for military who have been training for gun confiscation or military
officers I mean it's it's it's majors and up that are getting this question
and I've confirmed it but again most of these guys say no I can confirm it you
know look at this manual look at that manual in fact I keep forgetting when
you guys type in army field manual gun confiscation is I want to give them the
dash number and all that and I forgot to do it during the break we've written 20
articles or more on it but I want to give that out again people want to go
look it up but after we take these five or six calls that are on the phone board
that'll be your chance to call in 800 25 99 231 for military or police are now
training with them in gun confiscation you've got all these drills that used to
happen a few times a year now thousands of times a year checkpoints helicopter
assaults Houston Miami Chicago all this week I've sent the guys two years ago to
Chicago where they practice putting citizens in a sports stadium with
foreign trips and again I've shot video where the Marines trained to put
Americans in these facilities now it doesn't mean they'll get away with it
you're not supposed to get scared and run and hide under a bridge because of
this you're supposed to go hey this isn't morally right no no no if you
cower see the globalists hope you just get scared and shut up and go along with
them I'm looking for men and women who will go no we're gonna stand up against
this and I want to I want to go back to our guest dr. Jim Garo who again is one
of the largest chains of English-speaking teaching schools in
China since 2000 save over 45,000 little Chinese baby girls who would have been
killed after birth which they're now promoting here the big bioethics journal
last year people didn't believe it when we published an article linked to them
saying let's kill kids up to age three even if they're healthy that it took
three days for mainstream media to pick it up saying it couldn't be true and
they called it was a real study put out in their journal we're gonna get to that
coming up we're keeping a little bit in the next hour if you can do it because
again constitutional lawyer Bruce fine was stuck in court he apologized we
appreciate him he's on tomorrow talk about the constitutional attacks that
are going on and how to strike back against it but dr. Jim Garo is our guest
right now what about my point because I'm not a tough guy but you know if
tyranny is coming down on me I know instinctively or in my spirit to to say
no and stand up against it now if I can get out of the way you know short term
you know I sometimes I do try to back down but it depends on you know what the
gut level decision is and I know giving into tyranny historically intellectually
but also my gut tells me my gut says you will not back down like it's the
opposite it's like I have absolutely no fear which is like Ezekiel you know
saying in the Bible God they're gonna kill me but it burns in my bones I can't
stop I mean it's the opposite of fear it's not courage I don't want to be
thanked for what I do I can't control myself my whole gut my spirit my
intellect intellectually it confirms it you stand up to moves to intimidate you
and set up checkpoints and secretly arrest people and NDAA and all this you
don't you don't get scared but so many people email me and write me and go what
you say is true but I'm scared I've got ulcers I'm an officer in the army I
don't know what to do and I don't know about that spirit of fear you know good
thank God we know thank God people spoken up thank God this has come out
thank God what do you say to those that don't get this and think oh my gosh
what's the point of knowing this it's so negative isn't it positive to know so
that we can contend and wrestle with this evil absolutely you know what I
would do with those people who aren't willing to listen you you're you're not
responsible for them you're really not you're responsible for your own belief
system and then you're responsible for your own family so you know very much
like planning for anything else in life you plan for the survival of yourself
and your family that's what you've got to do that's what we're looking at we're
not we're not just this isn't theory now these people are moving they're making
moves forward that will take away your freedom they take away the guns remember
the first thing that the Germans did was declared that Jews were not quite people
and then the first people to lose the right to own a gun were the Jews and of
course that made them the easiest to be rounded up let's be careful here again
the caution should be think plan figure out your escape route figure out what
you will do when they come knocking on your door at night do you have something
to back you up if that happens or are you just going to be a ready victim
they'll just march in your home and take you and your family confiscate the guns
and take you and your family away do you have a plan for that that's what you
need to do let's start planning and I mean there are people out there who who
are accused of being you know the crazies the tinfoil hat kind of people
but and conspiracies theorists well you know conspiring together that's what law
is all about we make a social contract we conspire together to come up with the
laws and a way to handle and control society well this is going beyond that
and now they're going to handle and control us now what are you going to do
about what it is going to be your plan for your family I think you need to look
to that first and foremost responsibility and get it very clear
have plans know what you're going to do know what you're going to do in the long
term I agree with you but my point is they won't get away with this if we
simply challenge him and you know folks have always said the archival image of
the crazy guys he's yelling well we're yelling to get people out of their coma
some people are smooth like you other people like myself get upset I also
sometimes I'm calm but I found I've been successful not on purpose I didn't do
this on purpose by being upset sometimes to get people out of their learned
helplessness out of their mass Stockholm syndrome out of their normalcy bias
because I mean things have gotten so crazy I want to read this quote but if I
say I will not mention him or speak any more in his name his word is in my heart
like a fire a fire shut up in my bones I am weary holding it in indeed I cannot
because my uncle about 15 years ago I'm sitting across the coffee table from
he's a big Bible scholar probably listening right now my mom's brother
great guy Vietnam vet helicopter pilot patriot lived all over the world and I
said you know I can't help it when they death threat me I can't help it when
they get my face I I don't understand people that are afraid of the new world
order I can't shut up it's a burning and then he quoted the scripture to me which
I've never read but I mean I just wish other people had the burning in their
bones I mean I guess you're saying if someone's not called to fight evil I
guess that I mean you're saying just triage them no no I'm saying look to the
first responsibility that you have which is to your family make a plan for them
but make sure that your plan is thorough that you understand they will come when
you least expect it they're not going to come in broad daylight they'll come at
night when you're asleep they'll bang it on your door when you're least prepared
to react properly that's when this is going to start to happen they've already
you know done the groundwork they've got the evidence on you test last year where
Brandon Robin all these Marines honorably discharged officers no
criminal record would mildly criticize Obama and they would have the police
come and mentally commit them it's happened to a bunch of talk show host
already last year yeah and look what they're saying they're saying that
anyone who's been a veteran it's been overseas comes back you're you're
immediately suspect of being a terrorist or a terrorist threat what's that about
you mentioned Hitler first they went after a group who'd been demonized and
unpopular the Jews but it but then they went after every group you know the
famous quota they went after the Jews I wasn't a juice I didn't stand up they
went after the Methodist I wasn't a Methodist I didn't stand up I mean by
the end of it the Nazis my grandfather became an inventor because in Dallas
growing up he lived next door to a famous inventor had been involved in
venting indoor refrigeration or taking those systems indoor air conditioning
and so and this guy was a German immigrant since he was a little kid but
he spoke German and my grandfather you know had a lot of German ancestors so he
spoke some German Germans that came into Texas so they became friends he worked
with him some the Germans extorted he told me this story when I was a little
kid all the money out of that guy before and then right up to World War two
threatening to kill his family and the guy wasn't Jewish so I mean that people
that say all the Nazis you know didn't really do all this stuff baloney and
I'm telling you it's the same organized crime system that we're now seeing
unfold I mean this is a great danger oh amen and the fact that you've been
cautioning people for years to me is like wow you've been thinking ahead you
know you've been that that's the problem though you're so far ahead of the curve
of the reality of today like like everyone's secure it we're snug as a bug
in a rug things are working well society is great we got power we got water we
got gas in our car we can go on holiday we got money in the bank we got a job
yeah well wait until all of it is cut off what's your plan that's that's what
I'm I keep coming back to it like we're not talking about what what my officer
friend cautioned beyond but basically where he went with the whole the whole
scenario was what will the public do when they finally pulled the plug on
everything and well that's the deal they're there they're deriding the banks
they're deriding the country they're saying we're gonna go double the the the
the the debt to our GDP they're doing it on purpose to make us dependent and what
will happen when they drop the hammer I guess they're gonna say do what you're
told or starve to death and I want people to know when the global is take
down America it's not gonna be creeping anymore they're gearing up for an
all-out assault and scream yeah yeah that's great absolutely a lightning war
I mean it's incredible against us and man I tell you folks don't be afraid
speak out now I believe it's gonna backfire and they may back off if here's
the problem they've committed to an economic collapse they may not be able
to stop but but I see every sign they're trying to just accelerate the collapse
while posing as the Savior Alex you're absolutely right the signs that I'm
getting and the word that I'm getting back is that when I was told this that
last Monday morning that since we put it in to the public view look at the things
that have happened bang all of a sudden we've got well you know better what's
going on I don't know the list of things that are going on but things are
accelerating I think what we've helped to do is push them through fear and the
purchase of guns and ammo that's the big thing for they weren't counting up they
didn't count that the American public go in that direction you know what they
were hoping for was that everyone would just you know everything business as
usual you know it's only the government doing this doing that Obama you know if
they're kindly at the comedy father the great smile that he's not people he's
he's not gonna do anything to us this is all for our good sounds very much like
how Hitler was viewed as well the night that's coming and I keep saying it's
night because actually scripture talks about a night it's not when you're ready
for it it's it's at night that they're going to come and this is all going to
happen it's in that night when you will need to be prepared so what are you
doing to protect your own family what are you doing to network your
neighborhood so that there is a group of people to protect one another because
remember something it's overwhelming force that they're being taught to use
overwhelming force what happened at Waco and I bring up Waco as an example
because here was overwhelming force and in the end they just brutalized and
murdered all those women and children and then the military posed with the
skulls they were very very proud of the work they don't they could have arrested
Koresh in town who went into town every day and had a business in town we're
gonna come back and take calls can you stay with us 20 minutes the next hour
sir all right that way we can get through these calls that open it up for
military officers who'd like to call in and talk about this have you have you
been told you know will you fire American citizens and we know it was in
29 palm survey stay with us if you've ever wanted one of our best-selling
generators but we're waiting for an offer so crazy you couldn't refuse then
you're not gonna want to miss this exciting message here's why our solar
generators provide life-saving electrical power and unlike gas
generators solar generators run quietly emit no fumes and produce
electricity from the Sun so when the lights go out you'll always have the
power you need now here's the best part every year we accumulate a few solar
generators that we just can't sell as new we put them in a special spot in our
warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of each year we call them
scratch and dent units but they're really just like new each unit comes
with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe don't
wait they go fast go to scratch and dent solar calm that scratch and dent solar
calm for the craziest offer we've ever made go to scratch and dent solar calm
that scratch and dent solar calm
hello this is Ty Bollinger author of the best-selling book cancer step outside
the box I want you to know some very important information in 1985 president
Ronald Reagan requested that carnivore be sent directly to the White House at a
time when only the president could obtain this world-class healer now 27
years later carnivore capsules are used around the world to keep people healthy
now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of superbugs with
17 naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells
only without harming a single normal cell if you want to stay healthy now's
your chance to literally wake up your critical immune cells to attack harmful
invaders that don't belong in your body call one eight six six Venus fly or
order from carnivore calm that's car ni vo ra calm that's one eight six six eight
three six eight seven three five one eight six six Venus fly or visit
carnivore calm protect your immune system it's the only one you've got
hey there Frank Bates here have you heard about the weird device that could
wipe out 280 million Americans this is really scary stuff defense experts warn
that this odd device poses the gravest threat we've ever known in fact just a
few weeks ago former Speaker of the House Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed
piece for the Washington Post warning about this deadly threat I can't believe
that more people aren't talking about this it may be because the liberals and
the government are trying to cover it up that's why my friend just created a free
video at weird device calm that exposes this threat and blows the doors off the
conspiracy go watch the shocking video at weird device calm right now to
discover exactly what it is plus discover the number one way you and your
family can survive this deadly attack I'm not sure how long this video be
online so go to weird device calm before it's gone forever again that's weird
device calm
and again the way tyrants work is they just ease you into it but the general
population out there inside this giant reeducation camp that has become America
need to ask themselves do you want to be slaves under this now again we got a
bunch of calls for our guests they'll be all over the map some of them were
holding before he got on with us but then as each person hangs up we're only
taking calls in the next hour of military and police I mean again in fact
we put the army manual back up on screen if you haven't taken it down to people
the 2010 army manual internment and resettlement operations how to scan your
social security number how to put the children in one area of the camp how to
confiscate the guns how to lock down u.s. cities three dash three nine dot forty
internment resettlement operations so there's more proof of what our guest is
saying or the Army Times admits it Brigade homeland the big police chief
summit that they had Jan Napolitano at shed the new threat is an al-qaeda just
just this week but Monday the new threat is returning veterans gun owners
conservatives and libertarians we are violent radical extremists because we
know that globalists have taken the country over and again our guest is dr.
Jim Garo let's go to Diane then we'll go to Jeannie and others Diane you want to
talk about martial law go ahead well I got a couple things first of all I think
I'm in good company I guess I'm mentally ill because I believe there's an evil
plan but I'm not gonna get in fear it's gonna be scary but I've read the book
and I know how it is it's gonna be good I was wondering if you could confirm on
one of these sites you've had on before it's news.com but there was evidently a
truck pulled over that they found the martial law signs in the truck in
Houston and then I've been reading more and more articles I'm trying to keep
moving for you more I've been reading more and more articles about martial law
just being inflicted in the home where when we finally run out of food and
supplies will come out and submit and I was wondering what you thought about
that I have an uncle that's retired from the Air Force that thinks we're total
crackpots that there will not even be a problem with the economy or anything
against our guns for 10 or 20 more years and he just retired in the last six
years and yeah notice people that are delusional think it's all gonna happen
after they die it's always and see it's the old-timers that held all this back
and see that's the the paradox Patriots hold it back but still we're sliding so
we slowed it down and then as everything starts to happen like we said oh it's
supposed to be worse than this as we battle to win the war against these
people I mean it's such a mind game now that's been played but no unfortunately
that martial law sign thing I've been hearing for 17 years it's a proverbial
deal they're not gonna call it martial law it's gonna be called civil emergency
and they're already look it's martial law when the TSA sticks their hands down
your pants it's martial law when the police have checkpoints in your town
it's martial law when the TSA is down on Lamar right now running checkpoint
searching people without warrants in Austin where I live it's martial law
when the military does drill in cities every day I want to go back to our
guests thank you for the call ma'am you know what about her point about martial
law we're always looking for martial law martial law if there is a big martial
law it's what about false flags I asked that question earlier you never got to
it what about Obama staging things well you know and by the way I didn't hear
any of the the caller's words at all I'm sorry I was so but in terms of what he
does let's face it I think I said this before he's an incrementalist that's
what he does it's by small increments that he sees what he can get away with
and continues to go further and further and further at every turn so in terms of
martial law remember he's looking for a crisis and then he will as they said he
we will manage the crisis so the management of that crisis may be that
you lose your freedoms totally right now stay there back in 60 seconds I want to
hear more on this false flag or using crises straight ahead stay with us you
are listening to GCN visit GCN live.com today now that we have moved into the
winter season there is an increased need to support our immunity and health at
silver lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection
of silver-based products our most popular silver-based products are the
32 ounce nano silver solutions our 2 ounce nano silver nasal applicators as
well as our all-natural silver soaps just released is our 100% natural silver
gel our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly
evaporate and leave the silver at the surface but rather we have formulated
our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to
quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more
effectively visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what
silver-based products are best for you that's www.silverlungs.com
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN radio network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does
he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones MSNBC trying to get racial division going now full well they call
white people crackers and racists and all southerners scum every day that it
will make whites start thinking that blacks and people are all racist it's
just unbelievable evil going on to play a clip of that for our guests coming up
and we just had a phone line open there for a moment for current serving
military are they training you we know they're training you to confiscate guns
other showed the army manual where it says that but are they saying if you
won't fire on Americans you're in trouble that's coming up after the break
but our guest Jim Garo before we go back to calls again don't let a good crisis
go to waste but they staged fast and furious to blame the Second Amendment
shipping guns to Mexico what about them actually staging something I mean if
they're willing to do all this why wouldn't they stage something they've
done it before but wasn't Benghazi also something was staged basically it was
meant to be a kidnapping I suppose it a quasi pseudo kidnapping of the
ambassador and then he would work it through the details so that in the end
you had the blind sheik being released so that the dear leader could once again
look heroic to the Muslim population and instead he got killed instead the whole
thing and you know what two gentlemen stood up and put their lives on the line
and held back 500 people for how many hours Alex eight hours and screamed for
help and were denied it even though they had what a gunship up there they had two
drones and a gunship up there over the eight hours and the help was denied why
did they want him dead and you know this is all this is all information it's
available that we know that they had the gunship we we know that they had the
drones there we know that they had the laser targeting and these people were
left whatever happened out you know don't leave any man behind I mean this
this man in the White House is and I cannot believe no morals no scruples
well he gets away with anything and that's what's so scary he's been given
word he can move forward Janine in Wisconsin thanks for holding her on the
air hi how you doing good thank you hey I just wanted to share some ideas that
I'm currently using to spread the word and actually I got the information and
idea from you I think you had said once that we need to like go out on the
street corners with a sign that says you know 9-11 was an inside job or whatever
you know whatever you wanted to put on it and I actually have 16 signs that
line my front yard almost like the old political signs from useless people that
are running for city councils and stuff I actually have 16 signs that have
different various things from 9-11 to vaccines I have a six-year-old grandson
that's got brain damage from vaccines when he was 18 months so I advocate for
that and I also have magnets that I had custom made that I have on my truck on
both sides and the back info wars Alex Jones hear the truth and I got bullet
points of everything to direct them to you well ma'am that's the reason we're
reaching exponentially more people and God bless you it is a great idea in fact
I've been so busy with other projects I haven't announced yet we're gonna give
away a hundred and fifty thousand bumper stickers in fact I'm gonna shoot a video
about that tonight people have to sign a little pledge not to put them on other
people's property or any legal areas we'll send out 50 to 100 stickers
depending on what people request she can give them to people at church use them
as a topic point I put them on your property put them on other people's
property that have authorized you to so we're gonna send out a hundred and
fifty thousand bumper stickers that say info wars comm save the Constitution and
things like that there's five different stickers so that's a great idea ma'am
all of us need to just get the buzz of Liberty going god bless you anything
else you'd like to add what can I add to something is that sure go ahead sir be
oh good you know it there's the usual way where we stand up as a public we
wanted for council we weren't for City Council we run for different positions
that are open to us we run for school board but let me just tell you a little
bit if I may about about standing up and I love the woman's creativity I mean
that's my stay there we're gonna come back and talk to you long segment coming
up with our guests how to stand up we're gonna talk to the military the phones
are open eight hundred to five at nine nine two three one are you being told
kill Americans follow orders or get out the new year is a great time to take
charge of your health and wellness get serious and make a stand with
supernatural silver this is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver
supernatural silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses
infections yeast and molds supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound
care and is highly effective for water purification it is the number one choice
for thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect
choice for your emergency preparedness go to supernatural silver calm today and
give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance that's supernatural
silver calm check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook introducing pro
wine all of your filtration in one system portable on the go no more do you
have two or three filters to just reduce sodium fluoride you have a system that
cuts out the sodium fluoride and up to 95% of hydrofluorosolic acid advanced
manufacturing technology combines silver impregnated white ceramic with new
aqua medics advanced media for removal of fluoride and other heavy metals all
in one filter element it is the only one that does it and out of the gates we
have a discounted at 10% off with promo code water this is the only system that
in one unit helps reduce or remove pesticides herbicides chloramines
ammonia and chlorine hydrofluorosolic acid the most common form of fluoride
not covered by other fluoride filter brands and sodium hexafluorosilicate get
your pro pure with a new pro one filter today at info war store comm or by
calling 888-253-3139 millions of people are going to get sick this winter from
Coles flu and other illnesses don't be one of them protect yourself with
supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad-spectrum antibacterial solution
recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that
can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and help
improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every
day while powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as
strep staph pneumonia coals flus and other harmful pathogens this new
technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at
several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions
the Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter it is
virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to
supernatural silver comm today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20% off
that's supernatural silver comm and like us on Facebook
waging war on corruption it's Alex Jones coming to you live from the front lines
of the info war
you
ladies and gentlemen I'm gonna do a special report on this this week I've
talked a lot about it over the years and shown the news articles but it's close
to 59,000 when I checked last week people have died since 2007 in Mexico
it's approaching 60,000 and and I believe there's tens of thousands they
don't know about that have been buried there's some estimates over 50,000
missing so that could be a hundred and nine thousand but more people die every
year in Mexico than died in the decade of the Vietnam War 58,000 Americans died
roughly over that decade-long plus conflict we're talking about 59,000
since 2007 so five and a half six years and we need to get that number out
because all guns have been taken in Mexico from the people and the reason I
raised that is at least three shot at office complex in Phoenix Arizona this
is just breaking the last 15 minutes or so and an employee at a law office in
the area told newspapers he had seen four people take him in on stretchers
that's we've also got helicopter shots of that television footage shows dozens
of officers entering a building where police say people are injured and again
it's either gangs it's somebody going postal or it is a Prozac head it's
always the same mo the answer is have guns in there because there's a bad
person with the guns gonna kill you just like Mexico they got the highest crime
rate in the world they don't have the highest city though Mexico City is at
number one Chicago is by the way the Chicago Police Chief I've got that in
the stack he's saying don't worry you know we've had a 530 something killed
last year we've taken all your guns highest crime rate for any city in the
world it's not that bad that's the quote the Associated Press fact I have even a
video clip of him I was seeing this morning it's not that bad though he's in
press conferences wanting you to turn your guns in where he's taking the guns
the murders aren't that bad oh but it's sandy hook terrible that this guy got
guns illegally and and now you got to turn your guns in but when people get
killed in his gun-free zone it's a no big deal so numerous emergency vehicles
are at the scene video footage showing a person being taken on the gurney I
reached at the scene and it's gotten the point with more kids built a Lego it
looked like a gun with a Lego so the SWAT team was called that happened today
it's this total hysteria people drive by and see a kid with a nerf gun bright
orange helicopters police foaming at the mouth hyperventilating bubble
projectors now the police are being called and there's nothing more deadly
than a pink Hello Kitty bubble gun I want to go back to our guest Jim Garrow
and he want to talk about some solutions and standing up he's somebody that knows
how to stand up and we're gonna go to James in Colorado who's a marine who can
comment on has he been told you know are you ready to fire on American citizens
and the lines are open just for military people now we've got some others that
are holding from before I'll get to you as well but eight hundred two five nine
ninety two thirty one our guest of course let's talk to a quote living
military legend who says he's talked to other officers who are being told now as
a litmus test will you fire on citizens well I have the Army manual where they're
now training for gun confiscation and shooting us and the drills are waves of
protesters being mowed down by full auto Homeland Security's bought 1.6 plus
billion bullets the last 14 months as you know and now a new purchase order
for Homeland Security quote personal protection weapons we had that up at
info Wars calm yesterday from the Federal Registry for 7,000 fully auto
308 for personal protection just just you know that every week there's more
purchases so they're they're gearing up for World War three against us but make
your point about solutions standing up in your words then we'll go to that
marine well let's face it in your in your local community that's where you
have your biggest fear of influence generally that's just a normal joke like
just you and I and in our in our little neighborhood so what you do is you run
for office you run for dog catcher you run for police chief you run for
whatever's I want to give an illustration of the use of a linsky
tasks tactics I ran for school board in my local town I want I got on there I
started you know putting the boots to the the people who were just rubber
stamping whatever the administration wanted in the school district and it
meant spending money like like a drunken sailor so what they did is utilize the
media media fully socialist Marxist up here in Canada where I am at the moment
and I was back then and so they use that a linsky method they freeze you they
demonize you and they cause it that no one will listen to you because the media
of course tells the tale and controls the message and that's what they will do
you must have a vehicle some way of getting your message out if you're
gonna run for anything so that the truth is always available to the public the
public you serve but make sure that you have that vehicle if you don't have it
you're dead because the media will cripple you they will freeze you they
will demonize you they will put you out of business so no one listens to you but
now governor Cuomo who wants to basically ban all our guns total gangster
his his brother is now the morning CNN anchor but CNN's top show has half a
million their average show about 90,000 they are an illusion they are imploding
in fact there's news today when I was there and I've been to their studios
three times it looked like a third world facility I don't want to describe it but
I mean the the bathrooms because after I saw one I said they put me in this on
purpose I went and checked a few more the carpet light bulbs out dirt on the
floors in the studios horrible morale I mean these guys are falling apart but
here it is Cloward Piven strategy and of course that's the 1966 sociologist that
I first told people about 15 years ago that books have been now written about
by others my greatest success is even though you know I'm I'm not Rush Limbaugh
and Glenn Beck they just I make stuff popular and they pick it up which I
think's great you know I force it out there but it was a plan to bankrupt New
York City and other cities to make you accept socialism the plan is to get you
dependent and this is published and officially used by the Democratic Party
that's why they're gonna shut off your power plants they're gonna raise taxes
on working poor until you give up and go on welfare they want to run your life
let's go to some Marines here we've got James in Colorado we'll go to him in a
moment but first JC in Montana marine with news on general so we'll see what
that's about and then we've got Army National Guard Matt and Florida again
you just joined us our source a top general retired told him that they're
they're doing a litmus test now will you fire on US citizens and if not you're
ordered to resign your Commission I have all the background proving that's
already happening I found that in the news and in Army manuals the last three
years it's changed but what's unprecedented is totally unprecedented is
the the new sec def nominee Hagel came out and said you cannot trust the
military they're not on your side Obama you've got to have a purge of them if
you want your new world order that was Washington Post yesterday okay we wrote
an article about it at info wars calm I mean this is going on and it's a big
deal so let's go to JC JC well what can you tell us hey Alex hey Jim how's it
going that's going all right um first of all General Mattis mad dog
Mattis from CENTCOM was fired and I'll read you what the blaze put on it's like
United States Marine Corps general James mad dog Mattis was notified he was being
replaced as commander central command not by a phone call from Washington but
by a note by his aide according to foreign policies Thomas E Ricks general
Mattis was traveling in a meeting when an aide passed him a note telling him
that the Pentagon had announced his replacement as head of Central Command
and I saw that a while back for generals in the last month have been relieved and
and the CENTCOM folks are angry because they begged the White House in the
eight-hour Benghazi operation to let them bomb the targets and were ordered
to stand down that's come out CENTCOM general Mattis is loved he's a good man
he's a he's a marine I mean I'm a marine I mean everyone loves this guy I mean I
don't know if Jim's force was referencing Jim he's probably referencing
someone younger the way he talks that it was mentored by the general that he
knows but when Mattis is out of Central Command something's wrong I mean there's
no reason I mean and some of the some of the stuff I read was general Mattis said
he doesn't have the balls to come down here and tell me himself I mean this was
kind of man he is well you don't get a name like mad dog for being diplomatic
but I mean this was a man that protected America loved America and well that's
probably the reason he's not in CENTCOM no more but uh well no there is a look
look the military purge is already confirmed but but the but the the new
Secretary of Defense are trying to confirm that the nominee says you can't
trust the military and they're purging them all around us I appreciate your
call god bless you this just backs up everything Jim Garo Dr. Garo sang from
the MO and I looked it up and I know these guys run in the same circles I
believe it's General Boykin the former head of Special Forces because he's
already speaking out already know people that know him well he's anti New World
Order he's in the film that we sell Behold the Pale Horse with Charlie
Daniels he's speaking out right now about tyranny I believe it's General
Boykin but yeah what about the general purge of the military and the new
Secretary of Defense is a top globalist Hagel a fake Republican a fake
conservative saying that you know that Obama can't trust the military well to
do that what an admission here are the people that are ready to lay their life
on the line I mean think about this the difference here you got the military
ready to lay their lives on the line you got the politicians what are they ready
to lay they're ready to go out and have a great wine and cheese at your expense
and supposedly your purport to be representing you and they're the ones
that are afraid of the military well they should be afraid of marriage
military because they have not lost their sense of priority
politicians have lost the priority and Leon Panetta remember last year he
wouldn't go to any bases with any of the even the officers armed
remember that yeah could it be that they really uh would
rather not see him well I mean that's why they want to go
to robots and drones because despots have always hated
having to have real men do the killing for them and so they despise them that's
why as soon as they're out of the military
they're the number one enemy of homeland security you heard me again this is
public this is admitted our government says the military is the
terrorist I mean wake up folks
hello I'm Alex Jones myself my family the info wars.com team
want to relay to you and your families that we are intensifying our efforts
against the globalist on every front info wars.com is leading the fight
against the technocrats but we can't do that without your help
by getting the films bumper stickers and t-shirts and info wars.com
you will wake up people in your area and support
our operation as we move to the next level
we need your help to spread the word like never before
they wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle
between the forces of freedom and darkness you
are the response to the globalist technocrats
and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination the war is here
it's an info war the spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984
we all know that berkey water purification systems are the most
trusted name in water filtration as an authorized berkey dealer for over
six years and serving thousands of satisfied customers
the berkey guy offers amazing specials for berkey water filtration systems
the berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable
black purification elements that purify water by removing chlorine
pathogenic bacteria cyst and parasites to non-detectable levels and remove
harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides order
the berkey light system today complete with two black berkey elements for only
231 dollars and the berkey guy will ship your order
free of charge with the purchase of a berkey light the
berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride and arsenic filters for only
39.99 that's over 30 percent off the retail
price call the berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653
that's 1-877-886-3653 or order online at goberky.com
that's goberky.com today oh great now i've got to go to court
meet tina now facing a future court date i can't afford an attorney then learn
how to represent yourself in court step by step
without a lawyer how online at how to win in court.com
how to win in court.com how to win in court.com was created by a 27-year
veteran attorney so you can know how to win without a
lawyer now i can go to court with confidence learn how
at how to win in court.com the leader in lawsuit self-help since 1997
hi this is ted anderson have you ever wondered why banks stockbrokers
investment advisors won't talk about gold iras
they've been available since 1986 yet the financial industry won't recognize
the value of gold for your retirement gold has outperformed paper investments
yet no word about iras if you would like to have gold for your
retirement call 800-686-2237 don't get left behind by rising
inflation and low returns call 800-686-2237
secure your future and call 1-800-686-2237
lunch is ready and it's an MRE smorgasbord at longlifefood.com
in 1983 long life food depot was one of the first to sell MRE pouches to the
public and we're still selling them almost 30
years later today long life food depot has the world's most complete MRE online
buffet because MREs are all we do tasty
varieties of chicken beef salmon and pasta entrees plus
sandwiches and our easy to use pouches full moisture
long shelf life and ready to eat hot or cold we sell by the pouch or case
so the choices are endless and so are the graduated quantity discounts
the more you buy the more you save call 800-601-2833
or go to longlifefood.com to join our email list for upcoming announcements
like the rollaway food pod plus enjoy fast and free shipping
just call 800-601-2833 or visit longlifefood.com
emergency preparedness emergency relief longlifefood.com since 1983
sending real food to your real future
by the way one of the many generals that they've
kicked out is it's way more than four in the last few months it's been four
uh james mattes he said in order to kill the enemy you have to kill
an innocent don't take the shot don't create more enemies
than you can take out by some immoral act see that's what they don't like
though they want people who think it's tough to
just you know put al-qaeda in charge and then
later go in and fight al-qaeda after you give them control of syria
and a lot of the generals have been saying we should not be given missiles
to al-qaeda we should not i mean obviously you
shouldn't be doing this and the system doesn't care
they're going full speed ahead they think the public is so dumb
our government centcom had to put al-qaeda in charge of libya
now in syria and that's why they've removed
it's three top officers out of centcom alone so when i say four
total it's way more than that i mean they're they're kicking people out
everywhere there is a purge there is a purge of the military
because they don't want to be used domestically and they don't want to work
with al-qaeda and we're forcing that public debate and
that's a good thing uh let's uh talk with our guest who's
going to write shotgun with us for the rest of the hour
let's go ahead and talk to kevin the marine in texas
uh and then we'll go to uh james who's a marine in colorada
and national guard folks matt and bob who was in the
rob who was in the coast guard uh with an internal survey
on gun confiscation we know they've been creeping around with that for a while
but let's go to kevin kevin you're on the air go ahead and give us your point
hey thanks um just to go on with what you're saying about that whole purge of
the military well the marine force reserve is
actually doing a fizz rig where every unit's getting realigned
and a different mls which is going to
actually bring up you're going to have thousands and
thousands upon marine being dropped dropped out kicked out of
the military you got to make places for the new women to fight in the front
lines well right but like at my unit we don't
we're a combat arms unit but we're not like
infantry we're uh tracks and stuff 98 of my unit
is going to be dropped and that's going on across
across the nation so you're going to have all these
marines being dropped dropped out of the military and then to go on along with
what you were saying you know about uh how the military's not on your side
blah blah blah this is gonna i guess the way i'm the
way i'm thinking is it's gonna actually have a
a effect on you know how you say did you hear als charpton basically say we don't
need the military anymore we have drones and then if americans cause problems
they've got drones and we played the clip yesterday let's
cue that up in the next segment i want to play that for people
i mean that's every time i'm on the young turk show or i'm on another show
they go we've got drones now you gun owners are nothing they admit it's all
about them dominating us and and they hey sorry you don't have
your robot army yet it's still humans piloting those now uh
very interesting now now have you guys had anything brought up to you
about uh will you fire on american citizens um
i got a recent survey dropped in my email i haven't opened it yet but a
couple of my fellow marines have and they said there's some sketchy stuff in
there about you know what what would you do if you know
americans did this did that so i mean i haven't necessarily opened
it yet but i'm gonna go home and open it and another
thing have you seen the movie 2016
yes i have but let me just ask you a question
uh do me a favor send me that survey open that
and everybody send your surveys and stuff to show tips and info wars dot com
with uh military questionnaire in the forum everybody has a right to see this
it's not classified everybody send that to us
uh dr garrow's got a comment take over the call sir go ahead
uh actually uh he's covered the the ground i wanted to cover which is you
know what what information do you have at your back
and call right now uh because i've had other people say that to me you know
guys and this was a couple of marines who said it who actually said look we
just got something that said uh we are supposed to start looking to
very carefully at what the public are doing
um and uh get ready to answer these uh the following questions so
um i'm glad he brought that up it was exactly where i was headed and by the
way that's total treason that you know 29 palms happened i don't know 15 16
years ago but there's been others i mean this is in the army manuals but
we need to show that they're vetting people right now
officers are going to be asked point blank enlists they're going to have
these more creepy questions brought to them
let's go to james a marine in colorada what's your information on this front
uh yeah i want to get straight to the point alex um
i just want to ask all a question to uh to all the people that are listening
right now on your show that when was the the last time they
remember someone that has revealed a lot of things
of the government federal reserve you know exposing them a lot as
when was the last time someone has survived that
or died or gone to jail you know and uh well there's been g edward griffin myself
ron paul uh hundreds and hundreds of prominent people we're the majority
of thinkers we're taking america back we're victorious did you have a comment
uh have you been asked if you will shoot at americans
hold on let me get to my point okay we gotta go to break these are hard
networks satellite coated brakes we break at 30. we're on
the march the empire's on the run alex jones and
the gcn radio network
if you want an american company with american products
made by americans here is the cal ben soap company alex and his staff have
used these pure soap products for years these all-natural soaps are made from
the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils that are earth-friendly and
safe see them on the web at five star soap
dot com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog
buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good
as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply
of soaps for all your cleaning needs this is an
amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel see them on
the web at five star soap dot com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog
the new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness
get serious and make a stand with supernatural silver
this is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred
times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver
supernatural silver can be taken orally every day
to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds supernatural
silver is also exceptional for wound care and is
highly effective for water purification it is the number one choice for
thousands of people for immune system support
and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness
go to supernatural silver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a
fighting chance that's supernatural silver.com
check out our new low prices and like us on facebook
looking back on 2012 we asked ourselves how did we ever survive
from natural disasters like hurricane sandy and the devastating summer drought
to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous economy
our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at efoods direct we hear
from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand after hurricane sandy danny from new
york city wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed
but i managed to get my efoods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared 10 years too
early than one day too late i can warn you but i can't feed you heed
the warnings and do what alex has done call 800-409-5633 today
or go to efoods direct.com slash alex and build your food supply
it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet
call 800-409-5633 or efoods direct.com slash alex you can
bet your life on efoods direct
crashing through the lies and disinformation
it's alex jones on the gcn radio network
all right we got a shooting in arizona up to four injured and now i'm seeing
footage on fox we'll put it back up your tv viewer of guys that look like
they're in army outfits look like they are army
so they don't look like they're doing too good with all that gear so those
must be police you can tell they hadn't been carrying
they can't carry gear 100 yards much less 50 miles
punch that back up that is amazing and and and and they're saying that that
they think a man with a gun did something to the driver and grabbed a kid
off the bus i mean this is just getting bizarre
folks and if they keep hiding uh you know all this brainwashing out
there alabama police and hostage standoff with suspect
in fatal school bus shooting kidnapping
and i mean who knows if that was somebody's
dad who wanted his kid back or something who knows this country
the alabama man police they shot and killed a school bus driver
to uh well that was tuesday so i guess they're going back to it we just saw
that breaking and i thought not a new thing and now i guess they've
tracked him down and they're going after him
but again there's 315 million people our crime rate
violent crime rates down 49 since uh 1991
you can pull those statistics up at fbi.gov 21 of that just since 2007 so
it's accelerating but the media can take the events of 300
300 well this is saying moments ago i guess they've tracked him down where
he's at yeah that's what's happening so the
school bus thing happened yesterday now they've tracked down where they
believe he's at that's why they're it's it's it's new breaking news that
this happened just as we were going back live uh here on the radio
uh again right he was our guest the last hour he's riding shotgun when we take
your calls in this hour uh and he's dr jim garrow
he heads up www dot pink pagoda girls dot com
that's a group that saved since 2000 45 000 plus
chinese newborn babies that would have been infanticided
killed which the major journals bioethics journals are now basically
saying is a great thing to do here in the united states just
absolutely hellish they say kill the old people kill the babies nobody needs them
you'll get more tax money if we kill people once they
communalize and get things collectivized then they
can tell you how to live your life it's it's and then people dying
as bill gate says you kill grandma that's a death panel that's a quote
then you hire 10 teachers and the teachers clap
that's the sick collectivist model instead of grow the pie
and then you become north korea and everything collapses but they love it
but uh going back to the caller who was a
marine i think in colorado did he hang up
because he said he was a marine but i couldn't really understand yeah he
dropped off he was talking about
i couldn't really tell what he was getting into and then i said i'd come
back to him but i guess he didn't understand that
uh let's talk to matt in florida army national guard
matt in florida uh wants to comment again we know the army manuals who just
joined us in the last three years now trained for
gun confiscation and we know the military is being
prepared for domestic operations that's admitted
they're saying the new enemy is not al-qaeda it's conservatives libertarians
gun owners but now we've seen that the incoming if
it gets confirmed secretary of defense former senator
hagel saying the military can't be trusted
you know that obama if he wants his new world order has to deal
with the pentagon that they're not following orders
we know what the orders are give al-qaeda missiles set up checkpoints on
highways the military's been saying no so there's
a huge purge going right now if you're a new listener folks it's
mainstream news the government gives all kind of weapons now publicly
well why not they can take our liberties when they attack i mean i mean this all
is is so diabolical uh but let's go to another caller here
matt in florida you're on the air go ahead
yes um i've been commissioned for you know almost 11 years now
um i've been in the guard double time and i will
smile my up front i will never confiscate anybody's guns i will
fight that order i will never shoot on my fellow
of citizens i'll fight that's why they got the guys in katrina from another
state because they knew their guys in their own state their own
neighborhood wouldn't confiscate their fellow neighbors
guns see that's ridiculous if i'm from texas i wouldn't take new yorkers guns
i mean how is it different from a different state
well it's just it's just it's mental i think i mean if you're sitting there
right in your own city and that's why they originally got these guys that's
why a lot of them now i've come back and said well that's
ridiculous why did i do that i you know a lot of them were brainwashed a lot of
the young guys that just didn't know any better by the way that's what the soviets
did and at tiananmen square the same thing
that's why they had to wait eight hours they brought troops in from 300 miles
away from another province that spoke a
different type of chinese yeah and so my concern right now is this
whole dual status commander thing and i know you've tried to talk about
before but it's where a general in the in the national guard can command
troops from um the active duty so they can come down
as long as the governor says yeah it's good they'll come in and they'll be able
to basically be on the street with our soldiers you know shoulder to shoulder
with our national guard troops and that's you know
and then the round on posse comitatus and
it's ridiculous i mean it's it's just another way of them creating in that
active duty component they you know they don't know the rules and regulations of
the national what do you make of the new army manuals that
train for gun confiscation and lockdown of u.s cities
it's ridiculous and i've showed that to some guys and they're like holy cow the
guys in my unit they're like this is this is unbelievable where's this you
know and so the the reason i'm staying in and i've
last few years my wife has always asked me why are you staying in you know you
had the you know thing that you say about the military well it's like i stay
in because i want to warn people i want to wake people up that's why
that's my beautiful um and then every time i go to drill on my weekend
every month i i talk to them about what's going on i wake
to wake people up all the time that's why they want to have the litmus test
purge is to get the good people out and again
the military itself is individuals it's who's in command of
it people say well you're anti-military you
don't want checkpoints on the highway no i'm pro-constitution it's like saying
i'm anti-ford truck i'm not anti-ford truck
i don't want a crazy person running me over with a ford truck it's just like
i'm not anti-gun i'm anti bad people with guns but bad people
always have guns so i'm gonna have my gun don't blame me
for what somebody else does beautiful comments i want to bring up dr garrow to
bring up any points he's got well you know the whole psychological
breakdown here of loyalties because of familiarity
uh... that's a classic as a classic move to break down
uh... not only the
uh... the loyals
he won two another for for example you know that the guy you've worked with
been trained with this dinner
look after you and and and have your back
in a combat situation and you know that you're going to be loyal or they know
that you're going to be loyal to the guy who trained you at the officer above you
uh... or overall
policy the general uh... who has uh... showing themselves to be honorable and
uh... and very loyal to their man
and been a real leader i mean that's that's real loyalty well they want to
break that down they want to break it down because if if they can break the
familiarity pattern
uh... yes one another and knowing what the expectation is they can bring in
somebody new and guess what
you'll do what they say why don't know any better
but but then that actually destroys the military but they don't care the heart
of military is the honor and taking care of each other because they don't care
they want you to act like robots because they want robots
they'll follow their orders that's why they're going to robots
no man left behind happened we've just seen a huge demonstration of the fact that
that no longer exists with the commander in chief
well it wasn't just left behind
a lot of evidence shows they were he wanted actually that ambassador killed
because he wasn't playing ball they were transferring missiles
to al-qaeda we know they stood down for eight hours
with troops right down the street at a substation base in order to stand down
and only two navy seals
refused to not follow orders and went down and held off five hundred guys for
eight hours i mean this is just incredible
it is this is that
coming up some good news out yesterday
let me bring up some good news
i got a little thing and this is i'm calling this the most of the world
remember that silly movie with peter sellers the most of the world
uh... little
uh... it
principality of feswick or something like that gets an atomic bomb and and
because the united states to surrender
yes the most that
the most that were going to tell you about a little most of the road is that
that's happening right now
there's a lawsuit
uh... it's against unlawful
tyranny filed against uh...
mister obama
at the united states government for acting like a king
uh...
and it's here has been filed as a lawsuit uh... is to set us in who is
there is a proper has no money
uh... approach the court
uh... made his case
in fact
the judge wanted to throw it out but for the wrong reason
and so he's come back refile
and uh... having he's having her removed because she's an obama appointee
uh... who was obviously trying to protect obama because
this is kind of
it's about the natural law
uh... and uh... having an unnatural
uh... born citizen
by the way uh... obama has uh... two courts have slapped him down
for doing unconstitutional things on recess appointments
uh... and other areas uh... caller matt in florida
a uh... national guard officer anything else you'd like to add
yeah the other thing is um... guys that are in the army war college
you know as a national guardsman and they're basically being
talking about this whole dual status command thing
almost all the guys and luckily the guy that i know we've been there
was against the dual status commander they were actually trying to do regional dual status
commanders which they have a
as they have a commander that would be in charge of federal states
and uh... yeah what they're doing is they've created the ten
yeah they've created the ten regions with the governor saying you don't need
fifty so oh we we have governors the the governors
we appointed yeah they're they're trying to totally get rid of any
state control of the national guard when it's always been state go ahead
that's what i said i was like you know he said that that basically goes against all state
sovereignty law i mean that's just
basically he says the law of that governor and i guess they would have to be in on it
but still it's just like
you know the state sovereignty doesn't exist anymore at that point i mean
the final thing was i know you talked about this before as well but that that uh...
guard experience magazine that came out that comes out and i get it and i got it
since it was the middle of uh... year last year
and they had on the front cover the thread at home and they had a guy
his face was blacked out and he was in military uniform full battle gear
and it's like the thread at home talks about how
our returning veterans and he's on a guard national guard magazine and like
this is
i mean i i don't know if you're trying to every angle they're trying to you know
throw this at us and it's like it's completely ridiculous when they send our guys over
three four five six times huffed up on painkillers and depression medicine and they
and they come back and they wonder why they're upset or angry or they come back and
you know life is totally flipped upside down and they wonder why these guys are
are you know a little off you know it's completely ridiculous
absolutely god bless you and i appreciate your call we're gonna go to more military
calls but first get another comment from uh... doctor jim garrow
who's on with us right now but if we punch this up for tv viewers
uh... you can see at info wars dot com june first
two thousand and twelve we were mailed a copy of this
the actual magazine this is what the national guard is all mailed
national guard magazine cover story
specifies americans as great as terror threat
well it actually says veterans
they're telling you you're the terrorist now go fight yourself
and let's continue the latest edition of the guards experience
the national guards official magazine features a cover story titled the threat
at home
and it is a guy in a national guard uniform
with explosives tucked in
who and what are the biggest dangers to homeland security
now if you're a foreign megabank that took over america
you're getting ready to fully gut it
you're gonna say the veterans who were patriots and willing to fight they're
the enemy
i mean imagine if it is out of a simpsons episode with the spaceship lands
what's the name of the simpsons town
springfield
uh... it's one of the few episodes i've seen and and and uh...
the spaceship lands and ugg and gugg these big
fourteen foot green aliens
we are your rulers and the mayor and the
rockefeller guy
uh... comes up and says yes you're right we bow to you which is exactly how it
would work
this would be like a giant flying saucer landing announcing will destroy your
planet from orbit
if you don't bow to us
and by the way the new enemy is anyone that says
that the planet booble bapper or whatever isn't in control
and uh... you know now here's your new guard magazine
anyone that says aliens don't have a right to rule you as the enemy i mean
you know founding fathers are bad george washington's bad
uh... bill of rights is bad private property bad
a mouse a tongue good tyranny good i mean this is what they teach at the
colleges
and now they're saying that
alex jones and they say in articles on a terrorist i'm a radical i'm gonna kill
people cnn said they need to kill me
because i'm gonna kill them and they would want to be in a room with me
because i might kill on my have no criminal record
i mean these are mad dog tyrants
and you know since the guy mentions that see when i'm listening to a guest or
caller i know they're for real
cuz i'm immersed in this stuff
okay i'm not bragging i mean i live this i'd read this
so that they're saying things i know they're true or not
truth is already know almost all the stuff
i just have folks on to give their views on it
and different perspectives i'm here to get you to be aware of it
but the callers like it's so ridiculous they're teaching us the military or the
number one terrorist
in our own magazine
that's because they really are in power i'm sorry go ahead
they're stealing the last thing which back to that i think i think about that
uh... you've got a fact
you've got all about the man who's given service to the country and he's the
terrorist okay now the public's looking at terrorist
redefining
redefining the language
are we not
yes i mean i mean it's incredible
okay connect and do we have some time to talk just for a second about about
something that goes way back to this whole notion of redefining things is
stealing the language
absolutely
can we do that don't let me go
yes go give it to us let me let me go way back way back let's go into the
bible for a second
do you remember
do you remember when all of the disciples
polls first came together
remember it says something about
and they had
they held everything in common
it meant that the rich people brought in
uh... the goods and services that they had in the dollars that they have
because god had blessed them with it
what was the notion
they were going to share it they were going to have it in common
not a redistribution of wealth it's a big difference here there's a huge
difference between
as sociological kind of thing that marxist kind of thing
that they're talking about
obama and crew
so they held everything in common
later on we have the english or the british common law
what's it come out of
it comes out of the scriptures
what has obama dot
he has taken
common ism common ism and turned it into communism two different things
gives glory to god
for the balance
further blessings that he has given
and the responsibility do you have one to another
as christians or citizens one to another
you hold things in common
that's black
and if you notice boston common it what that isn't that that piece of land that
everyone has in common
is to be the principal park in the downtown of all the little villages
that were around the little towns there were comments
they were areas where they've been it was happy in common it was a privately
owned it was probably out it was held in common for the good of the common man
the common man
obama and crew are doing and and they're teaching this universities is stealing
the language so you think that because you give something away to someone that
that's being a good socialist
giving into those who have to have me because you have
well that's not what it is
the original christian message was that we
polls all things in common
from the bounty of god who gave it to us so we share that bounty of god as a
responsibility
not as a social nightmare
but defined by marxist
i'm just bringing that up for for uh... short message
there now you're absolutely right and right now on screen for t b viewers
i'm showing the p d f of the national guard magazine
and it says the number one threat in here is gun owners veterans and things
like that
next al-qaeda it puts malicious
next al-qaeda
next a counterfeiting
next to loan groups
and says it's the military's job
now to operate
domestically
and it's in search of the hidden enemy look everywhere but washington
with the globalists that have taken over
trust
no one
the government again that is the message they hammer home
more calls for military jason marine robin others
national guard straight ahead
if you've ever wanted one of our best-selling generators but we're
waiting for an offer so crazy you couldn't refuse that you're not going
to want to miss this exciting message here's why
are solar generators provide life-saving electrical power and unlike gas
generators solar generators run quietly
amid no fumes and produce electricity from the sun so when the lights go out
you'll always have the power you need now here's the best part
every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as
new we put them in a special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily
at the end of each year we call them scratch and dead units but they're
really just like new each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special
bonuses you just won't believe
don't wait they go fast go to scratch and then solar dot com that scratch and
then solar dot com for the craziest offer we've ever made
go to scratch and then solar dot com that scratch and then solar dot com
my name is frank bates
what i'm about to tell you in the next sixty seconds could get me a lot of
trouble
i just created a free video presentation at one two three cover up dot com
that exposes the electricity monopolies and government agencies for what they
really are incompetent line crooks that are counting on your ignorance and fear
to keep your power bills criminally high
some have called this a conspiracy
others have called it a cover up and you will be shocked to find out how deep the
conspiracy goes
my video at one two three cover up dot com exposes the truth and shows you the
secret of how i beat them and how you can beat them too
watch the controversial video that thousands of other smart patriots have
already seen in the last three months
go to one two three cover up dot com and discover one weird trick to slash your
power bill and protect your home
go watch my video now at one two three cover up dot com
before they force me to shut it down
again that's one two three cover up dot com
you land in buenos aries
then a shuttle to santa rosa where a nicely furnished cabin with all
amenities wi-fi executive food and wine and laundry service awaits
after a good night's sleep your adventure begins
you're on a golden stag safari for big game
but it's not africa
it's argentina
one-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo
big horn rams wild boar and the biggest stag deer in south america all gold
metal quality all the action you can handle
land rovers top rental guns with scopes all food beverages hunting guides ground
transportation included and more all more affordable than you can imagine
the adventure of a lifetime starts at golden stag safaris dot com
the big game hunting ranch
golden stag safaris dot com
don't forget this broadcast is listeners supported
and we have all the sponsors that i have vetted
that i believe in whether it's info wars health dot com
the finest health care products out there that have been incredibly well
researched
look at the studies videos all of it up there
uh... whether it's minus resources the name
for fifteen years uh... in precious metals
uh... they've got a lot of great deals on gold silver you name it just call
them and tell them
alex jones since you want the daily radio specials that are
the days lost leaders
and that's eight hundred six eight six two two three seven
uh... our online video bookstore t-shirt apparel shopping cart info war
store dot coms at the best water filters
all of it i support us so we can have other people
on the worldwide transmission
uh... to support what they're doing we are something here to magnify edifying
information and try to shake people out of their coma take a few final calls for
doctor jim garrow
who's been helping blow the whistle on uh...
obama trying to get the military to fire on citizens
it's good news though that a haggle came out and said he's got to get rid of the
entire military leadership that
the pentagon is in under the president's command
as the president came to congress
and told them he's under nato and you in command
the president is by that action
guilty of
tyrannical
uh... treasonous activity i mean it is that is what it is to me
this stuff show over the top words can't describe it
uh... let's go to rob who's a new york uh... coast guard
internal survey on confiscation rob quickly thanks for holding tell us what
you know
alex
don't want to speak with you and thanks for everything which is going to get the
message out there thank you sir
back in the early nineteen nineties
i'm going back maybe nineteen ninety two ninety three they did surveys back then
with the u_-s-military
and a lot of servicemen says no we won't fire upon american people you know
carpet if there was ever marshall you know that was in the news actually about
ninety four it was clinton
uh... yes so they tried this before the good news is
they try we fight they try we fight
it's an eternal battle go ahead
right exactly so what they did was since the united states military said no
faces okay
will bring in foreign troops on the united nations
that they did and yep and they hate them in the united nations biosphere is
around the country
well they don't even hide and they do the open training now under n l e and
all the rest of the god bless you great points
uh... your comments on that doctor garrow
well i mean let's face it uh... these people are planning to get a long range
plan in place
uh... i think that they don't think it's a rather big groups
moment
until you think
figures honesty covered out
but don't you think that uh... poor obama's got a going out
you shouldn't have said that in public
but we have the benefit of honesty for a change
well i mean hagel has been a builder burger hagel is somebody they really
like a you know ninety plus percent of the votes when he won the senate
work out on a company he owned
so that you give an idea about all all mister hagel let's jam in one more real
quick
captain briggs in illinois i go ahead
today uh... el jefe el guapo alexander one
and doctor garrow
and i have a lot of back and forth between texas illinois and new jersey
and uh... actually spoke to my son is on active duty in hawaii
uh... the words from the troops around those three specific areas is no they
will not find the american people
and when things go down
the national guard guys will melt back into the populace
and for those guys like the young marine called in earlier
do the right thing
maintain your oath remember your values
and those of you who are being displaced from
uh... dictator obama's ranks
take care of your neighborhood and do it as peacefully as possible but prepare
for contingencies
well yeah again they're going to stage a false flag or use some other uh... real
crisis to come after everybody and
i don't think they're going to get away with it and for those who just tuned in
senator hagel was in the washington post they were quoting him in a meeting
saying you can't trust the military that under your command
that's because
we know for the military's actions they've been refusing
unlawful orders
i want to thank doctor jim garrow for joining us he helps
save a forty five thousand chinese girls that would have been killed after birth
uh... picked up a girl's dot com great have a young great having that big
updates are
thanks alex it was great to be here
included but again
yet we'll talk to you soon on a few minutes overdrive
to talk to jesse dot and jason stay with us info wars dot com
thank you for listening to GCN
visit GCNlive.com today
now that we have moved into the winter season there is an increased need to
support our immunity and health
at silver lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full
selection of silver-based products
our most popular silver-based products are the thirty two ounce nano silver
solutions our two ounce nano silver nasal applicators as well as our
all-natural silver soaps
just released is our one hundred percent natural silver gel
our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents which quickly
evaporate and leave the silver at the surface
but rather we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin
nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin
while delivering the silver more effectively
visit www.silverlungs.com
and click on our store page to find what silver-based products are best for you
that's www.silverlungs.com
coast to coast
direct from austin
you're listening to the alex jones broadcasting network
big brother
mainstream media
government cover-ups
you want answers
well so does he
he's alex jones
on the gcn radio network
and now live from austin texas
alex jones
we're into overdrive you know i didn't even get to the uh... msnbc host
talking about cracker white people can we queue that up
and we'll go to that in a moment uh... jesse in arizona
was saying congress reported on arizona shooting beforehand
uh... you know they did that with building seven they said it had fallen
in its own footprint before it did an hour before and then
they said the same thing about jfk
because they get their timing off sometimes
uh... let's go ahead and uh... go to jesse jesse what did you say
uh...
thank you for having me on alex
uh... senator watching the local news
and they hadn't even finished blocking the building down
and the reporter goes let's go back to
the congressional hearings that coincidentally
are
being held
over begun violence and kathy gifford is having
you know her speech there
pushing all this propaganda from obama
and
this guy mark kelly goes
yeah i have information that there was a shooting in phoenix arizona this morning
with multiple injuries
and the people weren't even
at the hospital yet being reported locally
but they already knew inside the congressional hearing
well that's because homeland security is wired into all the local police
departments now and
but we need to time that because this won't be the first time they screwed up if that's
what happened sometimes they reported before it even starts and that's how we
catch them
yeah and it but he was knowing that there was multiple
multiple injuries and it's called it's called jumping the gun
uh... i'll have to look into that we were recording it this morning
and so we'll look into it thank you so much great point by the way aaron dikes
ran in with this report
msnbc
uh... edit portrays gun owners as heckling father
of sandy hook victim
remember msnbc is being sued
for editing the the zimmerman tape
or zimmerman's going uh... okay there's a guy with a hoodie walking around okay
uh...
what's he doing he's doing this uh... what color is the uh... looks like he's
black
they added it to yeah there's a guy walking with a hoodie he's black
and then got caught doing it so
this is breaking
uh... cable propaganda network deliberately edits out
sandy hook family member asking audience a question
which gun rights advocate responds to and makes it look like
heckling
uh... we're going to uh...
let's add the part about zimmerman in here
i think that's very very important to show they have a
history of this
speaking of msnbc
uh... let's go to a clip
of one of their people uh... on there
uh...
saying uh... crackers
again get white people to think everybody who's of color is racist this
is open race-baiting this this is racism to create racism for divide and conquer
here it is
those you know crazy crackers on the right like if they start with their very
hateful language
that is going to kill them in the same way the death knell for republicans is the
tone of the conversation they absolutely have even have a white woman
uh... this uh... finney come out and say it
and and it's led by that you don't turn your guns in your races cracker
you don't turn your guns in your southerners are trash al sharpton
that overcome the southerners and the constitution i mean it's just
it's it's absolutely we're northerners we're gonna get the southerners
trying to get northerners act like that when others are like that it's
we have the all sharpened about drones
here's al sharpened about door your guns mean nothing we got the drones now
here it is i mean if you look at the second amendment
it was that you would have a militia to protect yourself
in case the government came and attack citizens first of all
if the government were to come to disarm you
you would not be able to use an automatic weapon to defend yourself
let's be serious we're in a world
of drones now so
the second amendment would not help you in that area we're talking about people do
not have the right to unregulated rights you see and everybody's really smiling when they hear
about the drones oh those are our drones the government loves us yeah the
government's sworn to kill you
i mean you know i mean the people that run the government the globalist set up
planned parenthood to make sure most of you weren't born
and it's like the government's our friend it's that same look like little
kids like they've been after sitting on santa claus's lap government loves me
oh we got the drones now we got the drones we got the drones meanwhile what
is it more than half your men end up in prison
this is so sick it's so sick so sick