Big Brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups. You want answers? Well, so does
he. He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network. And now, live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
Well a senior Obama official says, quote, we're gonna kill the dollar. And CBS News
with a straight face has pundits on saying, it's time to scrap the Constitution. Quote,
let's give up on the Constitution as if it caused all the problems when we've been completely
allowing criminals to ignore it.
Welcome ladies and gentlemen, it is Monday, the 28th day of January 2013. And we don't
have any guests today, because I want to take your phone calls on all the things that we
see happening in this world. The incredible acceleration of tyranny. We'll get the number
out coming up in the next segment and just cover a ton of news.
Obama's meeting with police chiefs that are anti-gun and basically on the federal payroll
today. Acting like police wanna take the public's guns when national surveys show that
they can pull these up. Over 90% of sheriff's departments and police departments are actually
pro-gun.
Because despite the fact that they're getting federal funds to say that the opposite, they
know guns frustrate crime many more times than they actually are used in the commission
of crimes. They know the FBI's own statistics garnered and the standard of good statistics.
That crime's gone down 49% in the last 20 years, 21% just since 2007. So it's accelerating.
They know that. And that's why you see this all out attack on the Second Amendment is
because the gun culture is gonna kill the tyranny culture.
It's like it killed the tyranny culture in 1775, 1776, 1777, 78, 79, 80, 81. Now, I've
really done some deep thinking and a lot of what I'm gonna say today I've already said,
but I'm gonna try to say it as clearly as I possibly can. My great frustration is I'll
be sitting there making my children eggs or I'll be walking the dogs or carrying the laundry
in the laundry room and I'll just have these clear, concise points I wanna make.
And then by the time I get here to the radio and engage in management on a half dozen issues
and scan back over another 20, 30, 40 articles and watch video clips, I get in here and my
head's spinning. But I am gonna attempt to just basically break down what we're facing
as a society and take your phone calls.
We got a call yesterday about hacked emails out of a big British defense contractor. Paul
Watson's gone over the cash and it's scans of passports, you name it. There's thousands
of pages. If it is a hoax, it's an elaborate hoax. Watson, who's got a pretty good nose
for these things, thinks it's real.
At least most of it, they also mix garbage in. And the reason I think it has credibility
is it dovetails with something we've been covering for a year intensely the last six
months with our contacts like Syrian Girl and others. And of course, Israel said yesterday
they're preparing to strike Syria. They believe any of the rebels, including Western backed
rebels, they're calling the government rebels and the West rebels rebels.
If any of them get the chemical weapons of Syria that are guarded by Russia, that they're
going to use that as a pretext to attack the country. And hacked emails reveal Washington
approved plan to stage chemical weapons attack in Syria. We've actually seen al-Qaeda rebels
arrogant enough to shoot videos where they're testing sarin. Thank God they don't have VX.
Sarin's bad enough though. One whiff of that, you're dead. They send that up an assessment,
spray that over a city. Tens of thousands dead, bare minimum. And these are the historical
times where all the battle lines are drawn.
And when you see a World War I, World War II type event happening, and that's what all
the think tanks are saying. The CFR, others are saying get ready for World War III. I'm
not saying that, I'm reporting on what they're saying. And there's already just, I don't
know, five, six different nations in war in Africa with the West starting that.
Multiple Middle Eastern nations, just all sorts of craziness going on. We're on the
edge of some very serious things accelerating. So that's all coming up and they're getting
ready to legalize all the illegal aliens. Republicans are telling us this is the time
to submit to the new world order.
Now that we have moved into the winter season, there is an increased need to support our
immunity and health. At Silver Lungs, we are committed to meeting your needs by providing
a full selection of silver based products. Our most popular silver based products are
the 32 ounce nano silver solutions, our two ounce nano silver nasal applicators, as well
as our all natural silver soaps. Just released is our 100% natural silver gel. Our new silver
gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents, which quickly evaporate and leave the silver
at the surface. But rather, we have formulated our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing
chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate and nourish the skin while delivering the
silver more effectively. Visit www.silverlungs.com and click on our store page to find what silver
based products are best for you. That's www.silverlungs.com.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy? Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At eFoods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my eFoods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today, or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting non-GMO long-term storable food on the planet. Call
800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on eFoods Direct.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers. The prognosis for the entire planetary
economic system runs from bad to worse. The globalist model is to shut down societies
and starve patriots out until they acquiesce to the global takeover. That's why we've assembled
the most vital and important preparedness items at infowarshop.com. These are items
that I did research on that I personally use. You've got the LifeStraw so you can turn
fetid water into safe water anywhere you go. The Ktor Hand Crank Generator to charge up
key equipment during power outages or out in the field. Strategic Relocation Third Edition
by Joel Skousen. When Disaster Strikes by Matthew Stein. TheraSafe used by Homeland
Security to protect yourself during any radiological event. Hand Crank Shortwave AM-FM Radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at infowarshop.com
and your purchase makes our Infowars possible. We're getting prepared. Are you? Infowarsshop.com.
Defending the Republic from enemies born and domestic. It's Alex Jones. It is Monday my
friends the 28th day of January 2013. I am your host Alex Jones and whatever time zone
you're listening to us day, night or of course in the morning whether you're a ship at sea.
Our folks even listening as they fly into their local airport. It is good to have you
all tuning into the broadcast today. We're gonna have wide open phones. Let me just go
over the headlines here. Then I'm going to give the number out and then we will drill
into this news and more throughout the day.
But we are gonna have open phones throughout the full three hours today on the economy,
the Second Amendment, the dollar. The news coming out at infowars.com that hacked emails
reveal Washington approved plan to stage chemical weapons attack in Syria. Obama administration
complicit in war crime. Also, Netanyahu deploy Syrian Iron Dome as Israeli minister claims
US preparing surgical strikes against Iran.
We also have Israel saying that they believe that Al Qaeda is gonna get chemical weapons
so they have to attack the Syrian government who's fighting Al Qaeda. That's Reuters. The
Senate is reaching a deal to open the borders open completely. We're gonna get into all
that. In fact, it's amazing to see Jindal and to see even Rand Paul saying we've got
to get with the times as Republicans.
And just basically open the borders up. And the Pentagon's announcing they're taking any
crosses down out of chapels. Major denominations are taking the crosses down. I mean, the point
is it's all about social control and then and the Republicans are saying if we just
become the Democrats, then they'll vote for us.
And it's all a giant hoax. Conservatives and libertarians have said on record in the polls
have shown this. They didn't vote for Mitt Romney because he wrote the assault weapons
ban in his state and got it passed. The semi auto ban, Massachusetts. He was for open borders.
He was for the carbon tax, wrote Obamacare. Do I need to keep listing all this? Again,
people aren't voting.
They're voting by digging in and buying firearms. They're voting by stopping to pay income tax
the private Federal Reserve. I mean, they're reporting now 50 something million Americans
aren't paying income tax. Good, the illegal aliens don't.
This is what's happening. The American people, Congress has a 9% approval rating in the last
even fake Gallup poll. I'm sure it's lower than that probably. The only way they can
get you to support the government is by having a left right fake fight between Obama and
the Republicans to make you think there's an illusion, sucking you into the debate.
And having Obama come out for things so outrageous that then people are forced to go support
the Republican establishment. Who then tells them, you know what, if we just give up and
basically act like a Democratic Party of the 1990s. And then now the new Democratic Party
acts like Mao Zedong, then we're gonna win.
Well, there's no point in winning that because the globalists have won. And this is how they
got Europe to give up their rights and have on average a 65% federal tax rate. You add
local taxes in, the average European's paying over 80%. The average European is paying over
80%, look it up. In one form or tax or another, that golfer was talking about leaving California
a few weeks ago and got demonized by the media.
So what of the media, the dying dinosaur media demonizes you? And he was saying, a Mickelson
was saying, I'm paying 63, 65% federal and state tax. Well, that's only your state income
tax and your federal tax, buh-buh. 40% federal, 13% state and then the property taxes and
the fines, the fees, the regulation taxes, the water taxes, the cell phone taxes.
The land use taxes, the hospital district taxes, the light bulb taxes. I mean, there's
hundreds of taxes. Most of them you don't see, they're built in to the bill you get.
Or if you do, it's a big list of fees and add-ons. It's a joke. But if you're a quote,
globalist stakeholder, a Fortune 500, you're pretty much exempt from those taxes because
you lobby and control and have your politicians in there.
It's designed so only they can flourish. That's agenda 21. That's royalty 2.0 where the mega
corporations and the old royalty and the big six global banks are all exempt from the rules.
Congress is exempt from the Obamacare taxes. They're exempt from the pension taxes that
are now law. They're exempt from insider trading laws. They're exempt from the gun laws in
the new bill.
Think of all the things they're exempt from. They're exempt from everything. Now, I was
reading where Congress people shove a congressional badge and they can walk through the checkpoints.
People ask, well, then why does Ron Paul get harassed? Why does Rand Paul? They refuse
to use the passes to make a point.
But this is the model. In fact, studying French royalty, British royalty, German royalty,
Russian royalty in the last 500 years, go study it. It's a fascinating study. There
had been reforms in Russia, in England, in the continent of Europe, in Austria, in France,
in the Netherlands in the last 500 years that our forebears fought and died for in huge
wars, huge civil wars so that government wasn't God.
Because before that, the king or any of his designates would simply say, I want your wife,
Prema Noctu, you gotta give her to me. I want your property. You couldn't own a dog unless
the half its digits were cut off so that it couldn't chase the king's game.
If you had a sheepdog, it was specially licensed and had several of its paws digits or pads
cut off. You couldn't have a knife unless the end was cut off. You had to have it as
a butcher. There was a tax on it and the end of it was cut off blunt. Death if you were
found.
That's up. Same laws in feudal Japan. Feudalism is what the Club of Rome, the CFR, the UN
says they wanna go back to. Take the biological diversity assessment 1996, covered in my film
Road to Tyranny 2001. And I show them, I show copies of the biological diversity assessment
saying neo-feudalism is what we want.
Making people poor so they can be managed and controlled. And so less resources get
used better for the earth. They consciously wanna go back to royalty and the UN, the City
of London, the Vatican, Israel to a great extent. And now the mega banks, look it up,
they're pushing to get diplomatic immunity for their carbon taxes.
They already have it at the IMF and World Bank when the mega banks are involved in those
transactions. Now they want it in all of their transactions and to make their derivatives
a global worlds, not national security, global world security operation where they cannot
be investigated. These are just criminals taking it to the limit.
They're con men, so they tell you we are now above the law. And this is what I talked about
yesterday. By every definition historically, they are extreme royalty. They are more royal
than a British king 400 years ago. They are more royal than Henry VIII. Henry VIII had
to at least go to kangaroo courts to get a divorce or to kill somebody.
Before that, kings would simply say, take him away, take them away, take whoever away.
And he would get lords over the different sectors. Because you might have a good lord
for a while, things would flourish, but always a bad one got in because of decadence. And
then they would never get out of power. And they would start marrying their horses about
Caligula or, again, I use the Nero example cuz it's so incredible.
On record, they had these big 24 hour feast. And he would dress up as a werewolf and they'd
chain little kids up. And Nero would run in and rip their throats out in a feverish thing
with blood splattering all over him. I mean, that's what you get. I have articles here
out of North Korea, Sunday Times of London investigation, confirming that the people
eat their children.
And that even the middle classes now go and at the meat markets buy people that have died
of starvation and then just eat the meager meat off the bones. And that was reported
by Vanity Fair like 12 years ago. I was sitting in a haircutting place and saw it and picked
up Vanity Fair. They had an article about it, strangely enough.
The point is, this is total government. This is what it creates, stagnation and collapse.
And so the most extreme royalty could just say, take him away to the dungeon. Our forebearers
in Europe fought for reforms in revolt after revolt against trained militaries that live
behind the walls of the castle.
And if you dared fight back against trained men in armor, because they killed your dad,
killed your mom, killed your sister. You dared jumped up on one of them, beat their brains
out. Out would come 500 armed men and they would kill sometimes your entire village.
Burn it to the ground, kill everyone. They would come and do inspections of the little
shack huts in the middle of the winter. In some cases when a third of the village was
dying from malnutrition, you gotta go read these accounts.
And they would come in and they would say, I smell meat cooking. You've got rabbit stew.
And if you had an attractive daughter, they'd say, I'm gonna sit here and eat the stew.
And then I'm gonna have sex with your daughter. And if you don't like it, I'm gonna kill you.
Now that's if you were lucky, if you were lucky. A lot of times they'd already raped
and killed so much, they just say, who do I wanna kill? I think I'll kill your wife.
And they'd come in, and they'd tie your wife down, and they'd slit her throat right in
front of you. How's that sound? You want royalty? You wanna live under royalty? You think that?
Cuz they got big flowing robes and big crowns. People magazine, it's so cool. America was
born out of hating this, okay? The enlightenment, the renaissance, all of it was about spitting
on royalty, okay?
And that's why they bad mouth George Washington. That's why they bad mouth our founding fathers,
all of it. Because we are the antidote to their poison. We are the republic. We are
the best there's ever been. And now we're going the opposite direction. And the traitors
in the globalist media everywhere bad mouth our country and our forebearers and the Second
Amendment because they're bringing us back into slavery. The news is coming up.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive? From natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy. Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything. At e Foods
Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm
by having a supply of food on hand. After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City
wrote, almost all the grocery stores are closed, but I managed to get my e Foods just in time
to be able to help my sister and niece. It is better to be prepared 10 years too early
than one day too late. I can warn you, but I can't feed you. Heed the warnings and do
what Alex has done. Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build
your food supply. It's the best tasting non GMO long term storeable food on the planet.
Or call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex. You can bet your life on e Foods Direct.
Feeling like there are too many pressures and demands on you? Losing sleep, worrying
about tests and school work, eating on the run because your schedule is just too busy?
You may be under too much stress and it may be affecting your mind. Get your mental edge
back with Neutropic Mind Power from mindregard.com. Neutropic Mind Power is not a drug, but a
natural supplement. It's 12 powerful ingredients are natural and non GMO plus it's gluten free,
wheat free and formulated by Americans for Americans by an NSF certified laboratory.
Neutropic Mind Power is available at mindregard.com spelled M-I-N-D-R-E-G-A-R-D.com and comes
with a 100% money back guarantee. Free your mind with Neutropic Mind Power, cognitive
supplement from mindregard.com. Mindregard, clearly see tomorrow and yesterday, today.
HempUSA.org has a newly designed website and a new and improved detoxification product.
Order our new micro plant powder gold loaded with vitamins, minerals, iodine and probiotics
and we'll send you our travel size micro plant powder absolutely free. Micro plant powder
only at HempUSA.org. Call 908-691-2608. That's 908-691-2608 and see what our powder, seeds
and oil can do for you. Only at HempUSA.org. Only this offer ends January 31st.
Hi, this is Ted Anderson. Have you ever wondered why banks, stock workers, investment advisors
won't talk about gold IRAs? They've been available since 1986 yet the financial industry
won't recognize the value of gold for your retirement. Gold has outperformed paper investments
yet no word about IRAs. If you would like to have gold for your retirement call 800-686-2237.
Don't get left behind by rising inflation and low returns call 800-686-2237. Secure your
future and call 1-800-686-2237. Is 2013 your year to achieve more? More vitality, more
health, more well-being? Hi, this is Pastor Jenny. For 25 years I spent my life's work
teaching others how to achieve more. But in 2010 I got a lesson of my own about RNA drops.
I learned that there are millions of gene switches latent in every single cell of my
body that are waiting for an activator. I learned by taking RNA drops I could begin
to activate that power in my cells and achieve the more that I desire. I'd like to share
what I discovered with you and send you a free 30-day supply of RNA drops valued at
$50 for just the cost of shipping and handling. Go to RNAfreesample.com. That's RNAfreesample.com
or call me toll free at 888-577-3703. That's 888-577-3703. RNAfreesample.com. Discover
the more that's waiting for you. Ladies and gentlemen, I just want to finish up on the
history lesson and then I'll get into Obama and Piers Morgan playing possum. They always
come after the guns then say, oh, they're not coming after them. So everybody settles
down so they can gauge the opposition and then they move forward against the guns again.
I'm going to be breaking that down. We have articles up in fullwars.com. And again, we
expected that just like they wrote the NDAA then said, don't worry, we're against it.
I'm going to veto it so that no opposition would form. Then he still signed it. Then
they bring out bills to repeal the NDAA, expanding it to actually get rid of posse commentatis.
So often now they go, oh, we'll pass a bill to ban insider trading. Then the bill legalizes
it. We'll pass a law to stop you being secretly disappeared, where the king says take him
away. And a black bag is thrown over your head and you disappear into a spider hole.
And then they have a new NDAA come out that says we just completely get rid of the posse
commentatis. And then it's not even an issue. I mean, we've entered a world of deception
where even though I'm focused on it, 16 hours a day conservatively, it's so over the top.
It's such a full hologram like spectrum of lies that it even makes me get dizzy.
And that's why a lot of people that trusted the system are now waking up, but they still
have childlike minds. And so they then just believe everything's fake. Again, just because
the media and the government lies doesn't mean that every alternative media is going
to have all the answers. It doesn't mean I'm going to have all the answers.
Just because the system is knowingly lying and twisting doesn't then mean that there's
some other perfect truth out there as well. Remember that. Now, back to the issue of,
let's just take European history because it's dominated the last 200 years. Feudalism settled
in in Mesoamerica. Feudalism settled in in China, starting of course with the Chen Dynasties.
It settled in in Japan. It settled in in Africa. Same system, you'd have royal chiefs with
the dominant tribe and generally slave tribes around them who weren't really slaves. They
were mainly light serfs compared to Europeans, but they still had to give fealty and basically
bow down to whatever dominant tribe was in the area.
Same thing with the Native American tribes. I mean, humans set up the same system over
and over again. Middle East had the same deal pre-Muhammad, 700 and something years ago.
And so when I say extreme royalty, generally it would be rule of God king where the king
is worshiped as God, the Pharaoh is worshiped as God. And if you criticize in any way, you're
not just seen as a traitor, you're seen as insane and as the devil and you are promptly
killed or thrown into a hard labor slave bed.
Now, that's been the norm. But Christians, if you go back about 550 years ago in Europe,
lots of different sects started popping up saying no to feudal slavery, no to kings being
absolute God men, no to the general public being total slaves, total slaves, total. And
so because some people started to fight back and got some basic rights, well, everybody
still wanted slaves.
So the Arab slave trade was going with Africans they were grabbing out of the North and off
the Gold Coast. And so these transatlantic slave trade began because nobody, the Christians
weren't gonna put up, the real Christians in different groups, weren't gonna put up
with slaves.
They just been slaves. There were revolts all over France, all over Spain, all over
what's Portugal, all over, just constant wars by people saying we're not gonna be slaves.
Just like Chinese are revolting right now. They have hundreds of riots a week. Look it
up. People with broom handles fighting troops with machine guns, okay?
So people say China's gonna take over, the globalists are trying to prop it up. It could
collapse at any time and that'd be a good thing for their people. Our government helped
put Mao Zedong in in 49. It's because our government is a traitor government working
for tyranny worldwide.
And we've been taken over for a long time. Now they've just gotten bold in this program.
And so when I say extreme royalty, extreme royalty could just say, take them to the dungeon
off with their head, have you disappear. Royalty would smother their own family members, so
that they wouldn't try to murder them.
I mean, it was just the standard. Our forebearers in Europe, if you're European, fought against
this, got some basic rights. In countless civil wars, the Dutch settlers, British settlers,
others came over here for religious freedom. And of course, it immediately set up the same
slave system with Indians and blacks and others.
Because just because some people tried to get away from it, the same thing still kept
getting set up. So it's an ongoing generational battle. Now they make you a slave through
a prison record. Or they make you a slave where you've got to work for the government
to have a job. Or they make you take vaccines to have a job.
You see, see, there's all these new forms of high tech slavery, but the biggest slavery
is over the mind. The globalists know how to control your mind and program you, so they
don't have to physically have you chained up out in the barn, knowing you hate their
guts and want to kill them any chance you get.
They have taught us how to love our servitude. And now they're trying to bring back absolute
rule of monarchs under the UN, under global national security. Governments are operating
with extreme royal signets. They're operating like tyrant kings.
Here on the march, the empire's on the run. Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
And
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and use the promo code Silver2012 for 20% off.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com and like us on Facebook.
The New Year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to SupernaturalSilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's SupernaturalSilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
Tyranny is here.
The grim future foretold in 1984 has become reality.
It really says that the state is God.
The United States is now recognized globally as one of the most oppressive police states
on earth.
This film conclusively proves the existence of a secret network of FEMA camps now being
expanded nationwide.
Each documentary exposes how the continuity of government program has established an all-powerful
shadow state.
Police State 4 chronicles the sickening depths to which our republic has fallen.
Prepare to enter the secretive world of emergency dictatorship, body scanners, sound cameras,
citizen spies, stage terror and cameras on every street corner.
It's only the beginning of the New World Order's hellish plan.
The police state isn't coming.
It's here.
Secure your copy today at Infowars.com or see it online in the highest quality at PrisonPlanet.tv.
This is your last chance.
After this there is no turning back.
You take the blue pill, the story ends, you wake up in your bed and believe whatever you
want to do, you take the red pill, you stay in Wonderland and I show you how deep the
rabbit hole goes.
Remember all I'm offering is the truth, nothing more.
The answer to 1984 is 1776.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Show.
All right, we're going to have open phones throughout the transmission here today.
I'm going to get into some of the most important news right now.
First time callers are welcome but it's just an open free for all.
800-259-9231, 800-259-9231 and I did take a lot of calls yesterday once I got to your
call so I'm going to try to move quickly through people, 800-259-9231.
It's just the subject of understanding human history.
Those that don't know history are doomed to repeat it.
That's been said many, many times.
So no one knows who first said that give a man a gun, he can rob a bank.
Give a man a bank, he can rob the world but that's when banks use fractional reserve banking
where they loan out $1 for every 10 cents they have on deposit or $10 for every dollar
or $1,000 for every hundred.
Now they don't even do that.
They just create off derivatives a trillion off of $1 and then they buy the whole world
because we accept the illusion and the fraud.
The UN tells us they're above the law and that diplomatic immunity for narcotics trafficking,
mass murder, you name it.
The mega banks tell us they have immunity and are above the law.
The police tell us they have immunity and are above the law.
Not even true.
They tell you it's a privilege to travel.
No it's not.
Now they're saying it's a privilege to own guns.
But they just tell you over and over again.
Before I get to the news, we've launched two different big operations.
One of them is Operation Sleeping Giant at prisonplanet.tv, Infowars Nightly News.
You can get 11 memberships for $5.95 a month, create one username passcode, give it to friends
and family.
11 people can be logged on simultaneously and we've really upgraded and worked out bugs
on the site.
We've got 17 years of material, it's been up now 10 years, prisonplanet.tv and I wanna
thank all of you that are members and watch the Nightly News and download the films.
It is an armory of resistance but look, there's no excuse.
Now is the time to go get a membership or to buy a couple memberships because we're
giving it to you at cost.
The goal is just to pay for the bandwidth and then to get people to watch it and say,
hey, here's your free documentary film site.
It's got ebooks, my book, Paul Watson's book.
It's got the daytime radio show so you can watch it.
All the radio listeners on XM, AM and FM.
You should also have prisonplanet.tv memberships so you can watch the high-def archive of the
day show, the nighttime show live, special reports on The Rogue, there's so much there.
Prisonplanet.tv or get a yearly membership and this is gonna end next month.
We do this every holiday season into the new year.
You can get 5.3 months, it comes out to 5.3 months free when you sign up for a year.
You get five plus months off the regular cost and again, 11 people can use it simultaneously.
And unfortunately, not everybody who's got a membership or has been given the code is
gonna use it so it's probably like 20, 30 people could use the same username, passcode.
You may get locked out if more than 11 go log in but that's great news at any one time.
So again, get the membership, I've built the platform, built the news operation.
It's incredible reporters, research, guests.
It's all waiting to go, hey, here's your free alternative real news platform.
You are the Paul Revere, Operation Sleeping Giant.
And then speaking of Paul Revere, we need your help to go to infoawars.com, to go to
our YouTube page, to go to prisonplanet.tv.
Go to infoawars.com forward slash contest, infoawars.com forward slash contest and get
the four minute video for Operation Paul Revere.
You've now got three months until the 30th of April and you win $100,000 first place,
10,000 second, 5,000 third place.
And again, I did this because the money we make goes right back into the operation to
expand.
I can't think of a better way, conservatively, I would guess 15, 20, 30, 40, 50 million people
will end up seeing the 1,000 plus films that get made.
It can be three minutes long, it can be fiction, nonfiction, drama, it can be up to two hours
long.
And again, all of you win by entering the contest.
We need your help to get infoawars.com forward slash contest to have all of you go on IMDb
who are members of that.
For all of you who are listeners to go on YouTube, for all of you to go to all the film
sites and say, hey, here is this contest.
And you don't know who's out there that's a filmmaker, I saw people saying, I wish I
had a film degree, I'd make a film.
Folks, you go out and show corruption in your area, it isn't even about the quality, it
may be about quality, it's about the heart.
Because I'll tell you the real reason we're doing this is cuz it's a win win.
We will reach tens of millions of people, conservatively, I mean, one film somebody
makes will probably get seen 50 million times if it's like the Obama deception or loose
change that I produced.
And what you do is you defeat the globalist by making a film and that's how you start
your journey of 1,000 miles.
It's the resistance and then we're gonna take the top pool of people, may not even be the
winners.
This is whoever we can work it out with and come up with plans to launch three films produced
a year with budgets of hundreds of thousands of dollars a piece and then hundreds of thousands
of promotion to put it in theaters and I know that model, we can do it.
We have the platform to promote it and make it work, okay?
Instead of Dinesh D'Souza type stuff out there, we will have our films in the theaters, it's
gonna be huge, absolutely huge.
So you get a chance to then have films produced by Infowars, that's the real prize for filmmakers
out there.
The $100,000 is only the gateway.
That's only the money to get the word out and to have hundreds of topics covered, okay?
It's a way to get you to take action against the globalist as Paul Revere's in your area,
whether it's the Second Amendment, Agenda 21, the New World Order, CPS, the open borders,
public corruption, the military doing drills, now with live fire in major cities every week
unannounced to acclimate us to military occupation, infowars.com forward slash contest.
And yes, we have the new pro one from Pro Pure, all in one fluoride and it cuts out
the other fluoride derivatives.
Nobody has a fluoride filter in one with a silver impregnated ceramic.
Pro one from Pro Pure, discounted 10% off infowarsstore.com or 888-25-3139.
Okay, here's what's coming up after I take your calls and we start the next hour and
then go back into calls.
Law professor on CBS says, let's give up on the Constitution.
Senior Obama official, we're going to kill the dollar.
This is from one of the biggest money managers, hedge fund guys out there, Kyle Bass, who
I wanna get on the show.
This is chilling.
He says he met with them, that's what they said.
Brock's Glock in anti-gun DC media matters for America gave bodyguard illegal weapons
to guard founder David Brock.
Man, I tell you, these so-called liberal authoritarians are such cowards that every time I talk to
them, I run into them at CNN or wherever I run into them, they always admit they have
bodyguards.
Here's Morgan Light about it.
I've seen him on the news admitting bodyguards and being followed by three bodyguards.
They had bodyguards there, they had them following us, looked like detectives to me.
You know, all right, he's coming out, he's coming in, my gosh, there he is.
This is the type of stuff going on.
They have bodyguards, well, they're gonna exempt themselves where they can own guns.
Any government official, not servant, title of nobility, that's a title of nobility when
they're exempt from the laws and they get special perks.
That is what America was founded against.
See, you're all taught all day, black, white, Northern Southerner, Easterner, Westerner,
Catholic Christian against each other, male, female, gay, straight.
Meanwhile, the government is giving itself titles of nobility and corporations are exempt
from the taxes.
They lobby to get passed, I mean, so they get your tax money.
I mean, ladies and gentlemen, they're throwing the kitchen sink at it.
I mean, I see articles where they go, all gun owners are white racists, they are Nazis,
we will defeat them.
Don't wage war against them.
Just bizarro stuff while Obama plays the good cop going, I go hunting, I want guns, I won't
take your guns.
He's back to saying he won't take his guns when they've got something like 15 bills introduced
last time I checked.
To ban ammo, tax ammo, make you turn guns in, banning thousands, not 158, it's 158 basic
designs and all their variants.
It's thousands of guns.
Thousands of guns.
It's just all out and Obama's like, here's a quote.
He said that he's understandable that people are protective of their family traditions
when it comes to hunting.
It's not about hunting, buddy.
So quote, gun control advocates also need to do, quote, a little more listening than
they do sometimes in debate.
Did you hear that?
And see, Piers Morgan comes out and says, I've lost the gun control debate.
He's gonna be another mass shooting with the hype they've been doing.
They've got computer algorithms.
They know a nut's gonna copycat.
And if that doesn't happen, well, they'll have to help, won't they?
They'll just have to have somebody under a DARPA mind control contract for 30 something
thousand a year and with an Air Force psychiatrist over them, something will just have to happen,
won't it?
Of course, they would stage Fast and Furious that killed thousands, which it came out to
blame the Second Amendment.
The memos were doing this, subordinates are complaining, but they've been told it's for
a gun control push.
Imagine the ATF people picked because they'll follow orders and are bullies.
The most nasty federal agency out there cuz it comes out of the whiskey regulators.
Look into that whole story.
They were just mutineous, mutineous, a new word, absolutely out of control, piratical
group against the Constitution and the Whiskey Wars and all the rest of it.
That was one of the first federal agencies to go outside its jurisdiction.
Even they're like, why are we doing this?
They're like, well, we're gonna blame the Second Amendment.
Okay, I see.
See, there's no end to what they could pull.
So they're playing possum right now with Obama goes hunting, we go skeet shooting in Camp
David, everything's all right.
Come on, come on.
Would I lie to you, baby, when I say something that wasn't true?
Tell me, honey, would the government lie to you?
And the answer is, of course, they don't lie.
I mean, they're good.
Piers Morgan said there were no riots last year in London or in England.
He said, no, there weren't.
And he goes, I don't have bodyguards when I debated him.
Why not?
He has nothing but disdain for you.
He's an enemy operative.
I had Time Magazine call me up the other day, and I just said, you're an enemy operative.
And I said, I know what you're doing, and the guy was laughing.
And I said, don't laugh.
You know it's true.
And I'm done talking to you.
You're an enemy operative.
See, we got to totally recognize it or there's no future.
You either see it for what it is and stop, I mean, look at the Republican leadership
telling you, we got to do what the Democrats say.
That's how we're going to win.
I mean, what a sellout mind game fraud.
What a psyop, because the very same mega bank interest that run the Democrats have all financed
them and they're telling them, you get this done if you want to be president.
You get this done, Senator.
You get this done, House member, if you want to be part of this, you play ball while they
gear up for the collapse of the dollar and all out.
See, that's what Congress is getting in line.
They're being told, yeah, there's going to be blood in the streets, martial law, just
like Paulson told Congress four years ago, four plus years ago now.
So coming up, but again, Obama says you need to do a little more listening than you do
sometimes.
Imagine, a known liar patronizing you going, I don't want your guns, I never want to come
take them.
You need to do a little more listening, he said in a speech yesterday, and he's saying
it again today.
I don't want your guns, how ridiculous.
There's no big government.
Now, I'm not going to raise taxes on anybody's payroll unless they make over a quarter million
a year.
They raise it on people making way lower than that.
They know exactly what they are doing.
All right, let's start going to the phone calls now.
I haven't even scratched the surface yet, DHS buys 7,000 full auto assault rifles, calls
them personal defense weapons, full auto, which you don't need unless you're mowing
whole crowds down.
I mean, by the way, there's this fetishizing full auto, I wouldn't want full auto unless
I was guarding a fortified emplacement expecting to face human wave attacks.
Was it good during Chinese human wave attacks in North Korea?
In the Korean War?
Yeah.
Would it be good in a foxhole with a heavy machine gun being charged?
But they're worthless anywhere else.
Anywhere else they are worthless, worthless, worthless, worthless.
They are only good, which the army's been training for, and the Marines, they put it
on the news, where they train to fight US citizens in human waves, they mow them down.
And we got footage of that, people couldn't believe it.
Now they just say, we're having a fun game.
We're practicing mowing down zombies wearing football jerseys.
That's how they, again, it's all a big joke on us.
And now they're getting weapons, the only thing they're good for, and even then they're
not good, in my view, especially with these handheld fully auto, is to hold the weapon
down or have it on a tripod and just shoot across a crowd of people running at you.
And even then you don't want that, you want to go double tap each person.
But see, this is what idiots thrown into marksmanship want.
This is exactly, you like the New York cops that shot nine people, and then the media
tried to cover it up and say, one guy done it, when it was one guy shooting somebody
else and the cops just shoot, well, at least it was more than nine, wasn't it?
Just start firing wildly, cuz they watch Hollywood movies.
That's their idea of how to use a firearm.
DHS buys 7,000 full auto assault rifles, calls them personal defense weapons.
And again, they're saying, we got a federal law where all federal employees and all police
period, you're exempt from gun laws even after you're out of government, you are now God.
And they say, well, we got to protect ourselves, criminals will have guns and it's all a big
joke.
We're gonna take your guns and we're exempt.
How's that sound, scum?
And we're exempt from insider trading.
And power plants owned by the globalists, they're exempt.
Everybody else's, a bunch of big power plants being shut down today, one of the biggest
in Texas.
Brand new power plants that were built will never be opened.
And you're gonna pay more because see, the general public is literally in la la land
right now, and has no idea even what planet they're living on.
Here's some of the other ones.
Some of the other headlines we've got on the Second Amendment, Barack Obama, I go shooting
all the time, we're gonna get into that.
Big cities finance, war on guns may backfire, business week.
Bloomberg saying, well, I've already tried to sue gun manufacturers, it doesn't work.
And I've already tried to get money pulled out of them.
But these are such valuable stocks, everybody just buys them up.
Obama manual saying, banks shouldn't take any gun owners as customers, they shouldn't
take gun shops, that's called racketeering.
That's how a godfather would operate.
Yeah, you know what, you're not gonna be able to do any business.
We're gonna shut you down, it's outside of law, all right?
And I got articles here with the ATF showing up at gun shops and saying, it's legal to
sell semi-auto, but if you don't, stop selling, we're gonna shut you down, okay?
And they even tell him, quote, I'm not here to bust your chops, but don't make me hurt
yous.
If you've ever wanted one of our best selling generators, but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse, then you're not gonna wanna miss this exciting message.
Here's why.
Our solar generators provide life saving electrical power.
And unlike gas generators, solar generators run quietly, emit no fumes, and produce electricity
from the sun.
So when the lights go out, you'll always have the power you need.
Now here's the best part.
Every year we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new.
We put them in a special spot in our warehouse, and we discount them heavily at the end of
each year.
We call them scratch and dent units, but they're really just like new.
Each unit comes with a full factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe.
Don't wait, they go fast.
Go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
For the craziest offer we've ever made, go to scratchanddentsolar.com, that's scratchanddentsolar.com.
Time and time again.
You need to come here and help us.
We need assistance, please.
Those we should be able to depend on, let us down.
Federal and state and local officials saying help is on the way, while the folks here in
Bell Harbor say show me.
Don't depend on the government to save you.
Take action now so that you're prepared for the next disaster with mypatriotsupply.com.
Get the best prices on storable food, non-GMO seeds, water filtration devices, home canning
equipment, survival and self-reliance books, and more at mypatriotsupply.com.
Call 866-229-0927.
We are hurting down here, and we need help immediately.
Before it's time to survive, it's time to prepare, mypatriotsupply.com, mypatriotsupply.com.
Is this the year you finally get serious about your family's drinking water?
If so, keep listening for a special offer from Big Berkey Water Filters.
Did you know that over 60% of municipal water is fluoridated?
Berkey Water Filters distinguish themselves from many other filtration systems with the
capability to significantly reduce dangerous chlorine, fluoride, arsenic, and disinfection
byproducts from municipal water via the black Berkey and PF line of filters.
Then there's affordability.
At only 1.7 cents per gallon, Berkey Water Filters purify treated and untreated water,
even stagnant pond water.
Stop and think how much money you could save by simply reducing buying bottled water and
using water filtered by your Berkey Water Filter.
No need to be constantly replacing expensive filters with a Berkey.
A single set of filters can last for 5 to 10 years.
Choose the best size Berkey for your needs at BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
And right now, all GCN listeners get 5% off all ceramic filter systems.
Just call 1-877-99-BERKEY.
That's 877-99-B-E-R-K-E-Y.
Or visit BigBerkeyWaterFilters.com.
Free shipping on every order over $50.
Big Berkey Water Filters, for the love of clean water.
The preacher man says it's the end of time In the Mississippi River she's a-goin' dry
interest is up and the stock market's down And you're only gettin' mugged if you go downtown
I live back in the woods, you see A woman and the kids and the dogs and the
blues
Alright, we got two plus hours coming up here, just chock full of globalist treason.
They've decided to go whole hog because they know everything's gonna collapse.
They've decided to destroy the dollar.
We've got them on record with that.
It's just gonna be unmitigated and the power structure knows this and so it's us or them.
They're committed.
You have to understand that in police and military, it's time to decide which side you're
on and not just go buy guns and get ready for a civil war.
You don't want that to happen.
We want to push to turn this around peacefully and the globalists may back off if we do that.
Right now they're so concerned, they're backing off going, we don't want your guns.
Okay, you win until they stage the next event or use the next event that they provocateur
or the next real event to say, see, we told you so.
We're the good guys against violence.
It's like saying, I'm the president and I'm against cancer.
And anytime there's cancer, it's the fault of libertarians.
Oh, another cancer case, see, you didn't give me more power to fix that.
I mean, they know out of 315 million people, there'll be more shootings.
And they hope the public doesn't learn that crime has dropped by close to half.
They hope the public doesn't, well, they just want to get up there and be emotional.
We care so much and distract you from what they've done to the economy, to their looting,
to their fast and furious, to Solyndra, to all the corruption, to all their bodyguards,
to them trying to pass a law where they're exempt, I mean, that's unprecedented.
And then the Chicago mob boss, I mean, unbelievably corrupt, called the Godfather by the great
people of Chicago, Rahm Emanuel says, quote, we need to lean on the big banks to not do
business with any type of gun business.
I mean, that's called torturous interference.
That's what the mafia does.
Bad things are gonna, I mean, the ATF, and I'm talking to the gun dealers right now,
I'm trying to get them on air, they're obviously all scared.
Folks, if you give in to fear, it's all over.
Start the second hour and go directly to your calls, I promise.
We're gonna break in about three minutes.
Folks, see, I don't have courage, I got instinct, okay, where I get upset by bullies and scum
and people pushing me around, okay?
You've got to find that American instinct again and just say, look, I don't care how
this ends, I'm not gonna get down and kiss your big, ugly butt.
You understand?
It isn't happening.
Do you understand that?
I don't care.
I mean, I'm telling you, it feels so good to be committed.
And if these people want a war, don't worry, they're gonna get one and they're gonna run.
That's why they don't care if there's a war, they've done it in other countries over and
over again.
It's in the IMF World Bank, 112-point plan leaked in 2002.
They'll all pull out while there's a civil war here.
But listen, when we get the country back, we're gonna come get you under law.
Just like there were Nazi hunters, there's gonna be globalist hunters, and we're gonna
take you back here for a trial.
You're not getting away with this new world order, and they're all buying houses in Switzerland.
They're all buying houses in South America.
They're all buying houses in the Cook Islands.
Most of these globalists have left the country, folks.
Does that sound like they're very confident?
They have already evacuated the Death Star, okay?
They've all evacuated the Death Star.
You know why they've evacuated?
Because they know we're gonna blow this thing sky high, politically.
The question is, how bad is it gonna get?
So that's one reason they're getting even more criminal, is they're realizing they're
not gonna make it.
I can see where this is going, folks.
They're not gonna make it unless they cause World War III.
They need a big enough, giant, crazy war with nukes going off and bioweapons where everybody
gets scared and goes, I'll do what you're saying, I'll do what you're saying.
And you're not gonna make it out of that either.
You guys are going down like Hitler.
I mean, the communist Chinese, Mao was so bad they finally arrested his wife and made
him step down.
The same thing's gonna happen to you guys.
You are bad for business.
Even the criminal syndicates are gonna bring you down.
This is GCN, the Genesis Communications Radio Network.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e Foods Direct.
Waging war on corruption, Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Big brother, mainstream media, government cover-ups.
You want answers?
Well, so does he.
He's Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
And now live from Austin, Texas, Alex Jones.
All right, we're taking your phone calls.
I covered just a cornucopia of key news and information in the last hour.
I am your host, Alex Jones.
Let's go to your calls.
We've got a Todd, Truth Raider, Terry, Danny, Anti-New World Order, and many others.
The toll-free number to join us is 800-25-99231.
Todd in California, you're on the air.
Go ahead.
Hey, good afternoon and good morning to you, Alex Jones.
I've been a long, long-time listener, first-time caller.
Thank you for taking my call.
Thank you for calling, brother.
I have several questions.
I would like to start an impeachment process here in California against Dianne Feinstein,
Boxer and Pelosi.
Obviously, they have implicated themselves in financial fraudery.
And I've looked up several places online on how to do that, and I might even just take
this opportunity also to start the process in my filming of the whole process.
And what would you recommend that I do?
I know Mark Dice is out here, and I would actually like to get with him as well.
Oh, yeah, he's a super guy.
Go work with him.
That's a great idea.
What great work he's done, like when he did the video, people ought to go check it out,
where he went and talked about how they were zombies on the Black Friday deal.
Just a great, great journalistic idea.
Todd, I think you ought to do that.
So what is your kind of, or not kind of, but what would your recommendation be?
And by the way, just to let you know, as I'm calling in, I have turned on a probably over
2,000 people to your website, to your radio show, so I know they're listening to me right
now.
So as I'm speaking to you, I know there's hundreds of people that know me that are listening,
and I want to start this process within this week.
Well, I mean, by the way, we need to just point out that just because they say it's
legal to insider trade, you know, again, Congress has said it's okay to own people before.
That doesn't mean it's really legal.
We need to just talk about Feinstein, went to Congress with less than a million, and
now some estimates are 150 million, some are as low as 76 million.
And we'd like to know why biotech companies with no employees or no money get a $25 million
bill she sponsored, and then she gets a couple million of it the next day after they get
that money.
So, you know, it's time.
I would make a documentary, that's an idea of going and being in front of her office
or her house every day, and just showing what she does.
I mean, it's time to let these gangsters know that we know where they live.
You think you're gonna take our guns and exempt yourself and you're gonna have the guns?
You think you're gonna walk all over us, you witch?
We're done, we're done.
We're not your slaves, you big bucket of pus, you maggot-filled rat.
I appreciate your call, Todd, thanks for the call.
Let's talk to Truth Raider.
You're on the air, go ahead.
Greetings, Alex, and to all the listeners out there in the info world.
Hey, buddy, go ahead.
Well, I'm no longer sick.
I've taken my Beyond Tangy Tangerine and I'm detoxing for freedom.
Good job, brother, very exciting.
Right, two things.
Today, let's stop and take a moment to reflect the seven people who lost their lives today
in the spatial discovery.
All right, I appreciate your call.
Let's go to Terry in Georgia.
You're on the air, go ahead.
Hey, Alex, how are you?
Good, go ahead.
Yeah, I got something for you.
We have, of course, the NDAA, which is totally unconstitutional, but they don't follow the
Constitution anyway, so it doesn't really matter.
The problem that I have is a judge says, hey, we're not going to, no, this is not a constitution,
we're not going to accept this, this is not for the American people, and then their lawyers
go around, turn around, and overturn it right away.
The problem that we have is that information is at the speed of light, and with that information,
like back in 1776, information didn't travel like this, they're spying on everything that
we do.
But that's good, we can turn that around against them.
So what if the criminals spy, they know about our numbers surging.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com, or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now, or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning
needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com, or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds, flu, and other illnesses.
Don't be one of them.
Protect yourself with Supernatural Silver, a revolutionary new broad spectrum antibacterial
solution.
The advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver solution that can be used daily
to prevent bacteria, viruses, mold, and food poisoning, and help improve wound healing.
Supernatural Silver is safe enough to consume every day, while powerful enough to destroy
the causes of many serious diseases such as strep, staph, pneumonia, colds, flus, and
other harmful pathogens.
This new technology has the ability to terminate entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several
hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal or ionic silver solutions.
The Science Digest Journal says silver is our mightiest germ fighter.
It is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and use the promo code silver2012 for 20% off.
That's supernaturalsilver.com and like us on Facebook.
The new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness.
Get serious and make a stand with Supernatural Silver.
This is a breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective
than colloidal or ionic silver.
Supernatural Silver can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria, viruses, infections,
yeast, and molds.
Supernatural Silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification.
It is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support, and it
is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness.
Go to supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance.
That's supernaturalsilver.com.
Check out our new low prices and like us on Facebook.
We now take you live to the Central Texas Command Center in the heart of the resistance.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Show.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, I'm Alex Jones, your host.
We are back.
It is Monday, the 28th day of January 2013.
Hard to believe the first month of 2013 is almost gone.
And coming up, CBS News says it's time to, quote, give up on the Constitution.
Senior Obama official says we're going to kill the dollar.
That's a quote.
We're going to be playing video of that.
Act emails reveal Washington approved plan to stage chemical weapons attack in Syria.
Obama administration complicit in war crime, question mark.
Attack helicopters let loose with machine gun fire over Miami.
That's up at infowars.com.
This and much more.
Piers Morgan in Politico declares that the best interview he ever had was Alex Jones
and that this will be used to defeat gun owners.
He said that January 17th.
Now he's declaring they've lost today on his Twitter and that gun owners are all up in
an uproar.
Yeah, why?
Why didn't you have me back, Piers?
Why aren't all the other shows having me on it?
I'm so discrediting.
You see, Paul Revere rode and screamed arms to arms.
The redcoats are coming.
He didn't go up there and say, nah, nah, hi, I know it sounds like a conspiracy theory,
but the government's corrupt, you know.
That's why it was a big victory, ladies and gentlemen, and I'm not putting perfume on
a pig.
I analyzed it, what happened, and decided I did the right thing.
I prayed to God that I would do the best thing when I went in there against the enemy.
And I told him after the interview, I said, you are an enemy and I will rout you out.
You are a gangster thug and you will be defeated and all of you are on notice.
Those CNN crew, multiple women were crying and freaking out.
The men were hyperventilating and I said, I know who you are, traitors.
I marched out of there.
I didn't go in there and, you're so big, you've got such a big set, you're so powerful.
We're not gonna get this country back playing patty cake.
Does the dawn of Chicago Emmanuel play nice?
He's saying, we're gonna lean on gun manufacturers and banks, we're just gonna shut them down
outside of law.
That's called torturous interference, racketeering by any yardstick.
This is what we're talking about.
This is what we're dealing with.
And we're not going to get our country back playing patty cake.
We're gonna get it back going, we know who you are.
We know foreign banks have hijacked the government.
We know you're illegitimate and don't stage something.
And even if something happens, giving up our rights doesn't keep us safe.
So don't you blow something up and blame it on us.
We're watching you.
You understand that?
We're watching you and we know what's going on.
The time for games is over.
People probably notice I'm a lot more serious on air.
I used to joke around, have a little bit more fun on air.
People notice behind the scenes, there's no more games.
This is game time, folks, in the battle for the Republican humanity.
This is a life and death situation.
This is the real world, this isn't a game.
I'm not up here playing games.
I know where I live.
I know where the world is.
I know where I stand.
I know how dark the times are.
That's just some of what's coming up, ladies and gentlemen.
DHS buys 7,000 full auto assault rifles, calls them personal defense weapons.
Government wants to exempt itself from gun laws.
All government officials will no longer be called servants, but officials exempt from
all their laws, from insider trading to senators with quote underage prostitutes.
They're above the law.
And ABC News goes and talks to the senator in an interview never asked about the underage
prostitutes or the convicted sex offender for child abuse working in his office.
I mean, these people are sick.
Let's go ahead and talk to Danny in Tennessee.
You're on the air, Danny.
Thank you for holding.
Hey, thanks, Alex, for taking my call.
I've been listening about 15 years.
I think I called you once, maybe 12 years ago.
But anyway, no, I'm right with you as far as Piers Morgan.
I was very pleased the way you handled that.
I'm actually calling about a situation this morning.
I went to Walmart to pick up a 10-22.
They happen to have one.
I hold a valid New York driver's license and I live in New York and in Tennessee.
I went there and they were doing the Tennessee Bureau of Investigation check and the person
on the other line was giving my salesperson a hard time saying that he has a New York
driver's license.
He cannot buy a Ruger 10-22 in Tennessee.
I thank the Lord.
The woman was thinking and she looked at her chart and said, well, apparently you're wrong
or this chart is wrong because New York is a valid place to, you know, I can sell to
someone from New York and Tennessee.
They went back and forth.
She actually argued with the guy and finally the guy gave in and let me purchase the TBL.
Let me stop you.
I've talked to two different gun dealers and then I'm also getting emails from gun dealers
and I should wipe the phones out later and open it up for FFL, federal firearms licensee
dealers.
And I'm trying to get these guys on air, but obviously they get intimidated.
The ATF comes in.
They did this last year.
Remember when we were given some documents that were then made national news?
Were ATF in five western states, Texas, New Mexico, Arizona, Nevada, and California just
said outside of law.
They tried to pass the law.
They couldn't.
They put letters in and the ATF visited saying you will report to us and open a criminal
file when someone buys more than two rifles or handguns at one time or two or more.
And again, they're already when you call in, it's already in the next system.
There's already a record.
They just wanted to test outside the law.
Now they say that and the ATF is now going in saying you're going to stop selling semi-autos
or we're going to go through all your records and find a T that's not crossed and I that's
not dotted.
By the way, they arrest you for that.
That's why now they're all going to computerize systems so you can't make a mistake because
if there's a mistake, it'll kick it back.
But then that also computerizes it makes it easier for the ATF.
That's the problem.
And so they're harassing good gun dealers, but they've ordered to give guns to drug cartels
so they can blame all gun dealers and it's how this mafia operates.
And so what you're experiencing is happening to everybody.
I've talked to people who went to gun shows personally.
I've had the calls where you're buying a clip, a 10 round clip, and they follow you out the
door and ask you who you are like the clips that we're the new criminal class.
The entire Homeland Security apparatus, they admit behind the scenes for a decade was going
to be for us.
People are like, how did you know that?
You say Homeland Security is not for gun owners because it always was.
It was never about Al Qaeda that these offshore banks run.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
Oh, no, no.
Continue on.
I'm not definitely listening and I just, I was curious if other people have experienced
that.
But I am thankful for this woman who actually thought and defended what was true.
Well, Emanuel and all of them have said Schumer, Emanuel, Pelosi, who's the other one?
Bloomberg have all said, we're going to put pressure on the manufacturers and the sellers
to just voluntarily comply.
Well, that's like the TSA ran checkpoints all over downtown Austin last Thursday.
And then I got reports again over the weekend, but I can't just stake out Lamar.
That's where they're doing it.
And on South Lamar and then up into the city.
And they just show up with Austin police.
They have guns and they say, lay your bags out, get out of your car, get off the train,
and we're gonna search you.
And then when they go, what about the Fourth Amendment?
They told the news, well, they volunteered.
Armed men have their lights on and armed feds with guns on their hip and guns on their,
they wear them commando style on their thigh.
Armed men, sure, I would say, Fourth Amendment, you can't search my bag.
But most people literally cower.
They're the royalty, we're the scum.
And it's just color of law, gangsterism.
America is, government at every level is teaming up against us, swarming us, dominating us.
State police pull you over in Texas now, and I'm getting reports all over the country.
They go, got any firearms in your car, no, but if I did, they're legal.
What do you got at home?
Where do you live?
Is this your right driver's license?
And folks, they're doing this to, again, totally clean cut people.
They got a database on you, they know you have no record, and they look at you like
a criminal cuz you're the milk cow.
They get promoted, all of it's being recorded, they have a microphone on their tie.
And it's reviewed, they get promoted if they savage the American people.
I mean, this is a revolution of secret police activity.
Cuz you know, we have the article last week, they're announcing and they're putting in
audio in major hotels saying, if you see bags, please call the police.
The waiters are on a computer system at the hotel bars and restaurants, they're listening
to you.
They're filling out data, when the bartender's talking to you now, I mean, this is in press
releases, they're filling out FBI files on you.
I mean, it's stazzy out in the open.
I mean, do you understand the magnitude of this, sir?
I certainly do, I certainly do.
And I like to tell your listeners, too, that we have a group of people, we're friends,
and we've listened to you for quite a while.
And apparently, we're conspiracy theorists, too.
But actually, I look at it as we're conspiracy realists, because for the Christians out there,
Satan is the biggest conspirator of them all.
When you have a massive amount of people who are against Christ, they side with Satan,
and he is a conspirator from day one.
So I like how our opponents make us look crazy, we're actually not.
But another thing I'd like to state is, when it looks like there's no hope and that we
are a minority, it doesn't matter, because I believe that the Lord is truly on our side.
He is on the side of truth and righteousness, and as long as we uphold that, he will bless
that.
Amen to that, brother, and I appreciate your call, Danny.
Yeah, the feds were involved two years ago in a sting at the Austin gun shows to try
to shut them down, so the city could, outside of law, order the private owners of different
facilities to not let them have gun shows there, racketeering.
And it turned out they would send in illegal aliens with real driver's license the state
had given them, and then they would present real licenses, fraudulently given by the state,
a fraud.
And then private sellers, their private gun, not a gun dealer, you have to have a federal
license to be a gun dealer, they would do the private sale, people selling off their
gun collection.
And then they would put that person in jail with a kangaroo jury that was so ignorant,
saying, well, he sold an illegal alien, yeah, but he had a real license.
The judge would say, you are to convict.
I mean, this is the racketeering.
They are gonna persecute and fill the prisons with gun owners, and turning your guns in
won't help.
They're gonna take everything, pension funds, stocks, bonds, this is a criminal takeover.
We'll be right back with more of your call, stay with us.
Looking back on 2012, we ask ourselves, how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like Hurricane Sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy?
Our hearts go out to those that have lost everything.
At e Foods Direct, we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather
life's storm by having a supply of food on hand.
After Hurricane Sandy, Danny from New York City wrote, almost all the grocery stores
are closed, but I managed to get my e Foods just in time to be able to help my sister
and niece.
It is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late.
I can warn you, but I can't feed you.
Heed the warnings and do what Alex has done.
Call 800-409-5633 today, or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply.
It's the best tasting, non-GMO, long-term, storable food on the planet.
Call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com slash Alex.
You can bet your life on e Foods Direct.
It's time for a home security quiz.
Answer this.
What effective home security device is smaller than a coffee cup, fakes out burglars into
thinking someone is home at your house while you're away, plugs into any wall outlet, is
recommended by many police departments and sells for less than $35?
Yes, it's fake TV.
This year, about one in every 50 U.S. homes will have a break-in, with burglars usually
picking the easy target, a dark house that looks like no one is home.
Fake TV is a small electronic security device that makes it look like someone is home watching
TV by simulating the light from a real TV.
It's like a lamp on a timer, but far more convincing.
And for only $34.95, fake TV could be the difference between coming home to a secure
house or one that's been ransacked.
Go to faketv.com or call 1-877-5FAKETV.
That's 877-532-5388.
Or go to faketv.com.
Fake TV, the burglar deterrent.
Do you know how much the dollar has lost in its value against other currencies in the
last 90 days?
Ever think about how inflation will change your life, your savings, your retirement plans?
Remember inflation in Zimbabwe, Argentina, the Weimar Republic?
Put another way, who cares if your investments go up 10%, but you lose 40% of your purchasing
power.
Gold is the only monetary asset as no one else's liability.
Gold still buys the same amount of stuff it always did.
Gold does not require trust in a third party.
You can possess it in your hand.
You can take it with you.
Gold is real money.
Gold is honest money.
My name is Daniel Larson from Midas Resources.
To find out how you can protect your savings and roll over your IRA funds into precious
metals accounts, please call me at 800-686-2237, extension 134.
That's 800-686-2237, extension 134.
800-686-2237, extension 134.
Don't throw away leftovers.
Instead, throw all your leftovers, vegetable peels, eggshells, coffee grounds, pizza crusts,
and more into the Bokashi.
If you love to garden and compost but don't like the hassle of turning a compost bin or
the smell, then check out the EM Bokashi Food Waste Recycling System from Tereganics.
Finally a way to recycle all your food and plant waste safely and effectively and stop
using fertilizers.
The EM Bokashi Food Waste Recycling System.
Rather than decomposition, the Bokashi system uses fermentation to break down waste so it
takes less time to create nutrient-dense humus for crops or gardens with no turning and no
obnoxious odors.
To learn more and order your Bokashi online, visit Tereganics.com and click on the orange
button.
That's Tereganics.com, spelled T-E-R-A-G-A-N-I-X dot com, or call 866-369-3678.
That's 866-369-3678.
Recycle all your food wastes in about six weeks with the Bokashi Food Waste Recycling
System from Tereganics.com.
Tereganics.
Your life's getting better.
You know, sometimes I do special reports and things, and I'm very calm and people like
it.
But you can't argue with success.
I genuinely start hyperventilating and getting upset on air when I realize this is all real.
I've studied history.
It's not hard to figure out what's happening.
The government now admits it's totally illegitimate and above the law.
And we're in trouble.
I mean, we're in trouble.
Everywhere you go, the corporations are training all their employees to be spies.
And they're not looking for all kind of terrorist folks.
They're looking for the American people.
They're looking for patriots and constitutionalists and veterans and gun owners and conservatives.
And this is outrageous that they're calling us Nazis and criminals and baby killers, collectively
putting the guilt on us to try to have a purge against us.
This is just the setup when they blow up some federal buildings and blame it on us or stage
a mass shooting.
This is just the beginning, and that's what I wanna relay to you.
The globalists are planning to use a civil war that they'll call terrorism, they'll call
us terrorist if we resist going to FEMA camps, as a political cover to their implosion of
the economy.
Now, I don't think they're gonna get away with it.
I think they're gonna back off because the police aren't buying it.
That's why we've always targeted the police for the truth.
Because knowing that tyranny will come to your door in a uniform.
And so we don't want this war to happen.
And the police aren't stupid, they know what I'm saying is true and real.
Some of them are dumb, that's why they're trying to hire dumber and dumber people, that's
on record.
Still, it isn't gonna work.
But we've got to put the maximum effort out now.
Anti New World Order in New York, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Yes, Alex, I just want to say thank you for basically what you've done for the truth movement.
I've been following you for a long time, I started on 1310 a.m. in Rochester, New York.
You actually inspired me to start a blog, and last year we hit over 100,000 views.
It's the Anti New World Order party, and we are making connections all over the world.
I believe that with what you've done, you set a fire in the hearts and the minds of
American patriots.
And I believe-
But that's what you've got to do, and that's what you're doing.
All of us are here like incendiary bombs to set brush fires in the minds of men and women.
We are the resistance, we are Paul Revere, we are victory.
Absolutely.
And you've inspired me that I'm actually going to start an online or a radio program, and
we're getting sponsors, and it's all because of your work.
Exactly, just attack the enemy on every front, info war them, use their own corruption against
them, discredit them, expose their hypocrisy.
I mean, that should be instant discrediting, that they're going to be exempt from the gun
laws we're under.
And then they say in the news, well, we need guns to protect ourselves.
I mean, look at Charlie Sheen going, well, I've changed my mind about guns, no one needs
to own these.
Besides, I've got bodyguards.
Well, yeah, you make $3 million a week, Charlie, come on.
I mean, it's the disconnect of the ruling class living in their bubble.
God bless you, my friend, good to hear from you.
Let's talk to Phil in North Carolina, you're on the air.
Alex, how are you doing?
I just want to say thanks for everything you're doing, and me and my wife, we pray for you
and your family.
And that's a three-quarter, Alex, it's hard to break.
You there?
Yes, I'm listening to you.
I just want to set the board for the media, and it's so far left.
It just rips apart anything that has to do with this country.
And it's really, it's hard, it's my job, it's how I support my family.
When I've talked to them, they got me down as I'm a loony to them.
And when I try to explain to them- Yeah, yeah, they dictate reality.
They're the ones that are delusional, though.
Uh-huh, you're funny, you think America's scary with secret arrest and checkpoints and
bankrupting dollar and everything.
Uh-huh, you think there's something wrong with our government funding Al-Qaeda publicly.
What a weirdo.
I mean, you ought to feel sorry for those people.
They're nothing but cowards who do whatever they're told.
And actually, it's one thing to go along with something cuz you got to, that's bad enough.
But they actually buy into the lie because they think you just put on your political
beliefs like a suit of clothes, that it's about whatever feels good to them, and that
way leads to destruction.
I'm gonna come back to you, Phil, cuz I wanna hear what it's like to work in a establishment
media.
And again, let's break their terms.
They're not liberals.
Thomas Jefferson is a liberal.
George Washington was a liberal.
Alex Jones is a liberal.
Ron Paul's a liberal.
Lou Rockwell's a liberal.
G. Edward Griffin's a liberal.
Keep our money, keep our property, keep our families, worship what god we want, do what
we want.
That's liberal.
Liberal is not having the government tell you how much soft drinks you can drink.
We're on the march.
The empire's on the run.
Alex Jones and the GCN Radio Network.
If you want an American company with American products made by Americans, here is the Cal
Ben Soap Company.
Alex and his staff have used these pure soap products for years.
These all natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut oils
that are earth friendly and safe.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
Buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice as good as what
you're using now.
Or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for all your cleaning needs.
This is an amazing deal.
You can save thousands of dollars and you will love the way real soap makes you feel.
See them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog.
You prepare by purchasing gold, food, and firearms, but if you don't have a home security
system then you're missing a critical weapon in your arsenal for home protection.
When you're sleeping or away from home, who's watching out for intruders?
Check out Simply Safe.
It's a new do it yourself home security system that is completely wireless.
Go to GetSimplySafe.com.
Simply Safe is independent and off the grid.
It runs on battery power so even if the grid goes down, you're protected.
It's completely customizable so you can use it in your home, business, boat, trailer,
storage unit, or shed.
GetSimplySafe.com.
Simply Safe is also ridiculously easy to install yourself in under 20 minutes so there's no
need to let a stranger into your home.
If you move or need to relocate, you can take the system with you wherever you go.
You aren't always at home, but Simply Safe will stand guard protecting your property
24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
Again, that's GetSimplySafe.com.
Alex Jones here with a message to fellow freedom lovers.
The prognosis for the entire planetary economic system runs from bad to worse.
The globalist model is to shut down societies and starve patriots out until they acquiesce
to the global takeover.
That's why we've assembled the most vital and important preparedness items at InfoWarsShop.com.
These are items that I did research on, that I personally use.
We've got the LifeStraw so you can turn fetid water into safe water anywhere you go.
The Ktor Hand Crank Generator to charge up key equipment during power outages or out
in the field.
strategic relocation third edition by Joel Skousen when disaster strikes by Matthew Stein
TheraSafe used by Homeland Security to protect yourself during any radiological event and
crank shortwave AM FM radios.
Everything that we've researched and found to be the best is available at InfoWarsShop.com
and your purchase makes our info war possible.
We're getting prepared.
Are you InfoWarsShop.com coming up the videos up at InfoWars.com I'm going to play the CBS
news saying quote let's give up on the Constitution and all these new TV shows bad mouthing the
founding fathers whole shows about how they're trash situational comedies to make fun of
them set in the Revolutionary War period shows where militias won't turn their guns in the
new terror threat shows like founding fathers are Texans that think there's a new world
order folks this was all in production last year.
Now coming out now perfectly timed with the shootings all of it.
This is all scripted to a great extent.
And that's why I'm up here and I'm so focused and so hardcore because yes ladies and gentlemen
they could easily set me up easily kill me.
I've been physically attacked years ago I get death threats I've had dirty tricks you
wouldn't believe but I pray to God.
And I know I'm in God's hands and again that doesn't mean I'm some goody two shoes who's
up here saying hey I'm this big great Christian I listen I'm a bad man.
My flesh is bad.
I mean I have bad thoughts.
I think about you know literally gouging my enemy's eyes out sometimes but I repent of
that and I want to be a good person and I don't want to hate my fellow man.
The world is nasty.
The world is hard.
The world is bad.
The Madison Avenue shows us the red carpets and the models and the helicopters and the
money and we imagine that that's some wonderful heaven up there and our lives are dirt and
squalor.
It's not true folks recognizing beauty recognizing justice standing up for justice and helping
others and not hating each other is what will bring us to the next level and fulfill you.
No amount of money or power will do that and all the studies show that.
What will fulfill you is the truth and it doesn't mean that sometimes you don't get
mad at your family.
It doesn't mean sometimes you don't get mad at your boss or your employees.
It means that you understand the stimuli and the manipulation by the social engineers on
record from Edward Bernays 80 years ago to Joseph Goebbels 70 years ago to right through
to modern propaganda 101.
It's all about divide and conquer and play us off against each other.
I mean you turn on MSNBC it's like Kurt Vonnegut satire of a futuristic bizarro world where
all they do is go everyone knows people that don't like the UN are racist and gun owners
are scum and hate black people yeah and evil men had to be dealt with hey good news the
family's falling apart I mean you tune into it you're like what is this and they're unhappy
soulless mercenaries I mean I've been in MSNBC I've been in Fox I've been in CNN I've been
in you name it and I've been around the people and man they are absolutely alone.
They're all fake they're all trying to act powerful around each other everyone's trying
to not say anything show that so that they don't you know put themselves out there so
that someone can use it against them it's and then they go home to plastic husbands
and plastic wives they have plastic kids that commit suicide and they're totally empty I've
got the opposite problem I'm gonna just be honest with you I mean I I'm so tuned into
reality it is like unspeakably incredible and painful at the same time and I'm not saying
I'm at some high level I'm just at a basic human level I go read the writings of the
founders I read the writings of philosophers I go read the writings of great literature
and I see the same thoughts I've personally had that they had and and and and and and
then surpassing my understanding I'm nothing special except in a day and age of universal
deceit telling the truth is a revolutionary act as Eric Blair said I love the sound of
thunder going through the studio walls I just want to hike in the woods in the rain oh you
know that's that's that's that's one reason that's one reason that I really get mad and
hate the globalist because they do steal our future they don't just steal monetarily they
just don't steal culturally they steal our time and our energy serving their system the
fact that we have to spend time on them and talk about all the stuff they're doing that's
why if you attack them with a glancing blow and attack them within their paradigms you
only add power to them it's designed but you attack them from outside the box of how it's
a false construct of how it's an artificial society a stage that they train us to basically
be players upon when you realize that they do not like it when you go into the CNN studios
and they're dirty and pockmarked and gross and all the people look demoralized good I
was in CNN I don't know a decade ago and then three years ago and it didn't look like that
I was in the exact same studios rotting it's like your soul is rotting it's good to see
the enemy rotting it's good to see you weak look at info wars growing look at the rest
of the alternative media growing getting stronger good it's war and if they destroy me I'm personally
I'm not happy about that but it's part of the war it's part of the real the real thing
the tree being watered it's holy it's strengthening the species it's honorable it's a struggle
it's real I went and saw a film I forget the name of you guys look it up I actually brought
you in the ticket stub so you could know the name of it it's like flight of the monarchs
I think fly to the butterflies I went and saw it it's got UN propaganda in it of course
but that's like one percent of it very good film in fact I may go see it again with my
children I they went with me Saturday with my wife probably the best nature documentary
just for its simplicity but story I've ever seen because it was touching to me how the
four generations of monarchs start I'm not going to say where it starts because that's
the I mean obviously anybody that knows science knows where it starts for your kids I won't
tell them it starts let's just say starts around Texas and then goes all the way up
into northern Canada and it takes four generations to get to Canada and then there's like a b-52
version of the monarch that's like four times the size of a regular one that makes the long
flight back then waits all winter flies back to Texas from the south and then lays its
eggs and dies incredible and how that monarch uses electromagnetics to fly sometimes you
know ten thousand feet in the air electromagnetic off the Sun and off the poles and the meridians
and scans in flying everything calculated just perfectly they know to fly the three
thousand miles four thousand miles whatever it is and this incredible death race to get
down there and then four more generations to get all the way up to the top of the mountain
and then back down again and it's that struggle and we're in that generation you know it's
like the third coming the book that is that the name David Knight did a piece on you know
that breaks down these cycles in in in humans and I was thinking of our generation the fourth
turning excuse me the fourth turning teleprompter free here and I was just thinking about that
how all the generations come and go and this is going to be not just from the fourth turning
but other sociologists anthropologists historians this is the prime zone the globalists say
that this next ten years is going to decide the next thousand I mean this is the most
mega important point in all of human development this is everything on the line this is it
I'm sorry I it's not that I'm a good guy I am not fulfilled being a greedy bastard and
by greedy it's not even about money I am not fulfilled you know just to be able to sell
out to the system and be chauffeured around and have bodyguards and live in New York or
LA and prance around at parties with a bunch of fake people you know shelling out that
I'm a winner I made it to the top you made it to the top of a pile of skulls meant to
the top of a latrine you meant to the top of a spider hole I want to see humanity make
it to the stars and to really develop and I that's why I'm not worried about being killed
or destroyed or set up whatever I'm just a monarch butterfly man just like everybody
else I just want my species to go on look at all of what our species has done those
monarchs are picking up electromagnetic information in their DNA they're an antenna and so are
we folks and my antenna says fight the New World Order it says I'm not going along with
this everything I've got is to navigate me against these people I don't need all the
high-tech computers and programming and fancy systems the globalist have got I just got
to follow my spirit God gave me that literally resonates with my DNA and I got it all right
here man I've got an electrochemical computer and and billions of cells all in Congress
together literally that can recognize the beauty of the night sky and the beauty of
my innocent children and the beauty of my wife and the beauty of literature and art
and philosophy and friendship and everything honorable I don't just know when the sun's
coming up I don't just wake up as the Sun is about to crest because I my soul literally
picks up its electromagnetic pulse as it passes over the rock of the planet blocking it I
literally pick up what's good and evil I have discernment that's all it is we are a billion
times with that monarch butterfly is a little tiny creature that can fly four thousand miles
and navigate electromagnetically do you know what you are and these atheists tell you you
don't have a soul these atheists tell you you're nothing special that you're crap that
humans are ugly you hear it all the time we're a joke we're no good all day they tell you
that because it's a lie ladies and gentlemen it's a lie this species is meant to go to
the stars this species isn't it hasn't even gone to our next phase yet of what God has
prepared for us eye has not seen ear has not heard and the preacher's jobs out there is
to keep you from knowing just how incredible you are we are made in the image of the creator
of the universe look at how more advanced we are than that butterfly look at what we've
already built this is nothing this is nothing and evil are people malfunctioning and people
giving into destructive tendencies to dominate like cancer in a body you so-called elites
are unhappy and you think making us unhappy will make you happy you're inbred your disease
you're hateful you're unhappy so you want to do you want to poison us you want to pump
heavy metals into us to damage our DNA you think bringing the species down will raise
you up you will never rise bringing others down yeah I know you're coming down fast with
your miles above me I got it how about we all rise and then you can be rising fast miles
above us that's real power that's real power real power is saying I am now one with the
universe and its creator I step in to the time-space continuum I follow my programming
but I have free will I accept my programming I accept what I am I accept it and I telegraph
my information into the future through my species that is the magic of the universe
that is the meaning of life that is everything that ever was is and will be that is your
destiny those of you that serve darkness many of you there's still time to turn back there's
still time to join humanity in the great race the great march towards our destiny but you're
not going to partake of that destiny I'll assure you kneeling to the dark side you evil
people think you have knowledge of the dark side if you really knew the true knowledge
of the creator of the universe if you even had the spark the inkling of God if you even
had one micron of that fire you would then have knowledge of all the evil and you wouldn't
want nothing to do with it you dark practitioners think you have knowledge of evil I don't even
want to look into the knowledge I have of it you have not seen it or I will assure you
you would not be running so happily towards it let's go to your phone calls I apologize
I said I'd take more but I'm on a roll today because I'm really it's just understanding
how serious all this is this is what goes on in my mind 24 7 fill in North Carolina
tell your media story go ahead what it's like working inside a group suppressing the human
potential well Alex they just they basically laugh at us we're too far out there and you
know Alex they're going blind through a storm with a smile on their face they don't even
know what's going on Alex I mean they're clueless and it's all they care about is their football
game and their six-pack of beer and I know that I have nothing against football and but
now it's stolen their manhood their manhood is raising their children strong being good
teaching their children how to fix things teaching their children how to stand up for
themselves not waddling around talking about the team all day it's stolen everything from
us you're right Alex and I just you know that's all I really had to say thank you very much
for everything you're doing Alex uh don't thank me don't thank me yeah you're on the
air go ahead it's you brother is um you know I'm a Christian and uh my Christian friends
have always given me a hard time I'm a member of a gun range uh always go shooting they
always ask me why did I like to go shooting and uh you know what I told them and then
they asked me if I'm a Christian why don't I depend on God to protect me and I told them
I said God hasn't called me to be a martyr yet he hasn't called me to allow a car full
of people to pull up my front yard get out come in shoot me in the head rape my three
daughters shoot them and then or whatever I have take it with him he hasn't called me
to do that yet he may someday do that to me Alex but right now he's told me to defend
my property in my household in my family that's where I'm at right now Alex well listen listen
a hundred years ago the Rockefellers with the National Council of Churches about 60
years ago with the World Council of Churches I guess like 65 times flying they set these
up and the churches got paid off and and brought in to be uh charities not under 501c3 and
others not churches and so pretty much all the churches are saying turn your guns in
now I don't care if they're Catholic Protestant Methodist I mean you know whatever it is they're
state run basically clergy response teams these people call themselves Americans our
country was born out of the preachers across the spectrum saying this is a tyranny government's
not God government's abusing us we have a right and a duty to resist it the entire Bible
is the prophets different ways sometimes physical sometimes with information resisting corrupt
governments okay and and not worshiping the God of the state not worshiping the king but
worshiping God and so these people that say you shouldn't be armed trust in God God gave
you a brain gone God gave you all of this to protect yourself and you know look at God
telling Israel get up and defend yourself look at that is so evil to sit there and say
Christians should known guns I mean I see preachers on TV now saying the the early church
was wrong to not worship Saturn and being thrown the lions in Rome so I mean look those
are cowardly demons or you know they may just be deceived people but listen I wouldn't be
going to a church where they say guns are bad God bless you my friend wow we're gonna
come back with more calls stay with us ladies and gentlemen
if you've ever wanted one of our best-selling generators but we're waiting for an offer
so crazy you couldn't refuse then you're not gonna want to miss this exciting message here's
why our solar generators provide life-saving electrical power and unlike gas generators
solar generators run quietly emit no fumes and produce electricity from the Sun so when
the lights go out you'll always have the power you need now here's the best part every year
we accumulate a few solar generators that we just can't sell as new we put them in a
special spot in our warehouse and we discount them heavily at the end of each year we call
them scratch and dent units but they're really just like new each unit comes with a full
factory warranty and special bonuses you just won't believe don't wait they go fast go to
scratch and dent solar.com that's scratch and dent solar.com for the craziest offer
we've ever made go to scratch and dent solar.com that's scratch and dent solar.com
Hello this is Ty Bollinger author of the best-selling book cancer step outside the box I want you
to know some very important information in 1985 president Ronald Reagan requested that
carnivora be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the president could obtain
this world-class healer now 27 years later carnivore capsules are used around the world
to keep people healthy now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age of
superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells
only without harming a single normal cell if you want to stay healthy now's your chance
to literally wake up your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that don't
belong in your body call 1-866-VenusFly or order from carnivora.com that's c-a-r-n-i-v-o-r-a.com
that's 1-866-836-8735 1-866-VenusFly or visit carnivora.com protect your immune system it's
the only one you've got.
Hey there Frank Bates here have you heard about the weird device that could wipe out
280 million Americans this is really scary stuff defense experts warn that this odd device
poses the gravest threat we've ever known in fact just a few weeks ago former speaker
of the house Newt Gingrich wrote an op-ed piece for the Washington Post warning about
this deadly threat I can't believe that more people aren't talking about this it may be
because the liberals and the government are trying to cover it up that's why my friend
just created a free video at weirddevice.com that exposes this threat and blows the doors
off the conspiracy go watch the shocking video at weirddevice.com right now to discover exactly
what it is plus discover the number one way you and your family can survive this deadly
attack I'm not sure how long this video be online so go to weirddevice.com before it's
gone forever again that's weirddevice.com
got this story linked up at infowars.com set for takeoff Britain's deadly super drone that
picks its own targets but experts warn plane could mark the start of robot wars yeah the
Pentagon said back in the 70s that by 2010 they plan to have half the Air Force be robot
drone and humans can do it pretty much whatever we put our minds to at a certain point and
guess what by 2010 half of the Air Force was drone by 2020 they plan to have over 90% of
it be drone but the Pentagon totals got something like 30,000 predators totaled one of the branches
I think it's Air Force had some ridiculous amount like 18,000 of those and this amazing
new drone systems similar to what the US is launching it's a system that picks and kills
on its own and see then the globalist aren't going to need humans anymore the goal is to
have robots working on robots working on robots with robot trucks and trains that even bring
the parts in from the other factories and then humans that will oversee some of it but
almost all engineers will tell you now computer engineers electrical engineers that no one
knows how the microchip works by themselves it's all these experts together no one I mean
it's already like something like 1600 times smaller than it was just 30 40 years ago 35
years ago the the size of the so-called etching the wiring it's amazing and it's going to
get more and more advanced and that's why the globalist are laughing they can have for
a dollar in a few years a little robot with a weapon system that kills you with you a
shot designed to only kill you with your DNA sequence that comes into your house at night
by in fact biologically it can even be biological not even metal bites you and then you die
the clothes are coming out where they'll have nanotech vaccines which actually re-engineer
your brain bill gates has announced that and they say don't worry you're not going to be
stressed anymore we've decided humans are designed wrong you're not supposed to get
upset you're not going to be upset anymore this is going to inject you with a virus that
goes in and eats areas of your brain and gives you a selective lobotomy just google brain
eating vaccines you'll see a video I did two years ago on the subject or startpage.com
you can find it there so anyways I'm ranting this is the type of stuff we're talking about
but humans are going to beat this okay but the smart meters spying on us the electromagnetics
all the major new brands coming out have systems the smart meters dial into and then surveil
you and the CIA chief brags yeah we're putting microphones in all the new dishes and dishwashers
dryers computers there's nothing you can do we're watching you but still I'm a conspiracy
theorist because I told you 15 years ago MIT said that was the plan now what happens I'm
even worse you see because the yuppies are like he's still bad it's not you know Alex
is still bad okay so he's right it's good to have them watching us that's not bad it's
good to have the laptops the school issues watching us it's good to have the NSA spying
it's good to have the government running al-qaeda it's good to list gun owners as terrorists
I'm going to turn my guns in to prove I'm I'm see they're scared deep down and so they
submit to the system we're going to go to break and come back and go to John in Pennsylvania
Tim Tim Michael Doris Tona and many others when you hear somebody hang up it's your chance
to call in eight hundred two five nine nine two three one I'm excited about life I'm excited
about our destiny and I'm alive and I know you're alive and I I intend to fight tyranny
and stand up for a good trajectory for humanity I mean I want us to have a debate about our
future I want us to have a debate about what we can become I I've said it my goal is for
my great great great great granddaughter to be sitting there with her children on a distant
planet orbiting a foreign star at a beautiful beach that's my goal and I want your great
great grandchildren to be there as well you are listening to GCN visit GCN live.com today
looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters
like hurricane sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on
by a disastrous economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at e foods
direct we hear from customers every day that are fortunate enough to weather life storm
by having a supply of food on hand after hurricane sandy Danny from New York City wrote almost
all the grocery stores are closed but I managed to get my e foods just in time to be able
to help my sister and niece it is better to be prepared 10 years too early than one day
too late I can warn you but I can't feed you heed the warnings and do what Alex has done
call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoodsdirect.com slash Alex and build your food supply it's
the best tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet call 800-409-5633 or efoodsdirect.com
slash Alex you can bet your life on e foods direct waging war on corruption Alex Jones
on the GCN radio network big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers
well so does he he's Alex Jones on the GCN radio network and now live from Austin Texas
Alex Jones alright I got a bunch of clips and a ton of economic news to get to in this
hour but right now let's go to your calls John in Pennsylvania let's talk about troops
in the economy he's watching at prisonplanet.tv welcome sir thank you Alex I took the red
toe a couple months ago and I'm a happy man god bless you happy inside but aware of too
much I think all right I'm a Legionnaire and American Legion magazine coming in February
has an article not made in America now according to this military times reports although DoD
is required to purchase clothing and shoes 100% made in America they're coming from China
and I think that might be a big part of the problem why we have no money because nobody
could nobody here is working and we should be doing this like in World War II World War
I we have two representatives are leading an effort representative Michael Michard Democrat
from Maine and Duncan Hunter Republican from California and absolutely this is how wide
open we are did you know the components for the B-2 bomber and missile systems for nuclear
submarines are made in China and other areas on record most the military hardware is made
overseas now it's just put together here this has been a long-term strategic plan where
we give them worthless dollars then they buy real infrastructure with it this is how you
get the u.s. conquered by Communist China the insiders went over there they put Malin
in 49 always had deals with him always had deals with the Communist in China not so much
Russia that was early on but the Russians doubled across the globalist for a while they
were just as bad but the point is is that yes I've seen the articles in fact guys will
you print me that I meant to cover that a few weeks ago thank you in fact there's another
one that the army is the Pentagon's pulling crosses out of chapels thank you but the issue
is that think about it worthless dollars go out they still have value on the surface then
the Chinese use it to buy up infrastructure and ports and but then nobody can have a real
job here unless they're select globalist companies that work with China I mean that's just an
economic takeover plan you know Nixon started all this when he went to China and that was
the public oh we're gonna be friends now is it incredible yes yes it had been a setup
since 49 is my point the u.s. hauled the bacon of the Chinese in World War two so they did
whatever they were told and shank I checked was like hey help me and they said no you
know the stories of them giving them firearms without the firing pen and stuff and shells
without the powder in them that was that's all been declassified now our so-called government
put Mao in who then killed tens of millions of his own people greatest mass murderer in
history and you're absolutely on target what you say is the key to the globalist takeover
program and you can see it all and while we were worried about Russia the whole time China
was the one that was being set up for the takeover and now this gun thing comes up to
steer our eyes away from everything else that's right very well said John are people waking
up over there at the VFW American Legion American Legion yeah I purchase one of your hats so
every time I go out of the house I'm wearing info words on my head people people will stop
and ask me what it is and I've been trying to spread the word Alex well god bless you
I can tell you love this country and you love the ideas of it and love the checks and balances
that have made us wealthy and powerful but with that came the decadence of the wealth
so now we're falling apart and yeah the CFR every month brags that they're selling us
out to China not the Chinese people the Chinese government now that we have moved into the
winter season there is an increased need to support our immunity and health at silver
lungs we are committed to meeting your needs by providing a full selection of silver based
products our most popular silver based products are the 32 ounce nano silver solutions our
2 ounce nano silver nasal applicators as well as our all-natural silver soaps just released
is our 100% natural silver gel our new silver gel is not based on synthetic gelling agents
which quickly evaporate and leave the silver at the surface but rather we have formulated
our silver gel using the natural skin nourishing chemistry of aloe vera to quickly penetrate
and nourish the skin while delivering the silver more effectively visit www.silverlungs.com
and click on our store page to find what silver based products are best for you that's www.silverlungs.com
the new year is a great time to take charge of your health and wellness get serious and
make a stand with supernatural silver this is a breakthrough in silver technology that
is several hundred times more effective than colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver
can be taken orally every day to help fight bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds
supernatural silver is also exceptional for wound care and is highly effective for water
purification it is the number one choice for thousands of people for immune system support
and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency preparedness go to www.supernaturalsilver.com
today and give yourself and your loved ones a fighting chance that's www.supernaturalsilver.com
check out our new low prices and like us on facebook sick of the globalist eugenicist
control freaks adding poison to your water and laughing as you get sick and die start
purifying your water with pro pure my friends i've done a lot of research and the best gravity
filter out there bar none is pro pure and it's available discounted at info wars.com
its filters are silver impregnated to prevent bacterial growth there's no priming required
it's nsf 42 certified optional fluoride filters can reduce fluoride up to 95 easy to set up
and use doesn't require electricity purify water from lake streams ponds and wells this
filter system leaves in beneficial minerals which is key save money by not buying bottled
water and avoid bpa that leaches from the plastic probe here is the best gravity fed
filter out there it's what my family uses info wars.com already has the lowest price
on propior but if you add the promo code water at checkout you get an additional 10 off at
info wars.com you can also call to order 888-253-3139
i was trained in firearms i carried a concealed weapon i made the determination that if somebody
was going to try to take me out i was going to take them with me if i could have gotten
51 votes in the senate of the united states for an outright ban picking up every one of
them mr and mrs america turn them all in i would have done it defending the republic
from enemies foreign and domestic it's alex jones
this video is up at info wars.com we just posted it also prison planet.com and i found
it over at drugsreport.com it's a bright bart exclusive journalist accosted by security
over mayor bloomberg gun control question and it's a talk radio network senior investigative
reporter jason matera and again talk radio networks got over a thousand affiliates i
mean it's it's i don't know 10 times bigger than cnn 20 times i mean one of their host
is but i mean that's real media and we're going to play this video after we go to some
calls an explosive exchange outside the u.s conference of mayors meeting in washington
d.c. security guards for billionaire new york city mayor michael bloomberg accosted senior
talk radio network investigative reporter jason matera when he asked the mayor about
his strong support for gun control in the video bloomberg is seen surrounded by security
matera approaches bloomberg and asked in the spirit of gun control will you disarm your
entire security team see that's what they that would say it discredits you to point
out we have security that's hoping you stop bringing it up of course it doesn't discredit
us that they get waivers from their own gun control laws and have private security that's
what totally destroys them with the public so they're like that's why they freak out
and rough him up bloomberg's reply uh you will get back to you and this is coming out
of the uh washington d.c. mayor's conference and nypd out of their jurisdiction boom do
what gangsters do why can you defend yourself but not the majority of americans matera asked
as the mayor walks away look at the team of security you've got and you're an advocate
for gun control so he's letting them walk away you don't do that to don carlioni boom
security turns around cops out of their jurisdiction back you're about to get it and the video
is incredible that video again is coming up we've just posted it at info wars.com so be
sure and hit refresh there the video then cuts to matera walking further down the street
when one of the men guarding bloomberg identified as officer stockman nypd stops matera and
asked to see his photo id matera complies before asking is this standard procedure for
the press wait wait wait it's standard procedure to be questioned members of the press the
officer reaches inside his jacket and grabs a pen as if to write down the journalist's
name you're going to write it down now ask matera oh no sorry says officer stockton video
then cuts to the scene further down the street where officer stockman trailing matera once
again can be heard saying mr matera sir do you have a date of birth it's none of your
business what my date of birth is so again first they get the id out of their jurisdiction
i told them no matera's it's none of your business matera's january 18th on the street
interview done in conjunction with talk radio networks is not the first time matera has
received a treatment for asking liberal politicians tough questions and it just goes on there
in 2011 vice president joe biden warned matera let's get it straight guy don't screw around
with me when he confronted biden about the use of a rape reference when discussing republican
opposition to obama's uh jobs bill the washington post uh covered that
and again it's them all they're basically grabbing on him and stuff uh we'll go to some
phone calls here we got a bunch of other uh videos coming up as well uh let's uh go ahead
and talk to tim in idaho you're on the air go ahead alex how are you doing good brother
what's on your mind well number one i want to thank you for all your hard work you did
and you know we all know we got screwed because we should have an american president in the
white house you know i still look forward to president paul as my leader and the one
thing that i would really like to see you do alex is i'd like to have you inform all
of these people out here how obama is giving away everything of value in america to the
flippin chinese you know when i say the chinese alex let's go bk on those sobs because if
we don't buddy gun up because that's where we're going i have i'm a veteran from vietnam
i have stood on the mountain praying to god and unfortunately i have felt the winds of
war again i did not want to feel those again i am darn near 60 years old but i'm ready
to die for the bring them back the constitution that our forefathers died for and i hope the
rest of your listeners feel the same way i do i know you woke me up in 2008 and i have
probably brought more than 100 people more awake to your message well great job tim you
know in my first film made in 97 america destroyed by design i show the cfr plans that are public
that the chinese century doesn't mean the chinese people it means suicide nets and mass
enslavement and forced organ harvesting but the globalists went and made a deal they put
mao in they made the deal public in the 70s to have them have goods made so cheap nobody
could compete in slave factories you name it to then leverage out business over here
where only select globalists can do business with the chinese factories through the chinese
communist party and now the chinese government's buying the roads the oil the infrastructure
they're coming back with the dollars that are worthless once they devalue the dollar
buying up everything okay and it's also again about deindustrialization it's an economic
warfare operation the chinese people china could collapse anytime so it's either it takes
over it knows that in a big bubble or it collapses so the globalists are trying to prop it up
that's why they'll pay you know 22 billion dollars to ship the biggest general motors
factories in the world to china last year starting two years ago cadillac and vault
and others because that's the deal that's the globalist investments they all get the
money off the top from that uh so the chinese people want freedom they're good people on
average just like americans are good people you know i talk about the british government
being corrupt i'm not bashing brits when i talk about the israeli government being corrupt
i'm not bashing the general israelis or the average iranian is a good person who wants
freedom it government tends to be bad throughout history founding fathers told us that history
shows that you better keep government small uh but yeah i know this china issue i mean
i remember military officers telling me 15 years ago the plan was to use chinese soldiers
here and i'd be like what now they're talking in fema documents like nle09 about using foreign
troops using chinese troops to disarm americans uh i mean it's just insane and the chinese
government says take the americans guns i appreciate your call tim i mean it's it's
it's it's just it's insane to have newsweek come out last week and say we need the communist
chinese to tell us what to do we need piers morgan to tell us what to do in that article
piers pressure and alex jones has to be dealt with let him prepare his flamethrower we're
preparing for him and it's openly threatening and the article is it's good to have piers
morgan a foreigner telling us what to do america is done get used to being run by china and
the guy says it with pleasure and again people that say israel runs everything israel lobby
is a is a big manipulator in there but i mean i've done my research the china lobby and
the federal reserve lobby which is tied to israel is really at the top of the food chain
that very writer at newsweek saying basically america's done and celebrating it and celebrating
quote our waning power the guy basically wants to end israel i was reading his writings
he has a book out about it it's just like it's just crazy i'm not saying i'm not saying
i'm not even debating israel okay because that's a trap designed to be a trap i'm not
stepping into it the point is newsweek gave this guy a whole section to run down israel
and separately he's saying the chinese need to take over i mean it's just crazy and then
israel selling our secrets to china my point of bringing that up is where is the continuity
in this where do all these globalists think they're going to go once we're turned over
to the communist chinese just very bizarre just very bizarre it's mainly just open the
gates open the gates bring down our countries i'll sell out to you you know to the chinese
it's just like falling before the communist chinese just groveling to them and he says
it's good to get used to that they admit they're getting us used to foreigners telling us what
to do it's like i wrote the article but from a different perspective he's admitting hey
we're here to get you used to a world government and everything will be sacrificed for world
government the u.s you name it england let's jam in another call here doris and tennessee
you're on the air thanks for holding hey um i was listening to uh you know i'm a real
big fan just like you i liked john kennedy and um but i was listening to a 1961 uh speech
you made at the un where he called for global disarmament yes early on this is a great point
he he pushed through state department memorandum 7277 it's a little 40-something page manual
of memory serves it's online i've got original copies here in the office uh it's actually
in those uh bernadine smith big files i don't know where we put those but the point is 7277
says first all the individuals disarm then the militaries disarm except for paramilitary
un garrisons of SWAT teams in every city and how they're going to disarm the police after
they disarm us and yeah kennedy kind of bought into all that till he found out what it was
really about then he pulled out of it i mean you know people were really chumps back then
they didn't they didn't know all that we know go ahead uh that's what that might be you
know the the good old boy club wasn't ready for that back then uh aka is a new world order
so that might have bought into some of the reasons why they assassinated him yeah stay
there stay there i'm going to come back to you there it is freedom from war the united
states program for general and complete disarmament the peaceful world u.s department of state
department of state publication 7277 disarmament series 5 released september 1961 office of
public services bureau of public affairs we'll be right back stay with us
hello i'm alex jones myself my family the info wars.com team want to relay to you and
your families that we are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front
info wars.com is leading the fight against the technocrats but we can't do that without
your help by getting the films bumper stickers and t-shirts and info wars.com you will wake
up people in your area and support our operation as we move to the next level we need your
help to spread the word like never before they wish to hide themselves during this tectonic
battle between the forces of freedom and darkness you are the response to the globalist technocrats
and their program of global eugenics dehumanization and ultimate extermination the war is here
it's an info war the spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of 1984 hi there my name is frank
bates what i'm about to tell you in the next 60 seconds could get me in a lot of trouble
i just created a free video presentation at 123coverup.com that exposes the electricity
monopolies and government agencies for what they really are incompetent line crooks that
are counting on your ignorance and fear to keep your power bills criminally high some
have called this a conspiracy others have called it a cover-up and you will be shocked
to find out how deep the conspiracy goes my video at 123coverup.com exposes the truth
and shows you the secret of how i beat them and how you can beat them too watch the controversial
video that thousands of other smart patriots have already seen in the last three months
go to 123coverup.com and discover one weird trick to slash your power bill and protect
your home go watch my video now at 123coverup.com before they force me to shut it down again
that's 123coverup.com on the average americans work between 45 to 50 years hoping to build
up enough wealth to retire and live out their golden years unfortunately with taxation the
rising cost of food energy housing and medical many retirees are forced to live below the
poverty line is this a flaw free enterprise or is our monetary unit we call the federal
reserve note forcing us into perpetual debt ensuring inflation and higher taxes these
questions and more can be answered by reading g edward griffin's book the creature from
jekyll island congressman ron paul states it's what every american needs to know about
central bank power a gripping adventure into the secret world of international banking
cartel hi this is ted anderson i will give a silver dollar from the early 1900s to anyone
who purchases this book call 1-800-686-2237 and order a copy today it's critical that
the public be made aware of the system call and order your copy today at 1-800-686-2237
that's 1-800-686-2237 you land in buenos aires then a shuttle to santa rosa where a nicely
furnished cabin with all amenities wi-fi executive food and wine and laundry service awaits after
a good night's sleep your adventure begins you're on a golden stag safari for big game
but it's not africa it's argentina one-on-one guided hunts for water buffalo huger bighorn
rams wild boar and the biggest stag deer in south america all gold medal quality all the
action you can handle land rovers top rental guns with scopes all food beverages hunting
guides ground transportation included and more all more affordable than you can imagine
the adventure of a lifetime starts at golden stag safaris.com the big game hunting ranch
golden stag safaris.com coming up we got some videos and the audio we're gonna air of some
pretty amazing treason bloomberg goons grabbing reporters and taking stuff from them out of
their jurisdiction totally illegal uh man i tell you i just i had michael moore's guys
do that to me for no reason like 10 feet away with a camera hey michael what about this
why are you going after our guns boom they're like elbowing me and stuff i just elbowed
them back i mean i just can't handle it anymore i just can't handle these people thinking
they're royal and i'm their slave all right doris go ahead and start over with the point
you were making uh go ahead okay the point i was making is i'd read a book called accessories
after the fact that all the people that got killed after the assassination of john kennedy
then i went to listen to a speech about in 1961 to the united nations and he talked about
global disarmament it sounded a whole lot like obama and no no that's it but i mean
kennedy the difference was kennedy actually did do some good things he got sold on it
as a good idea but a year later he pulled out of all that a year later he he understood
it was a con game uh he signed an order to abolish the fellow reserve i mean uh he didn't
want to give nukes to israel he did a lot of things that made the power structure very
very upset okay now now we have two uh people that represent us corker and lamar alexander
and i've noticed they've been getting really popular lately with the president uh corker's
from chattanooga chattanooga tennessee is the only place in a economic recovery around
in that i see and um alexander walked out with the president the day of the inauguration
i don't believe we'll ever have another uh honest election um in my lifetime and uh well
no listen that's why the fix is in they've told republicans you vote for open borders
you vote for uh all of this or you're never getting back into office and and that's why
we're sold out senate group reaches immigration deal and folks we're already bankrupt now
they're going to bring in they say 11 million it's more like 30 and just totally legalize
the illegals and then let them legalize their families and let them get welfare and again
the goal isn't to actually empower people from mexico uh these people do contribute
to the country well there's really two different types of immigrants there's the ones that
come here and work and there's those that come here from mexico and just get on welfare
and become gangsters and that seems to be the kind our government wants uh and it's
just despicable god bless you man good to hear from you tona in uh arizona you're on
the air hey alex uh i've been listening last year um i i actually was talking to my brother
recently and uh you know i was telling him about what was happening about like the federal
reserve and like how they're taking the gun the guns and everything and he didn't he didn't
really believe me at first until he started talking to a marine uh from youtube this marine
was talking about um what the same things you're talking about and what's happening
but you don't have to believe me or the marine i have abc news admitting the army's training
for house-to-house gun confiscation in america but i don't just believe abc news i have shot
or been sent video let's not exaggerate a hundred times in the last 17 years of marines
training to take american's guns the role players wear john deere hats and say this
isn't right that's america you can't take my gun and they practice shooting you and
homeland security naturalnews.com dhs by seven thousand full auto assault rifles the story's
up at infowars.com as well calls them personal defense weapons on top of tens of thousands
of other machine guns full auto and the 1.6 plus billion they've gotten more bullets it's
like 1.6 and then a half million i guess 1.65 billion now i mean they're and that's in the
last 14 months i mean they're they're arming and digging in like it's the end of the world
i got a clip coming up where an obama administration official told a senior major fund manager
very well respected that they're going to kill the dollar well no kidding we know that's
their plan do you know what's going to happen when the dollar goes belly up yeah it's going
to be chaos it's going to be real bad real bad the point i was getting is my brother
he started from a different perspective one of you you know because the marines he saw
it as a man that has fought a war and he said that my brother has said that oh well alice
jones you know he hasn't been in the war but not not that i'm saying that or anything like
that but he was basically he the marine kind of made him woke him up but so made me kind
of thinking like oh i'm like uh alex jones right so i started kind of looking uh into
you your background and everything and and a lot of things like in secret societies and
all of that i just had one question if you knew anything about um the genesis genesis
the genesis of there's a lot of stuff called genesis this network no no it's spelled g
no j e s u i t it's like it's um it's some type of like from the vatican uh yo jesuits
jesuit yes do you know anything about that oh it's just it's just a question yeah sure
i'll tell you about the jesuits on the other side we'll be right back stay with us ladies
and gentlemen we're on the march the empire's on the run alex jones and the gcn radio network
millions of people are going to get sick this winter from colds flu and other illnesses
don't be one of them protect yourself with supernatural silver a revolutionary new broad
spectrum antibacterial solution recent advances in silver technology have resulted in a silver
solution that can be used daily to prevent bacteria viruses mold and food poisoning and
help improve wound healing supernatural silver is safe enough to consume every day while
powerful enough to destroy the causes of many serious diseases such as strep staph pneumonia
coals flus and other harmful pathogens this new technology has the ability to terminate
entire colonies of harmful bacteria at several hundred times the effectiveness of colloidal
or ionic silver solutions the science digest journal says silver is our mightiest germ
fighter it is virtually non-toxic and is emerging as a wonder of modern medicine go to supernatural
silver.com today and use the promo code silver 2012 for 20 off that's supernatural silver.com
and like us on facebook if you want an american company with american products made by americans
here is the cow ben soap company alex and his staff have used these pure soap products
for years these all-natural soaps are made from the highest quality vegetable and coconut
oils that are earth friendly and safe see them on the web at 5starsoap.com or call 800-340-7091
for a free catalog buy the one to two month sample package and enjoy soaps that are twice
as good as what you're using now or save big with a one to two year supply of soaps for
all your cleaning needs this is an amazing deal you can save thousands of dollars and
you will love the way real soap makes you feel see them on the web at 5starsoap.com
or call 800-340-7091 for a free catalog the new year is a great time to take charge of
your health and wellness get serious and make a stand with supernatural silver this is a
breakthrough in silver technology that is several hundred times more effective than
colloidal or ionic silver supernatural silver can be taken orally every day to help fight
bacteria viruses infections yeast and molds supernatural silver is also exceptional for
wound care and is highly effective for water purification it is the number one choice for
thousands of people for immune system support and it is also a perfect choice for your emergency
preparedness go to supernaturalsilver.com today and give yourself and your loved ones
a fighting chance that's supernaturalsilver.com check out our new low prices and like us on
facebook big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want to stop tyranny well so
does he live from the infowars.com studios it's alex jones revolution calling revolution
calling i'm gonna play this clip in a moment of nypd ndc out of their jurisdiction following
a guy down the street harassing him grabbing on him getting in his face i mean i'd be like
you're out of your jurisdiction you got an issue call the police and i mean let me tell
you physically you'd have a right to defend yourself they put your their hands on you
i mean these cops are so out of control man so out of control and i'm just getting to
the point where i can't put up with it anymore i mean i mean i'd be like yeah i'll give you
some id i want yours you're out of your jurisdiction you're in a lot of trouble it's like when
my crew was in kansas city like three years ago to interview william k black one of the
former top federal investigators of savings and loan fraud for obama a film we were making
fall the republic you can see the interview in there they're driving and they see a federal
reserve building show they well i'll tell the story in a minute i'll just sick i'll
tell the story in a minute by the way there are a lot of great products that we promote
and sell that erin dykes has used and others just had incredible effects and i'm on this
as well root beer belly an amazing probiotic sprinkles so you can store them it's not the
stuff you got to keep in the refrigerator and it tastes like root beer you can put it
in water or just eat it like candy truly amazing and innovative like everything longevity is
into and you can read more about root beer belly at info wars health dot com that's info
wars health dot com promotes healthy bacteria and the intestines contains five micro capsulated
probiotic strains only four calories per packet tastes great like root beer five times more
likely to cultivate than other probiotic supplements they've got all the studies there on the site
ten billion innovative probiotic strains included the time of production a minimum of five billion
guaranteed to support your digestive system boost your immune carrying increase overall
health inhibits the growth of harmful bacteria supporting healthy digestive system starts
with root beer belly available at info war shop dot com or call eight eight eight seven
eight nine throw that back on screen for me i'm gonna give that number out thanks again
i'll give you that number eight eight eight seven eight nine nine two seven seven again
eight eight eight seven eight nine nine two seven seven and give the info wars health
team a call eight eight eight seven eight nine nine two seven seven and also in force
health dot com has links to all the sub pages as well if you forget in force health dot
com you just go to info wars store dot com okay finishing up with this and then i'll
get into your jesuit things it's already went off on this topic um i want to play this mayor
clip i was just mentioning earlier and so my guys just naturally wanted to get a shot
of the big 20 story you know building from a ways back so they're off the property and
they shoot the building but not because they were scared to go on private property it's
just you know it's got a big open park area they videotape it and then they go what is
that and they go over the world war one city owned the national world war one memorial
really interesting and people in black uniforms with guns show up and say we're with the federal
reserve you've got to leave well who are your security guards will give us your id's they
do that even though i've told them if it's security guard don't then they go okay leave
now and start putting their hands on their guns total color law we could have sued them
and owned them we're just too busy fighting the big issues to get diverted off on this
and it just makes me physically sick to see this video exclusive journalists accosted
by security over bloomberg gun control questions it's up on infowars.com right now the video
of this from bright bart along with attack helicopters let loose with machine gun fire
over miami here's morgan admits defeat in gun control debate that's playing possum there
ladies and gentlemen a new article by watson the astounding hypocrisy of gun control the
astounding hypocrisy of gun control advocates very important article that ties into this
that's all up at infowars.com trying to find the article i know they posted it yeah it's
in the uh in the tiles there it was so it's in the tiles at the top good job guys uh they're
on infowars.com journalists accosted by security over mayor bloomberg gun control questions
so good they i knew it was posted a while back so uh it's from bright bart bright bart.com
now this is what needs to happen everywhere but i'm telling you if i was there i'd be
like hey get your hands off me i'm just asking a question that's assault and then i know
that the dc police wouldn't have done anything but i'd call the police to make a record so
i could sue them by the way i'm still considering shooing the tsa and the apd and i don't just
shoot my mouth off i've sued people before i don't like it but when i gotta do it i gotta
do it the austin cop saying you go through or you're arrested and then and then blowing
up and then trying to get them to not let me fly that guy was just like looking at me
like he wanted me to do something physical hey i got a big brain pal okay if i want to
i'm gonna go get the federal suit perfected and sue you and take away your jet ski okay
but you better know and better be lucky even though i was assaulted at that airport once
by somebody you guys tried to set me up with i don't know if he not him particularly but
that it was clearly a setup rob do saw it grabbing on me and threatening me some thug
they had in there i didn't even let the police arrest him and they were ready to because
i didn't want to deal with the trial and stuff i just said i forgive you in the name of jesus
but i wanted it on record you did this it was all on surveillance tape the point is
is that if i threaten to sue somebody you better believe it's being looked at right
now and i'm telling you i can't handle it anymore so we're going to play this video
i'll uh give you play-by-play uh fill in the parts that radio listeners can't see let's
go ahead and roll it here it is mayor bloomberg how you doing jason i grew up brooklyn in
the spirit of gun control will you disarm your entire security team uh you will get
right back to you'll get back over very friendly like a step in my very friendly body language
they're grabbing on him why grabbing on him dragging him why can you defend yourself but
not shooting back the majority of americans i mean look at look at the team of security
you got and you're an advocate for gun control one two three four five five i'm counting
the probably more i'm good i don't also start the nypd you have idea new sir all right let's
hit pause right there back it up about 20 seconds for me thanks imagine nypd at a u.s
conference of mayors meeting in washington dc how about you're out of your jurisdiction
goon i know you have stop and frisk checkpoints there but not all of america's north korea
yet goon i'm a tv host goon i mean i mean they follow him for a long period of time here
and even after he gives them the info it's not enough and and again this is illegal what
they're doing let's continue
sir how you doing today i'm good i don't also start nypd you have idea new sir i want to
see your i'm credentialed for this may i see it please thank you sure what do we get over
here no no no no no do you have do you even have jurisdiction absolutely yes i do security
there's absolutely sir i asked the question there's nothing i'm not that's all if you
have idea credential i hold it hold this thank you very much
do you have a photo id sir
do do do uh well yeah i'm not gonna give you my dc driver's license is this is this uh
standard procedure for the press for the way it's standard to be questioned standard procedure
in nazi germany was to take everybody's property and shoot him in the back of the head procedure
isn't law it was procedure for black people to be slaves in this country but it didn't
mean it was right so your procedure can go straight to the place where the devil dwells
it's called hades let's go back to this travesty members of the press stand procedure id sir
yeah it was issued by the conference we were just at well can i see id photo id that matches
that name please sure thing thank you sir goes it to him not enough you're gonna write it down now
oh no sorry you're gonna write it there you're gonna write okay we good thank you very much sir
now they come at him again never enough they want to put him in the database
those cops can put you in a terror database don't just tell me your business when my date of birth is
let's see look look we're getting followed ask bloomberg a question we get followed
that's what they did to me in new york guaranteed the same people except they were wearing the the
the uh windbreakers hey ellis you're planning to do anything
oh my gosh we even got some of it on video people are like nobody followed you in new york
come on the the dawn doesn't do in chicago the government's not mafia there either no
no no no there's no such thing as look close to nostra either you know back in the 50s what was
it 51 52 they had organized crime hearings with jaeger hoover who they'd go you know give tens of
thousands of dollars anytime he wanted to go gamble at the horse tracks the mafia would
it was a famous way to pay people off and uh he said there's no such thing as organized crime
and he used the term congressional record conspiracy theory that's right that's right
the conspiracy theory i mean it's a game they play look i see through you it's a con game
unbelievable okay on the jesuit thing uh the jesuits were set up what in was it portugal
by what was his name liola uh and people obsess over is it the jews is it the jesuits is it the
muslims is it the masons is it all big powerful organizations become corrupt and dominant the
nazis modeled their system of control with the ss off the jesuits i'm not saying the jesuits
taught them to be nazis they modeled the black uniforms and the power structure after uh the
system the guys asking me about them what else is it and you cannot deny that now the jesuits who
even took over the papacy for a while till it crushed it uh that the jesuits now today you're
the pope promotes world government and catholics should uh you know really be concerned about how
world government and new world order is being promoted by the muslims the catholics so many
other groups but then it doesn't exist at the same time there's also a popular thing that people put
out to sell books with zero proof or facts that i am a jesuit and it all started about seven years
ago i sent emails by prominent people that put forward the jesuit only conspiracy saying you will
have me on to promote my book or i will expose you as a jesuit now the way to get on the show is
here's my book i think i'd be a great guest not you will have me on or i will expose you i i
think they have a name for that i was like what kind of weirdness is this and um i have i mean
my family are famous protestants uh and i've told the story a million times but no one cares it's
easier to not have research or facts to just say alex's work is nothing i say he works for the pope
so it's true and it's beyond bizarre and they don't apologize to me nothing they they bear
false witness and they lie and i forgive them because that's that's what jesus christ you know
as as you know my teacher and my god has has taught me to do um is to forgive petty people
that are all screwed up um just amazing you know my ancestors came into texas and did not like to
the fact that people were being forced to convert to catholicism to get mexican land grants and so
my ancestor was william airs and david airs there was also a bunch of others very famous you know
raise colonel travis's son the rest of it i'm not going to even get into my family in texas history
because it's so over the top people wouldn't even believe it but you can actually there's been books
written about it if you'd like uh in fact people gone and got my people didn't think i was who i
said they went got my yearbooks they went and found somehow got my birth certificate which i
guess is fine the real spelling of emmerich not the wrong one on wikipedia um and now everything
else has the wrong spelling fans do it with wrong spelling so they give us the sites or facebook
has the wrong name you can't change it uh but they again cointel pro i don't think that's what
this is this is just opportunistic money making they always just put something out there that
can't be proved or disproved completely to to to to demonize someone and make it about the person
when it's not about alex jones the government's trying to take your guns
the government's trying to get rid of the borders and legalize 30 million illegal aliens right now
the government is trying to get rid of the bill of rights and constitution they're running tsa
checkpoints in austin right now and i told you that was coming and i was a coot now where i live
the army shows up at city events and the tsa is out there with guns searching people's bags
illegally but it doesn't matter because i'm supposedly a pop-tart jesuit uh and uh again
uh people don't fight tyranny they just they just they just say i'm bad i mean they've said for 15
years that genesis gcnlive.com is owned by some saudi arabian when it's a hundred percent a
different genesis they've accused genesis of being the porno magazine genesis ted anderson when he
first started this network 16 years ago wanted to have a tv network later so he called the radio the
beginning of it genesis and it's just mental illness and people say no you are owned by the
saudi arabians it's just it's just made up but then they don't get upset about current tv that
actually is run by the arabs now you see so that's how mass mental illness works all right so and
that's fine not everybody's gonna wake up to the tyranny and actually get in the game against
tyranny they're just gonna go down rabbit trails and you know this person's bad and that person's
bad and sit around anointing who's bad and who's good all day and it's sad for me not because i'm
being attacked but because it's sad because these people are just were never meant to have real
discernment or to fight evil they're tools of corruption and don't even know it okay let's go
to this clip here this is a senior obama official we're gonna go to this one first senior obama
official we are going to kill the dollar and uh kyle bass who knows a thing or two about companies
and finance recently spoke to a senior member of the obama administration about their planned
solutions for fixing the u.s economy and bass is a top uh fund manager you know very well respected
uh the answer shouldn't surprise you and let's go ahead and go to that clip now you're in charge
you're in charge of this thing called the united states government budget and it gives you political
and fiscal authority to do quote unquote the right thing yeah would you mark to market balance sheets
today and create the economic downside that that would follow or would you put in place
or attempt to put in place some kind of economic policies to get you to a better place down some
theoretical road i mean how do you solve a problem where you're spending ten percent of you know
you're running a 10 fiscal deficit you're not going to get growth in the absence of private
sector credit demand so the government's idea right now is we're going to export our way out
of this and when i asked a senior member of the obama administration last week how are we going
to grow exports if we won't allow nominal wage deflation and he says we're just going to kill
the dollar and i said okay more you mean um so that i mean that's the only answer and you that's
a dead answer it's a dead answer but it's that's where that's where we're at but see folks that's
the cover to all of this because they know nothing can ever compete with suicide factories with
suicide nets up around them at the dorms no one can compete with forced abortions in the factory
no one they've got regulations here where we can't even compete with mexico or india
okay you know they pay to ship the jobs overseas this is a way all we had left was our dollar to
buy all these goods that's going to go it's all been engineered it's all been planned out so the
chinese money and the rothchild money and the globalist money can pour back in and buy everything
up we're going to come back with another stunning clip this is alex jones with five good reasons you
should consider buying a solar power generator number one new climate legislation could easily
double or triple your electric bill number two our new energy czar wants to control how much
power your electric company allows you to have it's true total government control of electricity
in the name of smart grid technology is coming number three in some areas of the country the
power grid is dangerously overloaded and now new socialist legislation is only compounding the
problem number four dangerous weather is always a threat to local grids every year thousands of
families lose their power from weather related onages number five a solar power generator
provides powerful backup insurance and peace of mind folks i really believe in the solar power
generators offered by solutions from science one of my oldest sponsors you can get more information
at www.mysolarbackup.com that's mysolarbackup.com remember the government doesn't own the sun so go
to mysolarbackup.com or call 1-877-327-0365 we all know that berkey water purification systems
are the most trusted name in water filtration as an authorized berkey dealer for over six years in
serving thousands of satisfied customers the berkey guy offers amazing specials for berkey
water filtration systems the berkey light systems include a set of self-sterilizing and re-cleanable
black purification elements that purify water by removing chlorine pathogenic bacteria cysts and
parasites to non-detectable levels and remove harmful chemicals such as herbicides and pesticides
order the berkey light system today complete with two black berkey elements for only 231
dollars and the berkey guy will ship your order free of charge with the purchase of a berkey
light the berkey guy is also offering a set of fluoride and arsenic filters for only $39.99
that's over 30% off the retail price call the berkey guy at 1-877-886-3653 that's 1-877-886-3653
or order online at goberky.com that's goberky.com today injuries slow healing aches and pains
constipation weakness fatigue are all common the older one gets the progressive deterioration of
the body that occurs almost universally the older one gets can partly to significantly be prevented
with conscientious attention to nutrition if the hansa men can play rugby in their 90s then it is
possible for everyone in north america to experience a more youthful life as well one key ingredient
to warding off aging and reversing some of it is the type and quality of protein consumed all
protein foods or supplements you currently consume are heat damaged destroying 50 to 75 percent of
your ability to utilize the bodybuilding amino acids one world way is not heat damaged and
allows your body to utilize 100 of the amino acids this feat no one else has achieved the results to
your health can be amazing call 888-988-3325 that's 888-988-3325 or visit one world way
dot com that's one world w-h-e-y dot com
again how did i know they started having army show up at events where i live
at the park uh and tsa because they said they would
and i i remember shooting video for martial law in 1999 actually for the film police state 2000
and again people saw the footage and thought it was fake that i had hired the corona of the
land in san francisco uh hovercraft helicopters it had to be computer no way marines were training
to kill americans and take their guns you know they were doing interrogation where'd you get
the gun the helmet oh i got it from san francisco i'm i'm part of the militia people said this can't
be real they weren't ready in 1999 and then i was sent footage from all over the country of
of the boy scouts like 12 year olds training coming out to the marines and going what are
your parents have in the house well he's got three rifles and two handguns good job
kids in white t-shirts riding around hebron maryland
and then the marines go over with guns and say turn your cameras off i mean this is america
and then i had the army try to set me up and it's so insane mike hanson saw it i mean who
would believe i went to heb to brooksville florida and you're in the woods and a guy
jumps out because you're trying to film the military do gun confiscation drills in the town
and a guy jumps out and tries to set the woods on fire to blame you and you're like stomping it out
and then having to grab the guy and say i'm gonna you know physically beat you up if you don't do
this and then doombuggies show up and all this stuff and then you go talk to locals they go
i've been told not to talk to you the army came door to door i mean it's like a movie
folks the government is evil okay i tried to expose all this and they were ready to burn
things down and blame me with special forces now the military isn't bad people i actually woke them
up by doing that the point is is that we're in trouble listen to this on cbs news they have
people on this is just this is just this weekend it's every day you see this saying it's time to
give up on the constitution well that's nothing some of these shows bad mouth the founders
these people are collaborators the full videos up at law professor on cbs says let's give up
on the constitution here's that clip i've got a simple idea let's give up on the constitution
how about you go to hell i know it sounds radical i know you're a traitor but it's really not i know
i'm a sack of crap disobedience is as american as apple pie for example most of our greatest
presidents jefferson lincoln wilson and both roosevelds had doubts about the constitution
and many of them disobeyed it when it got in their way to be clear i don't think we should
give up on everything in the constitution the constitution has many important and inspiring
provisions that's enough but we should obey see see see this is the spin jefferson said it wasn't
enough protections and so did the others lincoln was the one that went absolutely hog wild and was
wild and was a tyrant it was abraham lincoln that arrested all of his opposition and let the army
rob everything even in the north i mean they use it as a power grab oh man and again i'm not saying
the south was good either it was all manipulated by british intelligence see it's not one side's
good other sides bad usually usually it's more complex than that and lincoln actually thought
he was doing good i've actually read his writings the guy owned nothing wanted to own nothing he was
very very strange person his wife was into the occult i mean this guy's a weirdo man
probably the weirdest president we've ever had i mean a real weirdo
the point is go read oh it doesn't even matter people like what he ended slavery
he said i don't want to end slavery he did that at the end it was not about slavery slavery was
already being phased out because whites in the south figured out slaves were being used to
leverage them and keep them as sharecroppers anyways oh my gosh i'm gonna go into overdrive
your calls are coming up stay with us thank you for listening to gcn visit gcnlive.com today
okay looking back on 2012 we ask ourselves how did we ever survive from natural disasters like
hurricane sandy and the devastating summer drought to the family hardships brought on by a disastrous
economy our hearts go out to those that have lost everything at efoods direct we hear from customers
every day that are fortunate enough to weather life's storm by having a supply of food on hand
after hurricane sandy danny from new york city wrote almost all the grocery stores are closed
but i managed to get my efoods just in time to be able to help my sister and niece it is better to
be prepared 10 years too early than one day too late i can warn you but i can't feed you heed the
warnings and do what alex has done call 800-409-5633 today or go to efoods direct.com slash alex and
build your food supply it's the best tasting non-gmo long-term storeable food on the planet
call 800-409-5633 or efoods direct.com slash alex you can bet your life on efoods direct
coast to coast direct from austin you're listening to the alex jones broadcasting network
network
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want answers well so does he
he's alex jones on the gcn radio network and now live from austin texas alex jones
jamming some more of these incredibly patient listeners michael in california the nick and
others mike you want to talk about uh weasel morgan go ahead hey alex what's up uh worldwide
broadcast brother what's on your mind well uh i just want to let you know i'm a huge supporter
um it's hard being a hard being a true supporter over here in los angeles i'm sure you know it's
a very uh well too liberal extremely liberal place to live but you know i truly believe
that it has nothing to do with your political party it has really nothing to do with what
your personal beliefs are it's about you know government control you know we have the the right
to choose our own party and the right to do our own things play america's so great but we shouldn't
you know we shouldn't um let the government control us the way they're slowly doing
actually rapidly doing now like you say well i mean so-called liberals are at the tail end of
the payoff the globalists are going to take everything they've got and it's important that
they remember why they've been enslaved see that's why they got to have the physical clamp
down because they know people aren't going to go along with this very soon right right totally and
you know i'm a democrat um but i'm more of a libertarian than a democrat and all my friends
are democrats and even they are starting to open up based on the information i share with them they
learn from you and i learned my own research well they better just figure out both parties are
controlled by offshore globalist and uh but it says you wanted to comment about piers morgan
okay yeah sorry uh so basically i think you did a good thing with piers i think um
i think you're absolutely right i think the guy's just a puppet i think the whole network's a puppet
um and you're right you know the it's beyond just the second amendment it's it's all the amendments
that are in danger if they take away the you know the guns from the people the second amendment
a lot of people here in la think the second amendment isn't that we don't kill each other
they don't know that it's really about um oh yeah they've spun it and said the second
amendment means you don't have guns god bless you good to hear from you look gun crime is
going way down that's just a fact all this hysteria is a big act folks why do they want
our guns they're getting ready to collapse everything let's talk to jim and virginia
about the monarch butterfly go ahead jim hi alex uh first time caller prison planet tv subscriber
oathkeeper i was with you in build a burger in shantilly i really like what you said about the
us being like the monarch butterflies i agree with you that we can be one with the creator
and that this can happen through jim i think i remember your voice are you the guy that gave
me some documents no it wasn't me i was kind of in the background uh kind of the uh let me get
back to our creator go ahead yeah i just wanted my dog barking and sorry about that that's okay
i i just wanted to mention he gets excited when he hears alex jones i just want to say uh stg
soli deo gloria to god alone be the glory is what bach wrote on all his musical scores
regarding us becoming one with the universe that pantheism is god alone who reveals the secrets of
the universe not god's creation no no no but i agree i'm saying but but the creation is
evidence of the creator absolutely yeah yeah well good i i just am uh just uh lighting fires with
you i'm a global warming guy the people are warming up to liberty and the worldwide fire
for liberty is going to is happening for you and me and all of us working beautiful beautiful
brother god bless you nick in california last time caller we have in this segment real fast
let's talk about hsbc go ahead well the top when sandy hook broke out the hsbc where the talk was
just about the settlement and it was just about to develop and it just disappeared so so quickly
that i got so suspicious that i i actually schizophrenic to think that even he had a private
organizational link to past and furious yeah the government wouldn't do anything bad i mean sure
they shoot people up with syphilis and kill the soldiers and secret tests but that's loving yeah
hsbc just got a 55 million dollar 10-year insurance distribution agreement with aig and
they've been fined and but i mean that's nothing i mean the big mega banks are involved in just
every form of bazaar as you can imagine look i'm out of time uh we got a call with a virus threat
we got you know what i'll do 20 more minutes of overdrive i can't help it i gotta do it i love
the radio transmission so brawn james and others and a few more callers 800-25-99231 we are coming
back straight ahead and then there'll be info wars nightly news tonight seven o'clock hello i'm alex
jones myself my family the info wars.com team want to relay to you and your families that we
are intensifying our efforts against the globalist on every front info wars.com is leading the fight
against the technocrats but we can't do that without your help by getting the films bumper
stickers and t-shirts and info wars.com you will wake up people in your area and support
our operation as we move to the next level we need your help to spread the word like never before
they wish to hide themselves during this tectonic battle between the forces of freedom and darkness
you are the response to the globalist technocrats and their program of global eugenics dehumanization
and ultimate extermination the war is here it's an info war the spirit of 1776 versus the mindset of
1984 in this unpredictable world disaster can strike anyone that's why an essential part of
any emergency survival plan must be stove in a can when power goes out and gas lines are down
the portable safe easy to use stove in a can cooks food up to four hours and boils water in as little
as five minutes stove in a can comes with everything you need the stove fuel even waterproof
matches all in a compact durable heavy duty container plus the all-natural non-explosive
100 waterproof fuel source can be stored indefinitely say goodbye to the hassle and
danger of propane lighter fluid or gas stock up now and protect your family with stove in a can
starting out at 29.99 special bundle offers now available with a 100 satisfaction guarantee
or your money back order yours today at stove in a can.com that's stove in a can.com
Hello, this is Ty Bollinger, author of the best-selling book Cancer Step Outside the Box.
I want you to know some very important information. In 1985, President Ronald Reagan
requested that carnivora be sent directly to the White House at a time when only the President
could obtain this world-class healer. Now, 27 years later, carnivore capsules are used around
the world to keep people healthy. Now you can protect yourself and your loved ones in this age
of superbugs with 17 naturally occurring compounds that instinctively respond to abnormal cells only
without harming a single normal cell. If you want to stay healthy, now's your chance to literally
wake up your critical immune cells to attack harmful invaders that don't belong in your body.
Call 1-866-Venus-Fly or order from carnivora.com that's c-a-r-n-i-v-o-r-a.com that's 1-866-836-8735
1-866-Venus-Fly or visit carnivora.com. Protect your immune system, it's the only one you've got.
He's the T-Rex of political talk. Alex Jones on the GCN Radio Network.
Okay, let's race through your phone calls on this live worldwide broadcast on the 28th this Monday,
and I'm your host Alex Jones. Let's go to Braun in Alabama. You're on the air. Welcome.
How you doing Alex? Good, sir.
You know me, I run wtfroi.com. I was calling about the Katrina virus and to inquire if you
guys had heard about it because it's supposedly posing a big risk with the new norovirus strain
and the flu spreading to all 50 states. Now he's talking about the guy that I interviewed on my
show, David Christiansen. He's a decorated Air Force officer and he's warning about the
possibility of a pandemic basically. I'll say this, I mean there was no heavy
flu season four years ago with that whole hype with the H1N1. But this year I've seen more people
sick, heard about more people sick. Overall, I've been super healthy the last few years and had more
energy since I got on vitamins and minerals. But despite that, I have been sick twice in the last
12 months or so, which is unheard of other than having allergies to hay fever and stuff that I've
pretty much had for about 15 years. And it has just been rough and we know that so many of the
flu shots they give actually turn into flu. That's admitted, it's such an incredible hoax
that people go out and take shots. But no, I actually just search engine Katrina like the
hurricane. He turns it Katrina virus, he was actually black bag NDA style before the first NDA
provision really came across. And he's documented all this in the federal court documents on his
website. Very interesting, I mean look, we know the H1N1 itself was not even really a real virus.
It was a stimulant virus released the year before by one of those major companies. I forget which
ones we had scientists on at the time. Again, it's truly amazing, I'll have to look more into that.
Thank you, Braun. James in Texas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hey Alex, how you doing? Fantastic job. Look here, I work on law enforcement. Some years ago I called
you to the station and you were just getting started on this Chinese stuff. Like say, we was
investigating a drug run and everything in Houston, right? So we stopped at 18 with a truck.
And lo and behold, we checked it out, it was a false bottom. Would you not believe that there
was a Chinese guy sitting up on a laptop inside of an 18 truck that was a false bottom. And this
was at the Port of Houston. People better understand that these guys are working on
the port and lots of stuff we can't get out there. But I'm telling you, your port and these
containers and everything, the way they just typically want to bring the Chinese into your
particular country would be the containers. Because used containers are basically to have
bomb shelters and everything else and use it for apartments now. And also, Ted Gunnison before he
passed away, poor souls, said to y'all, even Mr. Navy Seals, and I'm a military myself,
that the military was going after Seals, Special Forces, because we knew how to fight.
And then voices came on to explain the same thing too, what you got to say. All these people
down in the world don't understand and listen to what these people are saying. Even the politicians,
because if they come in here and take over Chinese, the politicians are going to understand
that there's going to be head on the chopping block too and left alone with us too. Because
like I say, once they take over, they're going to get them too. So they better wake up to the
fact of what's going on. And they're talking about a gun-free zone. Just put a sign up in
the United States, a gun-free zone, and any nation will take over us. But decide to come,
and our government, and the ones that they'll need, that's going to be a consistent-
Sure, sure, sir, let me stop because you're making a lot of really good points. And I can tell you
on a cell phone, I'm getting about 90% of it. Can you talk right into the phone?
Right, one second.
No, no, that's a lot better. Where's the phone now?
Okay, can you hear me now?
A million times better, I can tell that was a hands-free or something. Okay, start over,
because you brought up General Boykin, you brought up Ted Gunnerson. Yeah, I remember Ted
Gunnerson, now that you mention it, on my show 15 years ago, it was like 1998, saying in the future,
they're going to say veterans of the terrorists. And I remember going, whoa, whoa, whoa.
But it turns out now, again, imagine how over the top this is.
Now the Homeland Security manuals that they're giving police all over the country say
veterans are the number one enemy, bad mouthing the founding fathers. How obvious does this have
to get? A, B, you were talking about finding Chinese coming in in these containers.
That's actually come out in the news, AK-47s, drugs, and usually get swept under the rug.
Start over what you were saying. I want people to hear all this really clearly now.
And then specifically down in Houston, I guess you're a police officer, it sounds like.
Are people waking up now when they've got a bill saying the government can keep its
guns but the citizens can't? I mean, how obvious is that?
Yes, everybody's waking up now. As a matter of fact, if you go on any network to try to find
ammo and try to find weapons and everything. We just had a gun show in Houston this past
weekend at the George R. Brown. And you can't find semi-automatic weapons and everything.
People are realizing that the government is basically leaving us out there to dry.
And for anybody to come in, if people are saying right now, it's like, look here,
just put a sign in the United States to say, here, gun-free zone, come and take over and just take
over the whole thing. And like I say, the politicians better understand that we are the
first offense to help them because when it comes down to a long time ago, you remember a long time
ago when you had the sheriff's department round up a posse to say, we need the citizens to protect.
The same thing as we had back in the 50s. We had civil defense where everybody had weapons,
they had the civil defense training to actually go to help the country. Now it's been imported
where they've basically talked to giving us away. And the politicians better understand that
your people in America is the one that's going to be able to protect them if we get to the point of
getting overthrown. Because when we go, they go the same time too, and there's nobody to protect
them. They think they got redoubts, but like I said, again, they're letting them come in there
through the port. Listen, I agree, this is what crazy elites have always done.
They oppress their own people till the whole system collapses. That's why the third world
is the way it is. And it's just insane. And again, I go back to crime statistics. I don't
just believe every government statistic like unemployment or inflation. We know those are
cooked, we've had experts on. Worldwide, the Bible of statistics is crime statistics
set up by J. Edgar Hoover himself with the card index system.
They get the local numbers, they put them in, they're not perfect, but there's some of the best
numbers out there. 49% drop in violent crime since 1991. Now, everybody knows more guns means less
crime. And so the fact that the police are hearing turn the guns in, they're not stupid.
And so that's good news, though, because what you're saying is what I'm getting.
Even police that thought patriots were loons are now going, wait, it's all happening.
I really think the establishment is miscalculated.
But the thing about it, Alex, they need to go back to the civil defense because
we have given away our civil defense to, like I said, a long time ago. I'm 52 years old.
And we had that where we would defend the country, not put our country in harm's way.
So we need to turn the people around and say, look here, instead of us giving our guns away,
we need to protect even-
I mean, even-
Absolutely, and if we have a collapse, the good people need to be armed. The good people turning
their guns in during a collapse is the opposite of what you want. God bless you. Let me play this
clip for you and get your take on it, James. He's a police officer from Houston. This is Sheriff
David Clark of Milwaukee saying, hey, they're laying off sheriff's deputies. We're having cuts.
And he responded down to the city council getting on to him for the city. He's outside the city.
He's saying, look, you guys have got bodyguards. The general public doesn't. Here is that clip.
I'm Sheriff David Clark and I want to talk to you about something personal,
your safety. It's no longer a spectator sport. I need you in the game. But are you ready?
With officers laid off and furloughed, simply calling 911 and waiting is no longer your best
option. You can beg for mercy from a violent criminal, hide under the bed, or you can fight
back. But are you prepared? Consider taking a certified safety course and handling a firearm
so you can defend yourself until we get there. You have a duty to protect yourself and your family.
We're partners now. Can I count on you? This safety message brought to you by the
Milwaukee County Sheriff's Office. What do you think of that?
Oh, that's fantastic. I saw that and I'm aware of him and it was good because think about it.
The citizens is the United States bodyguard. Not only the bodyguard for the United States,
but you and I, because you want somebody, basically when I get in trouble, I want a
citizen to protect me. And also these guys are so-called corrupt. Even to protect their
sorry behind because simple reason that they're sorry, but you have a duty to do so. But they
don't understand that. If you disarm your people, they actually put themselves in harm's way too.
You're absolutely right. God bless you. Great points. Have a safe week.
Yeah, it's gonna backfire on them if we just hold the line and get back in their face.
They tell us, it's discrediting to get in their face. Baloney, they wanna keep you in a coma,
folks. You've gotta get angry and get moving. And stand up and others will stand up who've
been waiting in the shadows. Let's go to Bertrand real fast in Canada. Go ahead, Bertrand.
Hey, Alex. Thanks for taking my call. I gotta apologize to you. I confronted you quite a few
years ago on your show and I doubted you and I thought you had a hidden agenda. But you know what?
I gotta apologize. I became a Prison Planet TV member back in 2010, in 2011.
I'm sorry I didn't renew in 2012. Credit cards maxed out, but I'm gonna hopefully
renew again soon. And after you did that interview with the guys that made the movie
Lamp in the Dark, and you sold that video? Yes. On your website? Yes.
And I just wanna rant to those idiots out there that create this propaganda,
that you're a Vatican agent? That's a load of crap. You guys are idiots.
Well, listen, listen, listen. They do it to make money, but that's fine. It doesn't matter.
They say on everything else too. Let's just, and God bless you, I gotta go to break here,
but let me just say this. Let's just say I'm a bad guy. Okay, let's get that debate out of the way.
They wanna make my supporters defend me so that they don't fight the New World Order and wake
people up. Don't defend me, everybody. Okay, I mean, defend me if they ever falsely arrest me
or something, but don't defend me from made up crud. That's designed, the White House leaks
admit, with Cass Sunstein and others, to get us fighting with each other. Just ignore it.
Go wake people up about the New World Order coming down on us. Don't defend Alex Jones.
That's meant to divert you off. Let them have me, okay? Let them go after me.