Live from Austin, Texas, broadcasting worldwide, it's Alex Jones.
Police have now talked to, they're telling police that they heard the driver saying,
yelling, Allah Akbar, Allah Akbar, during this incident, which is now leading authorities
to believe that this is as a result, that this is now a terrorism case.
And I'm just getting an update now, the FBI is taking over this case, because it appears
now that this is terrorism.
The Arabic chanda Allah Akbar, God is great, sometimes said under the most beautiful circumstances
and too often we hear of it being being said in moments like this.
And then sitting right next to him is the former director of the CIA, who told everybody
that we should basically accept Orthodox Islam.
There is no end to these people, ladies and gentlemen.
That was Jake Tapper, the unintentional comedian, up there talking about, normally under beautiful
circumstances we hear Allah Akbar, really, when do we hear Allah Akbar?
When jihadis are killing people, and ISIS posted photos a month ago of the exact spot
where eight people were killed and 11 injured, would have been in the hundreds like nice.
But a police officer within 10 seconds of it starting, drew his firearm and began firing
on the vehicle and then killed the SOB.
There is no end to this, there is literally no end to this.
And look at CNN last night with their live coverage, citizens know what to do to the
enemy.
It's promoted and brought in all the illegals.
There are great citizens with our operation that Info Wars launched, CNN is ISIS, Mike
Serenos' idea.
Great job, folks, getting out there and doing it, do it everywhere because they are ISIS.
They represent Hillary and Obama and Al Gore, they called for an Arab Spring here in America
five years ago.
They finance one worldwide, this is anti-Christian.
Al Gore, let me tell you, behind the scenes is quarterbacking the attempted take down
of free speech in America and this broadcast.
In the next few weeks, I'll be at liberty to tell you about it, I'm not at this point.
But we have Soros, Al Gore, you've seen Podesta saying, Alex Jones, SH, you know what, T,
he never even tweets, but it's about me.
And I don't say that like I'm bragging, I need everybody's prayers and I need your financial
support because that's how we beat these people, is being able to stand against their operations.
But I'll tell you one thing, I'm proud of the fact that Roger Stone works for Info Wars
and he's being sued by Obama's law firm.
And I am proud that Al Gore is coming after me because I mean to pick a fight, I mean
to get them out in the open, let everybody see what they're doing and whatever happens
to me, that's the way it is, but Info Wars is a champion operation, folks.
We need you to buy the products and spread the word and hand share the videos and articles
and you've been doing it, we're defeating them, but we are in the thick of the battle.
And I wanna say this audience is not an audience, you are super active, you are in the arena,
I salute you, you are the strength and the backbone, not just this country, but worldwide.
We are the heart of the resistance and the enemy knows it and I think they can smash
us, all that'll do is invigorate us even more.
And as Winston Churchill said, we shall go on to the end, whatever the cost may be, we
shall defend our republic, we shall never surrender.
He said, we shall go on to the end, whatever the price may be, we shall defend our island,
we shall go on to the end, we shall go on to the end, and as you can see, we're winning.
But it is a war, quite frankly, I love it, I can't wait till I can bring all this stuff
out very soon, but they figured out we've got PIs and people on, they're getting really
freaked out, so I'm not telling you anything they don't know already, we'll be back, stay
with us.
If you go to info war store.com and get game changing amazing products, we've been sold
out of DNA force for almost four months, these ingredients are nutraceutical grade, the highest
quality, the bio PQQ, all of it, it's 25% off, the truck got in this morning and it's
back but it is a limited run because of all the testing and all the rest of it, it's the
highest quality, read about what it'll do for you and your family, it is amazing.
We've also been sold out for three months on biome defense, super high quality, probiotic,
it's 25% off, out of the gates, back in stock but for a very limited time, so you get the
highest quality, the very cleanest stuff out there, we're really really proud of it, DNA
force and biome defense, probiotic, now back in stock, info wars live.com, when you buy
products from globalist, it's an act of trading with the enemy, it is an act of war, it is
an act of standing up, when you spread the links, the articles and buy products from
us and when we commit to rampage against the enemy totally.
You are listening to an info wars.com frontline report, if you are receiving this transmission,
you are the resistance, from deep in the heart of fema region 6, Austin Texas, transmitting
worldwide, it's Alex Jones, we had a army intel officer recently retired into other
agencies or promoted, who I know has given us good info on air and then it's mirrored
information I've gotten from other sources inside the deep state and he's gonna come
on today but he got called into a meeting yesterday, they were listening and he's gotten
in some trouble and what did he say, he said there's clearly Saudi Arabian connections
to Vegas and that there's more imminent attacks coming in the next few days and of course
ISIS posted a photo a month ago of the exact route, the exact spot where the bicyclers
were run over by a cowardly sack of garbage, who would have probably killed hundreds like
we saw in niche, what 89 dead, hundreds wounded, if a police officer hadn't started firing
on him within 10 seconds, boom, that guy's running over people, that's on purpose and
then got him or he probably would have killed just like in just one of the many attacks
in France, what was it 89, including children, three, four year olds running like something
out of the original Mad Max, just running over babies, running over toddlers, screaming
like a retarded hound dog and oh, he was a refugee on one of the quote diversity visas
that the UN runs via UNESCO, cultural enrichment is what it's called, it's not a joke when
we call it that, that's their term and under UNESCO and the UN, it controls our state department
until now and then we admit to the country, whoever they say, is that not global government?
Look at this deranged inbred lunatic, that's why there's so much mental illness from those
rural areas of Uzbekistan and Afghanistan and other areas where this lunatic came from
and again, the numbers are there, there is more than a 35,000% higher instance of birth
defects in individuals from those regions that come from small towns and they are crazy,
just like royalty in Egypt or royalty in England would become completely insane.
You know, most of Queen Elizabeth's sisters had to be locked up in mental silence the
rest of their lives, usually out of five or six, they get one good one, that's why they
started marrying commoners 50 years ago, they said, gee, the genetic experts tell us this
is why most of our family are complete lunatics, there's a headline in New York Times, Saudi
Arabia awakens to the perils of inbreeding, they awakened to it in 2003, they also just
awakened to not wiping their rear end with their hands, I mean, I'm not against anybody,
I'm just saying, Jones is racist again, saying many Muslims are inbred, no, it's a fact,
Jack, arranged marriages and then you want to know who your daughter marries, so she
marries a first cousin and then you do it over and over and over and pretty soon your
mom is your sister, yes, your mama said again, your mom is your sister, your mom, oh, that's
very common, your mom is your sister and then you wonder why your eyes are pointing different
directions literally and why you're whacked out of your mind and why you want to kill
everybody because you're like an inbred breed of dog, you see just drooling on the side
of the street, they go look at my high bred dog and go, yeah, I see a mentally retarded
animal, look at this mentally retarded animal, let's put him up on screen, a vicious psychotic
inbred ISIS, look at that guy, look at that demon, oh, and he just culturally enriched,
and again, it's a cucking for the left, they leftist in their homes across the nation last
night weren't just making apologies like Jake Tapper saying it's beautiful but a lot of
them you can better believe were engaging in self-flagellation and I'm not joking when
I say that, they love this, the fact that the left can bring in millions of these people
with their eyes pointing different directions from the inbreeding and but totally psychotic,
always believe their God like a lot of other seriously inbred mentally retarded people,
it's very sad but this type of inbreeding creates psychotic psychosis in high numbers
so it's not just the religion folks, it's the inbreeding, armies of inbred psycho killers,
zombo psycho inbred Muslim hillbillies attacking, everybody knows there is the Appalachia where
some people are inbred, you don't mess with those people, they'll kill you in two seconds
because they're inbred folks, they're crazy, imagine if there was a billion Appalachians
in the world and half of them were inbred psychotic and they're just literally raining
them down on us, excuse me, I just got to tell you like it is, so Trump said we got
to stop these visas from unvented countries, this guy had terror ties, he'd never been
allowed in, in 2015 he was running around saying he was going to kill people so the
FBI went but that was Obama's FBI, just like San Bernardino or just like Fort Hood or the
hundreds of other attacks now in the western world, it's covered up and not an act of terror
but this guy in front of witnesses was chirping, chirping the Allah Akbar, I'm an inbred piece
of garbage, so he was chirping, I'm an inbred psychopath with delusions of grandeur, that's
what you get when you're inbred is a lot of times just delusions of grandeur, you think
you're invincible, you're a drooling idiot who wipes his butt with your hand but you're
God and Linda Sorsour loves you and wants to put women under it because look at Linda
Sorsour, looks like his brother, it's the same dude, same genetics, all scrambled together
all the slave trading, all of it comes from these folks and we're supposed to be culturally
rich and too bad you didn't fully take Europe 1400 years ago, too bad there was a counter
strike called the Crusades, we're going to apologize, please take us over, please inbreed
us and pour acid on our faces and cut women's genitals off and murder the gays, it's liberal,
murder us, murder us, we're liberal, oh but things aren't going too well, here's the headline
today, Hollywood accusers, harassers, molesters, rapists, the rap sheets, 56 so far and suddenly
it's pedophilia popping up, oh and who does Harvey Weinstein like, he wants to bring in
Muslims to cock your world, just like he likes to debase women and young girls, he's going
to debase the whole country, he said yesterday he's given the world a gift with what he's
just done, you're lucky I've given you this gift, I'm Harvey Weinstein, now just like
Europe just took in 10 million military age men, you're going to take it and they're going
to slaughter you all they want, it's liberal, oh it's so liberal, these are the insane maniacs
that think they're God but here's the thing, we're awake, we're aware of you, we're never
going away, we're never stopping, we're never backing down, we're never giving in and we're
winning scum, so enjoy the long dark night that's coming for you.
Now continuing here, let's read more about the cultural enrichment, can we put our enricher
back on the television for us here, we're about to go to break but there's our enricher,
he showed us and it was cultural, it's just culture, don't judge a culture, killing people
is his culture, everyone should thank him, the victim's families, those barely alive
should say, oh Allah Akbar, like Tapper said, I'm going to play it when we come back, Allah
Akbar, it's so beautiful, in the middle of this, Tapper says, oh it's so beautiful, it's
so beautiful, you are the resistance, fully cooked, ready to eat bacon, I'm talking thick
meaty, center cut, presidential bacon, savory and delicious, I buy some, I use some, I've
stored some, awesome, no refrigeration needed with a 10 year shelf life, NASA pack technology,
bacon, fully cooked, fully hydrated, ready to eat right from the pack bacon or warm and
served, life saving, ready to eat bacon, 10 year shelf life bacon, ships free at fully
cooked bacon dot com, fully cooked bacon dot com.
The answer to being in control of your own healthcare is freedom from insurance, become
part of a group of self-pay patients that come together to share in each other's medical
expenses, individual share amounts begin at $107 a month and $347 for families, choose
from three health sharing programs, holistic treatments may be eligible for sharing, see
guidelines, discount programs available for dental, vision and pharmacy, go to libertyoncall.org,
that's libertyoncall.org.
This is Dan Pilla, do you owe the IRS money you can't pay, are tax debts crippling you,
I've defended people from the IRS for over 30 years, I've helped thousands and I can
help you too, I wrote the book on IRS settlement and I'm telling you, there's no such thing
as a hopeless case, call 800-34-NOTAX to finally get free of IRS debt, with the IRS's new programs,
there's never been a better time to solve your problem, call 800-34-NOTAX, that's 800-34-NOTAX
or my website, danpilla.com.
kdarmor.com is your one stop shop for the highest quality body armour, period, why would
you go anywhere else, go to kdarmor.com and get your body armour today while you still
can, go to kdarmor.com, that's c-a-t-i-armour.com.
Propure water filters, most trusted, most tested, right now you can save 25% on the
Propure Nomad Gravity System, visit an authorised Propure dealer for details, it's p-r-o-p-u-r.
Alex Jones here to tell you about how you can help spread liberty worldwide, while also
enjoying what I have found to be the best tasting 100% organic coffee on the planet,
for more than a decade, my favourite coffee has come from the high mountains of southern
Mexico, where the Chiapas farmers grow their unique shade grown Arabica beans, we have
now managed to secure these sought after beans in a highly customised blend, discover and
try a bag of the Patriot blend 100% organic coffee at infowarslife.com, this coffee gives
you a long smooth pick me up for hours without the headaches and heartburn that so many other
coffees give me personally, hands down this is my favourite coffee and it's taken us years
to secure connections directly to the Chiapas Mexican farmers, drop by the site today, order
a bag or two and I don't think you're going to be disappointed, available in original
or with our immune support infusion blend, you will be supporting a free press, all the
while enjoying a truly great tasting cup of my favourite coffee, available at infowarslife.com,
support good oral health with our one of a kind super blue fluoride free products, infowarslife
brings you a revolutionary toothpaste blend with iodine and nano silver designed to deliver
a powerful clean, enjoy a minty fresh flavour made with peppermint oil or try our bubble
gum flavour, pair this ground breaking toothpaste with a super blue fluoride free mouthwash
and super charge your oral health, our amazing mouthwash features natural oils and ancient
ingredients used since aboriginal and biblical times, instead of containing fluoride our
super blue line is loaded with the good halogen iodine and an array of other beneficial compounds
that have been hand selected for their oral health benefits, super blue fluoride free
mouthwash and toothpaste are the first and only to contain all of these natural ingredients,
xylitol, nano silver and iodine, notice the difference with our super blue fluoride free
products, refresh your breath and invigorate your oral health routine at infowarsetour.com,
that's infowarsetour.com.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Show.
The Alex Jones Show, because there is a war on, for your mind.
Police have now talked to, they're telling police that they heard the driver saying yelling
Allah Akbar, Allah Akbar during this incident which is now leading authorities to believe
that this is as a result, that this is now a terrorism case and I'm just getting an update
now the FBI is taking over this case because it appears now that this is terrorism.
The Arabic chanda Allah Akbar, God is great, sometimes as said under the most beautiful
circumstances and too often we hear of it being said in moments like this.
They brought in 10 million people into the EU the last five years, 80% of them according
to Interpol are military age men, most of them are military refugees, they're people
that came and invaded Syria and other areas, they're fighters left over from the Libya
takeover and they're being brought into Europe and from Sweden to Denmark to the UK, they
take actual terrorists that are famous, killing people on television, killing unarmed prisoners
and they rehabilitate them giving them housing, welfare and classes taught by other emons
and it's all like this weird sick politically correct joke run by the EU.
And that's the thing is I think about this and how Trump was demonized for saying seven
countries that don't even have working airports or passport systems like Somalia, like Sudan,
like Libya, you don't get to come here, we're not giving you visas, I mean you can't go
to Japan unless you've got a visa, doesn't matter where you're from, you can't go to
Russia unless you have a visa, you can't Mexico, you tell them how long you're gonna be there,
you get a limited visa when you fly in to Cancun or whatever, you tell them when you're
gonna be there, where you're staying, your phone number and when you're leaving.
And let me tell you something, I know folks that have gone down to Mexico decided to stay
a couple extra days, they call the hotel up the next day and say, where is Mr. Johnson?
And if they catch you there illegally, six months to a year hard prison time, again,
but then all I hear about our super open society and country, then is racist and evil and bad
and then all these courts fought the president when the law is very clear, he finally wins,
nine to zero at the Supreme Court, and we saw Nice where the police did shoot and kill
the driver.
I was having a Freudian thing when I said this hero police officer shot and killed this
guy, he shot him and stopped him, killed his terror attack, he is still alive, which is
bittersweet, I wish he was dead.
But at the same time, they'll get more intel off of this guy, but they already knew in
2015, he was shooting his mouth off about killing people.
His imam to his credit said, hey, I told the police they didn't do anything and they could
have stopped him, but they didn't and why?
Which is rare to actually have one of these guys imams, I guess he didn't wanna spend
the rest of his life in a supermax prison, probably a smart move to have tried to stop
this.
And listen, folks, I didn't wanna go into the Middle East, I didn't wanna destabilize
Iraq to bring in the more radical Muslims out of Saudi Arabia, I don't hate people under
authoritarian regimes.
And I know there's been periods in the world when Muslims weren't all killing each other
and weren't invading all their neighbors, and I know Christianity has had its expansionist
and authoritative stripes.
But Islam today is out of control and is empowered by Soros and the globalist and is a clear
and present weapon being used against our countries.
It's incompatible, I can't go to their countries and practice my religion or not practice it
or be gay if I was gay.
That's fundamental, ladies and gentlemen, or be a Buddhist or be an atheist.
If I lived in Saudi Arabia, my wife or daughters couldn't take driver's education or drive
a car?
And I don't need to repeat all this, it's just we have attacks now every week in Europe,
every week in Canada or the US, every week in Australia.
There are constant attacks where the Allah Akbar individual will shoot four or five people
and scream Allah Akbar, Allah Akbar.
Just two weeks ago in Maryland, killed six people screaming Allah Akbar.
It didn't even make national news except for Fox.
People say, Fox is so right wing, they showed you it was a Muslim attack?
That's the benchmark of conservatism is just to admit another religious zealot programmed
to kill, went out and did it and killed six people and what, wounded four others?
It was a manhunt for the guy and it wasn't even in the national news, a manhunt and they
won't put it on television.
But now, this guy posted reportedly to the Internet what he's gonna do, he had two fake
guns on him, they're trying to blame guns.
There's a fake tweet out there speaking of fake guns of Hillary, it's satire, not fake
news, satire from a satire account, put it on screen.
Hillary reportedly tweeted satirically, but it wasn't Hillary, again, a spoof account
of Hillary Clinton tweeted, imagine if the truck would have had a silencer, exactly.
Just like Vegas, imagine if the truck driver had a silencer.
Satire is king in a world of lunacy, ladies and gentlemen.
So we have this individual, Saifulo Saipahov, if I'm pronouncing that correctly, New York
City, five Argentine nationals and a Belgian were among those killed when a man plowed
into pedestrians and cyclists on a bike path in New York City.
Police shot the suspect after he exited the vehicle and shot at Allah Akbar, which means
God is great in Arabic.
He is currently in police custody and officials said they're investigating the incident as
an act of terror, eight dead, 11 injured.
Saifulo came to the US from Uzbekistan seven years ago, he left a note referencing the
Islamic State of Iraq and Syria, ISIS, a federal law enforcement source confirmed.
And you know, if Trump wasn't in, there'd be no chance the FBI would tell you it was
even Islamic.
Under Obama, Pulse Nightclub, San Bernardino, they would come out and say it's not Islamic,
it's not Islamic.
And then four or five days later, you'd learn it was Islamic.
And then the guy's weirdo dad shows up at a Democratic Party function for Hillary.
I mean, it's just insane how arrogant these people are.
And they know full well that we're not invited into their nations and other countries.
They know full well they're not from tolerant societies.
And so let's stop pretending that's the case.
But I'm gonna go over the attack in detail and get into some other important areas on
the other side.
But Jake Tapper is paid to do what he does.
And he just said Allah Akbar is usually so beautiful, it's so beautiful, that's really
sick.
And what he is doing is virtue signaling from CNN that we got your back and keep doing what
you're doing.
Kind of like the individual that went out and shot Congressman Scalise and others.
That day, Wolf Blitzer had a guest on, saying that he was a hero.
Wolf Blitzer didn't disagree.
We'll be right back.
Stay with us.
If you are receiving this transmission, you are the resistance.
Hey, Daniel Bregman, why new manna storeable foods?
We believe in freedom.
America needs strong, independent families to endure what's ahead.
And we take this charge seriously.
We got options, organic, no gluten, without the chemicals.
Great taste and value, new manna is a no-lose investment for your family's food independence.
Get your new manna today.
Call 888-597-0775, 888-597-0775.
Online discounts available at PowerPrepper.com.
PowerPrepper.com.
In an emergency, you need a fire now.
But what if the wood is wet?
No problem for InstaFire.
Our non-toxic fire starter packs lights wet wood, floats, and can even burn on water or
in any weather.
Stains winds up to 30 miles per hour, and each pouch weighs only 1.75 ounces.
Need an emergency or camp stove?
Get the InstaFire Inferno stove that boils 20 ounces of water in under 3 minutes with
controllable heat.
Intense from 425 to 1500 degrees.
Free shipping.
Go to InstaFire.com and use discount code Radio30 up to 3 times for 30% off your order.
InstaFire.
Fire in an instant.
America is an information-based civil war.
That's why now more than ever, we've got to hit the streets of America and let these globalists
scum know we're not backing down from their bullies.
We're only intensifying our operations in the face of their wannabe dictatorship.
Being a conservative, a nationalist, a libertarian, or simply a free speech advocate is truly
the counterculture.
The real punk rock is being a patriot who's pro-America, pro-capitalism, and pro-freedom,
who at the same time is tolerant.
Modern liberalism is a counterfeit of Thomas Deberson's classical liberalism.
They are the anti-liberal.
To defend free speech, meet like-minded friends, and promote freedom worldwide.
We've got more than 60 original designs of high-quality t-shirts for men and women, as
well as more Patriot apparel at Infowarsstore.com.
Be part of the second American revolution at Infowarsstore.com.
We're not just going to have to end in the next week the Brain Force Plus special, 50%
off.
I'm going to have to end even sooner our caveman ultimate paleo bone broth, turmeric, chaga
mushroom, beet pollen, and more.
Concentrate.
You talk about next level meal replacement, next level compared to whey, and it's great
to mix with whey and then mix shakes.
It's incredible.
My son is growing like a weed using it.
It's bigger than I am already, 15, incredible.
It is amazing.
Infowarslife.com, 50% off caveman, but only a few days left.
It's about to end.
And, folks, the globalists hate it when you do this.
We're the tip of the spear because we're fearless, we're bold, because we understand the stakes
are too high.
The globalists win.
We're all slaves.
So don't thank me for what I'm doing.
I want to thank you.
We're all in this together.
And when you get the great Molon Labe t-shirts and you get the great books and videos, you're
funding the tip of the spear again.
Visit Infowarstore.com today and commit to helping the Infowar.
Choose to take control of your chemistry with Survival Shield X2 and Biotru Selenium.
This powerful combo is perfect for supporting your thyroid and health.
Biotru Selenium's formula is far from synthetic and is made from a source of 100% organic
mustard seed.
Our super high quality nascent iodine is an essential mineral sourced of 99.99% ultra-pure
deep earth iodine crystals.
This essential mineral is necessary in order to produce thyroid hormones which influence
every cell, tissue, and organ in the body.
With inadequate thyroid hormones, you may experience slow metabolism, lethargy, weight
gain, and overall brain fog.
Survival Shield X2 and Biotru Selenium work together to support the systems in your body.
Take control of your chemistry today with this super combo.
Discover the power of Survival Shield X2 and Biotru Selenium at Infowarslife.com.
You're listening to the Alex Jones Show.
Rallying patriots worldwide in defense of human liberty.
Now coming up in the next segment, I'm going to play six minutes of a phone call from a
caller that goes by the name Zach, who recently got out of Army Special Forces Command out
of Florida, and who's been calling for years, but really been giving us amazing information
that's open source as a citizen, not classified or secret, on the show.
And I know it's amazing information because I've already got most of the same information.
Sometimes I have more information, sometimes a lot less, but I get the same information.
Plus, I do my own research, so I can tell he's for real.
I said, I want you on for a full hour tomorrow.
They called him right after the show, they were listening, and they called him into a
meeting and are chewing him out right now, even though it's his right to do that.
Just like Colonel Shaffer got chewed out for exposing Benghazi.
And so much more.
So next segment, I'm going to air those excerpts of what he talked about with Vegas and the
big imminent terror attacks that are coming.
He said imminent.
And then, of course, hours later, we see another Islamic terror attack.
Look at that evil grin, that murderous, satisfied, psycho look that you see in the eyes of British
royalty.
It's the inbreeding.
And again, the New York Times even admits it, serious crime problems, mental illness
problems, birth defect problems with folks out of Uzbekistan, Afghanistan, Pakistan,
and other areas because of the inbreeding.
And it is a fact.
So we're going to be looking at that.
We were just showing you an image of the famous Habsburg chin that, again, a lot of our Islamic
friends have it as well.
Also the lazy eye is another thing.
But in England, they see lazy eyes as a sign of royalty and nobility.
I mean, you go to some highfalutin event with British aristocracy or, you know, folks in
the upper crust, and I've been to a few of them, I mean, there aren't hardly any eyeballs
pointing the right direction.
Excuse me.
The point is, is that we've got even more inbreeding going on here.
But I'm sorry, I am just getting to the bottom of the problem here.
Back to what I was about to say for the earlier segment.
We have people like Jake Tapper coming out and saying, oh, he yelled Allah Akbar, usually
such a beautiful, beautiful thing when we hear it.
But now all too often a bad thing.
That's a no-no on CNN to say Islamic terror, even Allah Akbar.
So the reporter is obviously going to get some trouble for that.
Notice they won't even say Allah Akbar in the text on screen for TV viewers.
There it is, 5.04 p.m., New York, about an hour and 30 minutes into it.
Witnesses suspect was yelling God is great in Arabic.
No, it should say he was yelling Allah Akbar, which is God is great in Arabic, but they
always do it.
It's how they whitewash.
It's how they manipulate.
And again, I can't go to these Muslim countries and live.
Their women have their genitals cut off.
They kill gay people.
What in the world is going on?
Why are the Hollywood degenerate pedophile elite?
The elite maggots, the alpha maggots.
Why are they lecturing us on how we should run our culture and run our life?
They want to bring in another group of people where child molestation is codified.
Nine-year-old girls are okay for men to have sex with.
It's okay for men to have sex with boys, just not with other men.
That's executable offense.
So pedophilia is legal.
Under Sharia, they actually call it man-boy love, which you notice the North American
Man-Boy Love Association.
Start to figure this out, folks.
There's a reason Hollywood is completely allied.
There it is, report ISIS leader encourages pedophilia.
Enjoying young boys is in the absence of women.
Enjoy young boys.
It's like you enjoy women, forcing them into harems.
That's a fancy name for sex slavery.
But the West is where slavery came from.
We're the bad ones.
We're the evil people.
We're the folks that have to be gotten rid of.
It's amazing.
I want to plow into all of this, but I'm going to spend a few minutes here first, just encouraging
listeners to understand that when you buy t-shirts or water filtration systems or books
or videos or other material from info war store.com, you are funding the revolution.
I mean, I cannot say it any clearer.
And because of the amazing success we've all had together in this endeavor, we are a bigger
target than ever.
And I don't mind that.
I'm not looking for the shade.
I'm not trying to hide in the weeds here.
I'm trying to take on the globalist cat on so people can see exactly what's going on.
And if you will just commit, it's so essential and make the decision to buy high quality
products in as much abundance as you see fit, we are basically unstoppable.
They just want to kill my name and sue us out of existence.
That's not going to work.
We've already done incredible work together, but I know together, we're going to build
even more resistance and be more effective.
And so it is essential that you purchase the products at info war store.com.
I don't want to thank everybody that has, but we've got the best fluoride free toothpaste
with colloidal silver and with high quality atomic iodine in it.
You cannot beat that for children and adults.
We've got the best mouthwash designed by Dr. Jones.
That's my dad with colloidal silver and iodine as well.
The concentrated as well from Emirates essential.
We've got the caveman.
We've got so many other great products.
The X2 is such an important thing.
The purest iodine that anybody's got out there.
It is just amazing the quality and it's the missing halogen in the body.
The bad halogens are the chlorine and the fluoride and the bromide and what we're being
bombarded with that lowers IQ and that again, if your body doesn't have the good iodine,
it will just absorb the bad halogens.
It's such a game changer that alone info wars life.com or triple eight two five three three
one three nine.
That's triple eight two five three three one three nine and we are ending the special today.
Anthroplex and brain force together, 50% off.
That is ending today, 50% off Anthroplex and brain force plus DNA force has been sold out
for almost four months.
It's so hard to source the PQQ and the co Q12 that are actually from the organic source
not synthetic.
We sell ours at the same price.
People sell a synthetic that a lot of evidence shows you don't even absorb.
So it's very hard, it's got a whole bunch of ingredients in it to get them all in, get
them all source, have them all past California standards, which this is doing.
We've got the test.
They've done the test there and found it and then they test it over and over until they
find a batch that goes slightly above California, even though the FDA says a thousand times
what they say California is what's dangerous.
We all know how the ball game works.
The point is we go through a lot of trouble making these be the very, very cleanest on
the market.
So DNA force, super high quality, 25% off out of the gates.
And unfortunately, we were only able to get a small run of these.
So it's going to sell out in the next two weeks.
So if you want to take advantage of that and support the broadcast, I want to thank you
all for your financial support.
But it's symbiotic DNA force has hundreds of studies we're even allowed to talk about
because bio PQQ and co QT and these other things and the reserve at all are known.
I mean, a lot of these are drugs in Europe, so you talk about cleaning out your cells,
you're talking about next level antioxidant.
This is the best there is.
They sell similar stuff in clinics for 400 to $600 and then people go well, it's from
a doctor.
It must be worth it when our stuff is better than most of the ones that are out there for
200 bucks on the low end, 600 on the high end.
People do all sorts of other wild things where they take these similar things intravenously
from a doctor.
This is taken in tablet, so DNA force is back 25% off and biome defense, the amazing probiotic
very best we could come up with the top companies.
That is also 25% off info wars life.com or triple H two five three three one three nine
and your purchase of the products stands with us stands with America stands with Trump stands
against the globalists and their satanic pedophile armies and that's who they are and they know
we know who they are and they're coming back against us.
So we need your support.
You go to info war store.com and get game changing amazing products.
We've been sold out of DNA force for almost four months.
These ingredients are nutraceutical grade, you have the highest quality, the bio PQQ
all of it.
It's 25% off the truck got in this morning and it's back but it is a limited run because
of all the testing and all the rest of it is the highest quality.
Read about what it'll do for you and your family.
It is amazing.
It's also been sold out for three months on biome defense, super high quality probiotic.
It's 25% off out of the gates back in stock but for a very limited time.
So you get the highest quality, the very cleanest stuff out there.
We're really, really proud of it.
DNA force and bomb defense probiotic now back in stock info wars life.com when you buy products
from globalist.
It's an act of trading with the enemy.
It is an act of war.
It is an act of standing up when you spread the links, the articles and buy products from
us and then we commit to rampage against the enemy totally.
You deserve a deep restful sleep with knockout by info wars life.
Our organic formula is made from high quality natural ingredients such as valerian root
extract L tryptophan lemon balm leaf extract and melatonin knockout packs a powerful punch
to get you through the night and achieve proper sleep.
Thousands of people around the world experience daytime drowsiness, but with the rapid speed
of life, we need to be able to keep up the pace.
Our natural mixture harnesses the power of 10 known ingredients to let your body relax
and get the sleep you need.
Wake up refreshed and take on the day info wars life wants to bring you a sleep support
formula that goes above and beyond other leading brands at an affordable price.
Get the sleep you deserve and experience the power of knockout head on over to info wars
life.com and say goodbye to fatigue.
That's info wars life.com.
Support good oral health with our one of a kind super blue fluoride free products info
wars life brings you a revolutionary toothpaste blend with iodine and nano silver designed
to deliver a powerful clean enjoy a minty fresh flavor made with peppermint oil or try
our bubble gum flavor pair this groundbreaking toothpaste with the super blue fluoride free
mouthwash and supercharge your oral health.
Our amazing mouthwash features natural oils and ancient ingredients used since aboriginal
and biblical times instead of containing fluoride our super blue line is loaded with the good
halogen iodine and an array of other beneficial compounds that have been hand selected for
their oral health benefits.
Super blue fluoride free mouthwash and toothpaste are the first and only to contain all of these
natural ingredients xylitol nano silver and iodine notice the difference with our super
blue fluoride free products refresh your breath and invigorate your oral health routine at
info war store.com that's info war store.com men give your body the support it needs with
info wars life Prostaguard it's time to start assisting the body in regulating proper prostate
balance before his life has set out to bring you formulations that are not only the highest
quality out there but formulas that you can use on a daily basis to give your body the
natural herbs and extracts that our experts recommend the Prostaguard formula does just
that with its mixture of plant based nutrients and antioxidants that help give your body
total support it's a hand selected blend of saw palmetto lycopene plant sterols zinc vitamin
d3 selenium and copper Prostaguard is something that the men on the info wars crew take every
day and from our research it's something that men should really be adding to their daily
regimen in order to keep their body going at optimal levels now's the time to start
naturally supporting your body get Prostaguard on your side today exclusively at info wars
life.com that's info wars life.com you're listening to the Alex Jones show
I'm your host Alex Jones thank you so much for joining us
The New York Times can truly be called an evil publication when I do read it every page
every headline screams deceit corruption evil lies the whole paper is dedicated to forcing
the United States into an authoritarian world government and here's just two examples in
today's New York Times the cover of the New York Times mile long Manhattan truck attack
kills eight the headline ladies and gentlemen the headline ladies and gentlemen should be
Islamic terrorist runs over eight people with a truck in act of terror but it gets better
there's a full page ad put out by refuse fascism that is a George Soros funded group you cannot
make this up and it says it begins November 4th overthrow Trump overthrow the government
but then when I cover the fact that they're planning this big launch November 4th building
up to the one year anniversary of Trump being elected next week that I've made it up their
actual news articles out there saying I made it all up nothing's coming November 4th well
we've already seen Vegas it's got Islamic ties clearly and we just saw this last night
and you better believe it's coming and coming soon and you better be aware of it and awake
folks we're going to play some key audio in fact it dovetails with that information right
now Zach called into the show yesterday he's been calling in for years but he recently
got out of being attached to the army special forces command in Florida and he didn't give
us any secrets he talked about what he is a private citizen I was talking to his friends
about and what he's researching and the information he's getting and the reason I know he's credible
is because I get the same information sometimes he has more than I do sometimes I have more
than he does but he's given us a lot of great information nothing secret just the fact that
they're getting a lot of chatter about Islamic attacks coming which we already see happening
now he was going to come on today for a full hour as a guest soon as he hung up the phone
yesterday he got a call and got called into a meeting for what he was talking about on
air and may not be able to talk to us anymore even though he wasn't giving us anything secret
ladies and gentlemen because the higher ups don't want the American people know what's
happening they don't want us to stand with the president who's been predicting the Islamic
attacks and how it's linked up with the left that's why they'll announce their attacks
announce that they're going to cop kill announce they're going to get violent announce their
training militarily all the Intel's come in we've shown you the undercover videos all
of it and then they go oh Jones is making that up Veritas is making that up louder with
the crowders making that up we're not planning anything November 4th and they've got big
giant articles this nightmare must end the Trump Pence regime must go November 4th it
begins be there join with thousands who gather in cities and towns across the country a movement
of protests that continue every day and night growing until we become millions determined
not to stop until the regime is driven from power 18 billion put in by George Soros to
be led by Linda sorcerer the pro-sexual mutilation Muslim now let's go ahead ladies and gentlemen
and go to the Intel they don't want you to hear about companies that should be investigated
and looked into for what they know because Saudi Arabia has promised through its surrogates
to carry out terror attacks in Russia and the US before if we didn't follow their orders
quote in tourist areas I'm not saying that's what happened when this was an Islamic attack
last night though of Wahhabism that's what Isis is so that's a Saudi Arabian gift a beautiful
thing as Jake Tapper said there's a lot more so beautiful most beautiful show so here's
the Intel they don't want you to hear let's go to Zach in Tampa Florida Zach you're on
the air with Shepard of Intel up yes Alex Shepard's great to be on with you how to connect
some dots because what they put off here in Vegas was just just too far so first and foremost
what we have is and this is public knowledge you have the for us fund management group
the LLC putting $42 million worth of put options on the MGM on I forgot that yeah I mean a
record put option the link before go ahead but yeah so I mean that's that's just part
of it so I mean you can't look past that that's obvious but also what we have here is the
private military company the Saudi Arabian based ETS risk management company that's confirmed
to everything the caller is saying is documented because this is the final pieces you had you
had all this royalty there and you had this Saudi Air Force there that week so yeah this
ETS risk management company is a PMC that's real shady and they don't work now within
the government because who's in the White House but they did work with during during
Libya with the Clinton's you know I got some guys down here in the forensic accounting
if you look into the contract let's start over Zach's recently gotten out of the military
and the whole intelligence area we'll leave it at that called a lot of good info in the
past six months so just start back over this is really important right so the timeline
is pretty unprecedented let alone with you know so you get the $42 million worth of put
options done by the by the uh the George Soros fund management group and also you have a
you have a contract being fulfilled by ETS risk management but this isn't this contract
was not fulfilled by DOD okay so this is sort of a this is where it gets tricky but they
were working and there are PMCs that work kind of in vacuumed in Libya in Syria and
they do certain drill stateside as well but they were there that weekend everybody knows
they were there that weekend so this is a private company that's great that is actually
ran and you can pull them up ETS but they were ran out of Saudi Arabia but they they
did they did work during 2013 in Libya and that's fiasco so when you're saying and people
bat their eyes saying that this is Islamic this is Islamic not in the sense that it's
done by Islamic groups but in a way ISIS itself was the creation of these private military
groups and if you want to you know back in the day they they turned like Al Ciaida and
this is real so you have these private military companies that are backed and written by the
deep state you know creating this chaos around the world and with full validation 100% ETS
risk management was on the ground in Vegas that night and this gentleman who you have
on he's talking about these choppers um being in the area he's spot on and the issues the
next thing I gotta bring up is the forensic accounting that's going to be brought up because
there's individuals that are aware of this in today's day and age when you have these
transfers and you're transferring large sums of money people in the intelligence agencies
who are either in or out are not going to stay quiet and this is big and this stuff's
coming out right now um so you have to put everything in perspective in the context of
during this whole war these wars in Libya and Syria where they're destabilizing the
region there were legitimate private military companies giving hundreds of millions of dollars
to kind of you know create this war there so when you have a new administration come
in to come into power and they're no longer you know getting those paychecks it's not
like they pick up new hobbies okay there's still guns for hire and they're still working
and technically um they're still ongoing investigations so I believe that Trump and the White House
is aware of what's going on this is a bad within I guess you could call the deep state
in the legitimate government because the reason that there were multiple teams there is because
they were aware of what's going on and the reason that some of these Saudi interests
are allowed to be there or how can they be there what's going on they have certain diplomatic
communities and there's ongoing you know projects and missions going on but with this specific
PMC that was they were working um you know this is pretty important and if you notice
the timeline they you have the war within what is the White House now and all these
you know quote-unquote intelligence agencies going on on 60 Minutes on Sunday you also
have the Amir of Qatar coming out okay who was sanctioned by the Saudis the Bahar the
Bahrainians and all this other stuff and we have our U.S. assets and our legitimate PMCs
in Qatar there the Amir of Qatar talked about this this PMC that he kicked out of his own
country and then you have the Saudis attacking him and remember three years ago Bandar Bush
threatened the Russians for the Olympics and he threatened the EU that if they didn't go
along with the Syria takeover by the ISIS al-Qaeda forces quote we'll launch terror
attacks inside of your tourist zones so is this the same thing the Saudis threatened
Russia with 100% and this is I mean sophisticated and the weirdness of it is is they have backing
sort of I mean this quasi backing from the U.S. not to the legitimate U.S. the deep state
Obama folks exactly this this is this is serious and I'm just going to tell you right now and
I don't want to rattle anybody but between November 1 and November 5 PMC contractors
are or the as far as max contracts go I mean there's a lot going on this within the next
I don't know six days five six days there's a lot going on there's obviously active threats
as we speak but this is a real issue because you technically can't put this stuff and televise
it how many people you're talking to in the special operations commanding people how there
are a few minutes left to that video and so we're going to post the full thing up on info
wars.com and present planet.com in the next hour so you can hear the last two minutes
or so of that we're going to start the second hour in just a moment but again the New York
Times says it was a truck attack non-islamic attack on the cover this is on by the Mexican
kingpin he's not even Mexican just the guy that went out there to oppress everybody and
take advantage of them and then another one here Antifa is announcing that they're launching
massive overthrow of Trump starting November 4th full page ad in the New York Times but
Main Street Media says I'm lying about this I am very proud to announce the introduction
of the highest quality info wars biome defense probiotic we wanted to come out with the largest
spectrum of high quality known probiotics that have been proven to improve overall digestion
and health and detoxification in the body biome defense is an exclusive blend of 50
billion live and active cultures from over 23 different probiotic strains that are known
to support digestion and intestinal function our researchers are confident that we have
been able to develop what will be the leading probiotic on the market secure your biome
defense in ultra strength or regular strength at info wars life.com today and get started
supporting your digestive system naturally we've been testing this formula for years
but this is the limited first run to the public so please take advantage of it today support
your own health and support the info war America is an information-based civil war that's why
now more than ever we've got to hit the streets of America and let these globalists scum know
we're not backing down from their bullies we're only intensifying our operations in
the face of their wannabe dictatorship being a conservative a nationalist a libertarian
or simply a free speech advocate is truly the counterculture the real punk rock is being
a patriot who's pro-america pro-capitalism and pro-freedom who at the same time is tolerant
modern liberalism is a counterfeit of thomas deverson's classical liberalism they are the
anti-liberal to defend free speech meet like-minded friends and promote freedom worldwide we've
got more than 60 original designs of high quality t-shirts for men and women as well
as more patriot peril at info war store.com be part of the second american revolution
at info war store.com you're listening to the alex jones show
in this present crisis government is not the solution to our problem government is the
problem from time to time we've been tempted to believe that society has become too complex
to be managed by self-rule that government by an elite group is superior to government
for by and of the people the alex jones show because there is a war on for your mind hello
me meet the real me in my misfits wave life dark black past my most valued possession
is always 2020 ladies and gentlemen we are back live i am your host alex jones roger
stone's plane just landed he'll be here in about 30 minutes i've got incredible congressional
testimony by the big social media giant ceos where they try to act like they're not censoring
pro-america and libertarian and conservative and christian and pro-veteran information
and boosting anti-fund blm cop killer garbage that's coming up and then they also get put
on the hot seat about the fact that they're operating monopolies but admit that actually
the russians in the aggregate were not pro trump they were basically hedging their bets
and then after trump won they jumped on the anti-trump bandwagon that's because there's
a lot of ngos buying stuff in russia that then is targeted at us just like the cia will
write stuff in foreign papers to have the lies come back here as well we don't know
where most of this is coming from just as president trump has said but right now let's
go ahead and go to this mark dyes report i'll play the clip in just a moment a great american
happened to stumble across a live cnn shoot in manhattan yesterday and did his duty to
god and his country to warn the people who for some reason happened to be watching cnn
about what it was that they were actually seeing i think when the charlie hepto attacks
if memory serves me there were there were some in some of the attacks in the urebs that
we've seen if he did make contact if he did make contact with isis they will have instructed
him not to just leave a note you really got to hand it to anderson cooper he's a pretty
good actor he didn't even break character well the guy was just two feet away from him
yelling that cnn was fake news of course they're on the scene where yesterday another muslim
immigrant did well you know what and many are wondering if perhaps this driver was inspired
by this democrat campaign ad which has recently gone viral which has even been covered on
all the major media outlets because it's so despicable which depicts a republican candidate's
fan ed gillespie he's the republican candidate it depicts one of his fans driving a big pickup
truck and running down a bunch of minority children notice the confederate flag waving
on the back of the truck trying to evoke the horrific tragedy in charlottesville a few months
ago and it certainly is reasonable to suspect that perhaps this perpetrator had seen this
ad and then decided to go and carry out exactly that kind of an attack even the far left waste
of paper the washington post the washington compost was disgusted by the ad it says an
ad that has no place in the virginia governor's race oh wait what's this political action
committee polls controversial virginia governor ad we knew our ad would ruffle feathers they
said in a statement we held up a mirror to the republican party and they don't like what
they see we have decided to pull our ad at this time said crystal ball j alex president
of the latino victory fund given the recent events of course which events are you talking
about their crystal ball we will be placing other other powerful ads into rotation that
highlight the reasons we need to elect progressive leaders in virginia of course they didn't
apologize for the ad they still just blamed republicans for the ad when their ad could
have very well incited this isis sympathizer to kill those people in new york yesterday
it looks like the producers of this ad actually cast some of the actors in the wrong roles
they did have a muslim in the ad if you'll recall who was walking home from school with
her black friend who didn't do nothing of course when they were then chased down to
be murdered by the evil white person driving the truck but it looks like the white person
driving the truck and the muslim roles were flipped around in the ad because as you know
it's muslims who 99.9 percent of the time are the ones who mow down people in vehicles
for a lot in other news we have plenty more anti-white hate crimes which continue to be
ignored by the mainstream media so let's just cover one of them now in philadelphia this
black thug just approached this random white woman who was just walking along the street
when he decided to kick her and then punch her knocking her out cold just for fun just
to play the knock enjoy all natural bath and beauty products with emmerich's essentials
we are proud to bring you a collection of organic based household products at infowarsstore.com
including non-nano spf 30 zinc oxide sunscreen date-free herbal bug spray concentrated peppermint
mouthwash unscented body wash tea tree shampoo and long-lasting natural deodorant emmerich's
essentials is free of chemicals and toxins that may harm your body we carefully select
pure and simple ingredients to create formulas that are certified usda made with organic
our mission is to offer you everyday organic household products to enhance your life truly
feel the difference by going organic natural without compromising on quality feel good
about using emmerich's essentials start saving money and stop exposing yourself and your
family to toxic ingredients visit infowarsstore.com and learn more about the new emmerich's essentials
line of organic products that's infowarsstore.com
Waging war on corruption it's alex jones coming to you live from the front lines of the infowar
stain and good old mega death bringing us in the threat is real the jihad threat is
real it is allied with george soros and the globalist they are the same people funding
the entire antifa movement that is anti-free speech anti-america and the essence of authoritarianism
refused fascism is the organization created and run by the very same lady that created
occupy wall street we'll be talking to one of the producers zach about that in a minute
because he made some good points during the break and i said make those on air and another
one of the producers in there running the video board is matt and he was bringing up
some really good points last week about this poppinopolis and how if you read the indictment
they act like they've got all these goods but even the indictment admits that poppinopolis
kept bringing stuff to the trump campaign about russians and every time they said no
we have nothing to do with the russians it actually exonerates trump the only person
it seems in this government not in bed with foreign governments is trump and it turns
out ladies and gentlemen wait till you hear this this is mainstream news we did a video
um over the weekend matt and i did breaking down the fact that the evidence points towards
him being the mole just in the indictment well now guess what he's connected to the
pp dossier from day one and if you don't think the democrats try to put plants in people's
campaigns you don't know what planet you're living on this is 101 of even local politics
you're running for city council they're gonna in a big city they're gonna put four or five
plants in your organization if you're running for congress they're gonna try to put 20 you're
a senator oh you're a president or you're running for president and you're a front runner
just like this lady's a democratic operative the the russian lawyer that met with donald
trump jr don junior donnie jr he's their 10-minute meeting okay you got evidence hillary's working
with the russians give it to me that's what you're supposed to do as a patriot and she
just kept trying to get into other subjects about influence and stuff he said no i'm here
here about corruption boom i'm out of the meeting you didn't give us what you were supposed
to so it's simply amazing matt let's go to you first this is really obvious what's going
on here with good old good old poppinopolis and and of course we now know that mueller
is very corrupt even mainstream news admits that he's like a pit bull he would falsely
charge suspects wife to apply pressure he broke all sorts of laws in the constitution
uh in in the way he supposedly got all this fake info so we know who their witness is
the grand jury it's poppinopolis uh this whole thing stinks to high heaven just like fake
informants and it's starting to unravel really quick yeah so poppinopolis um we shot a video
on monday that we we broke down why we thought poppinopolis just kind of stinks as a mole
and the reason we we thought that a few different things but yeah he was repeatedly shot down
um in his attempts to try and connect the trump campaign with senior russian officials
which also looked fishy because the senior russian official was supposedly a relative
of vladimir putin meeting with a junior aide which was it turns out he wasn't even a foreign
policy aide relating to russia it was he was assigned to matters involving greece um which
actually is the origin of his surname poppinopolis it's the most common surname in greece it's
like jones or smith exactly was that pronouncing it right earlier yeah poppinopolis poppinopolis
something like that sounds like a really good restaurant i go to sometimes it does uh so
now it comes out great names i start getting hungry i'm sorry what what really confirms
our suspicions uh that we were talking about on monday in that video that we did um after
the show uh is it's come out that he's now uh friends he's sergey malan the source of
the steel dirty dossier that's been discredited widely discredited um turns out that poppinopolis
is intimate friends with him on facebook and when i say that i mean that uh poppinopolis
only has a network of 240 friends on facebook and this sergey malan uh is one of them it
also turns out that they were in regular contact with one another uh additionally uh one of
the things that i read about this that just looks super funny um you know it's just super
suspicious when someone emails in an email thread in your uh in your campaign uh i think
the the headline verbatim was uh attempt or uh set up meeting with with russian officials
including putin like that just that looks suspicious it looks silly it almost looks
sure the whole thing in fact it's worse than that the stuff they say it goes on and on
we'll have influence where putin wants to back trump he's our boy the whole thing is
a complete setup we know it's a setup we know that's how the swamp operates the same thing
happened to me when i was in when i was in eighth grade i was not a drug user but i'd
smoked marijuana before and they were busting lots of kids for smoking marijuana and and
this one kid in the field house kept saying just buy a joint from me in the morning please
buy the joint from me in the morning please and i said no well the next day he follows
me in a bathroom at first period and says here please buy it and i went whoa and i took
it and threw it in the toilet they still called me to the office and said we know you just
bought a marijuana cigarette and i said no i threw it in the toilet your guy did it you
shut him up they went are you like an organized criminal you're saying no to us who told you
how to lie like this and i went you people are crazy and they were really mad that i've
been in a bunch of fights and stuff and thought i was a trouble kid or whatever because i'd
fight back against you know the gangs that were just going around beating up the white
kids and that's what it was and i'm not against black people but that's what was going on
they were racist some of them a lot of my friends were black the point was is that they
just wanted to teach me a lesson they were uh you know white principles and they just
got completely upset but it was so obvious you say what's that have to do with with poppinopolis
well it's so obvious when somebody's in your organization going just please buy an illegal
gun from me or just please buy drugs from me once or you know let's just do something
illegal i mean it's it's very obvious i've had informants and people they don't do it
anymore show a show of public events ago alex i want to bomb the police station do you agree
we should bomb the police and and then it turns out it's some federal informant so they're
incredibly dirty it's how they operate i wonder what they had on poppinopolis before or i
wonder if they inserted him on purpose but he's got to know they normally burn their
infiltrators at this level to discredit them in case they ever turn around and and and
tell what happened i mean he's got to know his days are numbered being the bag man and
the dirt man for old i mean if it's true we're just speculating here of course for old mueller
what do you think well i think that's in the cards for him i don't know who'd want to work
with this guy in the future because he just seems like a weasel at this point um the other
thing that uh is interesting to note is that it's being reported that they think that he
wore a wire as early as july of last year in cooperation with mueller's investigation
and with these indictments that came out on monday the only thing they have is unrelated
to the actual campaign again they're trying to put pressure on uh gates and manifold so
yeah i mean the word is and i knew this six months ago not filing proper tax forms for
offshore corporations paid the taxes just didn't follow the proper forms uh that now
pedestrian his brother just filed a few months ago because retroactively retroactively yes
retroactively he still committed the offense that's it and you know i've also been told
they're looking into things like did junior campaign people divert funds for their own
hotels or plane tickets or food i mean it's it's like they're looking for crooked toenails
and somebody that lied about it or forgot about it and that's all they're doing all
right great point roger stone's coming in studio bottom of the hour in studio and we're
going to come back and matt's going to pop in too about who is behind uh this whole antifa
movement with the soros money the same folks that were behind occupy wall street refused
fascism they got a full page ad the new york times katie armor has been on a mission to
manufacture the most comfortable body armor on the market and we've succeeded with the
release of our cqb technology we now offer the most comfortable concealable rifle threat
body armor available things may look good now but what if you need added protection
get your very own concealable rifle threat armor today at kd armor.com and for a limited
time get all plates at wholesale pricing only at c-a-t-i armor.com water is the single most
important thing your body needs so you want to be sure it's the best for you and your
family since 2005 thousands have depended on berkey purified water the berkey guy provides
the lowest price filtration systems in every size for incredibly delicious water now and
in an emergency get to go berkey.com or call 877-886-3653 877-886-3653 go berkey.com hunters
anglers campers and survivalists get back to nature expand your horizons with the highest
quality most versatile unique slingshots and sling bows on the market at slingbow.com slingbow
products are compact and models start from just 1798 they're perfect for your bug out
bag or storing in your vehicle give yourself and your loved ones the excitement and tradition
of slingbow a new frontier in archery and truly modern twist on this primitive survival
tool feel the thrill only at slingbow.com this is dan pillard do you have the irs money
you can't pay are tax debts crippling you i've defended people from the irs for over
30 years i've helped thousands and i can help you too i wrote the book on irs settlement
and i'm telling you there's no such thing as a hopeless case call 800-34-NOTAX to finally
get free of irs debt with the irs's new programs there's never been a better time to solve
your problem call 800-34-NOTAX that's 800-34-NOTAX or my website danpillard.com vitamin mineral
fusion visit infowarslife.com to secure your chemistry we have worked for years with our
chemists and scientists to create the most powerful and affordable great tasting multivitamin
formula available vitamin mineral fusion drink mix at infowarslife.com is loaded with a full
month's supply of essential vitamins minerals and amino acids that your body absolutely
needs in the history of info wars life we've brought out a lot of amazing products like
survival shield x2 super metal vitality and so many others with its unique delivery system
and proprietary manufacturing process designed for maximized effects this formula is the
platinum standard of multivitamin mineral products and this part is most important the
ingredients in vitamin mineral fusion are either plant derived or of the highest quality
lab standard that means it's clean that means it's pure and rest secured you're finding
the tip of the spear in the info war that's infowarslife.com and vitamin mineral fusion
take action now before we sell out now ladies and gentlemen we're running the biggest special
we've ever had for our best selling product brainforce now brainforce plus there's 20%
more in each bottle and we're now purchasing so much of it from the major organic manufacturer
here in the united states that we've been able to get it for less so i'm offering for
the first time ever 50% off and i thought i could offer this for maybe a month i'm going
to have to stop this special within a week because it is blasting out of our warehouse
because the fans of it already are stocking up they know how great it is a whole bunch
of organic natural healthy known nootropics and if you want good clean focused energy
then brainforce is for you and you're supporting the broadcast at the same time it's a good
deal at $39 it's $19.96 at infowarslife.com or simply call toll free 888-253-3139
you're listening to the alex jones show
big brother mainstream media government cover-ups you want to stop tyranny well so does he live
on the info wars.com studios it's alex jones
i have a tendency to wash my hands during a break uh and and then to not drive them
that's why i walk in here and and roger puts his hand out i'm like okay well they're wet
because that doesn't matter as long as they're clean so we're like now but not blood brothers
but i guess you know we've uh we've uh shared uh the the watery hands it's a secret cult
ladies and gentlemen okay i'm being really donald trump started this actually he's the
most obsessive hand washer of all time i guess when you shake millions of hands running for
president you got to do that or you constantly have a cold he's adamant about it getting
serious here uh you just got here you just walked in off the airplane so we haven't even
talked yet what on earth is going on terror attacks the new york times won't say it's
a terror attack they call it a truck attack antifa says they're going to start overthrowing
the government in full page ads funded by soros in the new york times starting november
4th and there are literally dozens of articles saying i'm insane nothing's coming november
4th what is going on with these people yeah you've been paul revere on this you have been
predicting this now literally for months based on your own sources uh i think it's it's a
hysteria because uh in middle america in flyover country donald trump is very popular i was
in washington yesterday i was able to see some proprietary polling taken by the republican
national committee uh and it showed that if the election were run again tomorrow alex
donald trump would win again he's actually marginally more popular than he was on election
day the erosion is in the support for hillary clinton four out of ten clinton supporters
now say that they're not sure they would vote for her again uh and the this of course is
so against type so against the mainstream media narrative that they're going out of
their minds it's emerging we just went over the evidence earlier i'm gonna do a special
report uh tonight on this is gonna air during the war room with owen schroyer and herself
just collecting all the evidence there's so much that poppinopolis was a plant from the
beginning uh by the deep state by mueller wearing wires as early as july and even with
that it's in the indictment how he kept trying to steer them into russia meetings and they
didn't bite i mean if you really get into the evidence their indictment is the evidence
that trump did nothing well and in fact his whole pedigree is as a neo-con as a he goes
from a series of think tanks all of which like the jamestown institute the hudson institute
all of them you know virulently anti-russia and then suddenly overnight who's advocating
uh meetings with the russians at the highest level about this guy poppinopolis uh i am
told that mannefort spotted him early oh he looked he just looks like a worm yeah no this
and he was evidently wearing a wire for at least three months let me ask this what is
the trump campaign dealing with people that look like that i mean i would i would run
from that guy well it's important to understand i mean he looks like a ne'er-do-well uh he
does he does look a little strange doesn't he well you know how those greeks are look
at that wow we love greeks yes we do greeks i know we're good looking that guy in good
luck spiro agnew is the one i was thinking it looks like a little jihadi or something
he does look strange i i guess the point here is that in a presidential campaign when the
media is beating on you for having you know no uh issue operation no no heft you put together
these largely paper honorific advisory panels and they can have a hundred people on them
uh but and in this case the the group that poppinopolis belonged to met one time i don't
believe they ever met with the candidate um the guy had no authority he wasn't on the
payroll he didn't even have uh a credential you know a security pass to get into the headquarters
which you know general election is kind of tightly controlled so he is a marginal player
to to put it uh mildly i think the that sarah huckabee nailed this uh particularly to try
to now depict him as some high level trump operative is just disingenuous and expanding
on this this is all they've got and then trump saying do something uh you've got them completely
involved with russia uranium one john podesta is now making almost daily tweets saying alex
jones eat sh you know what yes uh you know you're gonna get it i mean which is which
is a threat but strangely enough podesta hasn't been banned on twitter you see i've been banned
over allegedly threatening i'm about to say the word is you are now going to sue oh there's
no question i went to washington yesterday to meet with a number of and that's twitter
twitter but uh and i may be joined in this by others because our friend milo has also
been uh and you know i've been going around to the lawyers we have good cases i just haven't
taken the leap yet on what who i need to sue just to defend free speech but but it's amazing
that um you know keith oberman can threaten to burn my house down with me in it but he's
still on twitter uh john podesta can threaten you alex but he's still on twitter talk about
a liberal double standard look i i'm gonna own why do you think podesta's making all
these horrible statements just suddenly he hardly ever tweets and now why is he so angry
at me uh it's hard to say i think he understands that his uh vulnerability is going to come
to the fore here and he keeps trying to divert to pizzagate sorry i've never written spoken
said anything whatsoever about pizzagate i think we concluded it was a it was a false
and we're the ones that pointed out it was a false flag so they're trying to blame me
as the progenitor but of it but just because uh pizzagate turns out to be bogus doesn't
mean that the entire issue of pedophilia is false and notice that's exploded onto the
scene with hollywood extraordinary what do you make of this timing the nfl hollywood
it's all literally collapsing i don't think there's even forces behind the scenes doing
it i just think america's waking up they're angry they're not asleep anymore and they're
speaking out very interestingly that you know i came on uh the war room uh and i laid out
a scenario by which the president should demand that jeff sessions appoint a special counsel
to look into uranium one this would have the net effect of putting mr muller mr combi mr
mccabe the associate director of the fbi and uh rod rosenstein the de facto attorney general
of the united states in the hot seat where they deserve to be right immediately a piece
on vanity fair yesterday headline why roger stone's plan won't work a piece on raw story
the worst of the worst fake news left-wing seats why roger stone's plan is falling apart
you just told us what you fear you fear this move by donald trump i think general kelly
signaled it yesterday in uh his great interview with laura ingram uh i think the president
uh kind of uh revealed it in his tweet saying why isn't the focus on crooked hillary this
is the plan that turns the tables on the inquisitors and by the way if we weren't over the target
the old world war ii saying for bombardiers we wouldn't be under massive attack i'm not
ready to tell folks about it yet but you're here for us to meet strategize you're being
sued uh by the law firm of obama yeah he admits he put him up to it i have al gore i'm not
ready to get to al gore is directly uh i don't want to say it yet i'm actually proud i mean
wait till i tell you about this i just learned about it last night i mean can you believe
al gore man he's got a lot of nerve uh and what's the allegation what does he upset you
about i'll tell you about it later i'm not sure the lawyers don't want us to go public
i've been up against al gore before march the empire is on the run you're listening
to the alex jones show it's a no-brainer a big berkey water filter is the one you need
period you need a water filter that removes chlorine fluoride pharmaceuticals bpa and
other endocrine disruptors pesticides bacteria viruses and much more right and does it all
at only two cents per gallon get the original most trusted name in gravity water filtration
big berkey and now gcn listeners receive five percent off ceramic filter systems using code
gcn call or click one eight seven seven nine nine berkey or big berkey water filters.com
that's one eight seven seven nine nine b-e-r-k-e-y want revenge on the common house fly well
after ten thousand years someone has finally come up with a better way the bug assault
a miniaturized shotgun which utilizes ordinary table salt as ammunition non-toxic and no
batteries required thirty nine ninety five plus shipping and handling use discount code
gcn and receive fifteen percent off your purchase at bug assault.com fire your flies water and
get your bug assault today not a group you develop living defense for us it took you
over a year to do it why is this so good because people are actually waking up to the problem
that pretty much scares me the most i mean i try to make sure that i don't put toxins
from food and water and beverages in my system but right now we're dealing with massive parasites
which is anything that's harmful to your body that lives off a host mechanism right now
with all the refugees uh spreading disease around we have biological warfare going on
everywhere these are all parasites tell us about all the stuff it says there's so many
things that are in it you have the neem in there you have the organic clove bud the organic
wormwood i recommend doing a parasite cleanse at least twice a year all right well i'm glad
we've got some back in because i'm going back on it today it just came back in yesterday
living defense info wars live.com and folks you can't lose full of stuff that's great
for your body period and you support the broadcast info wars live.com thank you dr group from
the global healing center thank you so much for all your work sir on this great product
please listen carefully because i'm about to point out three things that will save you
a lot of money while you get high quality products and fund the info war a 360 win number
one when you choose auto-ship before checkout we give you 10 off on your order at info war
store.com number two you're also able to get items that are out of stock when you sign
up for auto-ship because we hold back a surplus for auto-ship customers number three we're
giving you free shipping on all orders above $50 listeners have been requesting this for
years because it's so easy to forget to reorder the products that you need each month just
go to info war store.com select your favorite product or products click on auto-ship and
choose how often you want us to send you another order as you know i coined the term 360 win
and with the new auto-ship feature at info wars live.com this is a sure win 10 off on
auto-ship win win win at info wars live.com free shipping on orders above 50 bucks and
all out of stock items are never out of stock when you sign up for auto-ship we're not just
going to have to end in the next week the brain force plus special 50% off i'm going
to have to end even sooner our caveman ultimate paleo bone broth turmeric chaga mushroom meat
pollen and more concentrate you talk about next level meal replacement next level compared
to whey and it's great to mix with whey and then make shakes it's incredible my son is
growing like a weed using it it's bigger than i am already 15 incredible it is amazing info
wars live.com 50% off caveman but only a few days left it's about to end and folks the
globalist hate it when you do this we're the tip of the spear because we're fearless we're
bold because we understand the stakes are too high the globalist win we're all slaves
so don't thank me for what i'm doing i want to thank you we're all in this together and
when you get the great molan labe t-shirts you get the great books and videos you're
finding the tip of the spear again visit info war store.com today and commit to helping
the info war you're listening to the alex jones show defending the republic from enemies
foreign and domestic it's alex jones monday through friday from 11 a.m to 3 p.m we're
live and we've watched the war room with ellen schroyer roger stone and others beat days
three to six p.m and of course we have david knight with the real news an analysis of what's
happening in our world every weekday morning 8 a.m to 11 a.m and i'm going to launch a
lot of other shows i'm hiring more people more producers more camera operators more
researchers more journalists it takes money to do that and it takes money to battle like
he's doing um sued by obama saying he's a russian agent no proof and then all this other
stuff behind the scenes i'm not at liberty to tell you about yet but i will because they
know our metrics folks despite the fact that they've tried to censor us and block info
wars and news wars despite the fact they've tried to shut us down and try to get criminal
investigations going on myself matt drudge and others those have all been dropped because
there's nothing there no russian collusion no connections federal elections commission
led by democrats wanted us criminally indicted that's all gone away because it's like trying
to indict me for being the tooth fairy uh it's just not true but seriously if you'll
just commit to spread articles and videos in the war it's exciting on twitter and facebook
and youtube hey this man right here has just been banned off twitter because he was having
such an effect they admit they've done it so it's but they can't ban all of you and
they can't stop you from making other accounts it's a information war they want to kick us
off these big platforms that they act like are open to the public but now they're on
the hot seat so please go to info war store.com we've got over 60 great t-shirts many of them
are only run for a month or a few months are limited edition a bunch of limited edition
shirts are about to be gone forever info war store.com also ladies and gentlemen we've
got new specials on dna force 25 off even though it's been sold out for more than three
and a half months the sales that are ending today are biotruth selenium 40% off survival
shield x2 these are the biggest specials ever 40% off secret 12 40% off supermell vitality
30% off and anthroplex 50% off info war store.com infowarslife.com or triple 8253 3139 biome
defense is now back in stock but whatever you do sign up for auto ship in an additional
10% off that way you get savings everything I do is about symbiosis symbiotic win-win
non-zero sum game everything I do is about a win-win it's it's my it's far beyond superstition
I'm obsessed with it okay and so I'm not like somebody like Harvey Weinstein likes to torture
women while he rapes them I mean I like my wife to have as good a time as I'm having
that's my enjoyment I'm trying to get graphic here the point is is that that's how Trump
is too we want prosperity we want to win but to do that you've got to energize us we energize
you the enemy knows where the resistance is coming from they know where the winning globally
info wars is this the reboot of Americana I didn't invent it I just brought it back
you brought it back all over the world baby info wars we're leading the populous revolution
America 1776 worldwide is happening something I've been saying for 10 years it's here we're
winning in the military law enforcement the bureaucracy we're taking the government back
and it's happening and the economy is turning back on so commit today to financially support
us get products you need it's symbiotic it's a win-win 360 win info war store.com or triple
a two five three three one three nine DNA force is back okay Roger I'm ranting I'm just
so excited here but but again you're saying I've been predicting this for six months the
SJW is the Antifa the communist groups have been saying we're going to launch our revolution
November 4th and many of them say we're gonna kill cops we're gonna kill talk show host
my security folks want me talking about the things that go on but the the issue is they're
saying hashtag kill Republicans on TV Democratic strategists they're celebrating Scalise getting
shot Wolf Blitzer had a guest on saying this guy was basically a hero he wasn't a bad guy
shoot the Scalise and the other people I mean they mean business folks they don't just attack
me and Roger when we walk down the street in San Francisco or Austin okay they mean
business they want to bully us back into submission and then they say in articles every day in
the last two weeks Jones is insane and claims there's some November 4th movement coming
here it is full page front section New York Times that cost $100,000 boys and girls funded
by George Soros at the bottom now what does that sound like to you Roger Stone well and
it's not it's not coincidental that Tom Steyer is up on CNN with these ubiquitous 30-second
TV spots attacking the president he's mentally unbalanced he's insane we can't have a man
like this with his finger on the nuclear button you see that the newspaper they say we're
causing a chain reaction that will drive Trump from power they say the detonation begins
November 4th yeah so these but these are connected events in other words as one who has an extensive
experience in political advertising I can tell you the newspaper ads the television
ads these are all meant for a you know a symbiotic a synergistic a coordination to whip up the
crazy chain reaction exactly to whip up the radicals and we're going to talk about this
on the war room this afternoon I think the establishment has the Mueller strategy they
laid it out for us this week the week and the indictments are building towards November
4th right exactly and then we're talking about their fallback plan a 25th amendment plan
to unhorse our president using that constitutional rubric we're going to be shedding light on
this all week here at Infowars because we have incredible inside information and that's
why you're here for this week because we knew the main enemy assault of their new offensive
starts November 4th and folks they've even sent me letters saying surrender by November
4th I'm the lawyers are looking at me going public with this tomorrow I'm going to show
you this as soon as we off here unbelievable unbelievable no look I think they have a game
plan guys ask David to bring over that that that that that thing from Gore please but
we're going to lay this out for the info warriors plan a is the Mueller takedown if that doesn't
work plan b is the 25th amendment takedown which I think is going to be in conjunction
with this overall Soros Steyer funded media oh they admit it so these these are interlocking
pieces of around by the way Soros claims he spends 500 million a year on average and off
election years of sometimes 800 million election year what does it mean that he's put 18 billion
in to this foundation and says he intends to spend it just the next few years overthrowing
Russia and the US I mean why is why is he walking around last night I was with a very
high level Republican lobbyist with very very close ties to the Bush family and to and Jeb
Bush specifically he had just had lunch with Jeb and Jeb told him confidently Trump will
be gone by December Trump will be gone by December what does that tell you oh my god
we should have started the whole show with that in fact take that clip right there no
start over start over and we're going to put that right in front of this interview this
is so incredible Roger folks never bluffs he's got the intel he's so Jeb Bush is saying
Trump will be gone by December what is he talking about that's what he's talking about
these ads these TV spots in a synergistic effort with a 25th amendment takedown of the
president their claim is going to be well he's unbalanced he's non-compass mentis he
can no longer do the job this is the overall establishment plot first they try the Mueller
assault if that doesn't work they try the 25th amendment assault backed by their street
demonstrations backed by the rowdies on the street demanding Donald Trump's removal so
the whole concerted next wave their biggest push comes this November 4th and they are
going to operate on every level lawsuits physical attacks cop killing you know out of the Soros
funded groups I mean they think we're all what's crazy is they think the threats make
us roll over when all it does is energize us where's their blind spot well it's interesting
I would have taken the Jeb report with a bit of a grain of salt but having done the rounds
in Washington yesterday I also met with another Republican lobbyist hold on stay there and
recap it when we come back give us the new info this is incredible Roger that's why I
was saying to come in here hey we have time to talk first tell folks what the whatever
the biggest news is tell us up front that's what we always do at info Wars we give you
the news a year before anybody else does and everybody knows it that's why they hate us
so get tomorrow's news today at info wars.com stay with us men give your body the support
it needs with info wars life Prosta guard it's time to start assisting the body and
regulating proper prostate balance before his life has set out to bring you formulations
that are not only the highest quality out there but formulas that you can use on a daily
basis to give your body the natural herbs and extracts that our experts recommend the
prostate guard formula does just that with this mixture of plant-based nutrients and
antioxidants that help give your body total support it's a hand-selected blend of saw
palmetto lycopene plant sterols zinc vitamin d3 selenium and copper prostate guard is something
that the men on the info Wars crew take every day and from our research it's something that
men should really be adding to their daily regimen in order to keep their body going
at optimal levels now's the time to start naturally supporting your body get Prosta
guard on your side today exclusively at info wars life.com that's info wars life.com go
to info war store.com and get game-changing amazing products we've been sold out of DNA
force for almost four months these ingredients are nutraceutical grade the highest quality
the bio pqq all of it it's 25% off the truck got in this morning and it's back but it is
a limited run because of all the testing and all the rest of it is the highest quality
read about what it'll do for you and your family it is amazing we also have been sold
out for three months on biome defense super high quality probiotic it's 25% off out of
the gates back in stock but for a very limited time so you get the highest quality the very
cleanest stuff out there we're really really proud of it DNA force and bomb defense probiotic
now back in stock info wars life.com when you buy products from globalist it's an act
of trading with the enemy it is an act of war it is an act of standing up when you spread
the links the articles and buy products from us and when we commit to rampage against the
enemy totally choose to take control of your chemistry with survival shield x2 and bio
true selenium this powerful combo is perfect for supporting your thyroid and health bio
true selenium formula is far from synthetic and is made from a source of 100% organic
mustard seed our super high quality nascent iodine is an essential mineral source of 99.99%
ultra pure deep earth iodine crystals this essential mineral is necessary in order to
produce thyroid hormones which influence every cell tissue and organ in the body with inadequate
thyroid hormones you may experience slow metabolism lethargy weight gain and overall brain fog
survival shield x2 and bio true selenium work together to support the systems in your body
take control of your chemistry today with this super combo discover the power of survival
shield x2 and bio true selenium at info wars life.com America is an information based civil
war that's why now more than ever we've got to hit the streets of America and let these
globalists scum know we're not backing down from their bullies we're only intensifying
our operations in the face of their wannabe dictatorship being a conservative a nationalist
a libertarian or simply a free speech advocate is truly the counterculture the real punk
rock is being a patriot who's pro-america pro-capitalism and pro-freedom who at the
same time is tolerant modern liberalism is a counterfeit of thomas deverson's classical
liberalism they are the anti-liberalists to defend free speech meet like-minded friends
and promote freedom worldwide we've got more than 60 original designs of high quality t-shirts
for men and women as well as more patriot peril at info war store.com be part of the
second american revolution at info war store.com you're listening to the alex jones show
resistance to tyrants his obedience to god it's alex jones roger stone just landed an
hour ago here in austin from dc with high level meetings with top advisors to the bushes
the clintons you name it and that that's why they fear him he's got the contacts including
the president he has just laid out during this break to me really serious info that
dovetails with their plan george soros has bought a full-page ad for antifa calling for
the overthrow of trump beginning november 4th they're all coordinating it roger stone
please give people an intelligence report on what you just told me well alex i was in
washington for the purpose of meeting with some of the most powerful and most knowledgeable
telecommunications lawyers in the country in preparation for a lawsuit against twitter
uh i heard only minutes ago that the official feed for the netflix documentary uh stone
fleck uh for get me roger stone has now also been suspended um so i will own twitter before
this is over there are first amendment issues there are uh there are antitrust issues torturous
interference but but during the time i was in washington i never lose the opportunity
to socialize and i had uh a cocktail with a very prodigious uh bush fundraiser somebody
um with close personal relationships to george w to george h w uh and to jeb uh and he told
me that he had seen jeb recently uh when the topic of trump came up you said that day at
lunch yeah at a lunch he said jeb said confidently bush trump will be gone by december now i
would normally take that with a grain of salt later in the evening i saw a very prominent
republican lobbyist who had just been with a major rhino republican senator who shall
remain nameless and ironically when the subject of trump came up he also said don't worry
about him he'll be gone by december now i see these ads i've seen that tom steier tv
ads steier being a kind of a junior soros by the way he's lost every election he's ever
touched now you bring this in these these full-page newspaper ads and folks this ain't
cheap the full page of the new york times that's 100k plus depending on what editions
it ran in and i see the synergy of their political strategy they are going to run a street revolution
against trump a revolt at the same time that's the astroturf it's the 25th amendment strategy
so plan a the Mueller takedown not looking very good right now because Mueller laid out
his cards and they are weak indeed if they were counting on Manafort to roll over clearly
they were they dumped these charges on him i can report to the info warriors right now
Manafort will plead not guilty and he will fight to the death he is not going to bear
false witness against the president of the united states he is not going to make up lies
about donald trump and the russians to please bob Mueller he is a fighter and he will go
down fighting if he has to but there is zero chance that they will break his spirit or
break his commitment to making america great again and taking on the globalist so i think
the Mueller plan is going to fail there that moves us to the 25th amendment plan alex and
this week here at info wars we're going to lay out who exactly the plotters are and what
their scheme is to remove the president they seek to do in the courts and through the constitution
in a bogus proceeding what they could not do with the ballot box absolutely this is
their biggest assault yet but let's remember they failed trying to steal the nomination
they did steal it from sanders they failed to then keep him from getting the final nomination
at the convention in cleveland that we you and i attended the rest of the crew and then
they failed to get the faithless electors to stop him from being seated at the electoral
college they have failed failed failed failed and now russia gate completely turns around
as you said a year and a half ago everything they accuse trump of and you and i of hell
asinine they have done no they've got the they've got the worst possible perfect storm
between uranium one and the revelations about uh fusion gps and the ties first revealed
here at info wars to the bush rubio republican money man paul singer uh and his henchman
dan senor uh and then passed that ball on to hillary clinton as the president noted
today in a tweet up to 13 million dollars now spent on this bogus narrative accusing
the president of sexual indiscretions completely false completely made up they are in retreat
they see the pieces coming together for their indictment uh and therefore the guy we really
have to count on the guy who i think is a hero uh who i've known of for many years and
somebody of extraordinary integrity is senator chuck grassley he is going to bust uranium
one wide open and in my view it is essential to have both mueller and rosenstein in the
hot seat answering questions under and that's why they're saying your plan is ridiculous
because they know the president listens on pardons you name it and you've been telling
him all along what was going to happen it's happened just as you said it would uh how
much i could say here but the president's got to know you've been dead on well i was
heartened by the fact that um general kelly in this terrific interview with laura ingram
laid it out laid out the need for a special prosecutor is kelly not suddenly getting a
lot better well and i noticed the left turned on him now the left has turned on him he clearly
has figured out that the way to stay on his job is to go to the wall for donald trump
donald trump is a man who rewards and appreciates loyalty and whether it is general kelly taking
on the whack job congresswoman from florida with her cowboy hats or whether it is him
pointing out that we need a special prosecutor here's the linchpin though alex what will
jeff sessions do when the president he's the weak link it appears that way when the president
orders him this isn't a suggestion jeff and the president's on tv saying do something
they're in bed with the russians exactly so it does not uh it would not shock me if jeff
sessions has to go he either got to follow orders and appoint a real special prosecutor
let someone like like uh uh uh mike mccazy or someone like well pregg yachty's already
said he wouldn't do it andrew mccarthy uh judge andrew napolitano he'd be great any
of them are more than capable of doing this job we need a real fearless honest process
let's boil it down we're in a mob war between a group that wants to restore the republic
and not have us sell the country out in a group that thinks they own the country what
about the wild card though of trump saying don't bring people in on these cultural enrichment
visas that's actually what they're called folks the chuck schumer and obama put through
uh seven years ago and then almost all the terror attacks we see are from the quote refugees
or cultural enrichment from the very countries trump is trying to block people unvetted where
folks in sudan or in somalia an imam gives you a passport who lets you cross a border
and then fly out on say uh you know a kenyan airways they don't even have airports that
work trump's saying he bans seven countries these are countries that don't have running
water we have no idea who's getting on the damn planes he better block them i wonder
if the people uh killed in time square feel culturally enriched today i wonder if there's
going to be a seven day waiting period like we have with the old brady law on rental trucks
because you know they had just a waiting period because you know the new york time says right
here the truck did it you know that it's like uh christine the steven king movie or maximum
overdrive you know where the cars come alive and kill you right here autobots transforming
murder mile-long manhattan truck attack kills eight i knew it was megatron the truck had
no driver evidently extraordinary extraordinary did he not yell ali akbar just before the
attack the i've seen that in several media reports why won't they call the truth the
truth why won't they point out that this is islamic terrorism at its worst and again listeners
know this i only generally plug once an hour over the years because that could fund us
and we grew uh symbiotically organically to the level we needed now's the main attack
now's the war bonds you spend money with globalist it's trading with the enemy you buy products
at info war store.com it is an act of total resistance to the globalist in soros and for
his billions millions can counter that but we need millions because i sell high quality
products at such low prices that i argue with some of my crew either in marketing i think
super low prices are the way to go and people just buy more we make more i'm right kinda
but sometimes not because then sometimes things are best sellers sometimes they're not i need
folks to go to info war store.com and get one of you know 60 70 t-shirts to spread the
word meet like-minded folks i need you to sign up for auto ship to get great products
like dna force and great probiotics like biome defense and brainforce plus and a bunch of
specials that end today info war store.com or triple a 25 33139 one of my biggest stressors
is trying to raise money to hire more crew to battle harder and fending off enemy attacks
but if you flood us with cash it absolutely takes weight off us to spend time in information
warfare so i'm going to say it now you want us to fight energizes flood me with greenbacks
and i commit i'll go to the death but i need the money that's how i wage war flood us with
money now we've taken thousands of years of known research and put it together with our
own four years of seeking and testing to find the very best systems that god gave us through
mother nature to detoxify the body that's why i'm introducing z shield toxic metal and
chemical defense support it's made in the usa it's filled with known compounds from
nature that are absolutely associated with detoxifying the body and it supports the info
war it is a classical 360 win this is the formula that i personally have been taking
for over a year and now we believe we have come as close to perfection when it comes
to a detoxifier as you can possibly get you it's yourself you owe it to your family and
you owe it to the future of this country in the world that patriots stay as healthy and
as clean and as focused as you can be because we need you the remnant of america to reignite
those brush fires the next level and to be healthy and as focused as you can be thanks
to your support and your prayers together we're changing the world now it's time to
change our bodies with z-field and infowarslife.com i am very proud to announce the introduction
of the highest quality infowars biome defense probiotic we wanted to come out with the largest
spectrum of high quality known probiotics that have been proven to improve overall digestion
and health and detoxification in the body biome defense is an exclusive blend of 50
billion live and active cultures from over 23 different probiotic strains that are known
to support digestion and intestinal function our researchers are confident that we have
been able to develop what will be the leading probiotic on the market secure your biome
defense in ultra strength or regular strength at infowarslife.com today and get started
supporting your digestive system naturally we've been testing this formula for years
but this is the limited first run to the public so please take advantage of it today support
your own health and support the infowar you're listening to the alex jones show
relentlessly attacking the power structure you're listening to alex jones
by the way roger stone you heard it here first three days ago is considering suing twitter
he's talking top lawyers he has a cut in their eye case of discrimination they've operated
like a utility they told congress for a utility so it's google so it's facebook but now we
have veritas video and internal documents across the board where if their employees
say men exist they're fired i know that sounds crazy but that's how cultic it is now like
robots we are the board there are no men there are no women and so he's getting ready to
file a big suit milo others are probably going to join i've been looking at it but they always
ban us and bring us back i've talked to lawyers we've got good cases but not as good as yours
and this brings light right as they bring in this new guy to head up the federal trade
commission who's an antitrust google buster and then we had the big uh executives and
people that i'm going to play later after you leave testifying uh that there really
was no russia collusion in fact the russia stuff was anti-trump yeah i know it's extraordinary
that the double standard that were experienced on twitter look every single day on twitter
people threatened to kill me kill my wife kill my children kill my dogs nothing happens
to them they're still there keith olbermann threatens to burn people's houses down with
them in them he drops the f-bomb constantly and attacks on the president the man is not
there but still he is verified and on twitter uh today uh an antifa spokesman announces
the future beheading of a number of americans still their twitter feed remains intact so
it's about time uh and i have met with a number of lawyers this is very simple twitter needs
to be regulated like a utility the phone company is a private company but they can't deny you
a telephone this is a first amendment issue and to say oh you used obscenity really well
you better look at keith oberman's feed if that's the measure um i didn't say anything
on twitter that hasn't been said now you said don lemon is a complete idiot well i said
he's a snowflake he's an imbecile he and his view again and they proved he's a snowflake
you got banned but the the the claim by don lemon is that the clintons have been completely
exonerated on uranium one no don they haven't stop saying that it's a lie and when you repeat
a lie it makes you a liar go to your next party and knock it off will you and a separate
issue then you're gonna go take a break and get ready to uh host the war room coming up
and the fourth hour here today that i'll join you in with what do you make a pedestrian
he hardly ever tweets when he does foaming at the mouth at you foaming at the mouth at
me making threats uh saying i'm gonna eat you know eat crap i mean what is going on
with him i think he's becoming unhinged you notice his brother was forced to step down
from their extremely lucrative influence peddling operation in washington dc uh they try to
divert attention to pizza gate but pizza gate's not the issue it's the art on the walls it's
the weird stuff written on your knuckles john we're on to you we know what you are and what
you do exactly and i'm i'm saying pedessa should be investigated from what's in the
wikileaks the new york times everybody diverted it to a pizza place we covered it we took
the bait but we got the documents and we got the pis on the ground for six months we're
not stupid no so look i think he's becoming unhinged because they are getting exposed
their whole carefully constructed russian narrative is falling apart before their very
eyes the exact thing that they were seeking to divert from the fact that they are the
ones in bed you know pedessa's watching right now i hope so listen he only talks about us
yeah well i i don't try to get your feed followers up just by saying my name it's ironic twitter
killed me just when i hit 300 000 followers and again they do that to suppress it turned
out like 80 some percent of obama's hillary's it's all fake we don't go buy followers i
could go buy 10 million tomorrow for like a 50 000 dollars yeah it's fake it's fake
no drudges is all drudge is the number one site in the world and he only has like a million
followers on twitter you know because he doesn't have fake followers roger stone great job
my friend we got matt bracken mike starting a bunch of more coming up on the islamic terror
attack you go to info war store.com and get game-changing amazing products we've been
sold out of dna force for almost four months his ingredients are nutraceutical grade you
have the highest quality the bio pqq all of it it's 25 off the truck got in this morning
and it's back but it is a limited run because of all the testing and all the rest of it
it's the highest quality read about what it'll do for you and your family it is amazing we
also have been sold out for three months on biome defense super high quality probiotic
it's 25 off out of the gates back in stock but for a very limited time so you get the
highest quality the very cleanest stuff out there we're really really proud of it dna
force and bomb defense robotic now back in stock info wars live.com when you buy products
from globalist it's an act of trading with the enemy it is an act of war it is an act
of standing up when you spread the links the articles and buy products from us and when
we commit to rampage against the enemy totally
everything inside with the fires of liberty of the information yeah it's alex jones right
down the hall but not the new world order you thought mike sternum which is coming up
in just four or five minutes matt bracket is only popping in briefly but i want to get
back on the war room and back on our show tomorrow is having some skype trouble in the
last 30 minutes we're just getting a pop in from matt bracken a counterterrorism expert
best-selling author former navy seal really smart guy predicting six months ago that there'd
be a big antifa uprising trying to overthrow trump that they would get very very violent
they're simultaneously saying none of this exists while they're calling for it but here
is the full page new york times ad calling for the total launch of a revolution on november
fourth this saturday and that they are going to quote drive the president from power we
just had roger stone on who met with one of the chief advisors to the bush family and
others saying trump's gone by december ladies and gentlemen they're making their move it's
a confidence game though because they said two months ago he'd be gone in two months
so their plans behind schedule his ratings are going up he's delivering on the economy
but just a brief snapshot matt bracken we've seen the situation while they had the saudi
arabian military doing a conference and other things in vegas and more and more that's emerging
as a deep state operation very sophisticated connected in different groups and then we
also at the same time have this latest islamic attack yesterday killing eight people the
new york times calls a truck attack in five minutes what's on your radar what do you see
happening um just for a short thing something that i haven't really heard a lot about in
terms of the uh the the attack yesterday they're they never mentioned islam jihad or a lot
a lot bar at the conference this morning or yesterday it's the them it's like martians
we're not going to surrender to the them or the they but they're so cowardly they won't
even say it imagine trying to fight world war ii where you can't say german or nazi
you can only say uh belligerent europeans you know it's crazy but the the actual translation
of allah akbar is not god is great that's a big mistake it's when they say allah who
and they put the ooh on the end of allah that means greater so it means allah is greater
than your god allahu akbar is our god they're saying our god our god dominates you we are
defeating you we are greater than you we have conquered you that's right and and watching
heraldo and these other apologists they seem to be saying that the solution is uh putting
up bollards all over the place anywhere a truck can go we're going to put up bollards
but i think we should call those things allahu ak bollards or allahu ak barriers because
that's what they are in europe they call them koran blocks they put up jersey barricades
and they put up these cement bollards they never had to do that in any other war it's
because today the war is among us and you know as mad as i as i am at this terrace his
name is literally uh sort of allah you know that nobody of our extreme vetting picked
up on the fact that his parents named this boy sort of allah and he won the is the he
won the isis lottery to come to america and bring 28 more i just heard today bring 28
of his closest inbred family here which i'm sure they're all on welfare they're plotting
more jihad attacks we pay for them everything and then they hate us because we're creative
and we're not inbred yeah and as angry as i am at these at these uh crazy jihadists
you know if a crazy farmer puts a fox in his chicken house and the next morning all the
chickens are dead yeah the fox is just acting according to his nature you know the farmer
is the one that's responsible so it's chuck schumer and these people that thought it's
a great idea to flood the country with you know tomorrow's jihadists they're like the
crazy farmer that put the fox in the chicken house the fox and the sword of islam is sort
of allah he's just going by his his own nature his true nature it's this liberals believe
that there's the in the what they call the magic dirt theory you take a guy who's raised
for 22 years to be a devout you know islamic jihadist hate women hate gays uh hate freedom
bring him to america and he's going to turn into a jeffersonian uh you know constitutional
republican it's insanity and the main people that we need to point the finger at and i'm
very glad that our president is doing it are these creeps like chuck schumer they're the
fox that is putting the chicken in the henhouse that's right he headed up the program and
we've shown the video of this guy after he's run over a bunch of people and jumped out
of the car with his fake gun before the cops get him uh he just he just literally looks
like a rabid dog you can tell when a dog's got rabies or is mentally ill kind of stumbles
around and acts weird i mean he just looks like an inbred mental patient and why would
they bring all these inbred mental patients in with to run around and kill us i mean i'm
so sick of it and then to watch cnn and the new york times were to cover it up i mean
did you see jake tapper call ala akbar say oh it's so beautiful yeah that's and unfortunately
that's you know woven right through their religion it's it's impossible to um to take
out of it and you know there's there's just no expunging it tommy robinson the brit has
a great book you know uh on the on the quran why uh muslims kill for it for uh the quran
you can't reform islam you know it is the ten commandments are all kill kill kill you
know there's no way to take it out and so he thinks he's doing something good and then
jake tapper goes it is so beautiful that's all a direct code to them saying just like
we supported the arab spring at cnn we support you brother good job just make sure it's a
church next time yeah the the moderate the so-called moderate muslims actually think
that this guy is an idiot for blowing their cover because the smart ones think look we're
we're going to win demographically we're going to win just in the war of the womb outbreeding
you five to one so brother you're blowing our cover you know we know you're eager to
get your 72 virgins but you're making us look bad and exposing the true aim and the way
he runs around in circles he looks like a cockroach yeah he he didn't have the guts
to actually pull a knife out and charge anybody though he just ran around with his toy guns
trying for a suicide by cop i'm very glad he got shot in the gluteus maximus so he's
available to uh to interview because he's going to be the poster boy for for islamism
i hope that they give him a microphone and a show because he is the rabid dog of islam
well matthew matt i want to get you back up on the war on today if you can because i want
to get your predictions for november 4th what's coming if not tomorrow thank you so much my
friend thanks all right everything got back up today because his sky pet problems for
30 minutes i apologize to mike cernovich for getting him on the label hold him a little
bit in the next uh segment at the bottom of the hour then we have uh stephen gern a highly
decorated uh marine and then contractor for the company as it's known uh who's been speaking
about the whole islamic invasion that's coming i want to get to that briefly with mike cernovich
and then into november 4th because they say again we're going to kill you and attack and
overthrow number fourth then they say oh it's insane when mike cernovich and alex jones
and others report on it nothing's coming november 4th mike cernovich what is the point of them
saying nothing's coming november 4th but then full page ads saying we're going to overthrow
trump on november 4th what is going on here i mean they're so weird and unhinged and as
we learned from when antifa was carrying a pedophile sign and then they go oh well we
didn't even mean to carry it someone just handed it to us like wait so if somebody hands
you a pedophile sign you're just going to carry around whatever anybody hands you they're
not thinking alex that's the whole point and they're trying to say that you planted it
with no proof do we know who do we know where the sign came from yeah there's zero proof
of any of this the media is saying it's a false flag and i go okay where's your proof
and they go well antifa wouldn't carry it and i go well they did carry it and then they
go well somebody gave it to them well okay who who no proof at all but like you said
yesterday now they're having to admit false flags could exist right which is a fantastic
narrative win so from my perspective i don't care if it was some people maybe from 4chan
or something who pranked them i don't care because we win either way yeah because no
one ever stages anything even though the new cia documents came out admitted they were
staging terror then mike cernovich is our guest we're going to come back get his take
on november 4th what antifa is planning to launch you can see the whole coordination
with the republicans as well the republican leadership is saying trump is gone in december
now i think that's wishful thinking but they're going to do their darndest we'll be right
back he's at cernovich i'm at real alex jones heart disease is on the rise clogged arteries
high blood pressure and high cholesterol levels may not be fully detected by you but the symptoms
are there loss of energy blood sugar spikes and drops poor circulation and irregular heartbeat
are just a few of these that can alert you that something is wrong hear how heart and
body extract is making a difference in thousands of people's lives across america my blood
pressure has normalized my diabetes has totally improved everyone is telling me now how much
healthier i look and i'm telling everyone how much healthier i feel i recommend heart
and body extract to everyone anybody over 40 in the north american continent should
be using this product as a preventative to keep their cardiovascular system healthy order
your two-month supply today by calling 866-295-5305 that's 866-295-5305 or order online hbextract.com
heart and body extract 866-295-5305 or hbextract.com in an emergency you need a fire now but what
if the wood is wet no problem for insta fire our non-toxic fire starter packs lights wet
wood floats and can even burn on water or in any weather sustains winds up to 30 miles
per hour and each pouch weighs only 1.75 ounces need an emergency or camp stove get the insta
fire inferno stove that boils 20 ounces of water in under three minutes with controllable
heat and 10 from 425 to 1500 degrees free shipping go to insta fire.com and use discount
code radio 30 at the three times for 30 off your order insta fire fire in an instant fully
cooked ready to eat bacon i'm talking thick meaty center cut presidential bacon savory
and delicious i buy some i use some i store some awesome no refrigeration needed with
a 10-year shelf life nasa pack technology bacon fully cooked fully hydrated ready to
eat right from the pack bacon or warm and served life-saving ready to eat bacon 10-year
shelf life bacon ships free at fullycookedbacon.com fullycookedbacon.com refresh your breath with
mx essentials organic mouthwash our formula is made from organic herbal ingredients to
help stimulate the gums and provide a cleansing effect while adding a pleasant refreshing
taste mx essentials mouthwash is non-gmo certified organic made without alcohol chemicals or
other artificial ingredients such as flavors fragrances or dyes the pure organic plant
extracts are concentrated containing antibacterial properties that work well to help tone gum
and freshen your breath this antiseptic mouthwash is a concentrated formula you will need to
dilute one part mouthwash to 10 parts water mx essentials mouthwash is a great addition
to your daily brushing routine it is effective yet gentle enough for the most sensitive gums
and canker sores go organic today with mx essentials visit infowarsstore.com to learn
more that's infowarsstore.com we're not just going to have to end of the next week the
brain force plus special 50% off i'm going to have to end even sooner our caveman ultimate
paleo bone broth turmeric chaga mushroom bee pollen and more concentrate you talk about
next level meal replacement next level compared to whey and it's great to mix with whey then
make shakes it's incredible my son is growing like a weed using it it's bigger than i am
already 15 incredible it is amazing infowarslife.com 50% off caveman but only a few days left it's
about to end and folks the globalists hate it when you do this we're the tip of the spear
because we're fearless we're bold because we understand the stakes are too high the
globalists win we're all slaves so don't thank me for what i'm doing i want to thank you
we're all in this together and when you get the great molan labe t-shirts you get the
great books and videos you're finding the tip of the spear again visit infowarsstore.com
today and commit to helping the infowar
you're listening to the alex jones show
ladies and gentlemen during the break i walked back
into the break room to get a cup of coffee and chuckie schumer was on fox news live in
the senate blaming trump for new york this is the guy this is the guy that got the bill
passed with obama he sponsored it he wrote it he's the chief sponsor of the diversity
lottery the cultural enrichment as the eu calls it we didn't make up these sick jokes
we call it cultural enrichment when they kill you know 89 people a niece and injured 280
or whatever or all the other stuff and scream holla at bar you know run your toddler over
as they run uh a chuck schumer beauty trump calls for the end of diversity visa program
and then this is schumer's response we're going back to mike cernovich here it is president
bush in a moment of national tragedy understood the meaning of his high office and sought
to bring our country together president trump where is your leadership i'm calling on the
president to rescind his proposed cuts to this vital anti-terrorism funding immediately
so just last week that uh and then and then there was more i saw where he's blaming trump
when they're trying to hold up budgets i mean this is just total deception what do you make
of this mike cernovich yeah trump though is doing deals with schumer um right that that's
what cracks me up is the people who are meanest to trump are the people who seem to get his
attention but then when you and i ever criticize trump they go oh you know jones and cernovich
are betraying us like no that's how schumer you have to to get anything with trump you
have to negotiate and that's what schumer is doing and that's who trump actually listens
to and does deals to so that that's interesting schumer's doing that i found out from someone
directly that that one video the night before the debate or two nights before i said you
attack or it's over and you're a joke and he was on the fence whether he was going to
attack or not and i'm told that video pushed him over the edge of me screaming at him so
is that the answer here cernovich yeah you have to push back i i did a video where i
said there's all this violence against trump supporters he won't call it out therefore
trump is okay with antifa violence against trump supporters a day or two later at that
rally in arizona trump finally for the first time called out antifa so people go oh you
know cernovich jones you guys are on and off the trump train no let the professionals do
our jobs we know what we're doing we're reminding trump that hey this is an ongoing negotiation
you're just not going to steamroll us and we see again chuck schumer gets great deals
out of trump because trump does not respond well to weak people into weakness he only
responds well to people who negotiate back very aggressively exactly instead of me just
directing the conversation you've always got big stuff in the in the frying pan and also
stuff on the back burner what's other big news in planet cernovich well vanity fair has come
out with stories that roger stone of course is broken you have broken i broken where trump
realizes what a disaster jared kushner is big write-up in vanity fair about the bad
advice from kushner to fire general flint that was the biggest mistake of trump's presidency
firing james combi that was a kushner idea too so the white house coup is at a how do
you want to it's been paused because general kelly is now tagged into the culture war so
general kelly has said privately to trump i know people who are familiar with the conversation
that now i understand why you're always hitting back because once it went after general kelly
when he was very very classy very distinguished goals our father he said oh wait so this is
what it's like to be attacked over nothing they're fabricating things they're lying about
me so kelly said i understand trump your tweets and i you know that was my next question man
you're always on target kelly really is gotten better now after they attacked him and his
family and is now and now the left's totally turned on him uh so so that's good to know
now kelly understands exactly so that is again trump's twitter has been much more effective
now the rhetoric isn't quite as fiery or hot but he's tweeting more often now this comms
team is doing actually a better job of twitter so so what got kelly to finally wake up i
mean just the attacks on trump lying about him and how he handled the phone calls or
what yeah the way they politicized the death of his son for kelly that was the red line
kelly was devastated by the death of it i mean anybody would be devastated by the death
of a child and the way the media politicized the death and he took it personal because
trump was saying exactly what kelly wrote for him to say kelly took that really personal
yeah and then the media is going after him now and attacking him and kelly realizes oh
wait these people fabricate information they they are liars right they they are liars they
are fabricators and kelly now understands that you have to be aggressive you have to
go on the attack all just like trump said in the press conference last week he goes
people are finally getting i have to punch back yeah so kelly's great now kelly goes
on tv he's talking about the civil war and now they're trying to say oh do you support
slavery and so general kelly remember this is an honorable man i i don't claim to be
the most you know i'm a very flawed human being i'm not a man like general kelly general
kelly is the kind of person who would have been a roman senator the kind of person who
would have been beloved by historians for throughout his life he's what you would consider
the best of america and the best of american values and now he realizes well wait a minute
they're fabricating things about me now they're saying general kelly likes slavery they're
they're making fun of his son's death they're they're denigrating him denigrating a service
he's realizing he's been compartmentalized inside the military honorable people he doesn't
understand the scum we're dealing with and now he's having to wake up to the literal
zombie scum attack and now he realizes why we all go so hard that was why he kept our
articles kind of away for the president because he didn't understand they're like well you
you know he had said we're all too aggressive and we shouldn't be so divisive you and i
we're under total attack unite america we want to bring americans together the media
won't let us the media divides they're using divide and conquer tactics hate rhetoric terrorist
rhetoric apologizing for terrorism telling people we need to have more terrorism look
the other way about terrorism look the other way as they did for three decades about the
rape and pedophilia in hollywood they're attacking cory feldman barbara walters attacked
cory feldman that was my next question mainstream headlines hollywood accusers harassers molesters
rapists the accounts at 56 now confirmed racist or rapists and molesters i mean this whole
thing's coming down quicker than i thought but what are the unforeseen blowback from
this well you and i and we can pull that footage up you and i said that harvey weinstein was
given to the media as a sacrificial lamb as a distraction from the pedophilia stuff and
then that was their ruse that's why they gave the media harvey weinstein because the media
didn't want to cover the pedophilia but the pedophilia stuff is coming out now that was
a it was going to come out one way or another so i predicted that there was going to be
a major pedophile pedophile scandal then you have kevin kevin spacey and by the way everybody
always told me was a boy raper basically i mean i mean i had the makers of a major film
here we were like let's not get into it because he's not in the film but yeah the word is
kevin spacey's kind of a kingpin yeah exactly and now what i find interesting is that the
fake news media will not interview the filmmaker about hollywood pedophilia so the filmmaker
is going on rt to talk about it and then people go why do people go on rt well because why
won't the media tell the truth about hollywood pedophilia unbelievable let me ask you about
november 4th when they kicked this thing off i actually my lawyers want me to get into
it but i mean literally al gore uh his whole deal like telling me i better roll over by
november 4th and all this other stuff i mean we are on the march the empire is on the run
you're listening to the alex jones show this is michael david from seattle i'm 51 years
old and six months ago i started taking andro 400 to increase my testosterone since then
i've lost 35 pounds of fat and my waist went from size 38 to size 32 i have more energy
and i look and feel 20 years younger and now my wife tells me i have to take andro 400
hi this is ron johnson from utah after 10 weeks of taking andro 400 i lost 13 pounds
and my waist went from 36 to 33 that was eight years ago i continued to take andro 400 and
i've maintained my weight at 172 gained muscle and energy i'm 63 now and feel better than
i have in 30 years andro 400 the natural way to increase testosterone lose belly fat gain
energy and feel great try andro 400 the safe effective affordable way to boost your testosterone
go to andro 400.com or call 888-400-0435 888-400-0435
support good oral health with our one-of-a-kind super blue fluoride free products infowars
life brings you a revolutionary toothpaste blend with iodine and nano silver designed
to deliver a powerful clean enjoy a minty fresh flavor made with peppermint oil or try
our bubble gum flavor pair this groundbreaking toothpaste with the super blue fluoride free
mouthwash and supercharge your oral health our amazing mouthwash features natural oils
and ancient ingredients used since aboriginal and biblical times instead of containing fluoride
our super blue line is loaded with the good halogen iodine and an array of other beneficial
compounds that have been hand selected for their oral health benefits super blue fluoride
free mouthwash and toothpaste are the first and only to contain all of these natural ingredients
xylitol nano silver and iodine notice the difference with our super blue fluoride free
products refresh your breath and invigorate your oral health routine at infowarsstore.com
that's infowarsstore.com protect your skin with spf 30 sunscreen lotion by emmerich's
essentials perfect for face and body this natural unscented sunscreen can be worn at
all times of the day whenever you need sun protection we source ingredients from nature
producing a product free of harmful chemicals and toxins this natural lotion contains 21
zinc oxide which is the largest particle size used and we do not use nanoparticles the larger
the particle the safer it is for your body the organic oils help hydrate the skin leaving
it nice and smooth the truly natural fragrance free sunscreen for the most sensitive skin
emmerich's essentials wants you to enjoy the sun and strives to bring you organic products
to enhance your life naturally protect your skin with spf 30 sunscreen lotion by emmerich's
essentials stop exposing yourself and your family to toxic ingredients visit infowarsstore.com
and learn more about the new spf 30 sunscreen lotion vitamin mineral fusion visit infowarslife.com
to secure your chemistry we have worked for years with our chemists and scientists to
create the most powerful and affordable great tasting multivitamin formula available vitamin
mineral fusion drink mix at infowarslife.com is loaded with a full month supply of essential
vitamins minerals and amino acids that your body absolutely needs in the history of info
wars life we've brought out a lot of amazing products like survival shield x2 super male
vitality and so many others with its unique delivery system and proprietary manufacturing
process designed for maximize effects this formula is the platinum standard of multivitamin
mineral products and this part is most important the ingredients in vitamin mineral fusion
are either plant derived or of the highest quality lab standard that means it's clean
that means it's pure and rest secured you're finding the tip of the spear in the info war
that's infowarslife.com and vitamin mineral fusion take action now before we sell out
you're listening to the alex jones show
if you are receiving this transmission you are the resistance live from the infowars.com
studios it's alex jones two weeks ago he was on the jesse waters show and predicted there'd
be big truck attack killings in places like new york two weeks later it happened steven
gern highly decorated marine and of course contractor with the company who last year
went public about when he's in these islamic countries almost all of them admit to his
face while he's training them to fight that there would love to kill him so he's here
with us coming up about five minutes to break down the latest with the eight dead eleven
wounded and this rat-like creature running around with a little toy gun after he's done
it i guess it's kind of bittersweet he's alive wish he was dead but i'm glad he's alive the
other side's getting information but the islam is definitely dovetailed with antifa george
soros and refused fascism same group that set up the occupied wall street as my producers
were pointing out says the nightmare must end the trump pence regime must go november
fourth it begins be there join with thousands who will gather in cities and towns across
the country a movement of protest that continue every day and night growing until we become
millions determined not to stop until the regime is driven from power this is the soros
astroturf to line up with the neo-cons and the rhinos and the democrats saying by december
he will be gone and roger stone was in dc yesterday i've got all the names the info
the republicans are saying yeah that the trump's gone in december yeah and he wasn't gonna
get the nomination either and then he wasn't gonna get seated either mike cernovich what
is your intel on this is this just them with all their threats and all their november fourth
threats you told me you've gotten some of the same legal threats now i guess everybody's
getting them are they just seeing who they can intimidate or what is the point of this
because all it's done has got me in pure fighting mode i mean they're walking on the fighting
side of me yeah they banned roger stone maliciously and without permanently right and they can
only push this so far they've lost every time they use their little alt-right sab saboteurs
people to end our march on google but now that that's over we'll just have a big march
that we can have big marches we can bring a lot of people and it shows how weak they
are they were so afraid of your google march yeah exactly we were going to do a march on
google and then they used fed fed embeds with these alt-right morons in charlottesville and
then next thing you know who by the way are admitted obama uh of occupy wall street they
three of them were formally funded by the occupy wall street that's now refused fascism
i mean it's totally obvious they're all little pretty boy strumpet leftists who think they're
smart enough to fall flag us exactly and then the next week we were supposed to have a march
on google the fake news media they lied about it and claimed as a white nationalist rally
was nothing of the sort so the media was able to kill that with their false flag terrorist
attack but the the demand is there the people are there the people want to do it they can
only push us so far and these frivolous lawsuit threats these attacks on the integrity of
the people the violence the pedophilia the the rape coming out of hollywood people are
done with it and they need to be very very careful who they're pushing around exactly
and everybody knows this but we got to be strategic about it but they're going to counter
strike but historically gut level everything humanity wants to be free and authoritarianism
is coming crashing down they had america and the rest of the world kind of mesmerized by
television and mainstream media for a while but now people are coming out of the trance
doesn't mean they're left wing right wing christian not christian any of that just means
common sense they recognize lies they see a fraud they see globalism for what it is
and i i just can't believe how the arrogance of hillary are they actually that arrogant
pedestal or is that their con man game where they act so confident because man i mean we've
gone from turning the tide to ripping their arms out of their sockets politically now
now this is like a stampede over them i mean this is epic yeah they're drunk with power
tony podeska of all people threatening to sue tucker carlson my god i wish tony podeska
would threaten to sue me i want to talk about that subterranean basement where he watches
dangerous works of art and other things that have been reported by the guardian the washington
post public photos of little toddlers with their butts beat red so i i want to know again
the washington post reported because they did a puff piece on tony podeska that's how
gross these people were they they got away with it for years and see i'm not matthew
velli but once they do it i am when when the media made up pizza gate off of the emails
that were there with wikileaks that need to be investigated diverted to the pizza place
we cover what the media was covering we said hey this is bull they took us being moral
as that we were weak and then tried to frame us for the whole story but i actually seriously
now it's almost like i didn't do it on purpose but like a setup because now i realize in
the mackie valley level i get Podesta his brother his brother is saying i like dangerous
art i watch it in a dungeon it's it's naked little kids here's my neighbor kids with their
butts paddled red and i mean i'm like how does the washington post publish images of
the little kids butts and but that was 2007 though when they just thought they'd throw
it in our face cernovich and then i'm thinking why am i scared of these people bring it on
let's go you know what well yeah that's the whole issue that's why i i've never apologized
i always double down because they do view because they're you got to remember they're
satanic people they're demonic people they're used to abusing and exploiting the vulnerable
you cannot show them any weakness because you and i are good if if i do something wrong
do you all say hey alex you know i didn't realize that my apologies you don't say apology
accepted this isn't how they live they go oh wait you apologized you must be a moral
person maybe you're a christian now i'm really going to go in on you now i'm really going
to try to destroy you they take your humanity as weakness like one time actually gave it
one of your sources you didn't get really mad at me i said i had a brain for it i apologize
you said hey that's okay but it was you didn't take it like a power over me but exactly that's
how they are yeah i even forgot that even happened but again yeah i never even brought
it up ever again you just realized that's life but that's because i have more of a higher
set of values where i'll accept an apology but these demonic satanic people in dc the
people like the podeskas who have no integrity spirit cooking let's talk about the spirit
cooking john podeska oh yeah ladies and gentlemen of the jury here they are at an alister crowley
event where he's being promised blood and semen to drink and so we investigated it yeah
there's a lot i would love to talk to them about i would love to to sit down with john
podeska for hours and say so have you ever drank have you ever drank soup that contained
blood and semen because that's what the recipe book calls for did you see where obama books
and i can show you the dinner that you were invited to by tony podeska so go ahead bro
let's talk about this let's talk about what you're into let's talk about the art let's
talk about obama podeska office is getting a painting of him by an artist that paints
at the semen that the obama official portrait is by a guy that paints in semen again i would
love to ask all these people these questions they get really triggered when you talk about
it but maybe they need to learn what discovery looks like maybe maybe they need to realize
that okay once you sue somebody and if you're suing them for defaming your so-called character
everything is an open book now remember that email they sent about dennis haster oh it's
sad what happened to dennis hastert i remember that email the podeska emails even mainstream
media had hastert in the news recently criticizing trump and they didn't put the article he's
a convicted boy raper mike cernovich powerful info please join us as much as you can at
cernovich on twitter while you're still there and so much more thank you so much for joining
us always a pleasure olives wow okay uh everything's back to about 15 minutes late today because
we had some technical problems earlier uh getting bracket on nobody's fault just the
way skype is we're gonna go to break and come back with a gentleman i was just talking about
stephen gern uh who again has videos with 50 million 45 million 48 million you name
it uh just talking about hey i've been in the marines i've been a contractor i work
for the company and i'm overseas and i mean the muslims i'm training to defend their country
admit they want to kill me basically um and you know one of the security guys i got working
here was one of them remember he heard eight guys trained 14 000 iraqis or whatever he's
one of the guys they would just most admit well i will kill you when i'm told to and
you're like training on how to use a weapon they're telling you i'm going to kill you
and it's just like this is insane this is what's going on and then the cultural enrichment
of chucky schumer bringing these guys into the country and then he was on the news earlier
blaming trump i mean they got a lot of nerve so we're going to find out what next shoot
and drop is straight ahead with our guest i'm alice jones news wars dot com news wars
spread the link we're not just going to have to end in the next week the brain force plush
special fifty percent off i'm going to have to end even sooner our caveman ultimate paleo
bone broth turmeric chaga mushroom meatball and and more concentrate you talk about next
level meal replacement next level compared to whey and it's great to mix with whey and
then make shakes it's incredible my son is growing like a weed using it it's bigger than
i am already 15 incredible it is amazing info wars life.com 50 off caveman but only a few
days left it's about to end and folks the globalist hate it when you do this we're the
tip of the spear because we're fearless we're bold because we understand the stakes are
too high the globalist win we're all slaves so don't thank me for what i'm doing i want
to thank you we're all in this together and when you get the great molan lobbe t-shirts
you get the great books and videos you're fighting the tip of the spear again visit
info war store.com today and commit to helping the info war now ladies and gentlemen we're
running the biggest special we've ever had for our best selling product brainforce now
brainforce plus there's 20% more in each bottle and we're now purchasing so much of it from
the major organic manufacturer here in the united states we've been able to get it for
less so i'm offering for the first time ever 50% off and i thought i could offer this for
maybe a month i'm going to have to stop this special within a week because it is blasting
out of our warehouse because the fans of it already are stocking up they know how great
it is a whole bunch of organic natural healthy known nootropics and if you want good clean
focused energy then brainforce is for you and you're supporting the broadcast at the
same time it's a good deal at 39 gets 1996 at info wars life.com or simply call toll
free triple eight two five three three one three nine not a group you develop living
defense for us it took you over a year to do it why is this so good because people are
actually waking up to the problem that pretty much scares me the most i mean i try to make
sure that i don't put toxins from food and water and beverages in my system but right
now we're dealing with massive parasites which is anything that's harmful to your body that
lives off a host mechanism right now with all the refugees spreading disease around
we have biological warfare going on everywhere these are all parasites tell us about all
the stuff i said there's so many things that are in it you have the neem in there you have
the organic clove bud the organic wormwood i recommend doing a parasite cleanse at least
twice a year all right well i'm glad we've got some back in because i'm going back on
it today it just came back in yesterday living defense info wars live.com and folks you can't
lose it's full of stuff that's great for your body period and you support the broadcast
info wars live.com thank you dr group from the global healing center thank you so much
for all your work sir on this great product america is an information-based civil war
that's why now more than ever we've got to hit the streets of america and let these globalists
scum know we're not backing down from their bullies we're only intensifying our operations
in the face of their wannabe dictatorship being a conservative a nationalist a libertarian
or simply a free speech advocate is truly the counter culture the real punk rock is
being a patriot who's pro america pro capitalism and pro freedom who at the same time is tolerant
modern liberalism is a counterfeit of thomas jefferson's classical liberalism they are
the anti-liberists who defend free speech meet like-minded friends and promote freedom
worldwide we've got more than 60 original designs of high quality t-shirts for men and
women as well as more patriot apparel at info war store.com be part of the second american
revolution at info war store.com you're listening to the alex jones show
i'm alex jones your host this is the info war and i'm not a hero i'm nobody special
i'm just a common sense guy that isn't gonna take it lying down i know you're not taking
it lying down either but all these islamists running around shooting killing stabbing and
running people over every couple days in the western world is just a symptom the cold sore
rising to the top of the underlying illness of the leftists and the globalists and what
they're doing why would europe bring in 10 million islamists unfettered 80% of military
aged men because they say at the un they want to break up the christian society the pope
says it i mean this is a globalist takeover of every institution that pope's not a catholic
and most catholics know that so this is an incredible time to be alive and the left and
antifa and george soros with full page ads the new york times say they're launching it
november 4th all over the country we're i should plug we're going to be live uh from
11 a.m until 8 p.m saturday info wars.com forward slash show on our own feeds is written
censored on facebook and twitter and youtube those stations want to pick it up they're
welcome to but it's going to be basically commercial free we'll air some breaks but
they won't be set breaks and we're going to reporters out in the field and different parts
of the country but this is a full launch and they're calling for cop killing i mean it
says right here overthrow the government and drive trump from power and they have threatened
us i mean i'm not at liberty to get into it right now because obviously there's a lot
of reasons not to but i've been given ultimatums to surrender by saturday you know when i'm
tired i get these threats i suddenly have energy and i mean i don't get why they think
these threats are going to work but i guess they work on some people uh they didn't work
on stephen gern who was reaching 40 something million people in his first video just saying
hey i've been training over here and training the muslims to defend their own countries
almost all of them want to kill us we shouldn't be here this is insane and there is no such
thing as you know a moderate uh this is a joke and then they basically kicked him out
of his contracting work leading large teams but he's here now doing great with his own
entrepreneurial operations and speaking out and not being censored and that's what it's
all about but understand the fight is now folks this is the second american revolution
they want it to be a civil war uh but uh thank you uh stephen gern you were here just a few
days ago and now another jihadi ala akbar or or our god is greater than yours attack
yeah exactly um you know obviously i was on my way to florida yesterday and got into florida
was on my way to the uh hotel and as soon as i get to the hotel i see what's happened
uh the funny thing about it is about a month and a half ago i was on the jesse waters show
and that's exactly what i said it's exact what they were doing in spain what they were
doing in eu what they were doing in france this was all how they were perfecting their
tactics so they could come here to the united states and do it now obviously we want to
talk about gun control we want to talk about all this craziness well let me tell you something
they didn't use a gun this time what he had a paint but a paint gun and a pellet gun and
i don't understand why that uh officer didn't you know shoot to kill but obviously that
that that's not my gig i'm glad that he actually didn't so now we can interrogate this individual
if we're going to even be able to interrogate them i doubt we will because there's so many
bleeding hearts out there that we're not even going to be able to properly interrogate this
individual but you know this seems to be something that it's happened here in the united states
before it's happened all over the eu and it's going to continue to happen and unless we
don't start doing what we need to do with proper vetting just like president donald
trump said in the very beginning we are going to see a lot more of this because they are
paving the road to allow this to happen in the united states and the left not accepting
what's actually happening here and the people who just don't want to accept that this is
this is not the norm i heard yesterday on fox news an individual say we need to accept
this as the norm no we don't need to accept this as the norm they accepted it as the norm
in the uk and you see what's happened to their country it cannot happen here in the united
states and it will not happen in the united states the only people who can stop that are
people like you and me who want to put a stand we want to stand and put a stop to what's
happening here if our if our officials if our elected officials aren't going to do it
we need to do it here right here on our level on the local and the state levels absolutely
and almost all these guys are inbred they wear these these women's nightgowns they just
wander around on welfare all day and then they just tell us how they're elite and we're
scum and then kill us and we're supposed to bow down to this guy who brought in 28 of
his rat-like family it's unbelievable and what's happening they're being attached to
a visa program this is this is what it all comes down to again here we are with the vetting
they're coming in on a visa a program which is like a lottery is what they call it the
lottery and it's and it's and it's bs it's complete and you know what it is it's like
logan's run it's a death lottery for us and like you said khan the islamist mayor of london
keeps saying get used to it get used to it accepted don't even put it in the news they
want us to accept them coming in and us bowing to them and then murdering us exactly there
is no acceptance of this it's just like you know in in islam and sharia law there is no
acceptance there is no tolerance there you're either sharia compliant or you're not sharia
compliant and you're either in submission to their god because as they point out you
know arabic brother 9 he didn't say Allah Akbar he said our god is greater what's the
difference well Allah Akbar it means you know god is great but but usually what you'll see
is they'll see you'll see people coming up and they're doing the whole number one sign
it's not a number one sign what he's doing is pointing up to Allah that Allah is the
greatest and that and that's exactly what it is and that's their thought process he
was what we would call sharia compliant and and we were talking about this as a matter
of fact that jesse water show he had said something to me and i wanted to go ahead and
clarify it if you are sharia compliant okay if you are sharia compliant muslim this is
what you want to do this is jihad what he did is committed jihad and that is how they
win that is that is like the the lottery for them to commit jihad that is the ultimate
so that's what he has done he committed jihad and that's where we are right now this this
is what's happening and we sure what do you make from your sources and we've got our sources
but it's them they say they're going to launch all sorts of hell come this saturday and we're
already seeing i think this is a tremor for more of this kind of comes we see islamists
and isis coordinating with the black lives matter uh and and with the antifa yeah and
this is what we were talking about you know earlier about the marxist movement this is
this is two groups or three groups of people one on one side one on the other side moving
parallel against what we believe in against our constitution try and destroy our constitution
our constitution is the longest lasting constitution in the world and we must maintain that we
must continue to fight for it and the people who don't want to do it like like antifa you
know i don't think the islamic state has anything to do with what antifa in in black lives matter
is but they are able to piggyback off of what is happening and you got your george right
because all the groups think they're going to end up in charge so the the the enemy of
my enemies my friend another islamic sting you're exactly right and that's all they're
doing they're piggybacking off it they're seeing that what they're doing is actually
creating these you know ripples in the water as you can see and they're piggybacking off
it and this is a huge problem so it isn't just about stopping the muslim brotherhood
antifa black lives matter and you know islamic state we need to stop them all we need to
stop them all and we need to have solid policies to do it and you know i'm not even worried
about policies at this point you know i said something about you know the uh this the the
suit wearing jihadas versus the pajama wearing behind his g jihadas we got to worry about
them all but and that's the thing they know they have missions they know they're committed
they admit it and and and so we have to be just as committed to stop playing games people
think oh that's a bunch of work no we have to have purpose-driven lives ladies and gentlemen
like our ancestors did this is the animating contest of liberty this is what let me guess
i bet you're even happier after 20 years overseas uh now you're really home in the real republic
in the homeland when the fight's key i mean i mean let me guess are you happier now back
home even with them persecuting you standing up for what's right you want to know what
at least over there i knew who my enemy was i knew exactly who it was i knew exactly what
i needed to do here the lines are so blurry and every time you turn around you call somebody
islamic terrorist or you say that it was terrorism or you say muslim or anything like that you're
the one who's persecuted for it no i understand it's harder in some ways because it's just
the fog of of complexity and war uh geopolitical war political war but i'm saying is it fulfilling
to now be reaching tens of millions of people every week though it is it's very it's very
fulfilling i hope i can reach a lot more people and you know this is just it's just the start
and it shouldn't be the start we should never have got to the point where we are but the
point but we're now awake stay right there we're gonna come right back with stephen gern
who predicted these attacks great patriot before i go any further and we're gonna co-host
some with him and roger stone coming up i gotta plug one minute an hour without you
we're not here so whether it's t-shirts or water filters or non-gmo heirloom seeds or
high quality organic coffee it's great it's all there sign up for auto ship additional
10 off free shipping and info war store.com on order for the dollars or more dna force
is back in stock a great probiotic bomb defense 25 off of that as well back in stock a bunch
of specials do end today i want to thank you all for your support we could not do it without
you but we need continued support so i don't want to just stay at the same size under attack
i want to dominate i want to grow i want to give my full exertion against the globalists
we are winning but they are launching counter-offensives right now stay with us
support good oral health with our one-of-a-kind super blue fluoride free products info wars
life brings you a revolutionary toothpaste blend with iodine and nano silver designed
to deliver a powerful clean enjoy a minty fresh flavor made with peppermint oil or try
our bubble gum flavor pair this groundbreaking toothpaste with the super blue fluoride free
mouthwash and supercharge your oral health our amazing mouthwash features natural oils
and ancient ingredients used since aboriginal and biblical times instead of containing fluoride
our super blue line is loaded with the good halogen iodine and an array of other beneficial
compounds that have been hand selected for their oral health benefits super blue fluoride
free mouthwash and toothpaste are the first and only to contain all of these natural ingredients
xylitol nano silver and iodine notice the difference with our super blue fluoride free
products refresh your breath and invigorate your oral health routine at infowarsstore.com
that's infowarsstore.com you deserve a deep restful sleep with knockout
by infowars life our organic formula is made from high quality natural ingredients such
as valerian root extract, el tryptophan, lemon balm leaf extract and melatonin knockout packs
a powerful punch to get you through the night and achieve proper sleep millions of people
around the world experience daytime drowsiness but with the rapid speed of life we need to
be able to keep up the pace our natural mixture harnesses the power of 10 known ingredients to
let your body relax and get the sleep you need wake up refreshed and take on the day info wars
life wants to bring you a sleep support formula that goes above and beyond other leading brands
at an affordable price get the sleep you deserve and experience the power of knockout head on over
to infowarslife.com and say goodbye to fatigue that's infowarslife.com you're listening to the
Alex Jones show and the resistance is in your mind to Hollywood the globalist all of it and
for all my foibles I am passionate I am upset I am angry I'm territorial I've studied history
and I see we're being conquered by a bunch of globalist opportunists but I see Hollywood their
whole system falling apart but I wonder how do they think they're gonna bring in millions
I mean there's just Muslim refugees all over Austin they weren't here five years ago it's just
everywhere New York London you think it's like an Islamic city and then my thing is they're rude
to you they're mad at you once they become the dominant group they're not accepting they kill
gay people they enslave women and you're not supposed to say that then the left-soul Jake
Tapper you know said oh beautiful God is greater God is great it's so beautiful when that when it
was reported that the guy was screaming Allah Akbar I already played the clip five times I'm
gonna play it again and it's like what a sick freak but no he thinks that's his muscle they
see Jake Tapper is a psychopath he takes us being nice as weak he sees Muslims willing to kill
people as strong he wants to cozy up as a sycophantic piece of crap am I accurate in
saying that or is that a is that an over oversimplification mr. mr. Gern no I think you're
accurate in saying it you know really what I'm what I'm seeing here is you know people people
think that oh these guys are doing what's right and what they're supposed to be doing what they're
supposed to be doing well in a way you know in the in Islam they are doing exactly what they're
supposed to be doing for this guy to say it was beautiful and and I really I really don't get it
and that's really what I'm what I'm having a hard time with now is that people like this individual
are accepting of what's happening here we saw what happened in the EU we see what's happening
all over in the UK there's no talking point accept it and say it's beautiful as a good cuck
Stockholm syndrome person like Tapper I know I heard it last night and I just yeah I guess I
guess so mad it was in it was unbelievable to hear somebody say this is we need to accept this
as the norm accept this as a norm no this isn't the norm and this isn't what we need to be accepting
at all not one bit we are America and we believe in our rights we believe in our Constitution and
we need a hold to it and anybody who doesn't believe in that I'm sorry to say but you need
to go someplace else because that's not the way it runs here in the United States and Stephen
Gern it's a formula they're trying to get us like Sweden to go under mass Stockholm syndrome they
know what they're doing if they can get us to accept Muslims murdering us with enjoyment with
knives guns and trucks then I guess we'll put up with anything and that's like namble is out
saying give us your kids now yeah it is and again you know here we are if we're not if we're not
willing to fight then we will fall that's all there is to it if we're not willing to fight well
I want to fight what do I do I'm trying as hard as I can to spread the word what else can I do
because I mean I'll be honest with you sometimes I just I just I just can't put much more you know
what this is this is what I think okay first of all I think we need to go to our local law
enforcement our local state our local councils and we need to start informing them we need it
we need to inform them we need to get them educated on what the threat is there's a company
actually it's an organization called understanding the threat and they are 100% dedicated to and
Frank Gaffney with the Center of Security Policy let's get him on yeah absolutely is dedicated to
informing people of what this threat is and what they're capable of and how they're infiltrating
us in the United States and yes what we saw yesterday was a act of jihad although how we
allowing this to happen is because we are losing on a lot of fronts when it comes to the pull it is
that I won't say the political but the the policy side of the house because you have people like
we're not people but organizations like the Muslim Brotherhood who have infiltrated our government
you know this is a short segment stay there do one more with us and Roger Stone's joining us
because I want you to come in it's been like five minutes on understanding the threat because I was
even you know a tolerant guy I was never pro-islam but I I still bought into some of the let's be
nice stuff maybe they'll listen that's that's just taking his weakness folks and sure you got
Muslims that are slave to other Muslims who mean well and aren't bad people but any practicing
Sharia compliant person you're gonna submit or they're gonna kill you and they're just waiting
to do it you go to info war store comm and get game-changing amazing products leave it sold out
of DNA force for almost four months these ingredients are nutraceutical grade you have
the highest quality the bio PQQ all of it it's 25% off the truck got in this morning and it's
back but it is a limited run because of all the testing and all the rest of it is the highest
quality read about what it'll do for you and your family it is amazing we also have been sold out
for three months on biome defense super high quality probiotic it's 25% off out of the gates
back in stock but for a very limited time so you get the highest quality the very cleanest stuff
out there we're really really proud of it DNA force and bomb defense probiotic now back in
stock info wars live comm when you buy products from globalist it's an act of trading with the
enemy it is an act of war it is an act of standing up when you spread the links the articles and buy
products from us and when we commit to rampage against the enemy totally waging war on corruption
it's Alex Stephen Gern decorated marine and she called paramilitary with the company doing
different operations all over the world is our guests and in comes Trump he says we're gonna
ban folks from these seven countries they don't have real passports the media freaks out and then
it's Chucky Schumer and Obama's program that brings in a guy and 28 of his family to be put
on welfare and walk around his diaper outfit all day bitching at everybody and then killing a bunch
of people and the media tries to cover up this Islamic attackers the New York Times today mile
long Manhattan truck attack kills a not an Islamic Isis attack kills a using truck no no it's a truck
attack then right beside it rise up overthrow Trump a full-page ad in the same section Wow
funded by George Soros who brings in the Islamic system Wow so finishing up you were getting into
what do we do I agree we've got to go out and speak out we've got to go out to city councils
everywhere and say the politically incorrect things to break their will they want to scare
everybody else they're not having free speech we have to exercise it up front so that others who
are more timid have the courage this is an information war so recap what you were saying
Stephen Gern what I'm saying is in order for us to fight this we need to be able we're not going
to be able to do it on the big government level it's just not gonna happen because they don't want
to accept it what we need to do is we need to go to our local law enforcement our local magistrates
where our local councils and so on and so forth our local churches we need to go out there and we
need to educate these people the people who don't want to be educated people don't want to accept
what we have to say we don't waste time on there's no reason to waste time on them I'm not gonna beg
somebody to understand what's happening here I'm gonna point out the things that are actually
effective and how we can do to stop this you know penetrating force that we currently have and by
doing that you're gonna be able to bring on you basically you're putting together an army in in
understanding the threat understanding what exactly is going on here in the United States
and until we understand that until we educate the the the younger generations until we you
know educate ourselves to understand what Islam is what you know Islamic law is all about and
what they're asking us or telling us or making us do we can't if we don't identify this threat how
can you fight it the first thing you do in any war is identify your threat and we're not identifying
it we're still not the Obama Obama he never identified it and just so you just said right
there they didn't identify the threat they said it was a truck that drove through negative it
wasn't a truck that drove through it was an Islamic terrorist act that's what it was it was
an act of jihadism and if you want to know who's in charge it's who you can't criticize to think
about this to see the persecution of people that talk about it when the biggest victims of Islam
are the people living in Islamic countries spend a minute on that and all the countries you've
been in how these people live how women are treated well it's unbelievable I mean those
few women is they don't even exist okay I mean I remember going over there you know my very first
time and the women are in the back of the trucks while the men are driving in the front and they're
out there you know doing everything so the women it doesn't exist at all there is no women's rights
whatsoever so anybody who believes that there is there's just not it doesn't matter they kill each
other in mass numbers in mass numbers they talk about you know what what America has done just
look at what happens in Iraq every day in Baghdad you know vehicle bombs going off killing a hundred
people it's the norm it's the normal over there and it can't be the norm here and that's the
problem is people aren't seeing that the people are just evil they don't care about anything and
maybe the reason why this this group of people are killed because they were Sunni and they were
in Shia or this Shia is killing a Sunni it just it's not ever gonna end I mean they're gonna kill
each other and they're definitely gonna kill us because and why would we export tens of millions
from the very worst poorest backwards bloodbath countries of inbred insanity why what is the end
game I can't figure out what the end game is I'm trying to figure that out in such a way just it
baffles me that the left hates America and hates Christianity and is ugly and they and it's a form
of cucking they want just like devil worshipers want to sacrifice a child to be bad this is just
an act of nastiness you're right it is I mean it just seems like the left is all about destroying
everything that we're about whether it's Christianity whether it's you know you know the
the Constitution whatever it is it's just they want anarchy it doesn't make any sense and again
if we don't if we don't educate ourselves we don't educate their generations and work with people to
understand what we're facing we are going to lose this fight we cannot lose this fight I just I see
like you said CNN MSNBC even Fox News saying it's the new norm relax let's just not talk about it
but when some scumbag lunatic white terrorists those and kills poor innocent black people nine
of them every white person was the blame every southerner was a blame every Christian was the
blame and I went wait a minute we're a diverse group we're not to blame for him but I decry
what he did but when Islam does it Oh Islam's not involved when you said he was following exactly
what Muhammad said to do exactly and again we go back to identifying our threat if we don't
identify it which we won't I mean okay so you know we have a guy who went in there into a black
church and he goes and kills a bunch of people okay what did we do what did we say we said oh
well he's a racist and you know the Confederate flag is a racism flag so we're gonna get rid of
all the Confederate flags now we're gonna get rid of all the statues we're getting rid so okay now
he killed him with a with a truck so are we gonna go band all the trucks now is that what the
Democrats gonna do we're gonna go band all the trucks that are being rented no they don't want
to identify the actual threat the threat that it was is the person and the disease the disease
ideology it's not an ideology it is what they believe it is 100% what they believe Islam is
Islam there is no you know it's not a sub ideology that's what I meant is it's the political Islam
it is it is the conquering cancerous Orthodox Islam yeah it's what they're trying to get us
to accept but you know I I'm having a hard time accepting it myself so well here's the deal we
can't let this continue and we can't lose our rights while we would then won't even profile
people do you know five years ago the FBI tried to arrest him Obama wouldn't just like San
Bernardino the FBI agents that investigated those guys two years before were under criminal
investigation for civil rights violation Obama's Justice Department tried to put FBI and federal
marshals in jail for investigating the San Bernardino shooters two years before they should
have gotten medals exactly they should have and again what it comes back to is it comes back to
you if you identify somebody who you think may not be right and you expose that person what happens
you get beat up for it you get called a racist you get called a bigot and that's the thing and
that's why I said on the other show if you see something that's not right if you don't say
something all you're doing is allowing this to happen it's for me if I see something that's not
right you know what if they're gonna call me a name because of it if it prevents a terrorist
attack then then that's what I'm gonna go ahead and again the terror attacks are bad we're sorry
for those that died but again there's the overarching drive politically of why is this
being done what's going on and then you look at Hollywood and all their hate of just anything good
it's just degeneracy all right my friend facebook.com forward slash steven dot g e r n steven
gurne thank you so much we look forward to having you back on very soon all right thank you
appreciate it alex hope you have a good day you bet yeah that guy has hundreds of millions of
views on his videos and you know 6,000 followers on twitter a lot more folks need to follow that
now roger stones hosting the balance of the hour and then he's gonna be hosting into the war room
in studio with owen schroyer uh so roger stone tell us what you got coming up well alex we're
going to talk about what has been learned from the jfk documents we exclusively broke here at
info wars the president's bold and courageous decision to release the classified documents
pertaining to the murder of president john f kennedy we're going to talk about the tug of war
with the intelligence services and their efforts to mount a rear guard action and cover up through
censorship the guts of those and it'll all be here on the alex jones show and then the war room with
roger stone stay with us info wars.com news wars.com i know i keep saying it but it's the
truth we're under attack our only hope is that you spread the word but here's the secret we're
your hope as well we're in this together stay with us want revenge on the common house fly
well after 10,000 years someone has finally come up with a better way the bug assault a
miniaturized shotgun which utilizes ordinary table salt as ammunition non-toxic and no
batteries required $39.95 plus shipping and handling use discount code gcn and receive 15%
off your purchase at bug assault.com fire your flyswatter and get your bug assault today fully
cooked ready to eat bacon i'm talking thick meaty center cut presidential bacon savory
and delicious i buy some i use some i store some awesome no refrigeration needed with a
10-year shelf life nasa pack technology bacon fully cooked fully hydrated ready to eat right
from the pack bacon or warm and served life-saving ready to eat bacon 10-year shelf life bacon ships
free at fullycookedbacon.com fullycookedbacon.com water is the single most important thing your
body needs so you want to be sure it's the best for you and your family since 2005 thousands have
depended on berkey purified water the berkey guy provides the lowest price filtration systems in
every size for incredibly delicious water now and in an emergency get to goberky.com or call
877-886-3653 877-886-3653 goberky.com hunters anglers campers and survivalists get back to
nature expand your horizons with the highest quality most versatile unique slingshots and
sling bows on the market at slingbow.com sling bow products are compact and models start from
just 1798 they're perfect for your bug out bag or storing in your vehicle give yourself and your
loved ones the excitement and tradition of sling bow a new frontier in archery and truly modern
twist on this primitive survival tool feel the thrill only at slingbow.com
choose to take control of your chemistry with survival shield x2 and bio true selenium this
powerful combo is perfect for supporting your thyroid and health bio true seleniums formula
is far from synthetic and is made from a source of 100% organic mustard seed our super high quality
nascent iodine is an essential mineral sourced of 99.99% ultra pure deep earth iodine crystals
this essential mineral is necessary in order to produce thyroid hormones which influence every
cell tissue and organ in the body with inadequate thyroid hormones you may experience slow metabolism
lethargy weight gain and overall brain fog survival shield x2 and bio true selenium work
together to support the systems in your body take control of your chemistry today with this super
combo discover the power of survival shield x2 and bio true selenium at infowarslife.com
we're not just going to have to end in the next week the brain force plus special 50%
off i'm gonna have to end even sooner our caveman ultimate paleo bone broth tumeric chaga mushroom
bee pollen and more concentrate you talk about next level meal replacement next level compared
to whey and it's great to mix with whey and then make shakes it's incredible my son is growing like
a weed using it it's bigger than i am already 15 incredible it is amazing infowarslife.com
50% off caveman but only a few days left it's about to end and folks the globalist hate it
when you do this we're the tip of the spear because we're fearless we're bold because we
understand the stakes are too high the globalist win we're all slaves so don't thank me for what
i'm doing i want to thank you we're all in this together and when you get the great molan lobby
t-shirts you get the great books and videos you're finding the tip of the spear again
visit info war store.com today and commit to helping the info war
you're listening to the alex jones show
i wish your buck was still silver i wish your buck was still silver it was back
back when the country was wrong back before elvis
back before elvis and before vietnam war came along
before the beatles and yesterday
when a man could still work still would
hard to turn merle haggard off isn't it it's the best of the free line hard to believe
2017 is the year he died so many people we lost this year trailing over stop rolling downhill
and i went rolling downhill like a snowball headed for hell well let me tell you that's
finally turned around the pendulum swinging back with no kind of chance for the flag
i'm gonna hand the baton to rogers he's gonna be on for hours coming up with that one schroyer
he has so much to get to i wish that if i was up here saying we're the heart of the rebellion
we're the tip of the spear you're the resistance we're changing the world if it wasn't true it'd
be comical when i sit back and i realize it's not talk it's not even a good feeling it's it's like a
sickening feeling but sickening in a good way like it's so epic so real so timeless so big
that you can feel the victory you can see the finishing line but you know it's going to take
everything you got to claw across it but then you look back at tyranny and other nations that
have fallen and who wants to conquer us a bunch of devil worship and pedophiles i don't just say
that that's who they are and you're like i need more energy to beat these people it's the opposite
of feeling strong or confident it's feeling like we need to get more strength we need everything
to defeat these people that's my frustration it isn't fear when they come after me of what
they'll do to me it's fear that i'm too weak i mean when you think about these pedophiles we're
up against ladies and gentlemen you think about the scum of the earth we're fighting i mean that's
who they are they've organized these forces globally and how bad they are and what they're
doing to us and you realize we have a chance to break their will they want to break our will
that's why i'm telling you when you share the articles the videos the links
we're seeing more censorship the last few months than we saw 10 years before
and soon i'll be able to reveal to you the stuff they're doing behind the scenes but
strategically we're not revealing it yet but they already tried to destroy my life and my family and
i'm not complaining i told everybody i'm asking for it i'm willing to do it i just need you to
know that it's not just you're watching alex jones or roger stone when you pray for us number one
providence when you spread the links the articles the videos the material and talk to people
in person when you go down to city council or other places that speak out where they can't
censor you or at the soapbox or the church in the third dimension not just online it moves the world
and gets more lemmings out of their trance now is the time of awakening and when you financially
support us and just commit to do it sign up for auto ship on whatever products it is that you need
to reorder whether it's coffee or supplements or you know whatever it changes the world and
i'm coming to you because it's like a man calling for a glass of wine before he fights or whatever
like they just say it's not even out of courage you do it it's out of your tool of life you know
you're so awake and you just want to ensure that you're not overconfident and that you've got what
it needs because in this war like any war money is king and so just go buy the supplements buy
the books buy the videos buy it all buy it aggressively put bumper stickers up get aggressive
start your own show do your own thing i'll have you on i want to win i want to get these people
off our backs look we didn't start this fight but man i'm not taking it lying down and i will
defeat them i will defeat john podesta i will defeat hillary clinton i will defeat hillary
all her minions and and and and soros and all of them it's not like we're in business fighting
with each other over a contract these people want to literally erase the renaissance they are a bunch
of scum who are threatened by freedom and i will not bow to them and their inbred hordes of of
islamicists they're bringing in i will not bow and i'm getting ready to go flame throwing just
and i don't see that in a position of like oh i'm about to get even tougher i know how times are
seasons are now is the time for all of us politically to really turn it loose and really
give them our full fight roger stones the next couple hours is hosting right into war room coming
up roger thanks for letting me jump in here but listeners please support us today make the
commitment or we're already going to have great victory into the future off of all the things
we've done and i and i know we're going to win but i want to win handily and it's so easy if you
commit to buy the products we will expand we won't just continue on we will expand we will be
victorious roger go ahead sorry for taking over alex uh many thanks you know i think it was nisi
that said that which does not kill me makes me stronger i agree with alex jones do the lefties
not understand that these personal attacks on us these threats to kill my wife my family my
children and perhaps worst of all my beloved dogs this only makes me angrier and stronger and more
firm in my resolve to expose the globalists to expose the globalists and expose uh those
who would destroy the foundations and principles of america cbs has a little film that they put up
let's show that uh because it shows you um how vicious the attack has become
so he's been fed and he's really great
we're having some technical difficulties we're doing two studios between each other today but
that's okay it's live it's worldwide and we're going to break here in a minute so we'll probably
come back over there but for radio listeners we can go over some of this for people uh and and
and just break down how savage and how vicious they've gotten how long is this clip guys and
then i can introduce it to you and we can come back to it after the break we'll come back to it
after the break uh coming up we're going to take your calls so i want to point out uh 888-201-2244
we're going to be taking them both in the balance of the alex jones show we're going to be taking
them in the war room as well this is my favorite part of being on info wars because so many people
as i move around ask me why don't you take more calls they like the interactive nature of what
we do here and we like to hear from patriots we want to hear what's on your mind and while you're
at it i want to say one more time brain force at an extraordinary discount right now on the
info wars dot com store i was up all night last night folks in washington dc doing high level
meetings to try to get a grip on what the globalists have in mind for their our president
and without uh brain force i would be unable literally to do this broadcast and by the way
roger discount you got the intel coming up that they plan to remove trump by december i forgot
to bring that up and he's got that cbs clip coming up to roger stone straight ahead stay with us
we are on the march the empire is on the run you're listening to the alex jones show
hello mr anderson the nsa has noticed how much time you spend on conservative news sites
we have no choice but to consider you a domestic terrorist tired of your internet activity being
monitored by big brother get virtual shield.com the world's easiest to use virtual private
network browse the web anonymously leaving pesky advertisers and spies in the dust get started
today at virtual shield.com take advantage of our free 30-day trial virtual shield.com you have the
right to remain private it's a no-brainer a big berkey water filter is the one you need period
you need a water filter that removes chlorine fluoride pharmaceuticals bpa and other endocrine
disruptors pesticides bacteria viruses and much more right and does it all at only two cents per
gallon get the original most trusted name in gravity water filtration big berkey and now
gcn listeners receive five percent off ceramic filter systems using code gcn call or click
one eight seven seven nine nine berkey or big berkey water filters dot com that's one eight
seven seven nine nine b-e-r-k-e-y america is an information-based civil war that's why now more
than ever we've got to hit the streets of america and let these globalists scum know we're not
backing down from their bullies we're only intensifying our operations in the face of their
wannabe dictatorship being conservative a nationalist a libertarian or simply a free
speech advocate is truly the counter culture the real punk rock is being a patriot who's pro america
pro capitalism and pro freedom who at the same time is tolerant modern liberalism is a counterfeit of
thomas deverson's classical liberalism they are the anti-liberalists to defend free speech meet
like-minded friends and promote freedom worldwide we've got more than 60 original designs of high
quality t-shirts for men and women as well as more patriot apparel at info war store.com
be part of the second american revolution at info war store.com we've taken thousands of years of
known research and put it together with our own four years of seeking and testing to find the
very best systems that god gave us through mother nature to detoxify the body that's why i'm
introducing z shield toxic metal and chemical defense support it's made in the usa it's filled
with known compounds from nature that are absolutely associated with detoxifying the body
and it supports the info war it is a classical 360 win this is the formula that i personally
have been taking for over a year and now we believe we have come as close to perfection
when it comes to a detoxifier as you can possibly get you owe it to yourself you owe it to your
family and you owe it to the future of this country in the world that patriots stay as
healthy and as clean and as focused as you can be because we need you the remnant of america
to reignite those brushfires the next level and to be healthy and as focused as you can be thanks
to your support and your prayers together we're changing the world now it's time to change our
bodies with z shield info wars live.com you go to info war store.com and get game-changing amazing
products we've been sold out of dna force for almost four months these ingredients are
nutraceutical grade you have the highest quality the bio pqq all of it it's 25 off the truck got
in this morning and it's back but it is a limited run because of all the testing and all the rest
of it it's the highest quality read about what it'll do for you and your family it is amazing
we also have been sold out for three months on biome defense super high quality probiotic it's
25 off out of the gates back in stock but for a very limited time so you get the highest quality
the very cleanest stuff out there we're really really proud of it dna force and biome defense
probiotic now back in stock info wars live.com when you buy products from globalist it's an
act of trading with the enemy it is an act of war it is an act of standing up when you spread
the links the articles and buy products from us and when we commit to rampage against the enemy
totally you're listening to the alex jones show
took you live
welcome back i am roger stone sitting in for my compatriot alex jones i'm a proud member of the
info wars team and it was here on info wars that it was revealed to the world that president
donald trump would declassify the controversial still secret and closely held john f kennedy
assassination records you see in 1992 the congress in the wake of the impact of oliver stone's
monumental film jfk passed legislation that set specific timelines for the release of this
bombshell data even in the initial releases in the 80s and 90s the deep state the military industrial
complex indeed those responsible for the murder of president kennedy managed to redact and censor
and hold back much of the data when i spoke to the president of the united states two thursdays ago
only two days before his historic tweet announcing that he would release this classified information
he was most interested in transparency he was most interested in full disclosure
and as i predicted the deep state the central intelligence agency principally caught by surprise
had to move into high gear on a rear guard action to redact that means black out sensor and hold
back as much of the data as possible hoping that the american people would learn little and that
their myth that lee harvey oswald a communist nut acting alone shot president john fitzgerald
kennedy three times from the back unfortunately now thanks to president trump's courageous and
bold decision that narrative hasn't held up what have we learned well one paragraph that was
brought to the fore in this release shows that the surgeon general of the united states concluded
that john kennedy had been shot from the front and that the bullet entered at the at the neck
at the trachea which is why a tracheotomy was hastily performed on him to hide that entry
wound big problem for the government what else did we learn well we learned that the russian
kgb conducted their own independent investigation into john kennedy's murder and they determined
that linden baynes johnson lbj himself old big ears was the man who orchestrated the death of
his predecessor you see linden johnson knew that the tennedy justice department was hot on his
heels in both the bobby baker and billy sol estes corruption investigations and he knew that
attorney general robert kennedy wanted him not only off the 1964 ticket but he also want him
want him in a federal presidential a federal penitentiary yes lbj was the man staring into
the abyss we also learned in the new disclosures that french intelligence at the request of first
lady jacqueline kennedy conducted their own investigation and they determined that linden
baynes johnson was the ringleader of the plot to kill our president what else did we learn well we
learned that linden johnson as a young congressman in his early political career was a member of the
ku klux klan that puts him up there with senator robert bird of west virginia no wonder they wanted
this information withheld and kept from the american people after all linden johnson who
a styles himself the civil rights president even though in his years in the senate he blocked every
major piece of voting rights housing rights or civil rights legislation was reinventing himself
for the uh for the consumption of the american voters lbj a member of the kkk we also learned
that the government was aware of two witnesses who saw two men running from the site of the murder of
the dallas police officer j d tippett and that neither one of those men met the physical
description of lee harvey oswald we also learned that the casings found on the ground at the site
of oswald's alleged shooting of tippett were from an automatic weapon yet when lee harvey oswald
is arrested at the texas movie theater only minutes later he's found with a revolver
so more and more information coming to the fore from president donald trump's historic decision
next up is going to be an examination of the incendiary diaries of the legendary cia agent
and agent provocateur e howard hunt it was infowars and alex jones who broke the story
of the deathbed confessions of hunt who said and told infowars that he he was on the ground
on the ground in dallas that the operation in delhi plaza was indeed a cia operation
that general edwin landsdale of the cia was present and yes my favorite
lbj he said was running the show we'll have more on that in infowars down the road now uh we are
going to be taking your calls here shortly again the number eight eight eight two oh one two two
four four but before we get to that i want to mention something that alex jones pointed out
we don't have wealthy billionaires standing in the wings ready to write giant checks to underwrite
our fight against the globalists we don't have a george soros or a rockefeller foundation or a
ford foundation or any of these extremely well-heeled operations we have to depend on
you and we can only depend on you that's why it's crucial you go to the infowars.com store
where silver bullet uh the incredible collidal silver uh product is now on sale for 50 percent
off i don't know how alex jones slashes these prices and does it successfully i guess it means
we can move more product more volume but that is what is paying for this beautiful new studio that
is what's paying for our expanded programming on the war room it's only because patriots like you
have stepped forward and gotten some of the very best all-natural products you can find anywhere
in the market today but when you help yourself you help us now i particularly like the t-shirts
the first amendment oriented t-shirts and let me say this when i speak around the country when i
spoke in salt lake city this weekend at least three people showed up wearing their their classic
bill clinton rape t-shirts now this t-shirt is still available at the infowars.com store but not
for much longer this piece is going to end up in the smithsonian folks get it while you can when
these run out there will be no more and i want to see them out there as i travel the country and i
speak because it's a way of identifying like-minded patriots so folks go to the infowars.com store
give us your support we will give you the truth we will continue to expose the upcoming coup d'etat
against our president donald trump i've been to washington i know what they have planned stay with
stay with us we're going to be laying it all out for you on the alex jones show and later at the war room
now ladies and gentlemen we're running the biggest special we've ever had for our best-selling
product brainforce now brainforce plus there's 20 more in each bottle and we're now purchasing
so much of it from the major organic manufacturer here in the united states that we've been able to
get it for less so i'm offering for the first time ever 50 percent off and i thought i could
offer this for maybe a month i'm going to have to stop this special within a week because it is
blasting out of our warehouse because the fans of it already are stocking up they know how great it
is a whole bunch of organic natural healthy known nootropics and if you want good clean focused
energy then brainforce is for you and you're supporting the broadcast at the same time it's
a good deal at 39 it's 19.96 at infowarslife.com or simply call toll-free triple 8-253-3139
enjoy all natural bath and beauty products with emmerich's essentials we are proud to bring you
a collection of organic-based household products at info war store.com including non-nano spf 30
zinc oxide sunscreen date-free herbal bug spray concentrated peppermint mouthwash unscented body
wash tea tree shampoo and long-lasting natural deodorant emmerich's essentials is free of
chemicals and toxins that may harm your body we carefully select pure and simple ingredients to
create formulas that are certified usda made with organic our mission is to offer you everyday
organic household products to enhance your life truly feel the difference by going organic natural
without compromising on quality feel good about using emmerich's essentials start saving money
and stop exposing yourself and your family to toxic ingredients visit infowarsstore.com
and learn more about the new emmerich's essentials line of organic products that's infowarsstore.com
we're not just going to have to end the next week the brain force plus special 50 off i'm
going to have to end even sooner our caveman ultimate paleo bone broth tumeric chaga mushroom
meatball and more concentrate you talk about next level meal replacement next level compared to whey
and it's great to mix with whey and then make shakes it's incredible my son is growing like
a weed using it it's bigger than i am already 15 incredible it is amazing infowarslife.com
50 off caveman but only a few days left it's about to end and folks the globalists hate it
when you do this we're the tip of the spear because we're fearless we're bold because we
understand the stakes are too high the globalists win we're all slaves so don't thank me for what
i'm doing i want to thank you we're all in this together and when you get the great molan labe
t-shirt you get the great books and videos you're finding the tip of the spear again
visit infowarsstore.com today and commit to helping the info war
men give your body the support it needs with info wars life prostaguard it's time to start assisting
the body and regulating proper prostate balance info wars life has set out to bring you formulations
that are not only the highest quality out there but formulas that you can use on a daily basis
to give your body the natural herbs and extracts that our experts recommend the prostaguard formula
does just that with its mixture of plant-based nutrients and antioxidants that help give your
body total support it's a hand-selected blend of saw palmetto lycopene plant sterols zinc vitamin
d3 selenium and copper prostaguard is something that the men on the info wars crew take every day
and from our research it's something that men should really be adding to their daily regimen
in order to keep their body going at optimal levels now is the time to start naturally
supporting your body get prostaguard on your side today exclusively at infowarslife.com
that's infowarslife.com
you're listening to the alex jones show
and here we go
i'm roger stone sitting in for my compatriot and comrade alex jones we're in the foxhole together
you know in a war against the globalists make no bones about it those who opposed
donald trump in the last election those who thought his election incredibly improbable
are committed to removing him from public office but we here at infowars we're not going to let
that happen when i attacked that dainty little snowflake don lemon on my twitter feed little did
i know that the twitter feed uber sensors would use that to close down my 300 000 follower twitter
feed now the folks at at stone cold truth on twitter still follow my exploits and although
i don't control that site you can keep up with my activities if you go there and you can also catch
up with what i'm doing on the infowars twitter feed so i invite you to go to both and there's
a petition up at stone cold truth to the twitter mavens demanding the improbable reinstatement i
will see these folks in court you see it's time for twitter to be regulated like a utility and
we will push until our first amendment rights are protected now let's go to your phone calls
my favorite part of the show robert in washington what's on your mind
roger how are you today terrific so my thing is and i see what's going on with november 4th
i've been trying to tell a lot of my friends and family prepare for something worst case
scenario something doesn't happen what if this is just another way to discredit the alt media
you guys prepare for something big nothing happens they come back and say ha look at another
you know lie that they tried to portray on the news and get everybody to believe
well i must tell you i think that is unlikely because what i found out yesterday is that this
agate prop that they have planned for the streets that they are ginning up with their tom styer
paid for tv commercials with their soros financed full-page newspaper ads that's just one part of
the plot this is a part and parcel of an effort to try to invoke the 25th amendment now under the
25th amendment of the constitution if a majority of the cabinet and the vice president decide
that the president is non-compass mentis that he is no longer mentally stable and able to fulfill
the duties of his office he shall be removed now the president can appeal that question to the u.s
house of representatives but why do we think the rhinos who control the house republican caucus
would be of a mind to keep donald trump in place we're going to be outlining this whole
nefarious plot this week on info wars but i see a political synergy here where the street operations
paid for by styer and soros and others jibe with the maneuverings of jeb bush and ben sass and
jeb bush and ben sass and others in washington who are attempting to engineer this uh this 25th
amendment coup i can report definitively here on info wars private meetings between senator sass
and vice president pence very very recently what was that meeting about senator let's go
to uh deborah in california deborah what's your question for info wars today my question is um
isn't it almost treason to put out that ad in the new york times that said we're trying to take the
government down well that's the great thing about our constitution and the first amendment although
they don't respect it at twitter we do respect it here at info wars you see i'm against censorship
i don't care if you're the looniest most whacked out left-winger in the world other than uh physical
threats of violence threats to kill my wife and my family and my dogs uh pretty much everything
else in my view is fairly protected speech but i do agree with you in this sense they have shown
their hand and these are interrelated operations this is not some street rabble paid for uh
by george soros they are working with members of the political establishment both republican and
democrat at the highest levels to attempt to achieve what they could not achieve at the
balance box which is the removal of our president thank you very much for your call now let's go to
uh jude in cincinnati uh jude don't bring me down what is your question i get that i bet you
so a big story that i've been um personally researching and thinking that is like it isn't
fairly covered and kind of ties everything in is really hillary's dating back when she became
secretary of state um she was taking a lot of money into her foundation from even like katar
and then when libya happened you know that whole thing with qaddafi we know you know bengazi turned
into the real story but it was really she was allowing qatar to fund rebel groups in this
country and then that broke out sort of into syria because then they were funneling those
fighters they're basically mercenaries cia is training them to syria and like the guy that
was on previously saying you know these guys they're either sharia or not they're committing
jihad a lot of these people that they were training committed jihad in syria created
this huge refugee crisis and the people that hate nationalism that really led to the nationalist
movements um that refugee crisis well you raise a good point and i guess i would say if you want
to know what's going to happen watch what happened in ukraine very carefully because uh what happened
there is that the billionaire globalist victor pinchuk paid the clinton foundation so much money
that he was allowed to mount a neo-nazi coup overturning the democratically elected government
of ukraine uh and it's interesting that their slogan uh blood and soil pops up as the slogan
allegedly of the of the antifa and ties in charlottesville coincidence i think not it is
exactly the same kind of coup that they have in mind here in the united states bill and hillary
clinton are traitors they worship the almighty dollar they are not liberals they are not
progressives they're not even globalists they are just greedy criminals and you could purchase from
them virtually anything in this case the united states government agreed to look the other way
while a violent coup was mounted against the democratically elected government of ukraine that
is what they have in mind here in the united states jude thank you for your call daniel in
alabama alabama a state that recently made major news with the rejection of senator luther strange
the hand-picked candidate of senator mitch mcconnell uh and instead uh nominated in the
republican primary judge roy moore a constitutionalist daniel what's on your mind
oh yes i just wanted to talk about the jfk files um y'all keep saying that trump's released them
off and he's only released the files associated with jfk's assassination
um well in fact i'll go a step further i would like to see the president go back uh and review
the material that was already previously released under the 1992 jfk records act which is far too
heavily readacted which means blacked out uh in my opinion i'd like to see him do with that material
what he has just ordered be done with the more recent disclosures which is get rid of the
redactions get rid of the blackings out and the president came up with a very clever and i think
smart response to his deep state handlers he's happy to withhold any information that revolves
around or regards people who are still living today that is very very very few in terms of
involvement in this data so uh yes i will be calling on the president to release it all and
the sooner the better i'm roger stone you're on the alex jones show and we'll be back for more of
your calls you're listening to the alex jones show