Alexandra Thurston color
Boy
Welcome to knowledge fight that is our official opening theme song
I love you
I will marry you
The first time
This is a show
I'm going to
Have a little discussion with my friend
Jordan here
That's me
We're off to a great
Monkey off the top
Experience podcast
Yeah I've been doing this for years
Wonk City
Country mix
So I have for the last while been a bit obsessed
With I want Alex Jones
Infowars Fame
The world has turned
That's cool.
A soap opera title
I have become more and more aware
Then I want
To do a better job of covering what he does
It's kind of like a Chris Hardwick thing
Where is the Talking Dead
Around wondering
We're all dead
But
I want to I want to I want to say this
Off the top and I don't want those
Ever
Come up as a confusion
First thing
Iron no way want Alex Jones to be taken off the air
I think what he does is
What was the number one podcast next year
His continued success
Pink wooden does borders on entertaining
And on the other side of that border is irresponsible
But at the same time
I am
Supposed to censoring things
I want people to view him in contacts
But I would never want to shut him down or say like he can't do what he does
Because
That's an easy
Attack
Slippery slope
Who's next
Say like professionally say
Dumb s***
Sure if we exactly exactly
Recorded in Summit
Is there a very foolishly on my part
If we start going after those guys
Snacks that
We like
Subscribed
Say whatever you want as long as
It's not
You know advocating violence against somebody a threat reliable
Okay
Whatever I'm going to say and whatever you're going to say I want this to be super clear
There's a big part of me that really admires Alex Jones
He is you're an insane person is an amazing broadcast
If you really take
The tricks of Broadcasting
And apply him to them
He's insanely good
Did you could not say a lot of the stuff
He does without being really good at your job
I think that's something that will come out we will see
Point where you be at
He's great
Right I admire his
Still
I don't like what he does with
Well I think that's probably going to be the central
The central Battle of this whole podcast is
You trying to prove to me that I should admire him and
I don't think so I just wanted to make a VR off the top because it's
It would be easy for anyone listening to think that this is just going to turn into a beat-up fast
NBA
I don't think people who listen to him or stupid
I don't think his fans are stupid
That's actually on the way here that's something I was thinking about where are we on the
Stupid / evil
Personally yeah
I'm not not not you
Although we're probably more on the evil side
Most of the evil things I've done in my life have been
Accidents
Let's today you're not a premeditated murder, you're like a second-degree murder
Mega mega
A Rube Goldberg machine and a kill someone
What happened
Let's do this you okay we want to start with I want to start out with something a little bit fun and it kind of I think isn't
Decorative
This is
One day
In the Life of Alex or from the January 2nd
Putting this out a couple days after
But we have to because of just like
We have jobs
I wish that I could just hire jobs are not
The brain battle as much as I wish it was
I wish
Then I could just sit around and isolate these clips
Illuminate on them but
Occasionally dropping out
Every episode we may change the name of this podcast
So
For those of you who don't know who Alex Jones is
He is formerly a wild conspiracy theory broadcaster
Aventurine
2A
B of A preacher
And then now is
Basically just
Super into Trump
Because he believes
The Trump is going
Destroy the globalist
Okay
Who are the
It's a nebulous job
What about the article
MS.
The globalist are but they are the ones
He's again and we know some of the characters
But you'll throw out these people who want
There to be more
Trans
Atlantic Partnerships
Philosophically opposed to
In principle
But
Small aspect
I might actually agree with him
Is it was just
Curon bile
All day everyday for 3 hours
Commercials commercial
Start with one of the things that I think
Is
Spectacularly indicative
Of
His style of broad
A couple of twists
From
This day's episode
That highlight
Attendance
See within him
Want to tell you things but not want there's this like
Music given take
That he does
Let's go back to the expert broadcasting thing there's an amazing like ability to
Tell you things and not tell you things simultaneously that's that's good
Bojangles
Let's
Let's talk about the central
What kind of idea of the spot
And Infowars obsessed
And I
Euro
Totally accurate by your description
I'm fat
Alright I believe that there's a certain responsibility the people have
Do you like my ex-girlfriends I'm just
Fascinated
Recent actions that don't involve me
Haikyuu Hinata
Bring up me and Alex's past relationship
Really
Brutal
Install your bike
All My Ex's Live in Texas
Also one of my favorite things
Is he says the opening of the show and talked about how he's
Deep within occupied Texas
The only occupied Texas Missouri
The first clip
In this one
It also showcases what I would describe as
Glaring
False humility that he has
Because honestly I don't think
Many of us are going to be able to hear you during those very near future I
I honestly believe that
Reading that I'm calling is my personal view on what I think is happening and like I said
Assassinated
Personally has a long-haul truck driver at this point I'm considering
Putting my dog going home
What I'm doing
So what's this caller is describing these paranoid fantasies about how someone's going to murder Alex jump
Alex is sitting there making a
Before before we get into it
The response crazy nonsense he's about
Here's the thing I wonder about right-wing people who are always assuming that
Crazy right-wing people are going to be assassinated
Always Harvey Milk or Kathie Gifford the mountains
Do good
Because
Liberals
And progressives
Ultimately
I think that's really what it is
Spin
Maybe I don't know
Operation
You know it's the globalist
Staking out the progressives in order to create social chaos
It's this sort of logic
You can't really get out of because it just becomes circular
This caller has raised this concern about how Trump and him are going to be taken out
And here's Alex
Imagine the media together
Just because
I don't need to warn people in person
I'm at the point where I just know that
This is so serious I'm like I can do more here
That I don't even care about me
Okay
Alright you remember bunker my man
He's in he's in the bunker
An occupied
The Infowars Studio
Right
The delightful people like Rob do
And Joanne McAdoo
Lee Ann McAdoo sounds like a made-up
These are people who I don't want to talk about
Some folks are going out digging in Dallas
Yeah podcast Network spin-offs
Owen Shroyer
We're going to we're going to be so busy we're going to hire different hosts
And at Age 3 it's going to start on the Alex Jones's kid beat
That's that's a good at raising raising up soldiers
Play three-year-old son
Will start covering Alex Jones 13 year old son who is a correspondent for
Equivalent
Open 203
Beat up on him he seems like a good kid
Avoid is
Adjust talkingshit
Who don't deserve it
I would say
In the name of those churches that we don't really look back on Van
I remember there was a see what the flag
We like the celebration we're before-school everyone gather up and pray at the flag
Pray for our
The horrible culture
Oh I remember doing that cuz I blocked it out of my
I apologize for no
My friends
And I really regret that now
And I feel similarly for this kid
Right like Rex Jones I don't know
Do like 8 if you believe
God bless you
8:30
Like no one
No one should believe what they will believe as an adult at 13
Never find a 29-year old man to be like
Time somebody took this thirteen-year-old down to pay I also wonder if he's paying him
New paying a song for these reports absolutely
Absolutely
I think indicated this beautiful thing that Alex does where he wants to tell you
But he was invited to have a meeting with drops
But then that wasn't enough so the end of the clip they had to explain
Another time that I think is
Pretty amazing
But this is actually
A little bit longer and start
What's with
What I can only describe
Amazing
Fanfiction
About political intrigue
I was hoping for Twilight but let's
Let's move on
Just changed couple names
The personal email server do face Glee have
Bella and Edward
Alright
Describe Hillary
Underneath
Like other spies have done
For everybody in the world
And he would say where she stood on China
So they knew what she was about
Not as far as I can tell there's no evidence
I also feel like he doesn't know what Dropbox is
Are Housewives
He likes to go to park in movies
And then the reading real life they just go through garbage that's another late Motif it'll come I'm not on this episode but a lot of Thai
He does use movies
2A
Explain the real world
Like recently did a breakdown of
The new alien movie that's coming out next year
About how what the Illuminati really believes about the train
Knows the plot to the new alien movie coming out next
It's got to be have you got documents absolutely
Rebecca
She also had one-sided policy
Fees for the aliens
Dropbox
By the way that's been confirmed
Push it
Perfect
Us intelligence
Stop
Double crossing Trump the next morning
Old Trump
Coming after you
Everything I said
How could they
But let me see
Alright
So it looks let's
Tear this apart piece-by-piece end up being a little bit long because
Before we start recording I want
I explained to you that I don't want to play Things wildly out of context
Unfair game to play
That is the best I
I'm going to
As fast as I can
I'm going to keep this deadly serious
Yeah
So
The point I think is that he talks to Trump
Well I think there's a few things that we get into there at the beginning is she's created
Digital dropbox
Yeah which is proving that is confirmed
Jeff just like
I feel like
Everybody
I have a drop box
Open app
He works for drop-off
Perry right there
We should keep a running tally of Goofy
Alex Alex
Right
Secret agent
For the Dropbox corporate
Okay so she created this Dropbox rather confirm find out what she's going to do to them
Right
I meant pay her to not do it
I guess
That's
That sort of the implication
Can't argue with that
How could you
Because
Beyond the realm of possibility
No why would you say that
First first
China is not a guy
It's not a guy before 1 billion Park
Together China as a as a
Like if you asked him to name the politburo in China
Do you think he could
I didn't know if that's a person or a building
States well it's a collective of the politburo 87 is from Russia
These are these are like
I don't know.
You could call them the Illuminati around and talk about what it is they're going to
They are not
100 likes and Altos active
Caillou
You know like
Inspire
Just lost Alex Jones
What episode is Alex Jones
Me zero lose because the
The fundamental Point Still Remains
That
The idea that you created a digital dropbox where people could find out stuff like that
As we keep saying digital
It's smart it's it's it's essentially
Grading of verbal hashtag
This is the End again
These are the elements that you have to take apart
Just be like oh this is what he's doing
In the same way as well
Is easily
Capable of sticking in your mouth
Like I said I know I can't get digital dropbox out of my head
If if somebody asked me to hey could you just put that in my Dropbox I be like
Underneath that park bench over there
But it is an Old Fashioned
Trick that oral tradition
Cultures would use
In the same way every time he talks about
The Chinese
He calls them the Communist Chinese
Right it's a it's a
Called using an epithet
And not necessarily like a negative epithet that but it's just using
Something to characterize a noun
Makes it stick in your in your memory more
And same way that they would always call Achilles rage-filled Achilles
Or Brave Odysseus
In in The Iliad and the Odyssey
It is a really good trick when you don't
I have paper
To get people to remember that
The mnemonic tree
And he uses that
So f****** well
Digital dropbox
Is probably not even in
Intended to be like that
But it still is
He's there was a deal made
Where is this
Right
The only way for this claim to be proven
Some information with the digital dropbox
But it's been confirmed
Through unconfirm Channel
Or whatever
Yeah I know I feel like you can just find somebody was like oh yeah I put something into
That Dropbox has been put money in account
Where
Digital dropbox and islands that are the foundation to make a donation to The
Foundation
So I meant like the only way for it to be proven that they
Hillary Step Down
Immediately because she was afraid of this information of the digital dropbox coming out
They had overheard somehow Trump
Actually has
All of the intelligence agencies in his way and all the only way for that to ever come out is for
It to go down
Yeah I don't know if you know anything about the intelligence agencies
They kind of are on Trump's side
Pretty pretty
Fused me
Is that
He's insisting that Hillary and the Democrats
Yeah made a deal on Election night
He has very few details by which I mean
About what
We know there's a deal we don't know what that deal is
The next
They are betraying
Right we don't know how they're betraying him because we don't know what their deal
It makes no sense to make that deal to begin with if you're going to flip on it the next morning
I think it makes perfect sense
He doesn't in his
Beach acceptance speech doesn't lay out all this dirty laundry
And here's all the s*** I have on Hillary now I want to tell it to you guys
Until I got elected
If Only They had made a deal with Me 2 hours ago
Hey if they betrayed me tomorrow I would have been fine as long as this deal happen to me
They've betrayed him and the Democrat
Which I feel like I feel like
It is a guy in his mind
It's Schumer
They're all Chuck Schumer
That's who he thinks all that matters.
That's who he thinks they are
To our next clip
Actually it was the greatest segue in the history of podcast
Claim
To be a very Subs
Substantiv
Narrative
Is been going on forever
On his show
It's something that I really take issue with example
References it and just lies about what it says
So George Soros is essentially his big Boogeyman
He's his evil globalist
Madman
Here's a little clip
Do the Alex dark by George Soros
The minute
Hate juice
You're about
To get a big juicy taste in the Broncos win
Nazi Collaborators like George Soros
Chow Chow
Running
Alfaro said that he just can't stop
A couple of people all together on the same
So let's let's party
Contains one of my favorite things in the world
Which is everyone is always surprised by commercial break
They're never f****** ready for commercial break
But all of their commercials are just for their supper
It's all just for
Super male vitality
It's all the in-house Infowars pills
You have complained about
Take pills at the 1:30 mark
Who could possibly be their target with super awesome to is he often goes on Jags about how I keep
Like you don't
Beaufort dump
Only the only advertisers
Product he uses
Right
Is that cool
Velform illegal because he was on the
The gsm network
Which is the Genesis
Communicate ogcn
Communication Network
Did he leave them because they became
The genocide
Communication
Network
George Soros
For Netanyahu
Be
Gcn was owned by buy gold
Consortium
So when he was
Broadcast by them
But now they've shifted over to this weird health food
Stop talking
And now they sell all this
Weird
I like
You know all your body really needs is a couple of these minerals
Switch totally is
Right it's also by this guy named dr. Wallach
We've actually
If you actually look at 2
He's a veterinarian
Uno's
Better dog doctor
Veterinarian
If you look up
The people who
Used to sell gold their website now goes to
To his
Weird health food store
Doctor from 30 Rock
All over a hundred percent
Parsing alright
Be my favorite
My favorite thing that he said right there
Got a
Taste
From WWII Nazi Germany
He got a taste of rounding up Jews
Are you aware of where that comes from
Where that where would he
Referencing
No okay so is he is all the time and in the same way when he talks about Nazi
Collaborator George Soros
Okay sticks in your head
Years ago there was George Soros
Was interviewed on
He was being interviewed by
What's this guy's name
Croft
I remember him from the cross Nixon
Interview
Steve kroft
Bothering him I will read you the transcript
Play the audio
I just want to pull up more s*** but I don't have ready
You're a Hungarian
Who escaped the Holocaust
By posing as a Christian
Right
Have you watched lots of people get shipped off
Camp
Right
I was 14 years old
And I would say that that's when my character was made
In what way
That one should
Think ahead
One should one should understand and anticipate events
And when one is threatened
It was a tremendous threat of evil
I mean it was a very personal threat Aviva
My understanding is that
You went
Went out in fact
And helps enhance
Application of property from the Jews
Soros
Yes that's right
Yes
I mean that's
That sounds like an experience that would send lots of people to a psychiatric couch for many many years
Was it difficult
No not at all
Not at all
Maybe as a child you don't
You don't see the connection
But it was
They created no no problem at all
No feeling of guilt
No
For example.
I'm Jewish
Here I am watching these people go
I could just as easily be these
I should be here I should be there
None of that
But his response
Well of course
I could be on the other side or I could be one of one from whom the thing is being taken away
But there was no sense that I shouldn't be there
Because that was
Well actually in a funny way
It's just like in the market
That is
Of course I wasn't doing this but somebody else would
Would be taking it away anyhow
And it was the whatever
Whether I was there or not I was only a spectator
The property was being taken away so the I had no role in taking their property away
So no sense of guilt
Okay
This
Interview
Alex Jones
Survival Story
Yeah
It seems like Soros clearly dissociated
From his own personal identity as a measure of
He survived
Heroin
His father hit him
With the Christian
Gentleman who was responsible for when Jews were taken away
They would catalog their belongings
Leaving
Or whatever but if you're a fourteen-year-old kid
Your primary concern is making sure
No one finds out you're a Jew
Right because you will be murdered and also
Where do UMass
Sure Corp
Yeah
Beyond that is different and they found out
FedEx
Do different
Circumcision is
Is the main
Selling selling selling point
Something
There's another quote that is about that time
His life it was actually probably the happiest year of my life
That Euro German occupation
For me it was a very positive experience
It's strange
I think you it says stage but
It's strange it's a strange thing
Because you see incredible suffering around you
And the fact that you're in considerable danger yourself
But you're 14 years old and you don't believe that it can actually touch
You have a belief in yourself
You have a belief in your father
It's a very happy making exhilarating to.
So people Alex Jones in particular take
These quotes
Twisted
To be like the happiest time in his life
Was when he was helping
Hitler Round Up Jews
Which is
Both on two counts
And I don't believe that Alex doesn't know that
These things
Yeah
It is my first reaction on hearing.
Crazy
And
Clearly he's Rich enough to be honest
Which
If if he was not written like imagine him as an actor playing that nonsense
He would be pilloried for
Weeks undoubtedly right
So he's Rich enough to be like hey this was a hugely formative experience in my life
It is one of the best I ever had
And somehow
Because of those
Stances that I was
Wound up being a positive
Experience for me
Okay
Clearly means
That he was in cahoots with Hitler himself and is trying to destroy the Jewish state
Because he was so happy then he wants to recreate
Well
A hundred percent
I mean I remember growing up whenever I was being beaten regularly
It was exhilarating experience definition
Can I constantly try and recreate it psychological
Unimpeachable logic that we have in our lives often if you have
Undergone some analysis than therapy
You don't necessarily think of them as horrible times in your life bumps and bruises make you
You stronger
They there are tons of people who asked
Valve
Let me know you're not you're not
Responsible
Often for the cards you're dealt
Put you in a
Sure
Episode
If someone doesn't after-show of our after show they're going to take that clip
Well I still think that's
You can take it or leave it
So did this really bothers me quite a bit because
Most of the
Stand up for George Soros
Is the best man in the world
The collaborator is
Is incredibly irresponsible
And the fact that I'm
Hundred percent sure
That Alex Jones
Watched
Eclipse
From that.
I've seen these things
He knows what he
He was talking about
To paint it as
He was helping Roundup Jews
Means the keys
Finding a false narrative
For a reason
Is that bothers me
Okay so that puts us into lying territory verses
Deceiving
Yes propaganda terrorist
Right
The other part of this
I I love about him and you're absolutely right about him be
At no point
In his entire show I'm imagining
Does he ever actually get into why
He would want this
Barely as ever he leaves it to your own imagination to make these connect
Clearly
If you survived the Holocaust
He also wants it
Which is also a great movie title surviving the Holocaust and loving it
Dracula
Leslie Nielsen as a slapstick
She went to Young that's
Now he's a great actor
Thank you Dad
So
He be even better at it
Before before we get
Because we already got
We already got sidetracked on to the nonsense he said responding to
The nun
You noticed that on the way
Soros there was like
Oh there's 30 different mismatch
She throwing shade at the wall to see what
The stuff that he was talking about Bibi Netanyahu
He's the best apparently there are police
I questioned him over to
Corruption
Stuff
That day on the on the 2nd
I'm having difficult times
Finding
Independent corroboration of that being any
Furious
It's difficult to say but it does feed into the narrative that they already have built up with
The United States
Turn their back on Israel
With the the sitting out of the UN 3830
A billion dollars
And military aid my position on that is Israel's incredibly complicated
Situation that I don't understand all the ins and outs of
Right I do believe
Palestinians have rights
How about that cuz I grab you feel like you're wrong there
George soros's against rounding up
Also
Go beyond that also globalist
Are islamist
Cuz that's how is everybody knows islamist
Are all for Global relations
Sort of narrative pieces of it is
To create their own
Like axis of Evil
In order to make Russia okay
The axis of Evil
That's a big tip off at the club blister like
Oh we're totally
I feel like he doesn't know dr. evil aspects
He's giving me the the doctor evil doesn't know he's fictional vibe
The alliance there
In order to make Russia okay
Right China
Saudi Arabia
North Korea
But those are the ones that are like a big problem
Especially
Communist China
Those are the people we have to be worried about
Just so Russia
Just want prosperity
Country is
Turning into a s*******
That he's he's
Rampantly doing everything you can to direct every possibility
A wave
From the fact
Garbage right now
Toilet
The deflection away from
Russian tampering in
How can they do anything they have
GDP of Italy
Alright growing up with that salad that's a solid to flex
Yeah but also probably has like 200 billion dollars is a lot of money
I can imagine she is that low doesn't mean that there aren't the resources
Like there's a lot of dark money
Some of that money that week
To that Olympic stadium and the roads that were never actually better
Somebody got all that money
Communist China got all that money
Communist China in Saudi Arabia
Conspire
With North Korea
Olympic I guess I don't know
Communist China and Saudi Arabia
Did he plan to say that he said that before
Nothing ever combined communist China and Saudi Arabia
I only if he doesn't like
Like I don't I think of you mad libs that one
Yeah he had to adjust
Irene
I think it was that the spirit got good too
And he was just like you like alright well
These words are coming out whatever which is a perfect transition to this next whip
So I might be one of my favorite clips
I don't want to do any setup
Well here it is
I told you
They're really thinking about
That's not diarrhea
Now that got dropped
Amarillo
Zero Hedge
Why you talk about Canary in the coal mine
Good bad ugly
Bet your bottom
Buck
Red Alert
This is getting crazy
This is so freaking out of control
Please help us
Go back.
This is this is on air
Obediently like
They put his hand over his face and makes he acts like he's going to cry it's astounding
This is so freaking out of control
Please help us open our eyes
Play protect
Please
Somehow stop evil forces of trying to stop
Israel
Start World War 3
Reach out to those that are still in darkness
Jesus Christ God direct us on
I don't do that
Well you might be sweating in 65 degree temperatures because he's too much goddamn super male vitality
But today after publicly
Is I don't do that
For sure
Literal show
You're doing that for sure
Would listen to end
It's time to pray what's Showman
I don't mean to beat up on religion I don't I don't want to box
Someone just for being religious religion is a great thing
Like it does bring a lot of meaning to a lot of people's lives and hooray but I do take great issue with the idea that
It's being used to
Basically
Yeah well I mean
I'm so sorry about abortions
Will dentist a stream-of-consciousness ranch
Gorgeous gorgeous
Why is
Netanyahu the canary in the coal mine
Because once they come for Israel that mean strength
Why would you go for Israel first
Never explain
So you're coming for Netanyahu because he's got all the dirt
He knows good and bad things that everyone's done so you got to take him out first
So you can't spill the beans
Again
The Good The Bad
The ugly
You got all of
Yes where why and how did he get any
He's been around the game forever so he has all of it just say I've been around the game
So I noticed Every Nation on the planet
Yeah but you can
If no one
That's a good point
Hear it here is the fundamental disconnect
Is that
I feel like before I say something
I should have at least the barest understanding of why that thing is
Haha
It's like when you make a public claim
Relatively uninformed
I've got a reason for
You know that you're saying it is a joke
Even even then
Well before we go any further
Soundrop
I love you
What I was watching
This
I lost my s*** work
At that moment like I was just like
If I were writing a character I couldn't come up with something funnier
Then yelling about that World War 3 is coming
Torreon
Amazing what is a 100
Genuine
Me to Prague moment you ever
Also that's a super professional wrestling
You can see somebody walking into the ring and being like hey before we wrestle
Don't have to be like
The Undertaker
He's got he's got an evil group maybe we call them the ministry of darkness and they're going to come get me we're talking about
Visceral we're talkin about the big boss man the canary in the coal mine
Shaker's coming for me
I am going to hear that 10 million times before I go
Play today
Salud isolated clip
Anytime
I'll just pull that up on my phone
You're there coming for Netanyahu first and if they get to Netanyahu first
That's not going to be enough to destabilise everything
Right
Why are those two connected
Or how are those
I don't know why reactivate have they ever met
Of course
What
So they've never met
Has Trump ever stated
Positive feelings
He spoke at aipac
Favor of Israel
Huge favor of Israel negative things about
Obama's handling
Of you know like
Backing away from Israel
Hold tight
Everything's going to be different after the 20th
Which was
Both in reference to Russia and
Which is it is nice that
They have the luxury of being like
We can we can weather the next
20 days because
Eventually
We've got Trump who's just going to do
Whatever it is undefined variable
Here's the thing
So they kill Netanyahu
JB this thing
That you could just Shanghai
I'm somewhere
You could just rendition his ass arrested on corruption charges
You trumped-up if the whole thing is that he's got tons of dirt you would have to kill
Tell him right I mean based on what
In order for the narrative Alex Jones Dropbox
Take out his neck
Like just don't feel
Okay I can see that like like Roadhouse
What else you want
I mean unless
He has access to a computer
Where are a lot of possibilities, Japan
You can learn how to write with your feet they're in League with the Saudi Arabians
In the movie Aladdin
But
You also then have to remove his eyes because some people can
Text to type with their
Remove those
Fortunate
I miss that thinking about the the Mayhem from Alibaba
The Labyrinth
Blankman
Looks looks
Call Alex Jones Angela go directly into this is about the movie Aladdin
Alright alright
So that but then we also have the technology now where we can read brain scans
Turn that into
It's still in infancy stage
Just but I'm assuming
If you know everything about everybody
I've got a murder baby
Yeah
Israel is
What
And so but but even then if they murder Netanyahu
Who's the next
L waiting in the wings
Let me ask you a
Alex Jones
I'm not making any claims
Frankly I don't know many of my Altima
My representative
Felt the need to call them
That's a good idea
If there's one thing that we can learn it
Don't call Alex Jones
Collier state representative
I love you I love you
I wish that the caller have been like
You know
There people calling any mention that
Yourself about this time
Listen
To The Alex Jones
People who need virility
Certainly if you want a discount on boner
Boner pills right
Vitality
It's about how like
You get your libido going
I don't know if it is
I think it might be boner
Cast
And Alexa basically they keep
Statistics on websites for advertising purposes
Quote you're castrated
Stuff like that
I've done some research on
What kind of traffic is
His website actually gets
If you do that
Have like 200 300 thousand
Hits a day unique hits on the website
What you still great
But then whatever like a cop is killed two goes up to about a male
Of course you're getting all that Viral content out there you're reeling in the races
Repeat dog cop killer narrative
You can see spikes
It is traffic
Whenever in the
See what happened is it okay
That was that when
You should like that
Which was also a false flag operation
Initiated by Hillary
Absolutely
WikiLeaks founder
They all know that
The plot to kill Netanyahu
To put this all together
And who is behind
Soros Soros
The Nazi loving Jew
Also the Soros
His claims to
Be fun
They they act like
Because he gives money
To help that cause
That they're his Goons
Squad kind of
It's insane and very racist
You're asking yourself this question who's list
Next clip
Who is
Who's listening
Doesn't Hillary know when she attacks me
You still close to just making out.
Call Buchan organization
Saudi Arabia
Like that
Heathrow Media Matters under the bus if you want
He's a catalog
I will give him a
I think those two things are also two related to pizzagate now
I don't think he wants to touch that one
Was was that his faults indirectly is that word did he start the whole pizzagate
Figure out
I think that after that guy showed up at that pizza place with a gun
It was a hot potato
And I
There
Clean the website of all of the mansion
Well not all of it but it's all of their like main reporting on it
All the stuff he was talking about it being something that needs to be investigated
Citizen investigators
Do something about it
That magic
Wish they had
And the guy Joe Biggs
Was the guy who used to work for him
Around the same time
So it's like there's a little bit
Suspiciousness
They've both put out videos talking about how late is I'm writing
Maybe that's the case
Close
I got fired from the TV show
You know I
It was time for me to move on I feel like my future is
Feature films I've already had a couple of meetings I will tell you there with
But frankly it's really
Just about me I've made all of my money Marvin Barnes I don't even care if I
I meet with
George Soros
About producing
The thing that made it stink to high heaven was Alex put out a video where he was talking about how talented Joe Biggs was
Dude
I know it's not true he has dirt on you
Bratz
Let's watch the rest
This clip
The people that
The military
The police
Judges
The lawyers
The Congress people they are
The Russian government list
Because
It's the only place you get it
This strong
This Focus
Discontinued
We don't take breaks
I would like to point out after him saying he doesn't take breaks he had someone else host the fourth hours
It's pretty routinely has people hoes 4th ourselves
He's putting himself
As the only voice
Spuds
Outlet other people say
Specifically the Pakistani government
Does he know anyone in the Pakistani
Maybe one guy does he know the capital of Pakistan
Cartoon
That's the capital of something
So there's no
Larry said it's not racist
I know I took a geography
Every class in high school and I know like
For state or country
That's it I don't know Pakistan
Not fun to say
No Burkina faso's capital
Ouagadougou
That's pretty fun
Cell phone
That is funny Madagascar
Antananarivo
Honduras
Tegucigalpa
Really I might be
That is good
High School
Like what
Brazil is Brasilia right
I mean like European nation
Let's go to Paris
You rolling your eyes
I feel like people are like capitals Leon California is LA
No Sacramento we all know that
Some of us some of us
That's true
Can we go back to the list
Just isolate the list
I'm going to have to take note
How do you want me to play or you
Judge
The people who
What is that what is that hanging out
I hope
Ifucking mean the people who do that
Like I think you talk about string people up
Yeah
I wanted to send Alex when it's appropriate
He wasn't going to say
Yeah because I was I was pulling that that would be describing racism in a situation where he's just being
Wacky you're absolutely right
And he is wrong
Yes
Are the military the police
So he starts with those as the people who do the bureaucrats the lawyers
The government
The Pakistani government the common
When is Chinese who hate him bread
Implication seems to me to be there like
All
10000 people who work in government listen to him
No f****** way they get any work done if they listening for hours a day to his pill ad
They have to listen to only place
He doesn't want to say
Buddy is the only place
That gives it to you this Folk
What I think is my favorite this Focus
At all
Rambling on about all the government
If we keep doing that
I will make a Supercut of all the times he says I've got to get to the story
And I'm not
10 times a day at least
But see that's against another brilliant move
Build You Up
The same thing then
Local news always does rats like
This story is about
Are your children
Comedian named Ron Ramey
Rhetorically on
Who do like
I got to go
Like a sort of thing that he's like you can be leaving any minute.
So it becomes like he's not going to leave but we like this
Is the same thing as I've got so much to give
Never get to it they just have more f****** pillow
But listen
I feel like
You don't believe
The people listen to his show
Adafruit for your b**** ass
Alex has some more words
See where we go
Well Chad Washington Post article mother editor
Star Wars basically
Russian
Everything they do
I want to take a break really quick to point this out that he says that all the f****** time which leads me to believe that the inverses
Very ugly we're doing is what they're doing
Kind of feels like
Propose to you
You're glue
Yeah
It reminds me of when
My brother would do something when we were kids
I meant accuse me of doing it to our
Remind me of very adolescent bullying
But he brings this up over and over and over and over again
Fifth like idea
The globalist
Accuse him of the
Things they're doing
Insane
Whatever
Anyway
So Trump reason for
Trump reads Infowars to 10th of March
Let me just go and tell the mainstream media cuz they don't seem to figure it out
He's not just Flint
It's all of them dummies
I'm not bragging
A couple website
I spy cam
I'm sorry
The generals all listen stupid
Define government
Stupid
Because they know we know what we're talking about
Chanhassen theater
He also says that a lot I wish I was wrong
From an ego
I wish I was wrong is
Like almost like a hook on her ass rap song from the show is wrong
I meant if you want two guys if you're looking to came to life
Sing the hook
Go to YouTube and just search
Alex Jones failed predictions
And there's wonderful compilations of like
100 times he's been
So f****** wrong about everything
The idea of wish come true
Also everyone with you hear my I don't want to play it on the show special episode
Do yourselves a favor and go f****** listen
Come to the Y2K episode of Alex Jones
He's been doing this for how long like 25 years
Whole goddamn s*** on December 31st 1999
He
Was creating a panic
Accentuate wow yeah he was feeding into a lot of like
Real horrible paranoia
And what's interesting about how
Russia is
Good guys
He's on board with Russia
And we all know that
Putin this guy Putin the ruthless
Evil
17 years is a long time number one
Number two
Here is the here is my
Favorite thing about the the Russian paranoia
Because that is
Like the
Flip on that was so fast
Weather
Well I mean
The right-wing
Crazy like
The moment
The Cold War ended they wanted to start a nuke
So now because of the whole tree
Now Democrats are all on this
Tamper with the
And they probably did
In some fashion
Whether or not it was like
Direct
Saying word indie
The one
Problem
Is that
He says
We've done
America's Best
Police Government Street
Unjustified
Banana Republic was not invented
Wonderful clothes
Overthrow
Our Corporation
Yeah
Get I get where they're coming from
To you
It's such a
Hugely hypocritical
Well the difference is I think you and I would be fair about that
Is recognized
The government has done very horrible thing
It is worse that it's happening
Because
With we are gone
Or if we're in some weird Flex
A great deal
You know
Given the entire stretch of history and how long
World
Eventually the time of the world is 6,000 years
We will have to go down at some point
Right it's just natural
No Kingdom
Kum & Go
Clearly
Tearing ourselves
As we speak
Let me know what is the average lifespan of every sort of
Kingdom
For a big guy
Colonial Powers about 200 years and it starts to fall apart basically
Guideline
I couldn't stay because
The big histories are written
In about people who laugh
Even those ones have discrete.
But if you want to go through the history
Chinese guy
One of the most Bass
Fascinating
Bo3
The Joseph the chin like that's all
Which we don't respect at all is history because
No I don't like it
Because it's
Interesting but it's not about
Right
Right but because it is a communist
Chinese
If
If you were to learn anything about history you would then have
App to apply it
Now
And that would mean
Changing a lot
It also requires you to
Load in a bit of empathy
Play against that struggling
Empathetic
What they're doing
Everything
I would say that no matter what I still don't want us to go down
Right now because
Bavarian
Yeah I mean
Epinephrine is a part of
Mortality where it is
You know if I have to die
Feel like everybody should go with
I used to smoke a lot of weed me and a couple friends with sit around or one of the things we've always
We're like super
The idea of being able to
Like what a privilege that would be to be one of the humans
Sofia at all
Yeah
There's something to be said
No
Live
Unicorn
It would be good to already be dying and then everything else starts
Here's another narrative
In the same vein as
George Soros
Sorry
Here is why Trump
Reed's Infowars
Was never an
Nope
He brought up
Here's why Trump did the
Quicksilver
You know what you don't like
Against the spirit got to good to
Yeah it's this thing that gets in here
The Boogie Woogie band it comes in and takes over literally any
Explanation you know that everyone listens
Okay that's Jame
You dumb dumb person
But he could have made up anything and because
Trump
Probably would have been
At the very least entertains at
Free password
Yeah not even that just like you know why you listen
Because everybody's got to read something on the toilet
I don't know that would be a
Real disappointing reveal
The mainstream media can't figure this out expected going to be something big
You listen because everyone important listen everyone important
Unless you're saying it's like a peer pressure thing
I think you're being intelligent
Obviously everyone does
Let's go far
The only person I have
Evidence doesn't listen
You
From a very
That's good is it really stressful
Just a tiny bit
Not very unfair but it's unfair because there's an implied answer
Zerohedge
Breitbart
Drudge
Alex Jones
Are the only people who give actual news
Okay so that's why Trump
Listen to m
Yes he actually
Lesbian
Reply dancers really spell out
He kind of Defense another narrative the
I was going to go to
To this other one about
From the movie need to cover cuz I don't know yet play the audio
He just basically like
It's about Merrick Garland being put into the
Record as a recess appointment only God
I mean I think so it is the earliest have a fair shot
I would rather it go be debated
And what have you
But
The point is that it's
Now we're talkin talkin about it
Cuz I don't want to act like I'm putting words in it
Gotcha
Wards.com
Support.com
Obama still
Good for
Under the court
Intercession
Recess
Show
No presents
Go on to the Supreme Court
So the park
100 100%
George
Kimpton May Theresa
I I don't remember that that was clearly before the
Institution was president
Since George Washington Washington appointed South Carolina
Congressional recess
He was
He was a
Still in the end
Infancy
He's making
Because of rutledge's political views
Occasional mental illness however the Senate rejected his nomination and Rutledge attempted suicide and resigned
American history so much
Beyond that New Jersey judge William J Brennan was appointed
The Supreme Court by President Dwight D Eisenhower in
6 by recess
Never heard of him
George h.w. Bush appointed Lawrence
Eagleburger as secretary
State during recess
That was clearly too far back for our
President Ronald recess appointment
What's an average of 30 per year
President HW Bush made 77 recess appointment
Hw77 total
Bill Clinton made 109 or 130
Disappointment
17 per year
President George Bush made 171
21 per year
And as of January 5th 2012 President Barack Obama
How to make 32 the least of anyone on this list
An average of 4.5 per year does not matter but all the Obama inform
Animation
Obama's a dictator and he's doing this
But it's always the least of anybody else that doesn't matter it doesn't matter beliefs recess appointments the least
Vacation days
Statistic
Don't match up but the reason I've included this
In terms of visible
This list of
A false narrative
He can't not know that absolutely
No
Does not know about Reese
Guaranteed
You think it's like a you're telling us from Court Justice to go play Force
REI
Well tetherball did you did you say any like it was George
Then who did the Supreme Court
The first one
Were there any other Supreme Court other than
Eisenhower
I don't know I didn't do a full
Because he's clearly.
2nd recess
Appointment that's not this
But you could do any cursory amount of research
Can find these facts
Yeah but
Not going to
He has a team
He has a f****** team but they're not there
Learn things
To learn
They're not there to develop a
You do not even that
There there
2 developer
So their entire job is to
To filter out a
Formation that
It's a Portsmouth
From information that doesn't
Right I get what gets
To Alex Jones
Is
Probably more the former than the latter
Yeah but you undercut your you're a you're telling me
That Alex Jones
Is doing
Any of his own race
I hope so I hope some
Genuinely
You listen to the hardest question I've ever been asked
The Alex Jones does his own research
Maybe he did
Way back when when you didn't have the the
The All-Star team
Yeah but now
10 years
It's tough to say I in my heart of hearts
I have to believe he's done some
But not much
What was the when was the last
Full book that he
And I'm not saying that is like as like a dig for
He does a
Before our show
All day
I very much doubt he has
Time to really go through all of this
It's probably none dare call it a conspiracy
Books
Radicalized him and Junior College
And his team's research
Yeah
Are they researching
Historians or they are aggregated information
That is on the
And they're going to get yelled at
They come up with something that doesn't fit
Oh absolutely
I think they won
Sing the doesn't fit the narrative
That is the
That is the situation
With bully
If you once you get to a cert
Certain point
You're building a house of
Support that Foundation
Otherwise the whole thing
If you just one piece of information
That doesn't support the narrative
And the whole thing goes
Fret so
Even if and again
Even if he
He did discover that
In his Reese
There is
Almost always going
Going to be a partner
Is mine that
Turns that
Into something that actually supports
I don't like that you're saying because I
I hear this as a very positive
Statement about him
How so
Because what you're saying is
He doesn't know that he
He's wilfully deceiving about
Recess
I would argue ignorance
Is far worse
In a broadcaster
Situations bad Direct
No I think direct lying is worse cuz that means you're doing it for a reason
Like do you agree with me agree with me
How much is making those f****** weirdo pills
Truth
Broadcast
And this is the way it is on TV
Nnn kind of broadcast
Easter is
Do any of their like
Most of them
Imply and some of them
I have sad
Get out
Good day I believe
40%
That's the job maybe podcast
Things different I believe pretty much everything I say
Well yeah but we're we're not being paid a lot of
Certainly not whatever it is worth
I wanted to I wanted to make the premise of the show that we pretended George soros's paying up but
It's too late now
George Soros
Did commit the entire hot
So it's time for a couple of
Music for that we are going to be
I'll buy a soundboard motorcycle Ohio
End of this podcast we're just going to play with the soundboard for
For the entire time I don't remember exactly what these two
Two clips are but I know the first one
So
Mystery
You know what I feel like we have to go offensive because we got to leave people with
The mystery right oh no
Most 2016
I don't want to say
But funding
Christian Christian
Israel
Would never stop killing each other
Clean up your own house
Before you run around
Lecturing the rest of the world
Muslims
Wow alright
Where was in contact here is the absolute problem
With that
Yes he characterized them
Asthma
Altogether
Aggressively
Muslims
But the problem
That's horrific
Who's accent does not help his
Texas accent
But here is the
The problem with that
Which there is a
If you learn the history of is
Tunisia
Has been the source of so much fun
Now whether or not
That is
Any difference
From
You know
Prospect
Decrying that
But
When did he
The twist
The Twist that he had was so genius
WhatsApp
Following the Muslims killing each other
He had the perfect twist which was
Implying
That Obama was
Funding
Islamic
Murdering Christians all throughout
That's a big that's a big narrative
So he's saying no vote was not necessarily anti
Right
But these
Funding
Murdering Christians all across the world is definitely anti-christian
Which which is unrelated to the previous statement
True I agree
What's
You got what you are correct
CenterPoint
So so we got that
Then we switch immediately back
Yep no vote is certainly anti-israel which as we all can guess
What is a very complicated
That I mean
Confusing no vote is absolutely the correct
Abstaining
Which settlement stuff is very
They're killing as many
Witch hazel
So much of like
The deep-seated psychological
Issues there of Israel
Potentially trying
Naruto
Palestinian
Is so fast
Yeah but because
Cure
To say irony
But just like that
That idea of like
Now it's time to get them out of his cleansing
It's but if you would it's like you look at the narrative
From the
Alex Jones
Of it
But none of them were Palestinian
Right
Destabilize
George Soros
All this stuff because parallel I have
Which
I think is
Uninformed and
At most
Andover General
Heard at least
But the only thing I can
Look up to
Blaine
The the Israeli takeover of Palestine
The settlement
The absolute unwillingness to
To even
Consider a compromise
Is like
You know how
Sexual abusers
A lot of the times windup
Having been
Sexually abused yeah
That's the one thing that I can think of that is a
Parallel that accept children of Alcoholics often end up dating alcoholics
Exactly create the situation
To make it right
12 minutes
But I don't know how that works as a society
If you want if you want to call any
Any unwieldy Nation
As a collection of children Act
Nothing half as smart
The smartest of them
I mean
Conceited
National identity
Like America
Regardless of what
Side you are on
In the two party system
There is definitely a national identity
Write the different from
Most other European countries
It's a ridiculous country that we have
That's filled with so many like different regions that have
Zero to do with the others
One consistent
National identity which is
F*** the government
Alright we're going random I really don't remember what this is
I would expect
Bunkers
5 minutes
Almost
The urgency of repudiating Obama
Repudiate
And all of these insane
Out of control
You just want to destroy Prosperity control
Pause real quick
Kissinger
Who recently met with Mike Pence
I feel like he does not know anything about kissing
Pull their that's Saudi Arabia in communist China
That's further on the tightrope
Apparently
I mean
Kissinger is an evil mother
It does seem that way
You want people to come after me
See this is another reason why up top I wanted to make clear
No I Just Want to Have Fun
Stanford
To kick him off the air
Well I mean our entire livelihood if you're listening to this
Number one podcast
On the planet
I'm really curious where this is going to go
Excited
You just think we're going to
And take it
I swear to you I didn't Loop that
Deserve a podcast award for perfect
Hell's your problem
I don't want
Okay I remember now
This is one of these great and I got to take
We're not going to take it
This is such a great example of Alex Jones
The thread halfway through a sentence
Trying to diss
Destroy the trying to take me off the are the independent
Also Madeleine Albright
Now
Time to really take Madeline off
This is where
Threadripper
Like a loses it
Entirely at the end of the sentence
Is
Well it's exactly like when you're
It's exactly like you've been on this situation
Insaan
Too drunk
Oh yeah and you're talking and you're
Getting to the bed
And then halfway through all the sudden your brain goes
So you just start saying stuff because you know eventually your brains just going to least
We're not going to take it
If he does find a thread
It's the wrong spread and he thinks he's going to find it again and he doesn't
Just goes commercial
How does
Turtle break end
Amazing
So he's just talked about how I can There Will Be Blood
Competition
Right
I don't want anybody to succeed
Walking on me
By somebody sports car before that's super awesome
No way
Is the first Gardner-White commercial music
Guy in a nice car pulls up a nice car and the guy in the car is like a sorry it's better than yours
But like not being a dick he's being actually a man
That is never f****** happen
Then the negative
Never happened you know what let's see where it goes
They don't
Turn off the commercial
So the globalist are people if you were cold where that sentence started
It had to do with people trying to kick him off the air
If you want to be very generous
You can say that the idea of competition
He's competition to them
I guess now they want to kill him
Put the metaphor with a car is amazing
Cuz it's not a metaphor
That's supposed to be a literal
Never happen to him it's never happen to anybody what car looks like
Also why does he Envy this car
Then say
I would never get one
I want to get that car but I wouldn't
I have one more clip that I don't remember what it is
He is so he's
Is he referencing that the Kurt Vonnegut short story
Which one
Do you remember the one where it's
The
The world is
Changed
To be equal to
Is this dude and he's the name
The short story is named after who
And so he's
Is perfect
Because of that they have to
Buddy else
Giant bottle
How do you say
Self as somebody who's being
Who people are trying to apologize for not being
Specific about
Communist China
All the things that this area has really
Complains about how there's a learned helplessness
The mentality and liberals
Right
This weird
I don't understand what the line is between like
One version
Paranoia and the other
I'm not entirely sure but
Mayonnaise
Here's
While we're talking
The only thing that I can
Tevive
Is
I want
Eventually
Try and under
So that's why we got to keep doing this show
Don't remember what it is but it has to do with them
Georgia
Looking to start over
Break
Georgia
Alex
This is where they want to
Start World War 3
In the plan
I know they always have
Sure having Hillary be elected would have been great
You know they can do whatever they want
Don't care it's because they're crazy and I think they're possessed
First place
Yep
They're damn demon
Their literal demon
Possess
Yep
He often makes the claims with people who are against him are literal demon
Or being paid by Soros
Those are the two groups of people who are against
And we can save 100%
Neither
Yes I would I would agree with neither
I would say neither
Brilliant move is because you're never
Is The Narrative of being
Possessed
But it could also be like
No that was a metaphor for George
Could be possessed
The globalist
He sells a shirt to that's like a George Soros as a goblin
That's I don't know if
I don't know you know what that's the next
Right
Is
Harry Potter
Hundred percent
The Goblins at the Greene
I like the one telling you right now
Harry Potter you heard it here first ladies and gentlemen
JK Rowling
Possessed
An incisor
Just getting relics
Well anyway
Those
Things that I wanted to tell you about Infowars today
Let's let's close it with with
This
Makes me laugh
Sohar
And I hope you enjoy thank you for listening
I hopefully will do more of these in the near future
Little bit
Over 2 hours thing is probably not going to work in our favor
Nope
Trey for whitening
Play for Providence
Defense and support
And provision for Trump and for Infowars
Ditto
Because of Duty
You can see it
We are the people resisting
Special just even more
Until Wednesday night
Free shipping for wine
Turn off everything
Why supplies last the problem is
10%
Superman
We got 30% off on those
Excuse about sell out
We have the liver
Cleanse liver