Andy in Kansas, you're on the air, thanks for holding.
Hello Alex, I'm a first time caller, I'm a huge fan, I love your work.
I love you.
Hey everybody, how's it going?
Boy, welcome to Knowledge Fight.
That is our official opening theme song.
I love you.
I will marry you.
If you're joining us for the first time, which of course you are.
You have to be.
This is a show where I am going to have a little discussion with my friend Jordan here.
That's me, I'm Jordan Holmes.
Also I'm Dan.
We're off to a great start.
Clunky off the top.
Experienced podcaster Dan Friesen.
Totally.
Yes.
I've been doing this for years and yet out the gates.
Still can't introduce himself.
Clunk City.
That is also the name of this podcast.
Info Wars Wars Clunk City.
The clunked remix.
Chopped and clunked.
So I have for the last while been a bit obsessed with one Alex Jones of Info Wars fame.
And as the world has turned to quote a soap opera title, I have become more and more aware
that I want to do a better job of covering what he does.
Right.
It's kind of like a Chris Hardwick thing where it's like the talking dead.
I want to do that.
You want to do an Alex Jones after show.
Yeah exactly.
Where we all sit around wondering who's going to die next week.
Exactly.
Spoiler alert.
It's all of us.
Yeah.
We're all dead.
But I want to say this.
I want to be very clear about a couple things.
Because I think it would be so easy to get things misconstrued off the top and I don't
want those things to ever come up as a confusion.
Okay.
First thing, I in no way want Alex Jones to be taken off the air.
Right.
I think what he does is...
Well one, when this podcast blows up and we're the number one podcast next year, our careers
are entirely tied to his continued success.
So we need him.
Yeah we need him.
I think what he does borders on entertaining and on the other side of that border is irresponsible.
But at the same time, I am so opposed to censoring things.
I want people to view him in context.
But I would never want to shut him down or say like he can't do what he does.
Right.
Because that's an easy attack.
And it's a slippery slope.
It is.
Yeah.
If you can go after him, who's next you know?
Like as people who say like professionally say dumb shit.
Sure.
On stages.
Yeah exactly.
On microphones.
Exactly.
Recorded in some instances.
Yeah very foolishly on my part.
Yeah exactly.
If we start going after those guys, you know, somebody's next that we like.
Sure.
That said...
And even beyond that there's a principle of it.
Right.
Which we do subscribe to.
Absolutely.
Which is say whatever you want as long as it's not advocating violence against somebody,
a threat, or libel.
Which he's done.
Which he's also done.
But that gets me to my second point.
Okay.
So whatever I'm gonna say, and whatever you're gonna say, I want this to be super clear.
There's a big part of me that really admires Alex Jones.
Absolutely.
And here's why.
He is...
You're an insane person.
Yes.
I'm nuts.
Okay.
He is an amazing broadcaster.
If you really take the tricks of broadcasting and apply him to them, he is insanely good.
Okay.
You could not say a lot of the stuff he does without being really good at your job.
I think that's something that will come out.
We'll see.
There are points where you'll be like, he's great.
Right.
I admire his skill.
I don't like what he does with it.
Right.
Well, I think that's probably gonna be the central battle of this whole podcast is you
trying to prove to me that I should admire him in certain aspects.
I don't think so.
Okay.
All right.
Fair enough.
I just wanted to make that caveat off the top because it would be easy for anyone listening
to think that this is just going to turn into a beat up fest and be like, hey, Alex Jones
is stupid.
Right.
That's not at all.
And oh, another thing, I don't think people who listen to him are stupid.
I don't think his fans are stupid.
And that actually on the way here, that's something I was thinking about is where are
we on the axis of stupid slash evil?
Personally?
Yeah.
I'm not evil.
Not you and me.
Although we're probably more on the evil side.
I would say I'm more stupid.
Okay.
Most of the evil things I've done in my life have been accidents.
Let's say you're not a premeditated murder guy.
You're like a second degree murder guy, like in the heat of the moment or manslaughter.
Yeah.
In the heat of the moment.
Oopsies.
Uh huh.
I accidentally trigger like a Rube Goldberg machine and a kill someone.
That's that's the kind of evil I'm at.
It's like, oh no, what happened there?
Gotcha.
Yeah.
All right, let's do this.
Okay.
We want to start with.
I want to start out with something a little bit fun.
And it kind of, I think is indicative of.
This is just one day in the life of Alex Jones.
Right.
All of these clips that we're going to play are from the January 2nd, 2017 episode.
Putting this out a couple days after, but we have to because of just like, we have jobs.
Right.
I wish that I could just.
Our jobs are not Alex Jones's job.
My job is not the brain battle.
Right.
As much as I wish it was.
I wish that I could just sit around and isolate these clips and ruminate on them.
But this podcast will also be us occasionally dropping out potential names for this podcast.
Yeah.
Every episode, we may change the name of this podcast.
Good luck finding us.
So for those of you who don't know who Alex Jones is, he is formerly a wild conspiracy
theory broadcaster who then turned, took a bit of a turn into a bit of a preacher.
Uh, and then now is basically just super into Trump because he believes that Trump is going
to destroy the globalists.
Okay.
Now who are the globalists?
It's a nebulous term.
I really don't want you to say a word that begins with J and ends with Juden.
What about the article?
Right, right, right.
DOS?
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
See, there we go.
MS-DOS.
Um, he, it's super vague who the globalists are, but they are the ones he's against.
Right.
And we know some of the characters that he'll throw out, these are the people who want,
uh, there to be more, uh, transatlantic partnerships.
I'm not, I'm not necessarily in favor of these things.
I'm not necessarily philosophically opposed to, in principle, some of the things he's
for, but.
If he didn't have at least some small aspect of like, God damn it, I might actually agree
with him, he would never be successful.
Undoubtedly.
If it was just pure on bile, all day, every day, for three hours a day.
Four, if you count commercials, which he does a lot of the commercials.
Oh, of course he does.
Which we'll get to in a minute.
All right.
But I wanted to start with one of the things that I think is spectacularly indicative of
his style of broadcast.
Okay.
Here are a couple of clips from this day's episode that highlight a tendency within him
to want to tell you things, but not want to tell you things.
Right.
There's this like, there's a give and take that he does, and this goes back to the expert
broadcasting thing.
Right.
There's an amazing ability to tell you things and not tell you things simultaneously.
Ooh, that's good.
He's working both angles.
Before we do that, though, let's talk about the central kind of idea of this podcast.
Yes.
You are an InfoWars obsessive.
But, but, but not obsessive.
And I don't know a goddamn thing about Alex Jones.
Yes.
You're all totally accurate by your description.
Right.
I'm not an obsessive, I'm fascinated.
Okay.
All right.
And I believe that there's a certain responsibility that people have to...
The same way I'm not obsessed with any of my ex-girlfriends, I'm just fascinated by...
Yes, there are recent actions that don't involve me.
Dude, I told you not to bring up me and Alex's past relationship.
Okay.
Sorry.
It was really fucking brutal.
I know, I know.
He broke your heart.
Listen.
And stole your bike.
Listen, you can read between the lines.
All my exes live in Texas.
Also, one of my favorite things is the opening of his show.
It talks about how he's deep within occupied Texas.
Occupied?
So what?
Austin?
Is that what he's talking about?
He's in Austin.
Okay.
He's in the only occupied Texas that there is.
It's occupied.
Right, right, right.
Okay.
So anyway, here's his first clip.
In this one, it also showcases what I would describe as a glaring false humility that
he has, and I think it's delicious.
Because honestly, I don't think many of us are going to be able to hear you here in the
very near future.
I honestly believe that they're either going to take you out or they're going to get murdered
in West Trump.
The reasoning that I'm calling is my personal view on what I think is going to be happening.
And like I said, they're either going to shut in followers down.
They're going to take you out.
They're going to either have Trump assassinated during the inauguration or right before or
right afterwards.
They're not going to let him be president very long.
And personally, as a long-haul truck driver, at this point, I'm considering putting my
job, going home, finding something to do locally because I don't think that, you know, even
something, what I'm doing, I don't think any of this is going to last very much longer
than that.
So while this caller is describing these paranoid fantasies about how someone's going to murder
Alex Jones, Alex is sitting there making a face.
Before we get into what crazy nonsense he's about to say, here's the thing I wonder about
right-wing people who are always assuming that crazy right-wing people are going to
be assassinated.
Right-wing people are never assassinated.
It's always Harvey Milk or Kathy Giffords.
MLK.
Yeah, it's always the people who are trying to do good because liberals and progressives
ultimately are pussies.
I think that's really what it is.
Well, now the narrative that he would spin, maybe, and I don't want to put words in his
mouth.
False flag operations.
Oh, so good.
Bingo.
You know, it's the globalists taking out the progressives in order to create social chaos.
It's this sort of logic that you can't really get out of because it just becomes circular
at a certain point.
So anyway, this caller has raised this concern about how Trump and him are going to be taken
out, and here's Alex's response.
I was about to say, I was going to be going on the road the next few days and going and
having some meetings and things, and I'm just going to leave it at that.
I'd imagine the media could put two and two together, and I'm tempted to not even leave
just because, but then I don't need to warn people in person.
Puts you that way.
Yeah, I mean, I'm at the point where I just know that this isn't about pomp and circumstance.
Exactly.
Like I've already, I'm not going to even get into it.
The point is, this is so serious.
I'm like, I can do more here.
I don't need to even go have somebody pat me on the head and say thank you.
I mean, you know what I mean?
I mean, I'm so in the bunker at this point that I don't even care about meeting with
the president.
I'm sorry.
Just go ahead.
Okay.
All right.
You're in that bunker, my man.
Uh, he's in, he's in the bunker.
In occupied Texas.
Yes.
The Info Wars studio.
Right.
Full of the delightful people like Rob Do and Joanne McAdoo, Leanne McAdoo, not Joanne,
how dare I.
Leanne McAdoo sounds like a made up name.
Owen Schroyer.
These are people who I don't want to talk about because I'm focusing on Alex.
We're digging into Alex.
We will develop an entire podcast network into the Alex Jones network.
There will be spinoffs.
Yeah.
Oh, absolutely.
We just cover Owen Schroyer.
Right, right, right.
We're going to, we're going to be so busy.
We're going to hire different hosts to deal with.
I'm going to have a kid and at age three, it's going to start on the Alex Jones's kid
beat.
That's, that's a good, raise them, raise them up soldiers.
That's what, that's what I say.
My three year old son will start covering Alex Jones's 13 year old son who is a correspondent
for Info Wars.
Right.
Who is also equivalent in, uh, in intelligence to a three year old.
Possibly.
I don't want to beat up on him.
He seems like a good kid.
You are, that's, that's exactly what we're trying to avoid is us just talking shit.
Especially on people who don't deserve it.
Right.
Like we grew up in the church, uh, in various churches and we did things I would say in
the name of those churches that we don't really look back on fondly now.
That's true.
I remember there was a see you at the flag was like the celebration where before school
everyone would gather up and pray at the flag.
Uh, pray for our horrible culture.
Oh, I remember doing that.
Yeah.
I forgot cause I blocked it out of my memory.
I apologize for bringing it back.
Yeah, no, I'm going to have to deal with that now.
But, but I would go around and try and proselytize to my friends and I really regret that now.
And I feel similarly for this kid.
Right.
Like Rex Jones, I don't know.
Like if you believe the stuff that you're saying, God bless you.
You're 13.
Like no one, no one should believe what they will believe as an adult at 13.
Yeah.
And it's, it's sad for me, a 29 year old man to be like, Oh, it's about time somebody took
this 13 year old down a peg.
I also wonder if he's paying him.
Is he paying his son for these reports?
Absolutely not.
I feel, uh, anyway.
And if he is, he's keeping it.
So that clip, I think indicated this beautiful thing that Alex does, where he wants to tell
you badly that he was invited to have a meeting with Trump.
He's having some meetings.
He really wants to tell you that.
You need to know that.
And if you're in the media who doesn't cover him, you can put two and two together.
Right.
If you covered him.
But then that wasn't enough.
So at the end of the clip, he had to explain the, I don't need the president to pat me
on the head.
Oh, absolutely not.
So he does this another time that I think is, is pretty amazing.
But this, this clip is actually a little bit longer and starts with what I can only describe
as amazing fan fiction about political intrigue.
I was hoping for Twilight, but let's, let's move on.
Just change a couple of names and insert a personal email server.
And you basically have Bella and Edward for years.
She would put data on there at her Dropbox.
She didn't go to a local park and drop the stuff underneath a park bench.
Like other spies have done.
She would load it up for everybody in the world to see.
And she would say where she stood on China or where she stood on this country or that
and what she was going to do.
So they knew what she was about to do and had to give her more money or she would put
in policies that weren't one sided for them.
Now, as far as I can tell, there's no evidence of this.
I also feel like he doesn't know what Dropbox is or how spies work.
They go to the park.
I feel like they go to park in movies and then the re in real life, they just go through
garbage.
That's another late motif that will come up, not on this episode, but a lot of times he
does use movies to explain the real world.
Like recently he did a breakdown of the new alien movie that's coming out next year about
how it depicts what the Illuminati really believes about the world.
Well, if anybody already knows the plot to the new alien movie coming out next year,
it's got to be him.
He's got documents.
Yeah, absolutely.
It was in Hillary's Dropbox email account.
All right, back to the clip.
She also had one sided policies for the aliens.
Hillary created a digital drop box.
And by the way, that's been confirmed and that's the data that's going to come out if
the Democrats keep pushing.
But the Democrats are so crazy, they don't even care.
They're going to go for broke.
They made a deal with Trump on election night to admit he won and to back off.
Perfect sense.
And that then Trump would put out the word to the dogs in U.S. intelligence to stop releasing
info.
And they began double crossing Trump the next morning and the American people.
And I told Trump, they're never going to stop coming after you.
I told him three days after the election, I said, Mr.
President elect, they're never going to stop.
They're never going to follow the deal.
They're going to try to kill you politically or physically.
They're not going to stop.
They can't stay.
I'm not going to say everything I said.
And I've said, how could Trump said?
But let me explain something to everybody.
This is deadly serious.
All of this is deadly serious.
All right.
That's the end of that clip.
It is.
All right.
So let's let's tear this apart.
Sure.
Piece by piece.
Oh, and let me be clear.
Some of these clips may end up being a little bit long because before we started recording,
I wanted to explain to you that I don't want to play things wildly out of context.
I think that's an unfair game to play.
And as the best I can, as best I can, I'm going to keep as best I can.
I'm going to keep this is deadly serious.
Yeah.
So the point of that clip, I think, is that he talks to Trump, right?
I think that's kind of the point.
Well, I think there's a few things that we get into there at the beginning, which is
she's created a digital Dropbox, which is proven that is confirmed.
Yes.
Just like I feel like everybody has a digital Dropbox.
I have a Dropbox.
Sure.
Right.
Also, you shouldn't you shouldn't need to say digital in front of Dropbox.
Also, Dropbox is a brand name, right?
It's an app.
It's Buzz marketing.
Oh, he works for Dropbox.
Holy shit.
New conspiracy.
New conspiracy theory right there.
This is deadly serious.
We should keep a running tally of new conspiracies.
Number one, Alex Jones works for Dropbox.
Right.
He is a secret agent for the Dropbox Corporation.
Yeah.
Okay.
So she created this Dropbox.
That's confirmed.
Where the Chinese could find out what she's going to do to them.
Right.
And then pay her to not do it.
I guess that I that's sort of the implication.
I feel like I can't argue with that.
Well, how could you?
Because that is so beyond the realm of possibility.
Now, why would you say that?
That's you seem like you're in denial.
So, okay.
First off, China is not a guy.
Yeah, it is.
It's not a guy.
He forms like Voltron.
Well, all of one billion parts.
Like I understand that he thinks of China as just like one dude.
Yeah.
Like if you asked him to name the Politburo in China, do you think he could?
I don't even know if that's a person or a building.
Well, it's a collective.
Like the Politburo, it's from Russia.
It's the governing body.
It's an oligarchy, basically.
Okay.
These are like, I don't know.
You could call them the Illuminati.
Okay.
Who sit around and talk about what it is they're going to do.
They are not one guy.
Like, and also...
But do they act as one?
Unified in attack and approach.
I assume that they get together and, you know, like...
Inspire?
That...
I hate to put words in your mouth.
I just lost to Alex Jones.
I don't think you did.
We are on one episode and it's Alex Jones one, me zero.
I don't think you did lose because the fundamental point
still remains that the idea that she created a digital
Dropbox where people could find out stuff.
See, that's how insidious he is.
We keep saying digital Dropbox.
Right.
It's smart.
It's the same.
It's essentially creating a verbal hashtag.
Right.
And again, this comes back to why he's a good broadcaster.
These are the elements that you have to take apart to see,
like, oh, this is what he's doing.
In the same way, and his cadence as well.
Everything, every single thing that he went through there
is easily capable of sticking in your mind.
Sure.
Like, I can't...
There's a hypnotic meter.
I know I can't get digital Dropbox out of my head now.
If somebody asked me to, hey, could you just put that
in my Dropbox?
I'd be like, wait, which Dropbox?
The digital one or the one that's underneath that park
bench over there?
Well, this is a bad example of it, but it is an old-fashioned
trick that oral tradition cultures would use.
In the same way that Alex, every time he talks about the
Chinese, he calls them the communist Chinese.
Right.
It's a trick called using an epithet.
And not necessarily like a negative epithet.
Right.
But it's just using something to characterize a noun
makes it stick in your memory more.
In the same way that they would always call Achilles
rage-filled Achilles or brave Odysseus in the Iliad
and the Odyssey, it's a really good trick when you don't
have paper to get people to remember things.
It's a mnemonic trick.
And he uses that so fucking well.
Digital Dropbox is probably not even intended to be like
that, but it still is.
To the point where you're distracted from the point that
there was a deal made.
Yeah.
No, all I can think about is where is this digital Dropbox?
Right.
The only way for this claim to be proven is for some
information.
Well, the digital Dropbox is confirmed.
Well, yes, but it's been confirmed through unconfirmed
channels or whatever, you know?
Yeah.
No, I feel like you can just find somebody who's like,
Oh yeah, I put something into that Dropbox.
No, no, no, no, no.
Only she put things in.
Everyone else put money in accounts.
Where?
You can't do it at a digital Dropbox.
Cayman Islands.
I don't know.
They don't know the foundation.
You make a donation to the foundation.
Ooh, that's some solid epithet right there.
The donation foundation.
That's just rhyming.
So, I mean, like the only way for it to be proven that
they like Hillary stepped down immediately because she was
afraid of this information of the digital Dropbox coming
out that Trump had over her.
And somehow Trump actually has all of the intelligence
agencies in his sway and all this.
The only way for that to ever come out is for the shit to
go down.
Yeah, well, it does.
If you know anything about the intelligence agencies and
the way they've been behaving, they kind of are on Trump's
side pretty solidly.
And then there's the thing that confused me is that he's
insisting that Hillary and the Democrats made a deal on
election night.
Uh huh.
He gives very few details by which I mean known about what
that deal entails.
So we know there's a deal.
We don't know what that deal is.
The next day they are betraying him, right?
We don't know how they're betraying him because we don't
know what their deal.
I think we can guess why, but why would they?
They're all globalists who are in the who are just hanging
out with China.
It makes no sense to make that deal to begin with.
If you're going to flip on it the next morning, I think it
makes perfect sense.
Oh, so he doesn't in his acceptance speech doesn't lay out
all this dirty laundry.
That would be wild at three in the morning.
That would be the greatest.
That would be crazy if he came out in his acceptance speech
with just and here's all the shit I have on Hillary now.
I was waiting to tell it to you guys until I got elected.
Yeah, if only they had made a deal with me two hours ago,
I wouldn't have said anything.
That fucking deal windows closed.
Hey, if they had betrayed me tomorrow, I would have been
fine as long as this deal happened tonight.
Okay, so they betrayed him and the Democrats, which again,
I feel like I feel like he's just using it as a guy.
Right, combo noun.
It is a guy in his mind.
It's a guy.
It's Schumer.
All Democrats are a guy.
They're all Chuck Schumer.
They're all Amy Schumer, actually.
Or Rahm.
But as we all know, let's be fucking honest.
It's George Soros.
That's who he thinks all Democrats are.
That is right.
That's who he thinks they all are.
In fact, that brings me to our next clip.
Excellent.
That was the greatest segue in the history of podcasts.
Thank you very much.
This clip is actually part of what I would claim to be a very
substantive, substantive narrative that has been going on forever on his show.
And it's something that I really take issue with because it's a good example
of a time where he uses something and references it and just lies about what it says.
So George Soros is essentially his big boogeyman.
He's his evil globalist madman.
So here's a little clip of Alex talking about George Soros on today's program.
The minute they take down Netanyahu, they're going after Trump.
So, hey, all of you that want to live under globalist Islamic rule,
all of you that hate Jews.
You're about to get a big, juicy taste of the globalist win of what it's going to be
like being under Saudi Arabia and communist China, politically calling the shots to the
Democrats who've openly made deals to sell us out to them.
Oh, and then have weirdo Nazi collaborators like George Soros, who's Jewish, sitting over it.
So, so, you know, get your anti-Semitism strike there.
You got this evil Dr. Evil over here running this whole takeover, who's Jewish,
and they're about to get rid of the Jewish state.
So just enjoy yourselves.
You got to taste rounding up Jews in World War Two, just so delicious.
Little Soros, he just can't stop.
And it's all the WikiLeaks.
And you know what?
The Jews haven't anything to stop him.
Hell, half the Jews are liberals love George Soros.
Hey, just have whatever you want, dumbasses.
So a couple of things that was a barrage of people all together on the same side.
So let's let's parse.
Wait, I want to say one thing before we parse.
OK.
I think that this this clip also contains one of my favorite fucking things in the world,
which is everyone is always surprised by commercial breaks.
They are never fucking ready for a commercial break,
but all of their commercials are just for their supplements.
It's all just for colloidal iodine, super male vitality.
It's all the in-house Infowars pills, but they never could plan it out.
I have no idea why those specific pills are the ones they're marketing.
Who could possibly be their target audience?
What's super awesome, too, is he often goes on jags about how, like, he turns down sponsors.
And it's like, you don't.
You fucking don't.
I guarantee that he only he only advertises products he uses.
Right.
Which he got he needs that and formal trouble through a male formerly gold.
Well, he used to he used to hock gold real hard,
but that was because he was on the GSN network, which is the Genesis
to communicate.
Oh, GCN, Genesis Communication Network.
Did he leave him because they became the genocide communication network?
I don't know.
I can't confirm or deny under the palm of George Soros.
Well, I just coming for Netanyahu, just to be clear.
The GCN was owned by by Gold Consortium.
So when he was I think he still is broadcast by them.
But now they've shifted over to this weird health food stuff.
OK.
So he used to be hawking gold.
And now they sell all this weird like, you know, all your body really needs is a couple
of these minerals, which totally is true, right?
It's all sold by this guy named Dr.
Wallach, who's actually if you actually look into Dr.
Wallach, he's a veterinarian who knows better what will affect the human body than somebody
who kills pets.
I'm a dog doctor.
Yeah, he's a he's a he's like a New Age doctor and veterinarian.
Never would have guessed.
Yeah, so never would have guessed.
If you look up the people who used to sell gold, their website now goes to his weird
health food stuff.
I've already that has Dr. Spiceman from 30 Rock written all over 100 percent.
Yeah.
So anyway, back to parsing.
Right.
All right.
So the my favorite my favorite thing that he said right there is George Soros got a
taste from World War Two Nazi Germany.
Yes.
He got a taste of genocide.
What camps?
Rounding up Jews.
And he's a Jew.
Are you aware of where that comes from?
Where that where what he's referencing?
No.
OK, so he references this all the time.
And in the same way when he talks about Nazi collaborator George Soros, it's the same
thing.
It's another epithet.
OK.
Sticks in your head easily.
Right.
So back back years ago, there was George Soros was interviewed on 60 Minutes and he was being
interviewed by what's this guy's name?
Croft.
Can't remember Croft's first name.
Who cares?
I remember him from the Croft Nixon interview.
Yes.
Steve Croft is interviewing him.
I will read you the transcript of that interview because I don't want to play the audio.
Right.
I just don't want to pull up more shit that I don't have ready.
You're a Hungarian Jew who escaped the Holocaust by posing as a Christian.
Right.
And you watch lots of people get shipped off to the death camps.
I was 14 years old and I would say that that's when my character was made.
In what way?
That one should think ahead.
One should understand and anticipate events.
And when one is threatened, it was a tremendous threat of evil.
I mean, it was a very personal threat of evil.
My understanding is that you went out in fact and helped in the confiscation of property
from the Jews.
Soros.
Yes, that's right.
Yes.
I mean, that sounds like an experience that would send lots of people to a psychiatric
couch for many, many years.
Was it difficult?
No.
Not at all.
Maybe as a child you don't see the connection.
But it created no problem at all.
No feeling of guilt?
No.
For example, that I'm Jewish and here I am watching these people go.
I could just as easily be these.
I should be here.
I should be there.
None of that?
And his response?
Well, of course.
I could be on the other side or I could be one from whom the thing is being taken away.
But there was no sense that I shouldn't be there because that was, well actually in a
funny way, it's just like in the markets.
That is, if I weren't there, of course I wasn't doing this, but somebody else would, would
be taking it away anyhow.
And it was the whatever, whether I was there or not, I was only a spectator.
The property was being taken away.
So I had no role in taking that property away.
So no sense of guilt.
Okay, so this, this interview.
Yes.
Alex Jones has taken a survival story.
Where it seems like Soros clearly dissociated.
A bit.
From his own personal identity as a measure of survival.
Yes.
He survives.
Yes, his father hid him with a Christian gentleman who was responsible for when Jews
were taken away, they would catalog their belongings.
It was thieving or whatever, but you got to imagine if you're a 14 year old kid, your
primary concern is making sure no one finds out you're a Jew.
Right.
Because you will be murdered.
And also where do you masturbate?
Sure.
Or pee.
Yeah, right.
Beyond that.
Jewish pee is different and they could smell it out.
The dicks, they're different.
So circumcision is the main selling point for Jews.
I don't know if I'd call it selling point.
I shouldn't have said selling point.
I should have said catching point or something, something along those lines.
There was another quote that was about that time in his life.
It was actually probably the happiest year of my life, that year of German occupation.
For me, it was a very positive experience.
It's strange, I think it says sage, but I think you meant strange.
It's a strange thing because you see incredible suffering around you and the fact that you're
in considerable danger yourself, but you're 14 years old and you don't believe that it
can actually touch you.
You have a belief in yourself.
You have a belief in your father.
It's a very happy making, exhilarating experience.
So people, Alex Jones in particular, takes these quotes to twist it to be like the happiest
time in his life was when he was helping Hitler round up Jews, which is false on two counts.
And I don't believe that Alex doesn't know that.
Okay.
He's citing these things.
Yeah, my first reaction on hearing that is that's some crazy shit.
Mm hmm. And clearly he's rich enough to be honest,
which if he was not like, imagine him as an actor saying that nonsense, he would be pilloried
for weeks.
Undoubtedly.
Right.
So he's rich enough to be like, hey, this was a hugely formative experience in my life.
It is one of the most tragic things that's ever happened.
And somehow because of those strange circumstances that I was in, it wound up being a positive
experience for me.
Mm hmm.
Okay.
That clearly means that he was in cahoots with Hitler himself and is trying to destroy
the Jewish state.
And because he was so happy, then he wants to recreate it.
Yeah.
Well, a hundred percent.
I mean, I remember growing up whenever I was being beaten regularly.
It was an exhilarating experience.
Well, exhilarating is some weird definitions.
No, it's an exhilarating experience, and I constantly try and recreate it.
Psychologically, that's unimpeachable logic.
But the traumas that we have in our lives often, if you have undergone some analysis,
some therapy, you don't necessarily think of them as horrible times in your life.
Bumps and bruises make you stronger.
There are tons of people who talk...
As do Holocausts.
Well, I mean, you're not responsible often for the cards you're dealt.
Whatever doesn't put you in an oven makes you stronger.
Sure.
Now, if someone does...
That is the end of this podcast.
We made it through one episode.
If someone does an after show of our after show, they're going to take that clip now.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I still think that is a piece of advice.
You can take it or leave it.
So this really bothers me quite a bit, because most of the...
Like, I'm not here to stand up for George Soros and say he's the best man in the world.
But this idea of painting him as a Nazi collaborator is incredibly irresponsible.
And the fact that I'm 100% sure that Alex Jones has watched the clips from that doc...
Or has watched that interview, has seen these things.
He knows what he was talking about.
The fact that he chooses to paint it as he was helping round up Jews
means that he's spinning a false narrative for a reason.
Right.
And that bothers me a lot.
Okay, so that puts us into lying territory versus deceiving territory.
Yes, propaganda territory.
Right.
Now, the other part of this that I love about him,
and you're absolutely right about him being a great broadcaster.
At no point in his entire show, I'm imagining,
does he ever actually get into why he would want this to happen?
Barely, if ever.
Right.
So he leaves it to your own imagination to make these connections of,
oh, well, clearly, if he survived the Holocaust, he also loved you and loved it.
Which is also a great movie title, Surviving the Holocaust and Loving It.
Dracula, Surviving the Holocaust and Loving It.
Leslie Nielsen as a slapstick young George Soros, but still that same age.
He went too young, that Leslie Nielsen.
Yeah, yeah.
He can't play it that young.
No.
He's a great actor, but...
I think he's dead.
He is dead.
Yeah.
So, you know, he'd be even better at it now.
Okay, so before we get...
Because we already got sidetracked.
He's a genius.
We already got sidetracked onto the nonsense he said.
But did you notice...
Instead of responding to the nonsense he said.
But you noticed that on the way to the stuff talking about George Soros, there was like...
Oh, there's 30 different mismatch.
Yeah, yeah.
He was throwing it at the wall.
He's throwing shit at the wall to see what sticks.
The stuff that he was talking about BB Netanyahu was...
Oh, he's the best.
Apparently the police questioned him over some corruption stuff that day on the second.
I'm having difficult times finding independent corroboration of that being anything serious.
It's difficult to say, but it does feed into the narrative that they already have built up with
the United States has turned their back on Israel with the sitting out of the UN vote.
Yeah, and the $35 billion.
$38 billion.
In military aid.
Right.
It's a very...
My position on that is Israel is an incredibly complicated situation
that I don't understand all the ins and outs of.
Right.
I do believe the Palestinians have rights.
How about that?
How does that grab you?
I don't know.
George Soros agrees with that and I feel like you're wrong there.
Oh, yeah.
George Soros is against rounding up.
What the thing that...
Before now, now I'm pissed off.
Also...
I just got hit with him saying that China and Saudi Arabia are on the same team.
Well, beyond that, also globalists are Islamists.
Well, yeah.
No, that we can skip over, because that's obvious.
Okay, so China and Saudi...
As everybody knows, Islamists are all for global relations.
Well, part of this anti-globalist sort of narrative,
one of the necessary pieces of it is that they have to create their own axis of evil.
Right.
And for them, in order to make Russia okay...
And it's super weird that they are calling themselves the axis of evil.
That's a big tip-off if the globalists are like,
Oh, we're totally evil.
Oh, yeah.
We're super...
I'm an evil Dr. Evil.
Right, exactly.
I believe that's how...
Again, I feel like he doesn't know Dr. Evil is fictional.
He's given me the Dr. Evil doesn't know he's fictional vibe.
Um, so he...
The alliance there, in order to make Russia okay,
is China, Saudi Arabia, North Korea, and some other countries.
Right.
But those are the ones that are the big problems, especially Communist China.
Those are the people we have to be worried about, just so Russia is cool.
Because Putin just wants prosperity.
Well, absolutely.
Yeah.
And also Putin's country is turning into a shithole.
Uh, that he's...
He's rampantly doing everything he can to direct every possible attention away from the fact
that Russia's economy is garbage right now.
In the toilet.
Yeah, and it has been for like ten years.
Well, I mean, Alex Jones even brings that up,
but he uses it as a deflection away from Russian tampering and hacking and stuff like that.
He's like, how can they do anything?
They have the GDP of Italy.
All right.
Well, yeah, but...
That's a solid deflection.
Yeah, but also Putin probably has like $200 billion or something like that.
Personally.
There's a lot of people hiding a lot of money.
I can't imagine.
The fact that the GDP is that low doesn't mean that there aren't the resources.
Like, there's a lot of dark money.
Uh, like, I don't know, like some of that money that went to that
Olympic stadium and the roads that were never actually built.
Sure.
Somebody got all that money.
Yeah.
Um, Communist China got all that money.
Absolutely.
That's what we know.
When Communist China and Saudi Arabia conspired to steal Sochi Olympics?
I guess.
What are we going with?
I don't know.
All right.
This is a conspiracy we're not going to be able to flesh out.
Communist China and Saudi Arabia.
Yes.
That...
Okay.
Did he plan to say that?
Probably not.
Has he said that before?
Has he ever combined Communist China and Saudi Arabia?
Uh, only as people he doesn't like.
Uh, like, I don't, I think that he mad libs that one.
Yeah.
He had to have just, I mean, even he, when he re-listened to that show, he was like,
Holy shit.
That's crazy.
I think it was that the spirit got good to him and he was just like, it was like, all
right, well, these words are coming out.
Whatever.
Lord, give me the Holy Spirit.
Tell me who I'm against.
Which is a perfect transition to this next clip.
Excellent.
So I think our segues are dominant.
This might be one of my favorite clips.
I don't want to do any set up.
Uh, ladies and gentlemen, that's what I said last week.
I said, if they kill Netanyahu or something, you know, world war three is about to happen.
Well, here it is.
And I told you, they're really thinking about arresting Trump.
They're really thinking about fault.
Remember all those rape charges and pedophile charges that were always fake names and were
never true.
And that's not entirely accurate.
No, that got dropped as soon as he won.
Claiming Jerry Epstein connections to him when it was really the Clinton and Hillary
and to both of them, really everything they're doing, they say we're doing.
So now this is zero hedge Israeli police internet.
Yahoo's home for questioning over corruption allegation.
Boy, you talk about canary in the coal line.
The globalist wouldn't move against Netanyahu's.
WikiLeaks shows they're planning to do via Soros if they weren't planning to have people
ready to imprison him or kill him if he starts trying to spill the beans on stuff.
Because Netanyahu has been involved in everything.
Good, bad, ugly, you name it.
And if they're if they move against Netanyahu, that means they're moving against Trump.
Bet your bottom buck.
Whoa.
No, that's not it.
We're readable.
Just red alert, red alert, red alert.
This is getting crazy.
This is so frickin out of control.
It's time to pray.
Our Heavenly Father, please help.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please protect the children.
How dare you get in the way of his prayer?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I have to go back now.
I'm sorry.
This is this is on air.
Start start the prayer again.
And he when he does that, it's time to pray.
He immediately like like puts his hand over his face and makes it.
He acts like he's going to cry.
It's astounding.
This is so frickin out of control.
It's time to pray.
Our Heavenly Father, please help us open our eyes.
Please help us be good.
We're so sorry for all the abortions and all the evil in our name.
Please protect the children.
Please reprieve us if it's in your will.
Please somehow stop the evil forces that are trying to stop this miracle that you've given us.
Please help there be peace in the Middle East.
Please stop those who are trying to overthrow Israel and start World War Three and bring in Armageddon.
Please give us a reprieve like Nineveh that we have time to wake people up and reach out to
those that are still in darkness and deceive.
Please in the name of your son.
Jesus Christ, lead God and direct us on in.
And I don't do that for show, folks.
I don't want to be here.
I am so upset right now that my head is burning.
I am sweating.
Even though it's like 65 degrees in here, I am so pissed.
Well, he might be sweating in 65 degree temperatures because he's taking too much goddamn super
male vitality. It's entirely possible or that he's coked out.
I have no idea, but first thing you say after publicly praying is I don't do that for show.
Right on your literal show.
You're doing that for show.
You're 100% doing it for show.
But I would listen to any techno remix of it's time to pray.
It's time to pray.
What a showman.
God, that's so good.
I want to be super clear about this, too.
I don't mean to beat up on religion.
I don't want to mock someone just for being religious.
Religion is a great thing when used right.
Like, it does bring a lot of meaning to a lot of people's lives, and hooray.
But I do take great issue with the idea that it's being used to, basically, for show.
Yeah, well, I mean, just the fact that you responded that way means it's time to pray.
Dear God, I just want to...
I'm so sorry about abortions.
Why did he start with abortions?
Where did that come from?
This is a stream of consciousness rant.
Okay, let's start at the beginning.
Why is Netanyahu the canary in the coal mine?
Because once they come for Israel, that means Trump's next.
Yeah, but why would you go for Israel first?
There's an internal logic to it that's never explained.
But, okay, so you're coming for Netanyahu.
Because he's got all the dirt.
He knows the good and bad things that everyone's done.
So you've got to take him out first so he can't spill the beans.
So, again, the good, the bad, the ugly, he's got all of it.
Yes.
Where, why, and how did he get any of it?
He's been around the game forever, so he has all of it.
But that's not a thing that...
You can't just say, I've been around the game,
so I know the secrets of every nation on the planet.
Yeah, but you can if no one calls you on it.
That's a good point.
That's a good... here is the fundamental disconnect,
is that I feel like before I say something,
I should have at least the barest understanding of why that thing is occurring.
Uh-huh.
So like when you make a public claim.
Right.
Yeah.
And even if it's dumb and relatively uninformed,
I've got a reason for thinking it, you know?
Even if you're saying it as a joke.
Right, right.
Yeah, even then, well, before we go any further,
it's time to break.
That's never...
Already two awesome sound drops.
...never not gonna be funny.
I love you.
It's time to break.
Oh god, that song is amazing.
When I was watching this, I lost my shit at work at that moment.
Like I was just like...
Like if I were writing a character,
I couldn't come up with something funnier than
yelling about how World War III is coming,
taking a long pause.
It's time to break.
Okay, all right.
Let me ask you, before we go any further...
Ending it with defending praying.
Right.
Amazing.
No, no, no.
Not defending praying.
Right.
Saying that it is not for show.
Oh, by the way...
This is a 100% genuine need to pray moment.
By the way, that's sincere, folks.
Have you ever...
Also, that's a super professional wrestling move.
Like you can see somebody walking into the ring and being like,
hey, before we wrestle, it's time to pray.
No, no, no, no.
It would have to be like, now.
The Undertaker's been trying to get me for years now.
There's a cabal.
He's got an evil group.
Maybe we call them the Ministry of Darkness.
And they're gonna come get me.
We're talking about Viscera.
We're talking about the big boss man.
Once you get Viscera out, that's the canary in the coal mine.
And Undertaker's coming for me.
It's time to pray.
Because you've got to say all the negative stuff first.
I am going to hear that 10 million times before I go to sleep tonight.
I'm just gonna...
In my brain, it's now in a loop.
I'll send you an isolated clip.
Oh, God.
Any time I am in a bad move, I will just pull that up on my phone and be like,
oh, no, no, life is good.
Yeah.
Okay, so here we go.
They're coming for Netanyahu first, and if they get to Netanyahu first,
that's not gonna be enough to destabilize everything?
No.
You gotta then go after Trump.
Right.
Why are those two connected?
Or how are those two connected?
I feel like it's so implied.
I don't know why you're such a libtard.
Have they ever met?
Yeah, of course.
When?
Of course.
Okay, so they've never met.
Has Trump ever stated before any positive feelings towards Israel?
I think he's tweeted a bunch.
And he spoke at APEC. Yeah, yeah, he's come out in favor of Israel.
Well, but we're all in favor of Israel.
He's also said some negative things about Obama's handling of, you know,
like backing away from Israel in the UN vote.
Right.
Like, I believe, what was his tweet?
Like, hey, hold tight, like everything's gonna be different after the 20th.
Right.
Which was both in reference to Russia and to...
... Israel.
Which is, it is nice that they have the luxury of being like,
hey, we can weather the next 20 days because eventually we've got Trump
who's just gonna do whatever it is we say, basically.
Sure, he's a weird, undefined variable that'll do whatever we want.
Okay, so, but then let's, here's the thing that drives me insane.
Your prediction was right.
This show is gonna be two hours long.
Yeah, does anybody ever war games this?
What do you mean by that?
I mean, okay, so they kill Netanyahu.
So you're asking, do we ever AB this thing?
Right.
What happens next?
Kill Netanyahu, then what happens?
No, no, no, not necessarily that.
You could just Shanghai him somewhere.
Right.
You could just rendition his ass.
Well, you could, I don't know, arrest him on corruption charges that you trumped up.
Right, but then at the same time, if the whole thing is that he's got tons of dirt,
you would have to kill him, right?
I mean, based on what he's saying, in order for the narrative, Alex Jones is spinning.
Unless he kept that dirt in a digital drop box.
Could be.
Then you can find it.
Or take out his neck.
Like, just don't kill him, but make it so he can't talk.
Okay, I can see that.
Like Roadhouse, they're gonna rip his throat out.
And then that'll be a message to anyone else who wants to talk.
You know what I'm saying?
Right.
I mean, unless he has access to a computer.
Or paper.
Or, yeah, or a typewriter.
That's a good point, there's a lot of possibilities.
So you gotta cut off his hands.
You gotta cut off his hands and feet.
Because you can learn how to write with your feet.
And they're in league with the Saudi Arabians, who are notorious for cutting off hands.
Right.
Or at least they were in the movie Aladdin.
But you also then have to remove his eyes, because some people can text-a-type with their eyes.
Oh, that guy wrote that whole book with his eyes.
Right, exactly.
So you gotta remove those.
Yeah, shit.
Now, unfortunately...
What about toes?
We're also...
We've already removed his feet.
Okay.
I've already established that we're removing his feet.
I missed that thinking about the man from Ali Babwa.
Right.
Aladdin.
Prince Ali.
Ali Ababwa.
So, which...
Why did they mispronounce...
They blatantly...
Okay, all right.
Let's get rid of the whole Alex Jones angle and go directly into this podcast is about the movie Aladdin.
Yeah.
All right, all right.
But then we also have the technology now where we can read brain scans and turn that into
type.
Right.
It's still...
It's in infancy stages, but I'm assuming, if you know everything about everybody...
Right.
You got an in there.
We're coming full circle now to...
He's been there for the good, the bad, and the ugly of...
It's gotta be murder then.
Yeah, it's gotta be murder.
Okay, so then your War Games scenario, you've gotta murder Phoebe.
So you murder Netanyahu.
Yeah.
And then Israel is...
What?
Yeah.
And so, but even then, if they murder Netanyahu...
Who's the next leader waiting in the wings?
It's not someone who has any different philosophies.
Right, and let me ask you a question.
Is that our job or is it Alex Jones' job to know who the next person in line...
It's certainly not mine.
I'm not making any claims.
Frankly, I don't know many of my aldermen.
Let's put it that way.
I know almost none of them.
I've recently found out who my representatives are because I've felt the need to call them.
I think that's a good idea.
Yeah.
If there's one thing that we can learn, it's don't call Alex Jones.
No.
Call your state representative.
But if you do call Alex Jones and you tell him you love him...
I love you.
I wish that the caller had been like, I know you do.
That would have been gorgeous.
He pulls the whole Empire Strikes Back move.
Yeah, so there are, you know, there are people calling in, you mentioned that.
So you might be asking yourself about this time.
Who listens to the Alex Jones show?
People who need virility pills.
Certainly, if you want a discount on boner pills.
I think it's boner pills, right?
Yeah, it's boner.
It's super male vitality.
Virility or vitality is boner pills.
He talks about how, like, you get your libido going.
It's got to be, I don't know if it is, but I think it might be boner pills.
It has to be.
Or it might just be like a shit ton of testosterone.
I've done some research on Quantcast and Alexa.
Don't know what that is.
There are two websites that are basically, they keep statistics on websites for advertising purposes.
Okay.
So if you want to sell ads, you can quote your Quantcast rating and stuff like that.
Right.
I've done some research on what kind of traffic his website actually gets.
Okay.
And it's substantially lower than he says.
Can't imagine how that would occur.
There are, like, he generally has...
Are you saying he exaggerates or perhaps outright lies about something?
Yeah, if you go, he has like 200 to 300,000 hits a day, unique hits on his website,
which is still great.
That is pretty good.
That's a lot.
Yeah.
Uh, but then whenever, like, a cop is killed, it goes up to about a million.
Of course.
Because, you know, you're getting all that viral content out there,
and you're reeling in the racists with the thug cop killer narratives,
and that drives a lot of traffic.
But you can see spikes in his traffic whenever, and like,
oh, let's Google that date, see what happened.
They're like, oh, boom, okay.
That was when Dallas happened, you know, shit like that.
But...
Which was also a false flag operation initiated by Hillary Clinton and the Globalist.
Absolutely.
She put that into her digital dropbox.
WikiLeaks found it.
They all know that the plot to kill Netanyahu is orchestrated by Communist China
and Islamist Saudi Arabia working in concert to put this all together.
And who is behind both of those?
Soros.
Soros!
The Nazi-loving Jew.
Now, actually, I think this podcast just ended because I nailed it.
I got it.
Also, Soros is claimed to be fund...
I mean, he does donate to Black Lives Matter.
He does support that group, but they act like,
because he gives money to help that cause,
that they're his goon squad, kind of.
It's insane and very racist.
I buy it.
You're asking yourself this question, who's listening?
And Alex has a couple answers for you.
Okay.
For our next clip, who is listening?
Who's listening to this show?
Doesn't Hillary know when she attacks me?
And when they say I'm all these bad things and lie about me
and have all their paid shills put out all this info?
Don't they know that only makes everybody two and more?
He was so close to just making up any name for paid shills.
He's like, they're paid shills and then pauses and be like,
oh no, it left me, I can't see Saudi Arabia again.
He could have just as easily said, correct the record.
Like that Hillary...
Oh, absolutely.
I mean, that was something that was proven.
Absolutely.
But he could have thrown that out there.
Would have been easy.
Throw media matters under the bus if you want.
Yeah, but you know, he's had a long day.
I will give him that.
I think those two things are also too related to Pizzagate now.
And I don't think he wants to touch that one.
Yeah, was that his fault indirectly?
Did he start the whole Pizzagate thing?
Or was it a random tweet that he turned into the echo chamber?
I think that after that guy showed up at that pizza place with a gun,
it was a hot potato and he had to drop it.
They had to clean the website of all of the mentions of it.
They got rid of all of it.
Well, not all of it, but all of their like main reporting on it.
All the stuff where he was talking about it being something that needs to be investigated
and citizen investigators do something about it.
Shit like that.
So he said the things that happened and then he was like, ooh, I wish they hadn't happened.
And the guy, Joe Biggs, was a guy who used to work for him
and he got fired around the same time and he was on the Pizzagate beat.
So there's a little bit of suspiciousness.
They've both put out videos talking about how like,
no, I didn't get fired.
I'm going on to bigger and better things.
I got movies I'm writing.
We'll see.
Maybe that's the case.
That is classic.
I got fired from the TV show.
You know, it was time for me to move on.
I feel like my future is in feature films.
Yeah.
I've already had a couple of meetings.
I won't tell you who they're with.
Nope.
But, you know, and frankly, it's really just about me.
I've made all of my money.
It rhymes with Barney Bernstein.
I don't even care if I meet with George Soros about producing these films.
The thing that made it stink to high heaven was Alex put out a video where he was talking
about how talented Joe Biggs was and stuff like that.
I was like, dude, like you're just, you're the canary in the coal mine now.
Now you're saying this.
I know it's not true.
Right.
He has dirt on you.
I love you.
It's time to pray.
Let's watch the rest of this clip.
Here we go.
And I don't even mean the general public.
The general public's important and there's someone awake now.
But the people that do the hanging, the military, the police, the bureaucrats, the judges,
the lawyers, the congresspeople, they all listen.
The Russian government listens.
The British government listens.
The Israeli government listens.
The Pakistani government listens.
The Japanese government listens.
The communist Chinese listen and hate my guts because they know, folks, this is the real
place.
I don't want to differentiate myself and say this is the only place you really get information
of this magnitude.
It's the only place you get it this strong, this focused, this dedicated, this continual.
We don't take breaks around here.
I don't.
I would like to point out after him saying he doesn't take breaks, he had someone else
host the fourth hour of the show.
And he pretty routinely has people host the fourth hour.
Well, and he also doesn't want to say that, you know, he's putting himself as the only
voice, but, uh, you know.
But I'm the only voice.
He's the only voice.
I don't want to say it.
I'll let other people say it for me, specifically the Pakistani government.
That's an amazing level of narcissism.
Question.
Does he know who anyone in the Pakistani government?
Uh, maybe one guy.
All right.
Does he know the capital of Pakistan?
Uh, Khartoum?
I don't know.
Is that right?
I have no idea.
I don't know the capital of Pakistan.
That's a capital of something.
I thought you said Khartoum and we're back on Aladdin, so there's that.
Ali Ababwa.
I'm pretty sure he's from Pakistan.
That might be racist.
It's not racist.
It's getting there.
I know I took a geography class in high school and I know, like, four country capitals still.
And that's it.
I don't know Pakistan's.
I don't remember.
Because it's not fun to say.
No.
Burkina Faso's capital?
Ouagadougou.
That's pretty fun to say.
So fun.
That is fun to say.
Madagascar?
Antananarivo.
Oh, yeah.
I know Antananarivo.
So fun.
It features heavily in the Civilization games.
Honduras?
Tugulgegalpa.
Really?
I might be out.
That is good.
That's my high school.
So none of the big ones?
None of...
Like what?
I know Brazil is Brasilia, right?
Don't know.
Okay.
I mean, like, European nations...
Like which ones?
I mean, pick...
Name one.
France?
That's Paris.
You're rolling your eyes.
Is that the capital?
You have no idea.
Probably.
I feel like it's the same way where people are like...
What do you think the capital is?
The capital of California is LA.
No, it's Sacramento.
We all know that.
Exactly.
Well, we don't all know that.
Some of us do.
You know who doesn't want to know that?
The globalists.
That's true.
So actually, Alex has...
Or Saudi Arabia or the Pakistani government.
Definitely not the Communist Chinese.
Before we do anything, can we go back to the list?
Just isolate the list.
Because the next time we record, I'm gonna have to take notes.
Doesn't Hillary know she attacks me?
Oh, do you want me to play it or are you...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Isolate just the clip of him listing...
The police, the bureaucrats, the judges...
No, hold up.
Before that.
Go back one second.
They all listen.
The people who do the hanging.
Yeah.
What is that?
What does that mean?
I think it means people who are hanging out.
I hope.
I fucking hope.
That can't mean the people who do the hanging.
Like, I think he's talking about stringing people up.
Yeah, he very nearly said lynching.
Yeah.
No, no, no, no.
Let's not...
Well, that would be racially charged.
And I want to defend Alex when it's appropriate, and that's not fair of you.
He wasn't going to say lynching.
No, you're right.
He wasn't going to it, but yeah.
Because...
I was pulling that...
That would be ascribing racism in a situation where he's just being wacky.
You're absolutely right.
And he is wrong.
Yes.
But also, the people who do the hanging still makes no sense.
The people who do the hanging are the military, the police.
So he starts with those as the people who do the hanging.
The judges, the bureaucrats.
The lawyers.
But I think he has to mean that...
The government, the Pakistani government, the communist Chinese who hate him.
Right.
I like how he singled them out for hating him.
But they listen.
Like, the Pakistani government is like,
eh, we like that guy.
Also, the implication seems to me to be that, like,
all 10,000 people who work in government listen to him.
Yeah.
No fucking way they get any work done if they're listening four hours a day to his pill ads.
They have to.
They have to listen to him.
Because it's his only place.
Because he's the only place.
He doesn't want to say it.
Yeah.
But he is the only place that gives it to you this focused.
Well, I think...
Which is my favorite thing he said.
This focused.
Yeah, he's not focused at all.
As he's just rambling on about different...
All the governments that he knows were in that list.
If we keep doing this, I will make a supercut of all the times he says,
I've got to get to this story.
And then not get to it.
Because it happens 10 times a day, at least.
But see, again, that's another brilliant move, because it builds you up.
It does the same thing that local news always does, where it's like,
this story is about kittens.
Stay tuned.
Are your children dying?
You know, like that kind of a thing.
Yeah, there's a comedian named Ron Raimi who would do a similar trick rhetorically on stage.
Yeah.
He would do like a, I gotta go.
Like this sort of thing that teased like, he's gonna be leaving any minute now.
Right.
So we gotta pay attention to this guy before he goes.
It's the same thing.
In the first five minutes of a 45 minutes.
Yeah, and then by the time you caught on to it, you liked the trick.
Right.
So it becomes like, he's not gonna leave, but we like this.
It's the same thing.
It's a call and response.
I've got so much to get to.
Right.
It's got this big story here.
And you never get to it.
You just have more fucking pill ads.
But listen, Jordan, I feel like you don't believe that these people listen to his show.
And for your bitch ass, Alex has some more words.
I am suspicious, but let's see where we go.
Well said, there's a new Washington Post article by their editors saying Trump reading info
wars can tank markets, start wars, basically.
And we put that headline back up.
They're getting ready to tank the markets.
They're raising interest rates to tank the markets.
They're getting ready to knock out the power grid.
They're going to blame Trump.
They're going to blame the Russians.
Everything they do, everything they blame us of is what they're really planning.
And Washington Post editor, Trump reading info wars.
I want to take a break really quick to point this out that he says that all the fucking
time, which leads me to believe that the inverse is true.
Well, yeah.
Whatever they say we're doing is what they're doing.
Right.
When it's like, it kind of feels like that applies to you.
I'm rubber, you're glue.
Yeah.
It reminds me of when my brother would do something when we were kids and then accuse
me of doing it to our parents.
Right.
Like it reminds me of very adolescent bullying techniques.
Then he he brings this up over and over and over and over again.
This like idea that the globalists accuse him of the things they're doing.
It's insane or whatever.
Anyway.
So Trump reads info wars.
Trump reads info wars to tank the markets, invite incursions.
Why do you think Trump reads info wars?
Let me just go ahead and tell the mainstream media because they don't seem to figure it
out.
It's not just Flynn that listens and reads info wars.
It's all of them dummies.
I'm not bragging.
And by the way, the generals don't learn anything from me.
There's only a couple websites like WorldNetDaily, drugsreport.com, Breitbart, info wars that
they can go read that they know are real.
You understand that dumb ass?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
God, I apologize.
I'm not trying to be like that.
I'm so angry for my normal filters.
Okay.
And I started thinking about the new world order.
I get really angry.
The generals all listen stupid.
The foreign governments listen stupid because they know we know what we're talking about.
We're dead on.
I don't say that from some ego perspective.
I wish I was wrong.
He also says that a lot.
He would never say it from an ego perspective.
No, he's not doing this for show.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
I wish I was wrong is almost like a hook on his rap song.
I wish I was wrong.
And then, I mean, if you want to guys, if you're listening.
Nick Dogg came to life to sing the hook on that.
I wish I was wrong.
Go to YouTube and just search Alex Jones failed predictions.
And there's wonderful compilations of like a hundred times.
He's been so fucking wrong about everything.
The idea of-
Then his wish come true.
We should all be so lucky.
Right?
His wishes are, he's-
Also everyone, if you hear my voice, I don't want to play it on the show.
Although maybe one time we should do it for a special episode.
Okay.
Do yourselves a favor and go fucking listen to the Y2K episode of Alex Jones' show.
It's on YouTube.
There was a Y2-
He's been doing this for how long?
Like 25 years.
Holy goddamn shit.
Yeah, so on December 31st, 1999,
he was creating a panic and trying to get people to riot, essentially.
Wow.
Yeah, he was feeding into a lot of like real horrible paranoia.
And what's interesting now, he talks about how like Russia is, you know, sort of good guys.
Right.
He's on board with Russia.
As we all know they are.
In his Y2K broadcast, he's talking about how Putin, this guy Putin the ruthless is evil.
He's talking all this shit on this guy who flash forward 17 years.
17 years is a long time, number one.
Now, number two, here is my favorite thing about the Russian paranoia right now.
Because that is like the flip on that was so fast.
What do you mean by that?
Well, I mean, the right wing was crazy.
Like the moment the Cold War ended, they wanted to start a new Cold War.
So now because of the whole Trump thing, now Democrats are all on this,
oh, Russia tampered with the election.
And they probably did in some fashion.
Sure.
Whether or not it was like a direct thing or an indirect thing.
The one problem I have with it all is that just like he says,
we've done all the same shit, man.
America's done all of that.
We've done worse, probably.
Well, I mean, we've deposed many governments.
Unjustified wars, but we...
Yeah, there's a reason the term Banana Republic was not invented by the wonderful clothing store.
Yeah.
Sponsor us.
It is because we overthrew a few governments for, you know,
our corporations to sell bananas.
For Chiquita.
Yeah, exactly.
Or Dole.
So I get where they're coming from, and it's always worse when it happens to you,
but it's such a hugely hypocritical concept.
Well, the difference is, I think you and I would be fair about that,
is that we recognize that the government has done very horrible things.
But I also, I would take the side that it is worse that it's happening to us.
Because if we're gone, or if we're in some weird flux state,
it does destabilize things a great deal.
Right, absolutely.
Now, I don't think that it, you know,
given the entire stretch of history and how long the world is, essentially,
the time of the world is.
Well, 6,000 years.
And if you don't believe that, it's time to pray.
It's time to pray.
We will have to go down at some point, right?
I mean, it's just, it's natural.
You know, kingdoms come and go, as it were.
Well, and we're clearly tearing ourselves down as we speak.
Sure.
I mean, what is it, the average lifespan of every sort of kingdom,
or big colonial power is about 200 years, and then it starts to fall apart, basically?
Isn't that the sort of guideline?
You know, I couldn't say, because, you know,
the big histories are written about people who lasted, you know,
a thousand years or whatever it is.
But even those ones have discrete periods within them.
Oh, absolutely.
So they're, but all I mean.
Like, if you want to go through the history of Chinese government,
that is one of the most fascinating, you know.
The Three Kingdoms period.
Yeah, the different dynasties, the Zhou, the Qin, like, that's all good stuff.
Which we don't respect at all as history, because it's so weird and different to us.
No, I don't like it.
Because it's interesting, but it's not about us.
Right.
You know?
But because they're the communist Chinese.
Also, if you were to learn anything about history, you would then have to apply it to now,
and that would mean changing a lot of the ways you think about stuff.
It also requires you to load in a bit of empathy.
Yeah, I'm way against that.
That's troubling to some.
Well, see, because if you're empathetic, you know,
then what they're doing is everything that you're doing.
Yeah.
I would say that no matter what, I still don't want us to go down right now,
because it would be very unpleasant for me.
Yeah, I mean, that is...
If it has to happen, let it happen after I'm dead.
I'm not gonna have any kids.
I do think there is a part of mortality where it is like,
you know, if I have to die, I feel like everybody should go with me, right?
Well, sure, I remember when I used to smoke a lot of weed,
me and a couple friends would sit around,
and one of the things we always were like super fascinated by
is the idea of being able to see the end.
Like, what a privilege that would be to be one of the humans who gets to see it all end.
Yeah, yeah, that would be cool.
There's something to be said for that, but I still don't want it.
No.
I'd rather live, or I'd rather it happen when I'm like 90.
Right, right, right.
It would be good to already be dying, and then everything else starts dying, too.
That would be pretty fun.
Yeah, that'd be boss.
Yeah.
Um, okay, so here's another narrative piece,
back to in the same vein as the George Soros thing.
Now, hold up one second.
Sorry.
Before we go any further.
Yeah.
Here is why Trump reads Infowars was never answered.
Nope.
He brought up, here's why Trump did this,
then immediately switched over to Flynn.
Yeah.
I am so mad, and he was supposed to answer why, and I want to know.
You know why?
Because, again, the spirit got too good to him.
Yeah.
It's this thing that gets in him.
The boogie woogie bandit comes in and takes over.
But I would have accepted literally any explanation.
He can't fucking explain why Trump listens,
because it's too important to let you know that everyone listens, dummy.
Okay, that's true.
Dummy, you dumb, dumb person.
But he could have made up anything, and because it's Trump,
I probably would have been, at the very least, entertained that notion.
Sure.
Should be like, hey, you know why he listens?
We gave him a free password.
Yeah, or not even that, just like, do you know why he listens?
Because everybody's got to read something on the toilet every day.
Like, I don't know.
That would be a real disappointing reveal.
Yeah, that's true.
He would never reveal that.
He did say, you know, I'm going to tell you why he listens,
and the mainstream media can't figure this out,
so you do expect it's going to be something big.
Right.
I guess the answer is that he listens because everyone important listens.
Everyone important listens.
Yeah.
But that's not a why.
Dummy, dummy.
Unless you're saying it's like a peer pressure thing.
Well, no, no, no, no, I think you're being unfair.
Even then, Trump doesn't even go to intelligence briefings.
Nope, because he gets all he needs.
And since they obviously listen to InfoWars.
Everyone does.
Wouldn't they be briefing him on InfoWars every day?
So far, the only person I have evidence doesn't listen to InfoWars?
You.
From a very forensic standpoint, I guess you're correct there.
And my cat.
I guess you're correct.
I try and keep it away from her.
She doesn't need this.
That's good.
It's really stressful.
I think you're being slightly unfair.
Just a tiny bit.
Not very unfair, but I think you're being a tiny bit unfair
because there is an implied answer in there.
And that is that Zero Hedge, Bright Bart, Drudge, and Alex Jones
are the only people who give actual news.
OK, so that's why Trump listens to InfoWars.
Yes.
Because he needs the actual news.
That's the implied answer to that question,
which he doesn't really spell out, but he kind of does.
That's another narrative that's going on.
I was going to go to this other one about,
I'm just going to cut this from what we need to cover,
because I don't even need to play the audio.
He just basically says that recess appointment,
it's about Merrick Garland being put into the Supreme Court
as a recess appointment.
Rich, we can only goddamn hope.
I mean, I think so.
It is the, or at least have a fair shot.
I would rather it go and be debated and what have you,
but Alex's point is that it's,
now we're fucking talking about it,
so I might as well play the clip.
Right.
All right.
Because I don't want to act like I'm putting words in his mouth.
Right.
Gotcha.
Now this just broke.
It's up on InfoWars.com.
It's up on DrudgeReport.com.
Obama still could force Merrick Garland onto the court
during intercession recess.
So no president's ever done stuff like this,
but they're talking about with 17 days left,
trying to force a new individual onto the Supreme Court.
So the part that-
Definitely not true.
A hundred percent.
George Washington made a recess appointment.
I don't remember that.
That was clearly before the constitution was written.
President, since George Washington have made recess appointments,
Washington appointed South Carolina Judge John Rutledge
as Chief Justice of the United States
during the congressional recess in 1795.
Hmm.
Uh, because of-
Yeah, but that was, that was, he was, he was, uh, you know,
still in the infancy.
He was, he was making some mistakes.
Because of Rutledge's political views and occasional mental illness,
however, the Senate rejected his nomination
and Rutledge attempted suicide and resigned.
Oh, I love American history so much.
Beyond that, New Jersey Judge William J. Brennan
was appointed to the Supreme Court by President Dwight D. Eisenhower
in 1956 by a recess appointment.
Never heard of him.
Uh, buh buh buh buh.
I mean, Eisenhower.
George H.W. Bush appointed Lawrence Eagleberger
as Secretary of State during recess in 1992.
That was clearly too far back for Alex Jones to have read.
President Ronald Reagan made 240 recess appointments,
an average of 30 per year.
President H.W. Bush made 77 recess appointments,
an average of-
Do you mean George W.?
H.W.
Oh, H.W.
Made 19 per year, basically 77 total.
Bill Clinton made 109, or 139 recess appointments,
an average of 17 per year.
President George W. Bush made 171 recess appointments,
an average of 21 per year.
And as of January 5th, 2012, President Barack Obama
had made 32, the least of anyone on this list,
an average of 4.5 per year.
But that does not matter.
But all of the Obama information always
winds up to being, Obama's a dictator, and he's doing this,
but it's always the least of anybody else.
That doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
The least recess appointments, the least vacation days,
all these things he's a tech for.
No, he played golf one time, so he's the worst.
The statistics don't match up, but the reason
that I have included this in terms
of this list of false narratives is it's-
One quick question.
He can't not know the facts.
He can't not know that.
I absolutely disagree.
No.
He absolutely does not know about recess appointments.
I would guarantee that.
You think it's like you're telling a Supreme Court
justice to go play foursquare?
You think that's what he thinks?
I, well-
Tether ball?
Did you say any, like it was George Washington
who did the Supreme Court.
The first one, yeah.
Were there any other Supreme Court other than Eisenhower?
I don't know.
I didn't do a full investigation.
Because he's clearly not going to pay attention
to any recess appointment that's not the Supreme Court.
But you could do any cursory amount of research
and find these facts.
Yeah, but he's not going to-
He has a team.
Recess appointments are not going to be something
that he researched.
He has a fucking team.
But they're not there to learn things or to learn.
They're not there to develop a-
Truth?
No, no, no, not even that.
They're there to develop a narrative.
So their entire job is to filter out information
that supports them from information that doesn't.
Right.
I get you.
What gets to Alex Jones is probably more the former
than the latter.
Yeah, but you undercut-
So you're telling me that Alex Jones is doing
any of his own research.
I hope so.
I hope some.
Do you believe that?
Yeah.
Genuinely, you've listened to his show.
This is the hardest question I've ever been asked.
Do you truly believe that Alex Jones does his own research?
Maybe he did way back when he didn't have the All-Star team.
Yeah.
But now, has he done any research for the past 10 years?
It's tough to say.
In my heart of hearts, I have to believe he's done some,
but not much.
When was the last full book that he finished?
And I'm not saying that as like a dig for,
oh, I read and other people don't.
I'm just saying that he does a four hour show.
I would guess.
He has an all day thing.
I very much doubt he has time to really go through
all of this stuff.
Well, I would guess that it's probably none dare call it
a conspiracy.
The book that radicalized him in junior college.
That's true.
He's probably read that 100 times since then.
That's possible.
I bet that's the case.
But even then, and his team's research,
is that are they researching historians
or are they aggregating information
that is on the internet?
And they're going to get yelled at if they come up
with something that doesn't fit.
Oh, absolutely.
If they say one part of the narrative,
if they say one thing that doesn't fit the narrative,
because then they get fucking Joe Biggs out of there.
Right.
Well, that's the thing.
That is the situation with belief.
If you, once you get to a certain point,
you're building a house of cards.
So everything has to support that foundation.
Otherwise, the whole thing, if just one piece of information
that doesn't support the narrative,
and the whole thing goes down.
Right.
So even if, and again, even if he did discover that
in his research, there is almost always going to be
a part in his mind that turns that into something
that actually supports his narrative.
I don't like that you're saying, because to mine ears,
I hear this as a very positive statement about him.
How so?
Because what you're saying is he doesn't know
that he's willfully deceiving about recess appointments.
I would argue that ignorance is far worse
in a broadcast situation than direct lying.
No, I think direct lying is worse,
because that means you're doing it for a reason.
Do you agree with me?
But he is doing it for a reason.
But do you agree with me?
And he's getting paid well for it.
It's a good gig.
Yeah.
I mean, who knows how much he's making
for those fucking weirdo pills.
The truth of broadcasters, and this is the way it is on TV,
and any kind of broadcaster, is if you listen to any
of their personal interviews, most of them imply,
and some of them have said, on a good day,
I believe 40% of what I say.
That's the job.
Maybe podcasting is different.
I believe pretty much everything I say.
Well, yeah, but we're not being paid a lot of money.
Nope, certainly not.
To say whatever it is we're told to say.
I wanted to make the premise of this show
that we pretend that George Soros is paying us,
but it's too late now.
Ooh, yeah, no.
We've already-
Next episode, we'll-
I've actually already kind of implied
that George Soros did commit the entire Holocaust.
Um, OK, so it's time for a couple of grab bag clips.
Oh, god, we're going to need some music for that.
Bam, bam, bam, bam, we're staying.
We're going to need some morning zoo crew,
like, bam, bam, bam, boom, boom, boom.
One of these days I'll buy a soundboard
and we'll just have all that.
Oh, the moment you do that, that's the end of this podcast.
We're just going to play with the soundboard
for the entire time.
So one of this, I don't remember exactly what
these two clips are, but I know that the first one
is offensive, so-
Oh, god damn you, I love you.
Would you rather go-
I love you.
Would you rather go mystery first or offensive first?
Um, you know what?
I feel like we have to go offensive
because we got to leave people with the mystery, right?
Oh, no.
Oh, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, all right, all right.
See what I'm saying?
Yeah, yeah, I got you.
Here you go.
This is offensive.
Obama's refusal to veto anti-Israel UN vote
ranked most anti-Semitic incident in 2016.
You know, I don't want to say it's anti-Semitic,
but funding jihadis all over the Middle East
to kill every Christian they get a hold of
is truly anti-Christian.
And where are the Christians complaining about that?
But I know this, it is anti-Israel to say,
turn it over to the Palestinians,
who if they took it over would never stop killing each other.
They can't stop killing each other
all over the Middle East.
It's a joke.
Clean up your own house before you run around
lecturing the rest of the world, Muslims.
Wow.
All right, now, here is the...
In context.
Here is the absolute problem with that is,
yes, he characterized them as Muslims altogether.
No, no, no. Aggressively.
Right, right.
But the way he said that, Muslims.
But the problem...
Yeah, no, that's horrific.
Get your own house and order, Muslims.
Yeah, no, that's...
And the Texas accent does not help his...
No, sir, no, sir.
Even if you're doing your best to not view him as racist,
the Texas accent really makes it hard.
But here is the problem with that,
which there is a...
If you learn the history of Islam, the Sunni-Shia divide
has been the source of so much violence.
Now, whether or not that is any different from any number...
Like, hey, let's maybe talk about Ireland for one little second.
And where are the Christians decrying that?
But when did he...
The twist, the twist that he had was so genius,
and then he hid it.
What are you talking about?
Immediately following the Muslims killing each other,
or right before the Muslims killing each other,
he had the perfect twist, which was implying that Obama
was funding Islamists murdering Christians all throughout, right?
Oh, well, that's a big narrative of his.
He said that...
So he's saying that the no vote on the UN was not necessarily anti-Semitic.
Right.
But the funding of Islamists murdering Christians all across the world
is definitely anti-Christian, which is unrelated to the previous statement.
Right, but if true, I agree.
Exactly.
Well, it doesn't get more anti-Christian
than funding the murdering of Christians.
Yeah, I'll put that on the shelf.
If we establish that as true, then yes, that is very anti-Christian.
Once you prove that to me, you got a point.
You are correct.
You got a point.
Right.
So we've got that, right?
Then we switch immediately back to the no vote is certainly anti-Israel,
which, as we all can guess, is anti-Semitic, right?
Or, I mean, I guess not...
No, no, it's hard to say.
That is a very complicated...
Like I said up top, Israel's very confusing to me.
I think the no vote is absolutely the correct vote.
100%.
Or not maybe the abstaining.
Yes.
I believe a lot of the settlement stuff is very exploitative,
and a lot of people are dying.
They're killing as many Palestinians as they can,
which is so much of the deep-seated psychological issues there of Israel
essentially trying to root out Palestinians is so fascinating to me.
Yeah, but because the pure, I hate to say irony,
but just like that idea of like,
oh, now it's time to get them out of our country.
The idea of Jews cleansing.
Yeah, that's really hard to justify there.
It's tough, but if you look at the narrative from the Alex Jones wing of it,
they aren't Palestinians.
Right.
None of them are Palestinians.
They're globalist Islamists.
Right.
Who have been brought in to destabilize.
Right, right.
Who are probably funded by the Open Society, George Soros, all this stuff.
The one parallel I have to that,
which I think is uninformed and at most an overgeneralization,
or at least an overgeneralization,
but the only thing I can think of to explain the Israeli takeover of Palestine
and the settlements and the absolute unwillingness to even consider a compromise
is like, you know how sexual abusers a lot of the times wind up having been sexually abused?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's the one thing that I can think of that is a parallel that makes sense in that narrative.
Or like children of alcoholics often end up dating alcoholics.
Exactly.
Because you're trying to recreate the situation to make it right.
Right.
Well, but that's how it works on an interpersonal level,
but I don't know how that works as a society.
Well, I mean, if you want to call any unwieldy nation
as a collection of children acting half as smart as the smartest of them,
I mean, I can see it being at least a national identity.
Like America, regardless of what side you are on in the two-party system,
there is definitely a national identity, right?
That's different from most other European countries.
It's Americana.
It's such a ridiculous country that we have
that's filled with so many different regions that have zero to do with the others.
And that's one of the things that make us so great.
One consistent national identity, which is fuck the government.
That's it.
That's really our national identity.
All right, let's go to this next clip.
I have no idea what this is.
All right, wait, we're going random grab bag?
I really don't remember what this is.
All right, let's do this.
Let's say a nuclear war was breaking out with Russia and they just fired ICBMs in 1967.
I would expect Walter Cronkite to be desperate and say,
everybody get to your bunkers.
The missiles will be here in five minutes.
Yes.
I mean, it's almost to that level now.
The urgency of repudiating Obama, repudiating the globalists, repudiating George Soros,
repudiating Henry Kissinger and all of these insane out of control anti-American people
who just want to destroy prosperity to consolidate control
and are willing to push us into World War Three to maintain their control.
Wait, press pause real quick.
Do you see Kissinger?
He did.
Who recently met with Mike Pence?
I feel like he does not know anything about Kissinger.
I don't know why you're saying that.
That's another grab bag poll there.
That's a Saudi Arabia in communist China.
That's a mad lib.
Kissinger could not be further on the side of Trump.
Apparently.
I mean, because you remember how Kissinger orchestrated the side?
Anyways, Kissinger is an evil motherfucker.
It does seem that way.
Yeah.
At a certain point, you want to arrest the independent press?
You want people to come after me?
You want to go after all of our freedoms?
You want to be able to do all these horrible things?
See, this is another reason why up top I wanted to make clear I don't want to go after him.
No.
I just want to have fun.
I want to find out.
I want to understand.
Because he's so paranoid about people wanting to kick him off the air.
I want to be clear that that's not what I want to do.
No.
Well, I mean, our entire livelihood, if you're listening to this a year from now,
when we are the number one podcast on the planet.
Hold on.
We got to get to the end of it.
I'm really curious where this is going to go.
I'm excited.
And then you just think we're going to sit here and take it and take it and take it and
take it and take it and take it and take it and take it and take it and take it and take it.
We're not going to take it and take it.
You dumbass.
You keep escalating.
You're going to get hurt.
I swear to you, I didn't loop that.
That was the perfect.
I deserve a podcast award for perfect timing on that.
Also, this is only halfway through the clip.
Believe me, you don't mean anything to me.
So I don't even want to see you hurt.
But not a dead rotting horse or something in the road.
I'm going to look at you.
That'll all brighten all you people.
The hell is your problem?
Bunch of sick freaks.
Bunch of neurotics.
Want to run everything.
Want to control everybody.
You can't stand people that are better looking than you.
You can't stand people that are stronger than you.
You've got some weird twisted competitiveness in you.
It's like they say in the great book, they turn into a film that will be bloody.
Goes, I have a competitiveness about me.
I don't want anybody else to succeed.
Okay.
I remember why I pulled this clip now.
This is one of these great.
We're not going to take it.
We're going to.
This is such a great example of Alex Jones losing the thread halfway through a sentence.
Oh, absolutely.
It's just this perfect like, hey, they're trying to destroy the, uh, you know, they're
trying to take me off the air.
The independent media trying to get rid of it.
Also, uh, Madeline Albright's mad at people.
Where did Madeline Albright come from?
She's mad at people who are more attractive than her.
Why is he mad at Madeline Albright?
Now.
Well, it's, it's time to really take down Madeline Albright.
So he's now, this is where the thread, like he loses it entirely.
And the end of this sentence is bananas.
Oh, well it's, it's exactly like when you're, I know, I know, but before we go any further,
it's exactly like you've been on this situation in on stage where you're too drunk.
Oh yeah.
And you're talking and you're getting to the bit.
And then halfway through all of a sudden your brain goes, nope, don't know the bit anymore.
So you just start saying stuff because you know,
eventually your brain's just going to at least pick something up.
Yeah.
That is exactly what we're not going to take it.
We're not going to take it.
We're not going to take it was.
Now what's great about this is he does find a thread.
It's the wrong thread.
It's completely different.
So he starts going down that path and he thinks he's going to find it again and he doesn't.
And it just goes to commercial, which is great.
But how this fucking commercial break ends is amazing.
So he's just talked about how like, and there will be blood.
It's about competition, right?
I don't want anybody to succeed at my expense walking on me.
But if you innovate, I'm only going to try to model myself after you.
And I'm going to admire you.
I mean, I've literally pulled up by somebody's sports car before.
That's super awesome.
And my car is parked next to him and that is an incredible car.
They're like, Oh man, sorry.
Sorry.
It's better than yours.
No way.
Is the commercial is the commercial music starting?
Okay.
It's like the Oscars playing.
Yeah, they're playing them off because they realize he's lost it.
Yeah.
Like this guy in a nice car pulls up and he's like, Hey, that's a nice car.
And the guy in the car is like, Hey, sorry, it's better than yours.
But like not being a dick, he's being actually like, Hey man, look,
I'm sorry.
My car is better than yours.
That has never fucking happened a thousand times in the negative.
Never happened.
You know what?
Let's see where he goes.
That's like, no, no, no.
Literally, I don't care that your car is so cool.
It looks like a spaceship.
You know, personally, I wouldn't drive a car like that.
It's brought too much tension, but man, that's really a piece of art.
You know, incredible.
You know, it's like people don't get it.
You know, they don't.
Competitiveness means you like the competition.
It's not that you don't like people that are successful, but that's who the
global star.
Okay.
And off to commercial and okay.
So the globalists are people.
If you recall where that sentence started, it had to do with people trying
to kick him off the air.
Right.
Which I guess if you want to be very generous, you could say that the idea
of competition he's competition to them.
Um, I guess now they want to kill him though.
Yeah.
I don't understand.
They want to.
They don't want to drive him off the air.
Metaphor with the car is amazing because it's not a metaphor.
That's supposed to be a literal story.
It's a story that has never happened to him.
It's never happened to anybody.
What car looks like a spaceship?
Also, why does he envy this car?
Then say, I would never get one of those cars, but it's a piece of art.
It's a piece of art.
Draws too much attention to you.
I want, look, I want to get that car, but I would never get one of those cars.
I have one more clip that I don't remember what it is.
He is.
So he's, is he referencing that, uh, Kurt Vonnegut short story?
Which one?
Oh shit.
Do you remember the one where it's the, the world is, uh, changed to be equal.
So there's this dude and he's the name, the short story is named after him.
And so he's this perfect Ubermensch guy.
And because of that, they have to make him equal to everybody else.
So they put these earmuffs on him to make him half deaf.
They put these giant bottle.
That's how he sees himself.
Yeah, absolutely.
He sees himself as somebody who's being, who people are trying to tear down.
Yeah.
I apologize for not being specific, uh, about communist China, having a digital drop box
with all the things necessary.
Well, that's the other thing that I think is really fascinating is that he always
complains about how there's a learned helplessness and victim mentality in liberals.
Right.
And then he goes on to say that the globalists are responsible for all his problems.
So it's like this weird, I don't understand what the line is between like one version
of paranoia and the other.
I'm not entirely sure, but one's about prosperity, I guess.
I don't know.
I think, man, here's, here's the thing that while we're talking, the only thing that
I can conceive of is I want to eventually try and understand how his brain works.
Well, that's why we got to keep doing this show.
We have to keep doing this show.
Here's one more clip for you that I don't remember what it is, but it has to do with
demons.
They're going to start over, it's time to break.
George in Texas, you're on the air.
Go ahead.
Thanks for holding.
Yes, Alex.
I just, uh, this is where they want to be.
They're going to start world war three.
This has always been the plan.
You know, they always have sure.
Having Hillary be elected would have been great.
You know, they can do whatever they want.
Yeah.
They were still going to start a war when she got in.
They were going to shut the press down when she got in.
It's in all the WikiLeaks.
They're just going ahead.
Like Trump wasn't even elected.
What does that tell you?
They don't care because they're crazy.
And I think they're possessed personally.
They definitely are.
They're damn demons.
Yep.
They're literal demons.
They're possessed.
Yep.
He often makes the claims that the people who are against him are literal demons or
being paid by Soros.
Those are the two groups of people who are against him.
And we can say 100% neither.
Yes, I would agree with neither.
Yeah.
I would say neither.
Now, but that's a brilliant move there is because you're never pinned down.
Like, yes, there is the narrative of being possessed, but it could also be like, no,
that was a metaphor for George Soros.
But also George Soros could be possessed if that's what you want to believe.
But that's a metaphor for the globalists who are also, you know.
He sells a shirt too.
That's like a George Soros as a goblin kind of thing.
It's like, I don't know if that's antisemitic, but it doesn't feel good.
It's like, I don't know.
Well, you know what?
That's the next question.
Right.
Is Harry Potter antisemitic?
A hundred percent.
Right?
That's an antisemitic.
Dobby is a Jew.
Oh, no, no.
I was talking about the goblins at the Gringotts Bank.
I gotta be honest.
That was antisemitic.
I don't know anything about Harry Potter.
I'm telling you, I'm telling you right now.
I saw one of the movies and I remembered Dobby.
I'm telling you right now, Harry Potter, you heard it here first, ladies and gentlemen.
J.K. Rowling is possessed and an antisemite.
Just kidding, Rowling.
It's time to pray.
Well, anyway, those are the things that I wanted to tell you about InfoWars today.
All right.
Let's close it with a clip.
This makes me laugh so hard.
Oh, I can't wait.
And I hope you enjoy it.
And if you've enjoyed this show, thank you for listening.
Hopefully, we'll do more of these in the near future.
And we'll come up with a better name.
And tighten it up a little bit.
This over two hours thing is probably not going to work in our favor.
Nope.
But anyway, here we go.
And so we are in the real world in this epic time and everything you do is having a giant effect.
Pray for this country.
Pray for awakening.
Pray for providence.
Pray for spiritual defense and support and provision for Trump and for InfoWars and for
Matt Drudge and for people like Stephen Bannon and others that are at the tip of the spear
of this fight because of duty.
But understand, this is real.
You can see it.
It's not our opinion.
We are the people resisting this.
You are the folks resisting it.
We're all in this together.
And none of us are perfect, but we've got God on our side.
Also, we're running, extending the Christmas special just even more until Wednesday.
And then it's over because people like it so much.
Free shipping store wide, 50 to 30% off everything while supplies last.
The problem is we've sold out of, I don't know, eight different things at InfoWarsLife.com
and for store.com.
So a lot of stuff has sold out.
But we still have brain force now with 20% more in each bottle, 30% off.
You cannot beat that deal and free shipping.
Time for auto-ship and an additional 10% off.
Wow.
Supermell Vitality and Human Vitality are about to sell out.
We've got 30% off on those.
X2 is about to sell out.
We've got, I mean, it's $20 right now.
That is unprecedented and free shipping.
We have the liver cleanse, liver shield with oxy powder for the gallbladder and liver cleanse.
That's discounted, 30% off when you get them together.
Again, we're talking 4.8 star reviews here by third-party review sites and so much more.
BioPCA for your hair, skin and nails, everything else as well.
Uh, we've got biome defense in the 25 billion.