Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody welcome back to knowledge fight I am
I'm going to call an emergency meeting of the knowledge fight
The knowledge fight bat signal went up
And we had to respond
Also there's no girls allowed in the
Learned
That's Milo yiannopoulos
Was going to be a gas
On knowledge fight
And we decided we f******
Can have to cover this
It was in a meeting
You going to be a guest on Infowars
Yeah
We have
To cover it
We had to get in the studio we had to take care of it
Now unfortunately
In between
For Heroes hero
I'm a policy wonk
My new favorite drop I just want to throw that everywhere
I swear
And somebody finally gives us
Techno remix
That got in there along with I love
For you guys do you want to make a hip hop remix of this
I'm a policy wonk
Ever been said
What up
F****** a****** loves people
He loves figuring out what
Bills are most important in the womb
Let me ask you a question
Unfortunately in between the time that we decided that we were going to do this episode about being on
Today
You're listening to this it will be yesterday's show on Tuesdays show
Let me backup
Milo was the opening
Ewok
I'ma dates walk
Milo was a guest on Monday
Tuesday
He had another guy
Another game
Which is way more important
Way bigger
He had
Putin's advisors
A confidant
And Friends
And the guy who's actually a philosopher
Mental Health
Really smart guy
A close associate of Vladimir Putin
Was a guest
On the Alex Jones Show
Add that to me takes
This changes the game do you mean having a top Russian
Dandasana in
Sibley American
Truths truths Americana
Yeah
So he had the Alexander
I feel like that's always
We talkin about unfortunately
It's not
Heavy news organization
Should be covering
We can't handle it
Are they
Not yet not that but do you think
Do you think they will
I'm still trying to say we're Russian shills behaving like Russian shells
Couple clips for Men review
6 technique
I know you are but what am I
Kettlebowl ship
Play racist I have no idea
Anyway
I have a couple clips from the Dugan interview and then we'll get
To the business of Monday's show but I want to illustrate
F***** up this interview
That he did
With this Russia
Here's the first one Jordan in
Enjoy
This
Disposition
We just want our right to be here
These framing that is Putin
Sandpoint
Alexander Dugan said that Putin is not imperialistic
He does not want to invade other countries although you pronounce
Which is fine he doesn't bring a little bit of levity to know that
We've got a Star Trek
Yeah it does
Notice how humble poop
The craziest thing I've ever heard
A bumper of man
Horses shirtless
About how
Russia is on the Forefront of fighting globalism and
Listening
Let's take three seconds
To absorb
What the f*** that way
Substantially worse
Sounds like a Nazi
Russian Russian accent
If you listen to that clipped
Within his
Yeah
They also discussed kicked out the oligarch
18 years ago
This was a big deal
Give him credit. We jump and replace it with an autocorrect
You did tear down the Oliver
Most of the reports that I've read by Thoreau journalist
Bogart's
He just told them I'm taking
In the cut
Yeah you just came into power and was like I want half of what you have
MSY Putin has 200 billion dollars
This is all just a
Narrative but as we all know from
Understanding
Give the mafia
Let's call it the Godfather
When you do that
When you kick out or when you just you know you become the overboss
They're not oligarchs anymore they're just really risky
Yeah yeah
There's an Italian word for it
Probably
Will probably end
You know
We've all lost our minds right
Has anybody ever explained what the
The f*** is going on other than people
Don't like us shouting
I think we are
Trump is it's our man and Putin is Sauron we're living in The Lord of the Rings
We Are Who has the one ring I don't want to be Frodo
It was cool in there can I be
Pastels
Lord of the Rings
Of course
Oh boy do I know this was about Lord of the Ring
You're a nerd
My other for America
Dies
In the middle of
Exactly
The other thing is that all of these
Aspects of the dirty dossier
Are starting to come out as kind of like
That looks like it might have been real
So it can't
Not be real
Individual
20% of Russia's state-owned oil inter
Image traced back
Untraceable bank account in the Cayman Islands
Well
I've heard a couple of different theories theories
About
Billionaires from
Saudi Arabia
As well as
About that guitar
What was the separate
Yeah
Which is another great
Guitars
What's an interview
Which I think
Should
Look I'm not saying
Did anyone needs to kick Alex Jones
I'm not saying
But this clip
Is so f***** up I don't even know
How to set it up appropriately
Awesome
So America
The world
I just give you some contacts beat that new Atlantis thing is
Francis Bacon's idea about America being a new Atlantis
Bubba blah
There's like
It's it's it's part isn't really all that
Nefarious
Coronavirus Atlanta
Just sort of like a metaphorical
He's about the beginnings of America and
State of America
We're basically taken out
Also
If you
He thinks the Russian czars were taken
Lalala Fantasyland
If you are unfortunate enough to listen to Infowars like I do
Make note of every time
That Alex says
But somebody's not perfect
And you will start
Sofia trend
That's very similar to Trump
Use of quotation marks
His tweets
Great
To use a racial slur whenever uses
Quotes
And something
He's like Bad Dudes out there or we have to stop
Quote evil from getting into the country
Stuff always wants to say
Something offensive
And the quote marks
Stopping
Whenever Alex says
They're not perfect
It's like
They're not bad which one of us is
Perfect
At the very least
Wish digenis
Also I've been keeping track of earbuds
There's no discernible pattern yet but
Texas here
He was talking about the booze out during the Superbowl he talked to her
On the British
Russia helped defeat the Germans better for history of Russia wouldn't have
Even the Russian propaganda
This is like that s***
Razee
The Nazis are bad
Yeah yeah yeah
Well I mean the Nazis
Look Nazis
Perfect
Virginia Woolf
Sylvia Plath
You're thinking of Sylvia Plath
Clearly you weren't depressed
Teenager who is also a girl
I went hunting directions
I went to God
I went directly to wiccanism
Do I have a bunch of Christian Scott
The most dangerous
Quite literally
Suggesting that the world might be a better place if the Nazis had won World War II
The other thing that you slept in there that I think
Who got silver
He said Russia got but
Trade ya
Do you know who
Would have betrayed Russia in this
No do know you're talkin about Germany betraying them right
No
Germany map
Betrayed because of global
That's your
Idea there is that
Russia was
Betrayed
Instead of
Russia
Ape shirts
Yeah like
What he's really he's baked
Typically rewriting history to
That Churchill and FDR worm
People I think
I think that Alex would probably argue that
I don't know how he feels about Churchill necessarily a shrew
You know Churchill still has a busted
Churchill in there which
Cuz I don't know if
Almost 20 days into Trump's presidency
Alex
Still takes time on the show
Complain
About how
Someone claimed
But Trump's throughout the bust of Martin Luther
Weather report at no one really cared
Also
No one would be surprised
I think
There is
There is like a lot of fake news now
It
But the problem is
The news about Trump is there's nothing that you wouldn't believe
You could literally spend any lie and it has
The Ring of plausibility
Can't go
Far enough outside of the realm of possibility
Lock that in that deposition
I'm sure you can walk
He's being blackmailed by Russia
Which muscle We Can't Stop
There's no we can all believe that
Ali any other president you're like
That's crazy
There's no way
Anybody
President
Rechargeable leave literally any others
Yeah
He's blackmailing the president
Bucked up
The Monday
We got some fun with this we can get that
Before I get to this cuz it's
From boring-ass David Knight
But he takes over at the end of the show
Andy accidentally let slip
He has a little slip of the tongue
Play it here but he sucks
One last one
About the whole Russia
If I was going to
If I was going to put together an idea of what
Russian flag
Now.
Here is what here's what I would
I'm I'm
They are trying to
Demolish
All of the United
Nations
Whether or not they're going to do anything but
America in
Either
Non-issue
Somehow there
Lackey
Domingo there
Is whenever they separate everybody else
Then finally they can act
Really get vericon
Yeah because
Does he have
Because
They keep f****** with people and their stats
So so they do that
Keeps them from being beholding to the say
Of the United
God knows that's probably
John McCain
The least worst person on the
The sanctions right now
Noel open trader
With all of these other name
Who otherwise wouldn't
And they have massive oil Reserves
Really both
And then
Backcountry
Whenever they get that
They are going to do the Ukraine
To all the time
Old Soviet Union
Vindicated
My theory is to what
But we're not here to be speculative show we're not here to make
Guesses
And mock out
So
Keep in mind
Alex Jones
Is a policy
I keep that in mind
For the rest of time
Alex starts this show off
By explaining that
Ikea's fuc
Sickened
Buy something he's red
Oh no
Now that's the only
Free Press learn.
Maybe didn't read
About last night
It makes me sick to myself
Do you want to try and guess what the plans are
God
Make Alex
Musically
Jessieville
Physically sick
Polonium poisoning everybody
Okay
Where I live
Here in Austin Texas
Has been
More than 25 years
As the global
Model City
Of the future
Berthold not sure why you're mad about that
He sounded so angry about that
Have been telling me
For 25 years
That this city
Is animes
Eating place to live
And it's going to be whatever
And that
Seconds
Occupy
Sickens me that
This place is so enjoyable to live in
We'll see if he can explain it a little better than
Just your city is awesome
And when you actually read what they say they're going to do
Under Agenda 21
And you realize it's only
1 Japanese City
Read what there
Somebody just pop up
I just realized I don't pick up on the mic
I have energy
Drink it wasn't a beer
That sounds like I'm being Alex
That it's just makes me want to cry
It's so obvious
And not give it the True Justice of making a no
30 minutes documentary
He's on minutes sticks of talking about it
Usually starts with I don't want to talk about this
F****** nuts what is going to happen really ramping up
Is it is there going to be an MD
Spoil anything but no
As fast as I can research
It's so big it's so old it's so plan
Can you find out
How many people are involved in
Then you realize about half the people fling
San Francisco in Los Angeles
F*** you
Banner coming here
To collude with it
Weather
And to help suck everything
And everybody off
And then
Move on in 20-30 years
Conferences in
Wrench and you're hurting people in your
At the doctor Houma
Lobbying at the convention center
All world leaders were do
That's not what I'm getting into
Nico I think I actually gave you my stack on that
F****** nothing nothing
DM f******
Traffic that was
Describe how evil nothing was
Anythink
Letgo app
I don't know I know Shanghai
I could be in Hong Kong
I don't know
Germany Munich
Munich Airport
Be fun
Look up with the detour
Which is where we landed
44 the Dorf on golf as well
Are there cities in Japan Tokyo
What is he f****** talking about gender and age
The order that
To take out all the Younglings
It's one of the most thoroughly debunked
Conspiracy theories it's been lingering since the 90s
Is it making everybody fits
Physically ill makes Alex physically l
So what helps.
I don't want to give like a whole primer on this but if you want to look at
Google
Find all this stuff out
Beware that's how they get you into Agenda 21 you know that right
21 was a paper put out
By the UN about sustainability and growth
In the 90s
And had to do with third world countries
Basically Rising
People out of poverty
Protecting the environment
It was completely non-binding
100-percent voluntary
And there's no there's no
Dictate
It's mostly just about like
Ideas
Is it was 178 countries voluntarily signed on when it first came out
People have been really bad
Destitute
Interested
Bunch of
Is a good idea somebody
Dab well I found
This guy who is research
I had a really
Good quote about it
Like that explained
In the
Assertive anger at it was the quote Alex Jones is full of s***
Michael Barkin University political scientist
Conspiracy theory
You go to the thing anytime you get
Some sort of un program
Suggest any kind of change in the way people live
Even if it seems outwardly benign
It's going to be taken up by people with Atkins
Conspiracy band
That
Let's believe that 21 what's going to happen is
Is under the eye
Pictures of Environmental Protection
And under the auspices of trying to help the poor
Everyone is going to be pushed into
They're super compact
Everyone's going to be living in basically
Closet Apartments
It's it's
It's not
Absolute nonsense
Because of the name
Like I said that's the order that Anakin
Needed a plan to make the 21st century better than the last
That's why it's called 21
Contagious
Good ideas for people
That would be awesome
You can risk
Construe good ideas
Hey guys this is non-binding
Do these
Naming things not
Hear the voice
Oh that means
I think back in like 8
It was 92 when it was Saved by the Bell
Omar Limehouse Beyond days
All day all night
But I think back then
People didn't have the same
Crazy
You know like we didn't have the same people who are out there
Making everything
You know so I don't think
Agenda 21
People take
Somebody
I think it kind of sounded catch
21st century agenda agenda for the 21st century
Good at good ideas
The answer is almost always
Or not
I've looked into this one pretty extensively and given it a score of
Thumbs down
Thumbs down on this being a legitimate
I was going to say
Classic deck a SeaTac
Conspiracy
Makes Alex sick
Cuz there's a sinkhole
There's something that he feels is 21
Code next
God
F***
Evil name I don't know
People named slickback has really weird cuz
You choose like
They sort of vague word
With the same stuff
Yeah it makes sense
Be scared of
You scared of everything
But
They're not the greatest
Yeah
Empathic
Empathetic
If you don't
Climate change
Just real
Then people trying to push for things
To protect against
What's climate change
Obviously you would think that they were up to no good
If you believe
His premise
What is promise
Is horribly flawed
Do you mean non-existent
He's had nothing to f****** say nothing everyone
Yeah and then getting to
I just wanted to make you guys
X bankers
Being interrupted
Administration
About how he knows everything about these
Contact bankers
Does not remember one of their name
Which is a little bit.
I always said
I'll let go monkey
All of them
And watched it happening and for
One half of that is true the other the second part
Years and years are very
Alex
Claiming that everything I know all about these guys
Tigers as pets
That's Rick Perry not remembering agency
To demolish
The super important don't want this always in charge of nucleus
No
So far everybody that's been hard for everything his headache
Complete look of shock the moment they found out what it is
Did the people who are in charge
Putting them in charge
Of those agencies
They want
The reason to privatize out of
Entirely that government is wrong
Mirror
In the next decade to come
Can't we and then reject the next
10:15
NFA please no please
Did the other thing I think is really unfortunate about
That clip is he's talking about
Steve mnuchin
In particular was
Pretty heavily implicated in
He
He just failed miserably at it and then stole all their money along the way it was pretty
How much do most you can fail at like
If his goal was to get people
Cheaper housing steal all of their money
Man he did a really bad job
Clip I was really high one day and I saw a clip of this
Daredevil
His name was death wish.
That is some f****** great
Naming right there
You screwed up everything
His nickname is like tiny fridge
This next
Who is George Soros
Infowars
Needs to be list
Composite
I think it might document
It's like psychotic break
Call Alex point it's worth it instead of just a borderline Alzheimer's
He just Rambles about how sick things are and then
Forgets what it is
George Soros
Explain but then
F****** wet
But here are the headlines
Rally House
Goldman Sachs Economist are starting to worry about President Trump has Bloomberg's putting all the bad news
News out now
Wait what time to sell the Dollar on our policies
Delete last week by good intelligence agencies
What's that
George Soros
Is basically naked shorting the dollar
And the pound to punish us to get us back under Global government
And so of course
We should have him
We got to have JP Morgan
And Bloomberg and Goldman Sachs all come out against America
So here we are
He thinks George Soros shorting
Games that he's
Evil but also
Let me beyond that
Accuracy
It came out from good
The George Soros
What he's referring to is what we talked about
No date
Financial organization accidentally posted
Everyone short online when they weren't
Supposed to they post those short bet
It was a German Bank
The Deutsche Bank came out
Eman Eman saying
Did it comes from good intelligence services
Is lying about the sourcing
Is absolute
Those are good until
Yeah
The Patriots game
The football team they didn't need any help
No
In the
You remember that one
But Alex will talk about that
But
Speculation
Possibly time to get worried about our currency
Become erratic
It's not saying hey everyone
It's saying
This could be dangerous times ahead
Responsible Financial
Advisor would probably
Without getting panicky
Tell you like
Keep an eye on
I see they don't have to do that anymore now that the
Sushi roll
For their own good
So why would you have a responsible
Yeah yeah he's a f******
Exactly that's against the law
Can't be profitable
Anymore
Anyway
Was it ever
Psychotic break
Oh yeah
Thank you oh yeah oh cuz I forgot
Cuz Trump works for you right he's doing what you want now he's doing the opposite
Doesn't even deserve
I'm serious
You're right
Frozen Arctic
God forbid to give you a space heater or some food God forbid
What did we do to the other way
Channel 7 other than the torture The Invader
You know
History American history slavery races
Make a really compelling
For karma
This is a this is karma doesn't work, ethically though I thought
What's the right way to phrase that it doesn't work karmically because
The people who are going to be most hurt other people
You don't like Trump coming into power is only going to hurt the people who deserve retribution
Yeah yeah well
It's going to be like
Grindhouse films victim
Is also the one
It's called again
Yeah yeah
Goes far deeper
You don't deserve that like Eliza told me it is a public
Is a bunch of scum Alex
Evil
Alex you'll never be your one of us
One day you'll come and work for us one day that's why we're going to let you live
I know the truth about this as I am and together
I don't care what you
I'm not lowering your level and feeding on them
I'm not a cannibal
Bloomberg Warren
Profile he wants to run every fast to your life
225 square foot apartment
Endomorph and Total Control
Monster wants to decide what you're going to eat
Self the Great technocrat
He made a billions of dollars extra just the last few years
Because he's
Vote the systems with the NSA that literally control you in
Was the Great
Technocrat in The Flintstones
Whatever that one
He's like a Time magazine article that's called the Great technocrat
Article article
Causes of the great Michael Bloomberg
Decide what I'm going to
Looking at this looking at the cereal aisle
I'm trying to figure out what cereal to buy
Just wish
Bloomberg
Answer call
Bloomberg app
Alright
And so if your Microsoft wants a system to game use for Amazon wants one or Alibaba
To screw you over makes me sick
He's loving it
Because all the Publications and little announcements you one
Idiot
Pleases prendie
Yeah cuz whatever is we follow the whatever is be like
Whatever is the cool social out rate
You're to be tricked by you goddamn friend
Fed MSN live
I don't know I don't either
Infowars which is why
You texted me 8 different conspiracy theories
About what's going on
I did not I did not
I'm starting to suspect
That possibly Rodger stone is pulling the strings
How do you say it was true I said it's possible
Anyway
Call Austin
Wonderful
Make sure you're not letting dog poop
Code next
In the board of the Malaysian
Assimilated to be
Destroyed
The end of humanity
Thousands of white papers I read 20 years ago
There's people with huge mustaches
Screw you Alex
It's a master plan
I think your mustache is cool actually
I think your green and red sauce
You're not individual by being screwed over by this and then by believing this is how you're cool
Agreed
What happened
Bora Bora
What is going on
This is imagining a person who's taunting
In the same way earlier in this he was imagining some guy at this agenda 21 conference
Suicide
I know he's using creative license
Is the movie phone voice
Dan LaFontaine
Justin Bieber
I'm serious no world
Nothing
And Tom Bombadil Taunton
Have you seen
Star Trek
Just a little bit more put the punchline is definitely the
You got this big mustache
All your friends
Home Alone
Cuz there is no family none of it's real
You're living a simulation
You're living a fraud
In sports is a primitive form of virtual reality it's real reality
Confine
Won't affect the power structure
VR
Total systems that remove you from reality and I could see that myself
Building fortresses in Jungle Mountain
Hawaii 51
He's also saying from Tasmania to
It's just that talk about Peter Thiel
Teal and Mark Zuckerberg
He's not everyday
Hippie 20
I have information on a great
Swath of Elites moving to Jungle fortresses
They're just two people who announced they were creating like vacation but if you're going
Mountain Fortress
I got to get an even better
And then eventually
Uber clearly fighting
Other from Jungle Mountain Fortress as the rest of the world especially Austin
Because you know where they hide their lies
Austin their mustaches
OSHA
You know like your mustache
If it's the only way to get Ally.
Death as believable as Agenda 21
Introduced a little bit
Call Alex
I really want to get into house
So is his idea of primitive virtual reality
Games
Games games
No
Playing games
Stuff like that
Kind of like a
You're creating a false reality to live in for a while
Correlation without coming election
I love it
Lake brienz all the sports
Billionaire
Want
Military
He wants you to go to college
Marion sports teams
Evite your life destroyed all you can do is be
The modern guy in France
Russian
Again
Cruz's first part
We don't want the most
Aggressiveness
Are you in the military
They're going to do a graph
Reviver read all of history
Vicky
The most aggressive
They're not on the right side of History
They're usually bad but the idea that
Sports is created to keep aggressive
2 people out of politics
Is wacky realize it's all a trap
To become a coach
Earned
Do something with it pretty f****** happy with being a coach
It's that good
Exercise
It's good way to
Trying to import good messages to
The kids about team
Building voucher
Making it
It's actually very valuable to curb male aggression in
Keep them out of
Sports a little bit later with some theories
It is time
To get to the Milo interview
I brought
Italian wine
To celebrate us
And we're almost done with it
And I have a bottle of Moscato because we don't deserve good favorites
This interview I really didn't know how to cut it up into separate clip
So it's just an interview
There's a couple of important things that I want
Let me know and I'll pause it
Also it starts with Alex saying that he's not going to
What he and Milo have planned
And at the end of the clip
Straight up
Alex Jones
I don't know
Some sort of a
Set up
It's an interview with Milo
Also planning something
I on the street in the next few weeks
I really
I've never actually heard
Studiously avoided his Mountain
I'm sorry to bring this
Listen to your life
Forest
Stalking British
Speaking
Wild inaccuracies
And total b******* erupt
No not really
Any interview that he does is largely like rhetorical
Worst Christopher Hitchens
Somewhat yes yes
Ender
I read Hitchens memoir
West Coast
Uc-davis UW Seattle uc-berkeley things went talk and we had the page
Black clothes.
You're always welcome
So
His is framing of this like everything was going well until the West Coast
I mean that's not entirely accurate
Unless
What he wants
What's to say is that when he was at
University of wisconsin-milwaukee
Xbox
The s*** out of her
Yeah kind of gave an account of the
He was going
Project a picture of her years before when she was
What the f*** tranny everyone ever
She was in the crowd and was terrified one of the quotes
Her transition was the way you know he's failed
Is I could still banging
What the f*** that kind of speech
Is so f****** inappropriate
What's that
You didn't
Hade
Why
I don't know what is there
Reason
Money
Specifically
No but this sort of thing gets him a bigger reputation
Will she was a student actor
Against
Again president
Basically docs are on
And I know it's not the same
That is
Harry level
Powers everyone in that room
F****** dead
If I like legitimately if
She had killed herself after that
Nonna Pizza
Laughing at me
They don't know I'm in the room
While a charismatic speaker is mocking me on stage
Believe me
And for something that has been difficult for me growing up
That's what I think is it
We talked about what people actually is evil
Rule that's the
Roulette f******
That's childish f******
Crazy hair
8 year old
Someone who's still in college
Could you get more punching down
What a f***
Monster
He's the f****** worst
Part of his part of the tour that
It's gone well
Maybe some crime involves
I believe that she filed
With the school but I don't know what ended up happening with it
I can't imagine
Aunt Sue
There's some sort of Publix
Slander harassment
Dennis article I think
There might be
Bubba Bubba. That's for something about a book deal
With Milo has
Anyway
I hope it gets you
F****** truck
There's a book out called Dangerous
Alex Jones
Cuz it's too dangerous
Push the buttons
The PC left
I don't think most people I know who are on the left don't care
Particular
300 on the list right now
So f***
Monster at his events
Seattle
Be angry about that for months yet
Seattle protester got shot by one of his
And
If you
Even if you disagree with
Hazard
Because of
What happened in Seattle
Between so I apologize
To Berkeley that there were
Essentially riot
But also it came out then one of the things that he planned to do it
Berkeley
Was to
Much as he did with that trim student
He was going to out
Illegal immigrants
Students
And make a Target
The idea that he's expressing free speech and that's what being shut down
It's really not all that accurate reminds me a lot of
Something nothing like
You wanted to commit
Some sort of
Right huh you would like some sort of underrepresented minority
In front of your fervent supporters
In order to
It might be a good idea if you were sort of
I don't know people the money Players behind one was a really
Member of another underprivileged group because
Some stuff a little bit you could also pay him a lot of money to do it as well
Ears ears
Here's where that
Officially
Done no further
There's no further conversation about
You have a long talk with you about that
Here's what I would say in this long talk
Hi Milo
You're not
I can't even do an impression of him
Do you know that first clip how Alex was saying nothing
Time 45 minutes Milo's really good at that he can just
Spin sentences where there's no substance
Manager voice cadences
Argument
Once again
Alright
First Amendment
Congress can't make an outline
Sayings
That's a really big part of the First Amendment
You can't go to
Yeah no one have to f****** listen
YouTube
If you're getting here
Then people who are Institution
Duchenne is paying this guy
100% right
To be like
F*** you you
I want to make one point
That is mildly defending him but it's not
And that is that the First Amendment
Spirit
Truly is to protect
Abhorrent
Torrentz2
The powers-that-be
Football
You know things that are fancy
And I fully agree that Milo's should be able
To see the things that he wants to say what does not have the right
Do essentially harassed
People
And threatened
You
He should be arrested
Berkeley was a threat
Hippie people
Illegally
Also limits to free speech as much as you want to say
You can't threaten people you can't commit slander
These are two things are built into the first
He's doing
Computer some people are here illegally
But it is
It's an absolute
Fire in a crowded
Now we have to
Deal with the aspect of it
Which is
The idea that
Leftist
Well-organized well-funded protesters
Again it's a Soros narrative
Are the ones who caused
Chaos and rioting
I watched a bunch of videos of the beginning
Of what was going on there. Going to say it's responsible for all of it
There's a lot of people at
Meditating the Proto
There's a lot of people who are getting up in their face
Trying to get them to be violent
Video of the guy Eddie Brock
Yes
He was pulling into them
People's faces and literally
Forcing them to CM from their face bone in their face
Again
Nazi
Here is Arizona
And the First Amendment
And how we should have
It should not be
Illegal
To espouse Nazi
Okay it should also not be illegal
To punch.
Now
I agree
The very that you know what I
Stan white people
Push back against
We got some more Milo to get through life
Okay everybody gets
You get to punch a Nazi
If you can prove they're not
You get to punch a Nazi one
Field day on Milo now
Absolutely
You know what
Let me ask
Ever seen we're not to get punched ever been like
I wish they protected that
RPM jump in his
Archaeology artifact
Falls in all aspects he's probably
He's waiting.
But God damn it if the man doesn't punch your goodness
Handmaid's tale 1984
Backwards
Maybe it will they feel about
F****** nuts
Absolutely
I only say no.
Tipping Point matter what George Soros
Media
And lied about sick of having dinner
I was just speaking what we should read them and then what we should know
Expresssos
Yeah
I don't want to play
I really want to play the rest of this
F****** brutal
Listen to this man talk
Is
It is heartbreaking on so many levels
Kissing from Alex and a bunch of nonsense
Bring up
Maybe we can get to Exotic it's kind of early
Apart
About people
Call Target
Nevermind
They're voting the complete opposite direction
Pelosi
Promenade
The main problem is that
We're not doing s*** for us either
Lying
I know you're out there listening
The numbers
Episode
Each one teach one another word knowledge fight for the truth
Opposite direction
Keep your mouth shut about our show
Settings
Are coming world
Tucking authoritarian
There's a point where Milo talks about how
He saw Robert Reich
Responsible
Right-wing forces were responsible for the
Milo
What size it is
Is an absolute bulshit
It's one of the most sickening
Crazy
Conspiracy theories
Island
By George Soros
It is well
Well organized and paid
One thing
Better at being non-violent
Really want
No
Because
He doesn't
He doesn't give a
I do agree with Robert Reich
I don't agree with Robert
I don't think
Gets the right-wing I think
Everybody is losing their s*** right now
Exactly the right-wing doesn't understand
What's happening right now
They're starting
To get this like inkling of
That is driving
And there's no stability in our
The left we're aware that we're getting f***** and apparently we have zero power
So there's all of these
Powerless
Surrounding surrounding each other
One Small Place
You're going to get violent,
Because you only punch the people you see
Call everybody
He's mad at come back to this over and over
Over to the point where these idiots vote
We just never debate necessarily really about who they are
It's a broad group it's very
Some of it's disconnected it's complicated they think it's good globalist
Which is appropriate
I think it's pretty obvious that
Once all of the corporations no longer have any
Then now it's not about any country
Get their money
Capital is self-perpetuating
Teams that are going to eventually
But they just can't
They don't understand that because they can
It's but it's in their very nature
R2
Themselves
Dangerous
Because eventually you're going to have to come up with
If everyone is America first
Germany first
There will be no room for compromise event tonight
Is it
Really crazy how every time there's a giant nationalism outbreak everybody
F****** goes to work it seems like it's better
Yeah but I want to make a few more points but Milo before we move on to some crazy bulshit from Alex afterwards
Great little bit more
So he want
He claims that he was kicked off Twitter because he made
Sure
Very very good
That's a big part of it also tweeting
Fake tweet
Were allegedly they were created
With
Make it look like I said it
Things
Infected is it there
6 a bunch
Really crazy
People ever make
Leaked nude pictures of her and s*** like that
It's up
You get kicked off Twitter
What
What what could possibly be
Possibly
What
Much of a monster
I don't know
Walk down the street
And suddenly find myself walking
Behind a woman
Had a very similar Pace without me going through this way
Does she think I'm a murderer
I'm not a murderer I don't think I have an X
Essential meltdown
Because I'm horrified
Of walking
10 feet behind a girl at the right
Speed
Run to get ahead of mixture that I
Knock
Fusing myself with better because we're p**** lip tard Cox and that's why we're never going to make it
Sure
Maybe be better if everyone is a little bit more squeamish than they were aggressive
First second
And just think
Maybe
Maybe it would be helpful if we thought that way
Am I good news about
Here's another good piece of news about Milo
He's a horrendous p****
So
Very laughable even more even more
Frustrated
If you're going to be a nothing
At least
Play the victim
Every f******
Astoria
So
Around when he got kicked off Twitter
He was making the rounds in the media
He was also
That he was going to lead
A gay pride March
Stockholm
Muslim neighborhood
Because he's like
They didn't hate
But one of those big things is that like
There's all this immigrant crime is going on in Sweden has become a home of rape gangs and either killing gays
Stuff like that it's under-reported might like that
None of these things have happened
So he was going to lead
He made a big
F****** deal out of this use even on Rogan's podcast and I was going to do this
Canceled
Security team in a review the situation and
Breitbart News
Does Campbell Milo's appearance
Despite his commitment
We're not confident that we can ensure his safety
If I were at a pride parade
And Milo is there
I don't think it would be
Muslim gangs
I'll tell you that just from you
Yeah on this podcast as many times as it was said in Inglourious Basterds
Already
There's no other word
Pejorative
The only one I can think of that's worse than not
Except
Double knot
Nothing nothing nothing
Little Caesars
We made a big deal
I think you realize I'm like
You f***** up at this parade
And then
I can't I can't
I can't cancel the right type
That's a p**** move right there it is
So anyway Alex
Kegel muscles
Alex finishes up his interview with him they talked about how they do have plans on the
What streets Alex is going to join him
Free speech thing
Can't wait
Then
To his old tricks
Vague f****** angry desperate
New system
Sounding new settings
Launching new ships
Washing new personalities
Launching new movements
I sincerely want to turn the tide
Isn't it I have to get people to restrain themselves
I want to do it very judiciously
By the book by common law
By the Constitution
And here's the strange
God is ascending Vengeance just get ready
I'm not the one
Why not
How f****** scary is that laugh
Yeah.
Hahaha
Usually gets to his role in the whole thing
I'm just sure I'm only up here
What the f***
The shifting gears into reality in the war is coming against the
Pedophile
Toucan
I agree
I totally agree
Yeah it's an if-then statement
I feel like most of the people he wants to die though have 20 kids
Personally killed and raped
With Rome
So after this after this
He gets into a sentence
I don't know I don't think you should be able to murder
Nope
Bad
I'm going to even I'm going to agree with Alex
Devil worshiper seem pretty cool
Yeah I know
So far they've done nothing but good in the world which is very
Piles of dead kids and their base
For whatever may or may not exist
You kill kids
Bad
Afura do you know what's the through-line
Necessary
I feel like that's the that's the part that you would
Just being Satanist
Fine
Find
Killing kids
Alex Jones accidentally
I think you meant to say this
GM's of accidentally
He doesn't does not mean to
Accidentally says something that is quite literally black
So right after talk about how God hears the screams of these children
Literal black
Those of you that have splice humans animals
Chimera
So that others fear ever doing what you've done
God
Spider-Man
No
That's the last
How God works
I looked through the Bible as best I could to try and find any indication that
Care about me you guys take it
Yeah yeah I don't think
Pretty sure Jesus take the wheel nut
Jesus I'm still drunk but
Quite literally the reverse is in the Bible
Literally
Going 100 mean we can take all the wacky
The energy stuff but he says and that sort of bizarre religious bat he has it is very much.
Zoroastrianism
Like crystals like this dude is this is all over the place religion
Religious stuff a little bit towards the end of the eclipse
So we have
Say something
It's not racist
Let's find out
And in Europe now and they're trying to
Trump's plan to reboot and then power of the third world
I have a one-sided deal that helps third world
We've been part of an economic War folks economy
Yep
Band needs to be a big liberal
Loans to small businesses
People oughta be kissing the feet of rum
If you want to be kissing is
Kissing his feet
Because
These people are really committed
Focus
Straight nose
100 Centigrade flashes of a picture of band and he looks like 3/4 around
Picture of Bailey looks like
Keys
It looks like he's slowly turning into Jabba the Hutt he's got the bucolic knows that comes from drinking too much
Trump is Trump is salacious crumb sitting on his shoulder
But also like
Black people should kiss Trump speech
In there too
The second half
I think it would cut myself
Because he thinks that
Clearly because black
People
Enlarged margins because the Republicans
Azar
As we seen before giant f******
Braces
Yeah like there's no other there's no way around it
GOP
Your races
That's the way it is
We're getting close to if you support them you're all
60/40 Malnati's in the GOP now
You're supporting taking us back to some of the darker
Just parts of American history
Parts of f****** European history
The guy who's going to put over the FDA doesn't think
The drugs
Reprove
Before they sell them
Dismantle the EPA cool I love I love not having
The Earth
Made indications that they want to sell off publicly National Park
We're going to go back
Watch dark time
What what
1890s whenever children were forced to work in factories
Okay you know
Betsy Davis getting in
Is going to be really bad for schools but it's not going to matter cuz they'll be in the mine
People eating
Feudal law
Can't believe
That's how that's how we're going to deal with all three every morning I wake up and I open Twitter
Don't retreat flush it
Aunt Patty
This is
F******
What how is it
How is it
Half
Doesn't
River Country that did vote
Voted for Hillary Clinton
Yet somehow
We're in The Darkest Timeline
Like we're in The Darkest Timeline right
Couldn't
It would be worse than where we are right now
In that interview with
Xander Dugan
Have something to do with everybody
Insane now
So
You had an enemy in life how would you do
Describe that
Like what would you say Bordeaux enemy
Gay
Transgender youth
Hahaha
Also the guy wearing a white hat from
Raiders of the Lost Ark
Insult them were you going to say
Nothing
Different words about George Soros
They're not they might be the mildest words I've ever heard
Makes me right now
The stop Trump
Bloomberg and Soros
These Global is the Rockefellers hold up some just
Just stop trying to make a super uncool
People like that
A long shelf-life mine public
A reaction
He went on a 7-minute tirade about the
Sickening
Nothing
You're so uncool
Super run cool man
Bro
She believes or at least claim to believe the George Soros is a literal Nazi collaborator
Economy and economy
I'm he's
You can keep your money
What
No
Well
It could just be that he ran out of adjectives
You know when you're when you're riding a really long piece
And you start
You know you start looking at all the words used in you realize oh I said
I said
Shitzu or sick of which we've heard
In every single clip
Pick up something
Momentum with words
Episode
He kept calling everything
Powerful
You talk too much
He's such a malleable little stew
Isn't he
He said
I talked myself into believing
15 years from now he'll look back on this
Nothing that I regret
You know Trump
I didn't have integrity be wildly optimistic
Suggesting
Any of us will be here
I just want to crash and then we'll be coming back
I don't know man
I just don't know
Like I said we're in the dark
It could be 50
It could be
Could be the
And believe me
I don't think any of us
You mean Alex I don't think
Galaxy out
Going to die because we have no resources
No resources
Bitcoin gold
No
I'm thinking let's go
Today
Rio
Definitely could
Anywhere Kickstarter to move us.
Gazelle
You know you need us more than
If enough people to eat at me
I will start that pic starter as a ghost
You are really hammering home that you are
I really do
We need more we need to show to spread
We need to spread
But we needed to do better
I'm not going to sell you survival gear fake pills but it'll be
Be great if you
You could get people into us
Retwist
I'm just not used to being this boldface
You can follow us on
You're going to have to give us
You know you're going to have to give people in a
Open Dan to make sure that he doesn't have a stroke of sad
Loneliness
Knowledge fight on iTunes please
Give us
Braiding Filipino review
Don'ts
Okay tell people
Dares
Treated me with Alex's handle
Someone kidnapped
I would love it if I was listening one day
We're doing emergency episode the entire episode
I'm talking about
We got one more clip
This is also another thing that I think is
Bordering on a psychotic break
Start
I believe with more weird theories about football
Let's go let's go with one quick prediction
This is the Eddie Bravo Memorial Bridge
Tell me about alien
So
So far
In the time that we started this
Seems like
Alex has gone crazy even by his own
Crazy like
Do you think he's going to pull it back
Or do you think
He's going to lose
No no I mean
In the on in our future rapper
No no he's going to lose
Spiral
To keep spiraling into crazy right even for a second the whole thing
The show that he did over the weekend
Yeah Rogers
Stone on
Clear I will never Play a clip with Rodger Stone
Cuz he's evil
I know I just think that he is a a
Spinning spider as they say
Whatever you say is is b*******
Sure I don't I don't care to give him any
I don't want his voice on my
But he and Alex were talking about
I could not make it through without crying
Yeah but
The he was on and they were talking about how their leak
Coming out of the Trump White House
And basically what they were saying is there's the
The Bandit
Overworld
And you know General
Flint neighborhood
Trump people
Got it then you got people like
Andre
The ship
20 days in
They've already decided that
Internally there are enemy
So like
They can't even blame the Liberals
It really destroy the media necessarily
To eat themselves alive and that is
No the next stage of
And then what
Start not trusting yourself
Situation where
Your
Your entire thing is built on distrust
You know
The more the more you
The more you desire purity of Belize
The more you start tearing people away
Yeah you show even the slightest bit of disloyalty to Scientology
And you are a missing person
It has
Purity Bass
Religion or ideology or whatever
Religion
With sinners
So what we're saying is
Just about all religions betray their own beliefs by there
Somewhat I believe if I'm not mistaken of starts
Gruesome wacky shirt about football
Amanda leads into
Is not a Christian
You know the beliefs that he started espousing
The sort of out there
12 dimensional multi-dimensional yeah
Some of that stuff has
You never talked about it
It's bleeding
Yeah it's bleeding through
Okay
Today how they're saying it's white supremacist because there's a few
He did get into it earlier by the way
Can we just let it go
Well it's all look I'll just be like hey the paper
Who won the Super Bowl airing on white supremacy at all let's just leave the
Reacting to something
What was Richard Spencer
Stuff about how
Tom Brady when he of warriors
Let's play
Punch Richard Spencer Twitter
Richard Spencer
F****** racist is she
No one was really saying
Hey this is racist because they have a white quarterback
No nobody
Let's all just be like hey
Education
Secretary
Football team
One f****** anything
It's a petty squabble
Petit pois
Meant to distract us
We have a good quarterback
Good receiver
But that's what they're doing
It's not what they're doing
You shouldn't
It's not true this stuff is so obvious it's like I've have eyesight
And the General Public
I'm awake on this planet exists inside of eyesight I have touch I have some a liability
Plane
No there there
Trying to wake him up so you have goggles on
You can't wait
Somebody up
Mega
They got blinders on
They don't want your help
Watch
I'll just take one goggles off and say you're a bad guy
You don't want to give them shot
Their profane
So this this is a paranoid fantasy
Mixed with Plato's allegory of
Sync
This makes
Zero cents
You don't think it's just sort of a bizarre sort of psychotic version of the allegory of the cave
Philosophy 101
Proto
It doesn't make any sense
Of course not
F****** in sex
What
What weight
Wake somebody up out of
That's not how blind
Note episode of House
But it was also everything
His house is basically
Episode of House
In order to see this patient
House will have
Kill her
That was a real promo
Do the great Epic
I love how
Houses basically where Alex gets all of his ideas of right
Greg Gregory House
Does not
But anyway
I don't know where ever going to
Deal with it but on Tuesdays show
He starts to show you his grandmother was before
Just passed away
Sweet
It's nice you know like
Those human moments
He's a human being all the time
But then within a minute of starting the show talk about his grandma
He talks about her getting a vaccine
And how that was a soft
Kill
On her
And she lived through like all these years after getting this back
Polio vaccine
Did she get polio
I don't think so use this whole like
This is Grandma's death
In order to sort of
Espouse
Anti-vaccine
Human feelings for him at all
The humanity out of
I'm going to kill people does he talk about his daughter loving is Cookie Monster
I was talking about
Nuclear war
Uniworld
Everyone
Killed by
I bet this
Allegory of the cave ripoff
Pretty insane you're right but it's going to get a little bit more
They don't deserve the site
There's a lot of things that happened I'll never tell anybody about
Is he
But I was just tell you there's a lot going on this universe not books
Elite know all this stuff
They know it
And they don't want you to know
You're like a composite of all
Wait was he talking about
The elites know the stuff that's not in the books
Like the religious books like the Bible
Confused
We talked about the elites know stuff that
So he's
Ostensibly
Espousing Christian beliefs
Somewhat yeah and there's a lot of stuff in those
In the Bible
That they
Don't tell you though
Well I mean if you want to just
Like take a really simplistic person I don't think this is what he saying
Gospel
Not all of them
Some good but if you read like those extra biblical text
Bunch of books that aren't in the Bible
Pretty wild stuff
Enoch Enoch goes up to heaven with God and he never dies and
Joseph Brothers there's a bunch of stuff in other text
People have never died
Simple version of it
I don't think that's what he's talking about
Yeah that's somehow the elites know more about
Metaphysical beliefs
Of
It's too heavy
About all that
Just say something
Some of it I agree with and
Joe and will have to sit out after he's done
Kind of trippy
Search
Complete
Contradictory nonsense man it is
This is where we started this I thought we were going to get
I thought we were going to run out because
Everyday
Time we listen to him there's a new facet of
Theory
It's not a secret I want to like
I want to love
And then like maybe
One night while we're asleep
Sleep in bed together
While wearing a globalist
Like in the movie The Purge
The only way that I was regular prime or legal for 12
Which might be soon
Again if we're going to go crazy might as well just f****** go all in
Is
That
Alex went on Rogan
Michelle
The trippy s*** he was saying
Alright I realize
Oh I can cater to
Assertive
Shroom heads out there
He has already called trendy
2 sticker
Yeah yeah
If you want to go to church and let's B'Elanna and let's go to
Dementia
Again I have to save it
Some of this stuff
Some of the stuff he's going to say
I meant
Okay
I'm not
Keep notes
Before you in the human Journey
And their genetics
Access all of that and the enemy knows that
How they've confirmed
The trees have fungus net worth of the trees communicate with trees
Hundreds of miles away
Underground
Internet of Things
Of course I show you that movie Avatar 2 years ago
And the global artificial system
Ancestral memory
All this stuff should be no
And I'm certainly
Play games with people
I got a loaded phones here but I'm sorry I'm out of time no pressure on David if you want to flush him out of hand of the great people
So also I want to say this before you get to your
Potomac
At about 1 our 6-minute Mark of the show he announces the lines are open is going to start taking calls
I'd like you to guess
What timestamp
Pocky sticks
He takes to call
Let's go with the first 12 hours and
20 minutes
1 hour and 31 minutes
Only a half-hour after he open the floor
And then it was only if I
I don't know
45 second call was just saying
The globalist
You communicated with I think so
Had a listener who disagreed
I know you mentioned that
You know what
This is Alex
Let's talk about it
I disagree with you I think it would be important for you to be in the White House
I disagree
You're better than you think you are wonderful
That's the only push back
I've heard from any caller anyway what are your predictions about 3
Did you love the tone
That's all the positive
Call
Here's a thought
It sounded like he was in a sleeping bag with me
In the forest
Ohio mushrooms
The conversation starts with
Hey Alex
Do you believe in
Now
And now let's get into ancestral memory
Yeah I agree that genetic memory
Trees do have an underground fungal Network and that if
Future
Miles away
Instantly the other trees will know somebody
It is true that
Brighten every Rock and every creature in every
Forest
No
I'm not sure I understand
Communication
What's going on with that
Some sort of a transmission that is true
I think there is a
Basic level of conscious
Implied
New release
Not you
This smells the oils and Olive
I do kind of think there's a base level Consciousness Within
Most
Plan
Dances well
But it's unclear whether it's a breathing carbon dioxide on them or so
Either so it's so hard to isolate any Ella bright
Prove or disprove any
Which to me means
That no matter what you do
No matter what you eat
You are killing something that is alive
And is aware and is
Screaming is it
Unless you're one of those who only eats
The fruits that have already fallen off
Stats
There are those people I don't know exactly what their children
Means those are abortions
If you eat it going
Fruit
Depends on the
Morphic knowledge
Was that mean
There's an internet
Documents
Not sure on that one
Well the theory behind acknowledge is
Like they observed that I want to say like
A couple of
Island
A species of bird would suddenly
Figure out
How do you say
To get to some
And then within a week
Even though there's been
No contact
That same species
Somewhere else
Would have
The same sure
Exact humans
The studies that have been done about like old crossword puzzles being easier than new one
Is there a morph acknowledge that we all share
I'm going to go with
It's fun to think about
But I'm not sure that
Mmm another step
Even trip.
Like lucid dreaming where people
There are indications that people are able to dream together
Which written test practice
Also Fitz
It's not clear
I don't know if I
Their methodology
And I don't
I certainly never had any experience like that but
It is interesting to think about I'm not sure I believe it I'm going to go
Acknowledge
Put myself firmly in the no column
The next one
Ancestral memories
Rape
Genetic
Shut that goes back
Back to instinct
From from bygone eras were afraid of monsters because of like
He also brought up the
The idea of the wolf you are little kid with
With an old man
I think that was
The separate thoughts
There was a pause and I thought
Isaac that was Benjamin Button
That I don't know if you believe or not
It is
He knows all about it you missed one
What was that
What that one go
Came from
True where do you think
Imagination
Jerk
Creativity
I think is one potato
Especially because
He's still obsessed
Please
Every single
He thinks is something that
Has actual
He's trying to send a message
Right
Comes back to what
And that is the culture and movies and all that stuff is
What's
Do program
So something comes out in a movie
Super true
Powers that be don't want you to think
Think it's true
That stupid movie
Yeah that is
That is a
Really impossible
Mainly because
That's what most conspiracy theory stuff comes down
Wildly unprovable
I meant
The old Carl Sagan
Anika where the woman came up to
There's a turtle underneath the Earth holding it up
She's like a bigger turtle
What's below that any Turtles all the way down
Yeah
There are you
Right
To be an infinite Loop of
You'll never
Where's your mother
And I've noticed turtle
Also back to your
I do not believe it
Question you missed one do you believe this
I'm a policy wonk
By far the greatest thing
Whatever happened
Violin entire like morning Zoo crew bump level
Missy said 10 Missy's dead ones
I love you you're like a doctor
Drew book upload
Any musical scale please do something
Well that's it was Monday
Jordan
Always a pleasure
So much fun
Next time we come back
Do you want to give out our personal
Also though
We are going
With a better sign
Yeah what do you think
Hotels
We Believe
Alexandra Thurston color