Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work
June
We do indeed
Please do
Can you
Put it in the form of two questions
Alright
If you are about to be in
Where I
Where you about to be indicted
Let's bring it into the subjunctive
Would you appreciate it
If the leading propagandist of our times
At least the crazy
Propaganda t-shirts are the most effective
Against All Odds
Alex Jones very effect
Would you like it if he was a huge fan of yours
No it probably will probably be bad probably be a bad look good
It sort of
Analyze who else is he a big fan of
And then it starts
To become like
That's really good analysis and that suggests
Answer to my next question
What is that who knows more about Alex
Stressful open into a corner with a double?
Electric novelty beverages today
We're on the Elysian Fields
Space dust IPA
Or whatever the beer company is here I feel very bad now not knowing what the company this is
Stacy
Student email
I think you were f***** up yesterday
Hi yesterday the definition of sober
Look I got to have both
Otherwise one of the other doesn't work
Well I'm not judging
Today we're going to be going back
Into the past
We're going to begin a new investigation
That will be one of many investigations
Before the show
And the present
Really sucks
Yeah it's
Easy to see through his games
Quite frankly
We just had to November 4th
Communist uprising
How did it go
Went well they took most of the Eastern seaboard
Like a pillow this to
We all knew the the idea of like
Alex
Creating
Possible scenario
I might want to talk
These games are being played over and over again and then at the same time
And there's all the
Sincerely nonsensical batshit stuff about helicopters at the Las Vegas shooting
Sharai and what have you and that's just
I mean
Not that fun
No we're still going to be talked about the present but I want to I want to take
I miss the 2015 investigate
Is what
Maybe have sex with his mom maybe maybe
Great guy and get on the train
Shrug on trains by friend
I'm so I'm going to I'm going to do we have a couple of time travel episodes
Policy wonks
Suggested
Spaceballs directionally a little bit more difficult than I would like to admit
Because they've just given date I've said I would like
It's too late
Showing vulnerability
With us
I'm working on the time travel episode
Specified date
But not years
So going through various Gears of a specific date and time to figure out did something happen this year
It's a bit of work but I'm working on them and I will have something eventually
But for now I'm going to embark on exploration
But I want to figure out along the way
Today we're going to jump off on the investigation of
We now know why Alex Jones join
Trump that's what I heard but how long did it take him to go from
I love Rand Paul but I like the things the Trump is saying
All right we got is Fort Drum
To being I will die for truck
How long does that transformation take
And I suggest
It's not going to take long I think this is desiccation is going to be
I think it happens in January 2016
I think he becomes like a fully dedicated propaganda outlet for Trump
But today we're going to be going over January 6th and 7th
Cuz in the new year he has David host
A better nurse that hangover affect that New Year's hangover
Answer we jumping on
January 6th
New Year's is his favorite holiday cuz
If you get to dress like a Nazi
No Halloween for every holiday
You could dress like a Nazi anytime you want
Alex Alex Jones does spiritual come on now
We're going to get into this January 6th
Episode and we don't have a lot of new list
There's because that would sound very weird if you hadn't had a blatant
This bike has to go back through
Of the back-and-forth of Sandra Bullock's husband's activities
So he I'm going to play a clip of Barack Obama's
And oh my God I can't wait to hear him speaking speaking about a recent
Shooting
In January of 26
Left
Still look pretty to think
Clip
The Fey play on Infowars
Some spooky music but it's important to hear the phrasing
Sing in the words that Obama uses because Alex
Complains about this clip
For almost the entire January 6th episode
So here is former President Barack Obama
We have a congressman
Actions within my legal Authority
So that is
Never heard it's a good thing
So I know to be afraid of it I absolutely
And the important thing to remember and I'm playing this up front because it's going
Come up
Pretty and inter
Mentley
Pull out of the phrase into the uses is
Until there's a congress that's in line with the majority of them
Keep that in mind
And we will get back to
On this on this episode
He gets into the globalist to bit
Here is a globalist
A little bit about the other plans
Visa vie
If they're being successful or on their own
Yeah
Bangladesh
Destroy your own future
New Rochelle
In the pond as long as it's practice station
I hope you enjoy yourself I hope you're proud of
Love yourself
Now because Patriots
After 15 years
When did they admit that
The military
Actually sees how really evil it is behind the scenes
People in federal agency
Sure are some of the most people
So this this
Is the least intelligent
Sentence I've ever heard my
Spread our articles
That's kind of the subjects of it
But at the same time he's fulfilling a couple of his narratives one the military is the most awake they know everything
That's largely because he gets a lot of calls for military people
I meant beyond that
The globalists are 15 years behind playing
And they have admitted it
When did
Now let me admit something
I'm 15 years behind on my life plant certainly
I'm 15 years behind on just general video games
12 hours yesterday I am exactly who I just got a switch
Seems like 12 hours is a soft
The very idea that they even in their their white papers are there
Cockamamie
Teams like complete nonsense do they have conferences like the Hilton
But you know me this just
Satisfies the other piece
Piece of his narrative videos like
The reason that were not in FEMA camps right now is because of me
I am stopping the globalist
Because of me
And people like me let's say Joseph
McCarthy back-in-the-day people who slow down the globalist plan
Welcome like you're welcome you're welcome
Huge fan of Woodrow Wilson he really took down the globe
All the time baby
I'm sure
I was watching the coverage of the supposed antifa riots
On Saturday
Who hosted the first
Like two hours of it and that's when I turned it off I was like I'll watch an hour and a half
Evans bucket
And he needs to trim up his beard and that's
Me talk
And a beard trim
And that's me saying why
He looks like s***
Griffin
It's just it was so boring it was terrible that Owen Shroyer on the street
It was just a man on the street interviews
Right
The kids this time
Nothing it was just like it was background noise no one wants to talk to you
Basically no one did they do you like Trump want to talk to you in about
And then just walked away
Which I guess is the right thing to do.
But didn't want to just Dimension was
I got I got to watch the live
Chat a little bit oh no
A lot of blame the Jews
Anal hole lot of people posting 1488
Which I don't know if you know about
Is that Nazis I feel like that's not
Placemats
4088 is the SS route
Heil Hitler
Okay I'm on the 14 is the 14 words
We will protect The Preserve
I mean that's the subject
But what it is about preserving the future of our children
Right right and making sure nobody in different races f*** each other
Neo-Nazi
Then let me give you reasons why
But that's the thing that's the thing is like
We're Nazis but where is Humane
How could you play me Richard Spencer even talks about that like nonviolent ethnic cleansing
And stuff like that
Opposition has gone out the window
Let's not break that down to fart less you advocate for someone's murder
I agree
Under the laws of parody I'm sure this is at least somewhat legal
Spell parody
The other parity
Want to talk about though is
Whether or not Alex Jones is okay with it or cool with it
Nazis flag
And he should know that there's a reason
You know what I'm saying
Like that that
It's not really an accident like you don't know Morrissey has a large
Hispanic
Sand Bass
And people don't really know why
Like everyone's confused
Not not sure why this is the case.
Weather
Speaks a lot about emotional issues that are shared by
First or second generation immigrants in LA
Okay alright that's reasonable
I don't think that's so I don't think that explains everything
Fine
That's a reasonable enough
And that's why we need to build a wall around
Picture
The Holden is here
Enough explanation for a sort of bizarre counterintuitive fanbase
There is no explanation needed for why if you have a Nazi fanbase
You need to you
You might be playing tonight you are doing something right order to get that fan base
And Alex should be aware that
Which is interesting Jeff Foxworthy made a career of
Kind of making
King fun of Nazi
Is that is that true now that we know what redneck
Really mean
Oh boy
Exact
Civic
Yeah it was next clip
You just might be hazard
In this next clip Alex
So we can
So in the next time we find that Alex at the beginning of 2016 has not lost his hard-on for Russia
Over the new year he got drunk
And it came out of that hangover
Still loves Russia
There's nowhere to run
Digital
So now
He doesn't do a terrible job of diagnosing I'll probably
I think he's right he's not right
He's correct calm down he's not right but he have a pretty decent
Point to make
About the idea of
You know centralized banking
Having a detrimental effect on
Especially third world population disenfranchised
No cheese involved
I mean there's some juice involved
I don't I don't like you saying either put you hold off on
To talk about a blatantly anti-semitic subject
Without
Having some like I just don't like it it's it's tough because we're dealing with someone who has
Such bailed and
Powerful under the surface answer
December 10th
Using parody with him
It often
Temp sound
And feels very uncomfortable
It's tough but I want you to hold your tongue about
I mean about any like he has a point
Because it falls off the rails pretty quick
And doesn't know
Or other organizations
Rothschild
Oligarch
First years ago
Wasn't true and then turned out
This suit
Boris Yeltsin homeless people
A roll of
That's not
Until then
So there is
That narrative
Spelling here
I'm going to just come from a kernel of Truth
There were members of the Rothschilds family that sued I believe it was
The The Daily Mail
Reliable
Seems reasonable
Anybody who's in The Daily Mail probably has standing to sue the Daily Mail
Alright yeah I would
But in this case I wanted one of the reasons especially in terms of politics
Superhot is very difficult
2 proof
And what it what they posted
In the Daily Mail was that
This child
Who is Diaz
It described in this independent
Article here
XB Scion of the banking
King Dynasty in friend of seemingly everyone in the Spheres of Finance
Business and politics
The Puppet Master to the baron of Hartlepool in Floyd
I'm having a great time
Turtle poop
His name is Mister Mandell
And so the case
They did this libel case
Because it was found
Deeply involved with influencing mr. Mendelssohn
That's why you shouldn't people when they're right
Right it's a bad idea
It's one of those intimidation things that can go too far
Justice system
Peter till would have gotten his ass handed to him by God
Yeah
Unfortunately
Over it
The daily mail's account of his and Mr mandelson
Trip to Russia in January of 2000
Mister mandelson whatever I can play
The Delight just to hear you say mister mandelson he is a Labour politician
And Britt
He has also recently said that he will work everyday Around the Clock
To undermine Jeremy corbyn
So we can tell that he's probably more
Yeah
Labor people are the pro-corporate Democrats
Corbin is your Bernie Sanders
Except somehow he's
Kind of Steel for brexit
It's a very strange thing I understand slightly where they
From 5
I think it's I think it's
I don't know
I don't understand the intricacies of British Politics as well as I'd like but I have heard a couple accounts of
Arguments for brexit
I think it's probably clunky and will be much
More negative
I just logistically
I don't think it's going to happen
No
Thanks it's going to happen
If you thought it was actually going to happen
And they would have to start building borders between Northern Ireland
That will be a terrible blow to Alex's Patriot narrative
Cuz it's one of the Cornerstone
Knows that it's a terrible idea it was a terrible idea
I just wanted to get elected
It's just like it's just like Republicans Trump was a bad idea
It's amazing to me
What they will hide underneath will of the p
When they're lying to the people right right
Like with the Republicans in like
Huge tax cuts to the corporate Rich are going to help you out and it's like it's the will of the people we can't go against
You could just tell them the truth
What's the difference between like if you want to take him to a medical perspective
16 lichen
Unscented informed
You need to have when people are making
A medical decision they have to be aware of the risks
The literature and stuff like that and then once
Once you have done that but you have informed
Consent for vacation
To make a decision
There should be
Some of that for voting
But I said anytime anybody tries to restrict voting we always
What even was
That was a tactical
Yeah the racist voting restrictions
I'm sorry about the Rothschilds
Standard Boogeyman
Alex Jones and
The Terrible
Big
Look up above the politician
Pulling the strings
Is the Rockefellers aren't really around anymore
Well David just died
Yeah but yours back
Maybe you're so good
Because it's been
So many years and generational has been split up among a bunch of people and none of them Wheels
The same power that like the baron of Rothschild did a hundred years ago children of Henry
Come anywhere near the power that he even like the wolf
Keys and stuff like that
They have
Regionally or in small conclave
It's big influence
Like what they could have had during these
Like back in the days of Henry Ford
Not even close to that
Like the kroenke's live in Columbia Missouri
Fortune
Credo
In terms of paying athletes
Some stuff like that illegally car and I like
Weird under-the-table recruitment stuff that everybody's aware of
Argument is
App for another time but
It should be legal athletes should be paid
Of course
They can do that
But no no
Did they can effects like Columbia local politics
Stuff like that to a certain
Extent that they
Dan seems like they can't send us to war
Like you could have
So I'm going to read this this next paragraph and at the end of it it gets dicey
For the present
Mr Rothschild claims he was subjected to sustained and unjustified attacks
In the May 2010 article which portrayed him as a puppet
Dangling his friend Lord mandelson in front of the Russian oligarch
Oleg deripaska it to ease the passage of
Colossal biz
Do you recognize that name
Oleg deripaska
It sounds Swedish
So I'm going to assume he's Swedish no it's not to mention positive could have been Middle East
Is Isis Russian
He's Russian
Do you know what Russia has done Risa
Do you know what recently indicted gentleman was very involved with Oleg deripaska
I am still going
Is it a Swedish politician
No he's British there are no swedes in this story
Oleg deripaska is the Russian oligarch
That
Paul manafort offered to give briefing
Things to
Indication
That's all there is
A lot of financial debt
Between the two men
Corsage
Bringing up this libel case about the Rothschild
Is a very interesting window
Because
The only Russian oligarch involved is a person who's involved
Trump's campaign manager
The Rothschild Nathaniel Rothschild
Brought Lord mandelson
Along
To Russia
Pretend
But if we can get some business deals going
Mandelson will be on your side in British politics
Which is
You're like making a pattern
It's a good thing for him he doesn't read it because
Totally
I mean if you just replace mandelson with manafort you have almost a parallel exact same situation
Playbook
Russian oligarchs and billionaires
A playbook
It's almost like somebody we know Rhoda Playbook it's almost like somebody who's been on Alex
Fashion show
Wrote The Playbook that is taught in Military Academy
It's weird
Back in 1910 with the Pez dispenser to try and make that kind of a claim with
About Alexander
I would get sued for libel by The Daily Mail
It's overestimate this because he is like super involved in a lot of f***** up stuff
In the stuff that we're talking about it makes him sound like
A big bad
So he's not the not the final boss no but he is a a cancerous influence
Couched in intellectualism
And what have you
ITunes
Worth talking about but
To pretend like
It all goes back to Dugan
Placing some people on Twitter
Sort of making those sorts of
It's just because he has he has such a
Long-standing history of anti liberalism
Anti-americanism
Letgo
I like all that.
Need to focus on
I don't know
Anyway Alex bringing up the Rothschild stuff there does not work in your favor
That's interesting interesting
It's fascinating to see him
Talk about
Global org
Realization as being something that he hate
Wait so desperate
Yeah I have no idea how
Global organization
Complicated system
We're in even the bad guys are good sometimes and the good guys are bad
Because it's
Interlochen
Where everybody trying to play this longer game and you do this whole thing
And so he has no concept of complicated systems
He only understand
Like he doesn't get it
And it is a failing in terms of him being able to be in news
About about the
Variety
But I was watching
The quote-unquote
Antifa riot
So
Owen Shroyer was out on the
At the Austin
Gathering of the
Resist fascism or whatever
Right and
Most of it was covering
How there were
More Trump
Fans there
The protesters really kind of didn't know it was going to happen and the Trump people
We're like
But the other thing is
The lottery was Joe big
Dancing around with pre-made sign
I would have you
Like
They're covering
An Infowars reporter
F****** with
Quote-unquote antifa
Optic side of the story
If you want to be a journalist
If you want to be doing journalism
Well there's that
But also if you are Infowars anyway
Yeah
Don't become as the story
You're sending in that Rambo Biggs on Twitter
Report
Him
Resisting the antifa it's so stupid
I know your point and I agree with that
But like from
Totally agree but real world
Get smart from
Sandpoint
But if everyone understood to have journalism
Should work unbiased
External that's
It'll be like this is embarrassing you know he's still kind of works for you
Well but the the situation that we don't really know what the deal is
So
Right
I wish some jobs would like give me that kind of leeway
It's a good thing nobody got shot anyways you're going to take a day off right we're going to give you one day almost
Somebody leave
I'm in your back
We all exactly of course of course they don't
Want to do real journalist
Cuz that would be still
And hard so hard to do
To call you have to check sources information down the road
You can't have a 26 27 year old dude with probably like a sports
Fitness degrees
I like
He'll make it a whole thing or hotel and restaurant management
Like its
Maybe I'll tell you that right
History degree that I'm having like a media studies or something like that degree
It really is much better than Alec
Manipulating
Like
You could see it in the way he's pivoted he did that
I'm pivoting away from Trump thing
Pushing back against
Trump
Like you
Like that
I don't I don't believe
But that's still a much more cogent
Argument
For your behavior than anything else
Yeah it's a little more savvy
And probably will last longer
That's
That's true
Almost nobody brings up any was involved in gamergate
Stuff and almost nobody brings up all the f***** up stuffy
We don't know the reason that it is a good idea for your dumbass
Is like Joe Biggs to Kobe and inserts
Themselves into
Story
Is because if you're Alex
Jones
Your
Higher
F****** business is built on
A personality
Inserting himself into the story more or less go
Crazy story
That's interesting
Personality
They are about the guy
You're onto something there
Possible
I'm so I apologize that it's been almost half an hour since I played that clip of Obama
Into the in bringing this up
Here is a Alex
Bringing up this cliff
And like I said
I wanted to make a point of pointing out that what Obama actually said
Was we can't wait
For Congress to get in line with
The majority of them are
There are things that I can do within my legal Authority
To try and put a stat
Against the tide of gun deaths
Unnecessary.
The year is Alex Jones
Covering that
Largely innocuous
The President says Donald Trump disqualified
Even
This was also in the context of comments being
Disqualifying and that sort of thing it wasn't like
Disqualified
He wasn't allowed to run it
I don't think I know I know Trump is a huge marathoner right past the physical
Is there a physical
Trump's wife
What's it called
When you quote literally said quote quote
Joseph Stalin
Lenin
Frank Darabont
Dusty Baker
Dusty Rhodes Rhodes Scholars
Better
About what
So at this point he's getting a little bit too much into his Yosemite Sam voice
Service here just listen to this
React
I like your face didn't even boot like you took your eyebrows
We're at this point without like
Incredibly offensive I was starting to think about my white guilt
I do think it's okay if you're black
Parody
Sufferin Succotash
You good to him but he just
Like I'm going to go for it
Those are the same people who insisted
Because I don't like his economic
Right
No he's allowed to do everything he wants cuz he's black you guys
Now
Isis going to keep foreign treaties secret is that the method
Military treaty with Syria
And Russia
With no one else knowing
Let's go Patriots
Totally
I'll do the next play Alex
Is Kettle action pot calling the kettle black
Here we go with this
This is
Emily. Obama
Up there
English
How much more will we put up with
Together
A satirical piece
14b or should I get a full view of it
Have you
So Alex you have brass balls
Brass f****** balls
Look
If anybody knows what fake crying looks like it's definitely Alex
Right and I think that that is why he makes claims like that it's like
I think deep down he's like
Humans don't have emoji
I know that if your feet if you're looking like you feel something you're Faking It by do what is Obama trying to sell
Does he have a mineral line what is going on
Dude if Obama told brainforce
I might be far more likely to
First of two comedy pieces on this episode
Play Obama's press conference Ruiz
Hardly speaking about
Beach shootings
Open house we need to do a better job
On Sunday there was just another one
I actually just reinforces that
I like I like how
He's saying this like it's a drumbeat how much are we going to put up with hands like yeah no
You nailed it
That is exactly what he saying that's exactly what he's doing
And that's a question that we are
Absolutely
Incapable of asking
I think most of the country who are not the Holden
To the NRA
And what have you
Alex is dumb
Question we ask ourselves a lot
Like how much
I mean you didn't show that there was a shooting like a couple blocks away from our houses together day
Yeah I had no idea yep that's that's how it turned out in like soda like
I mean what are you going to local big news
That's f***** up no
F*****-up Chicago
Yeah
Which is the I-10 again we can talk about statistics all all day it's like
Chicago has a lower shooting death rate than any other routes
But at the same time we do live in a place where the second highest population third highest population in the country
Nonsense
Anyway
Alex thinks that Obama is faking cry
Right now let's enjoy this next clip which
The sort of the
Chaser to that shot
During the break I am in just a state of grief
Morning but also explosive will resist at 5%
Please give me the
Rita Marley
Google back to that metaphor I also notice says amen
He prays a lot on air but never says amen
Weird
Is it the thing
I mean you're supposed to say Amen right I mean that's Attica
God needs an over and out
Jesus Christ what a stupid
Religion
NASCARs
Get angry
Not great
You don't have to give me more
I love America
And I'm angry because I'm so sad
Right
It's if you watch the video it is so
I have tears in my eyes I don't want to know I don't want to have tears in my eyes
Is the most revealing Statin
Nobody who's ever cried against their will has been like
I'm doing this
Even though I don't want to
To do the I feel this so powerful
I can't I don't even want to do that do you know what to it it's just fascinating to me the idea that he is
Fake crying
It is very fake
Banana in the middle of saying that Obama's
Tears are fake
David Obama really with crying
From everything I can tell it's
Seems like he was sincere and genuine
Right I don't know I don't know the man personally
I haven't spent as much time studying him as I have
Alex true
I'm willing to believe his tears were real I'm not willing
And based on that dichotomy the fact that he's like
Alright
I'm trying to say the present
Fake crying
Right I really need a
A good cry
This month
I am going to
I will show you how it's done
Goddamn emmerich
F****** Jones and Sandra Bullock as a Nazi
88rising
Like
It it's so in line with what I have
Determine the terms of Alex's psychology
Talking about Obama fake crying but
Alex
Absolute
About
Made a massive discovery
WhatsApp
Now it's a discovery that we kind of already know
Well it's it's it's something that we had the sense of
Before we didn't have as many
Concrete
Examples
Alex Jones
Chucky
The Alex Jones
Is flattery
You can compromise him and corrupt him through flattery
Incredibly
The same way we suspect the Trump
Possibly through his business might be more on the up-and-up in terms of business
But if anybody tells him
You're awesome
We love you
He falls in line
As we heard you talked to high-end Russian
Putin love the show
And Putin listens all the time and what have you
You can get
High-end mail-order bride
So I assume
No these are high in military Rush
Did he married
You need to know
Is at the beginning of 26
Alex Jones
Scored an interview with Louis Farrakhan
That
Is now my favorite thing
That you've ever said
Now we won't get to the entire interview on this episode
No because
You haven't heard it yet
The timeline that we're in
Jesus a good week and a half do you need it for the Conte
He is screaming about Louis Farrakhan and Hate
And hates the Nation of Islam and thinks they're a bunch of race-baiters
All that
Naturally
He gets to go talk to Louis Farrakhan
Now listen to this
The show transgender
All the race car
Doesn't sound like it
And that's really what's so important about a possibility we have
Disagree
You love him but matter
Famous 2-0 everyday and every week
Farrakhan
Every week
What is Milo
Divide and conquer
Buy concrete
It's the Final Chapter folks you know what comes next
The dreaded false flag
Is a
Shooting
Cameras
Have your phone ready
And uploading
Agree
Asphalt
Immediately
Eric went on longer than I am
Tattoo
Is soft
Herscher
False flag
Like you pointed out
Obama's
His approval rating was over 50% right now Trump has it sitting right around 30 minutes
And no one
No one
On the left
Is asserting
Latest church shooting in Texas
Was a false flag
The trumpet organized or anything like that
I'd I know that that's a little bit ugly to even
Put into words
But the reason I want to do that
2 mirror
What other version of Alex
Would be like right
And trying to look at like
What
How a
How gross
Anybody else
Then Alex doing the things
He does ra
It's unthinkable
Well is unspeakable that anybody else would do this
But the polar opposite to falsehood isn't a
Current type of fault
That's true
Like we're we're people who tell at least as
As far as we are
Research
Reality
Like a the Lusitania probably was
Was sunk
As a false flag
Absolutely
Play all of these things but it is definitely something that exists
The f*****-up CIA
Talk about how people having a lot of guns
Is a bad idea
It's fine if you have died like I'm very
.
But
I get it
If you hunt if you have a gun to protect your family I get it
Even for fun
Intuit
That she just likes to take out to go to the shooting range
And feel like she has a dick for an hour
Wichita misogynistic
Well I think that's what most people have guys feel like they have a bigger
Yeah I mean I don't know if that I don't know if that's necessarily the case
And recreational purposes having a gun is
Is totally cool but at the same time
It is a situation where you should do
There should be records
Nobody had a gun
But that's not going to
At this point I would prefer if nobody used a gun to murder large groups of people at one point would it be if
Everybody will hunted with went back to bow and arrow I mean
Yeah it would be really like
If you kill something
Like an animal with a gun
Not really that impressive
Take one out with a bow
Way more impressive
If you were going out with a knife
You got it right now
I watch Lost
I know what it's all about
It always comes back with a gun
When lock went out there
F****** took down a peg
The Great
Anyway at the point is
Yes we we can we can walk a middle ground because the the reality of the world
Is The Middle on this very episode about
The idea that
Centralized banking
Interests are detrimental to the world
It's not that there
Some sort of globalist
Cabal
That are that are doing it
But they're not
Like
Is that they all have certain
Tacit agreement
But they don't necessarily
Talk about
But there is always going to be
Oh you guys did this will f*** yeah we can do that too illegal s***
And jumping to
To Alex's version
Aahat
Bigly
Eats a big lie
So whatever you whenever you
Get into the idea that there are Global corporations
Is there a global bank
That are interested in the profit margin
Interested in making as much money as they
We can discuss that in terms of
Regulation
Should be
Are treaties between countries
Should be enforced
For Country should no longer exist
That's a whole lot of
That's a whole lot of the whole conversation
That one is
Unreasonable conversation
Just to get back to my point
B b the did the distance between
That the recognition
Corporations that are out for the bottom line
Yeah
And
Jumping
They're Satanist
And they want to
And they drink blood because there's adrenaline in it
It's it's where you is it's where you ruin a legitimate conversation
Yeah it's like
I don't know who it was but I wanted one of our listeners sent me a message about how
Through the overseer
Sensationalism
Through the fetishization and
Satanic Panic asked
Service
To the idea of the reality
Crimes against children
Absolute
Because you're creating
False reality where
People drink blood and there's
There's there's
These
Giant
Like
That demonic orgies and what-have-you right
That is not
Real
And when
You presented is what you're up against
You're never going
To get through the truth
Is it there are
Done
Two children
Massive
And you're never going to
To the bottom of that you're never going to solve that problem if you focus on
This bizarre
Over Amplified Eyes Wide Shut
Kind of reality
And it is
It is what he does with the banking stuff to it's what he does with all of these problems
Unsolvable
More or less
Yeah you have no power
Give me money
Give me
It's it's of the
Best
Type of scientific bulshit articles that you can read you know the
The headline is insane and then you read the article and was like
No sorry sister said this probably isn't true
We're going to make this huge
And it was that
Young blood transfusions into the elderly is a good idea I think so
May help Alzheimer's
Like to finally get ahold of cuz it's like
Now all
That's not a transfusion
Liberals no transfusion
Cuz it doesn't go in your bloodstream
That's what they want you to the globalist don't put that out in the white
Papers look look they told you that their plan was 15 years behind
That was a false flag to get old people to drink young people's blood okay
Is interesting
That that's in the same way that like
I don't know the same way that locks
Gym bars
We're cool for a bit in the 90
Feel like there are these things there are these things that like have some sort of like scientific in
Creed
And I
Certainly this point I don't think the Sciences in about putting young blood in you
But it is interesting in that sense
Also Brian can go through a European blood transfusion
Did your native blood
Why not
Whatever
I don't give a s***
Let's move on
I think we all
No I love Kobe Bryant Kobe was one of my favorites when I was younger
Not just as a basketball player but as a human
Get out there and saw that opioid crisis Rex
Lord's work
F*** you man
When I was young for no reason the New York Knicks were my favorite team cuz I love like
Anthony Mason
The shave things on the side of his head
I thought that was really cool and all the guys would say
His bald ass head I thought your favorite team would have been the Celtics cuz they were the last team
No also Charles Oakley was really cool
So he was that like badass Enforcer
F*** you
I mean the next original name was the Knickerbockers and we all know
The theater
I have no idea to Nickelodeon
No didn't have something to do with socks
I feel like it was a very important might have been
On this January 6th episode
What Alex Jones
Address point
Are there are like maybe 15 instances of him saying that Obama said
Yeah instead of getting line with the majority of the public payment which again if you're going to say
Quotes
You should
Quotes right and he's acting as if
Obama said get in line with me
Right and then place the clip
Which I think is unwise
As a propaganda
Not a good idea
You should not play the clip make people search it out cuz you know they're not going to
Course just say what you want to say and move along
So he doesn't like
10 time probably in the episode and I left out the other night
The Supercut
Which is an interesting thing for somebody like him to say considering
You want they're going to get in line
I could make a Supercut
But I got I just got to switch
So I don't have time
So for the rest of the episode
Amarillo
So good so good Mario Odyssey is the best
They're also shades of the Odyssey
Bennett
Is that why it's called Mario Mario Odyssey I don't think so cuz there are like a bunch of suitors trying to get p
That would be awesome that would be amazed
Bowser and like a piranha plant
Hey that's very important
Right
Yes
How Maybe
Anyway
The rest of the show
Alex Jones
Is visited
Buy a guy
Play who believes Arrigo
Can lizards
Oh okay
David Icke David Icke makes a little comeback
Really long interview
Not important
But I just have a few
So you're the first one where he's
Give him a little bit of an introduction
And gets
Mobile lock
Schedule for months now
Sure
He is referring just do that same
Mo Bamba
Coming up
Constantly
Complaining
So before he gets
It's a little bit
It's always a long-ass
Yeah before David Icke comes in
He has to brag about his own
Place in the world a little bit
And it's probably
It furthers this
Being
Being co-opted through flattery
Siri
I think that's the entire story of Alex
But if 20 years ago bill Klein
Headquartered Alex
He never would have listened to Larry Nichols
It would have been
He would instead be a triangle a Centrist Democrat
And we all know how damaging that could be this podcast would still exist
You and I would just switch chairs
That's an alternate reality
Will be a struggle for six months and then we both descend into similar insanity
But you know be fascinating though to like if they had done that story of our friendship is this
Decided to do the same because the first time
Oh I'm going to talk to you for the next 6 hours
That's low
Buffalo anyway one day we'll do a how we met podcast
About that's the new gameplay
Talk over
We could we come up with a couple things like that like
How we met
These these things that are of no interest to anyone
We have Larry Nichols on the phone
No I know you are in Nicaragua
How do you think Dan and Ice friendships
But we were doing some comedy
Now
I can't remember their names s***
Here Alex is bragging
If you just flatter him
That's all you need to do
Like
Russian high command
Watch the show
Flies
Global warming or Global governance
Destroyed
They are tuning into the reality it makes sense to them and then they learn more
Outside the box
So
That
Tell me why
And then
I was like
I'm going to keep being critical of Putin
Until I found out
He loves me
Well clearly Putin's right
Course
Wow yeah it's dumb
Does he realize have dummy is I don't think he knows what he's saying
Play cuz that that clip indicates that he's aware of the
Trajectory
Like you wear of the fact that like
I was critical of food
High-end Russian
Because he loves me loves all I do is talk about other globalist want to take out
I mean if you really look at the reality is especially as it relates
The oligarch situation
Alex is there
Completely off
In terms of that
Kickout oligarchs
Cisco
Did you see the news about the Saudi Prince
Yeah alright
Now if you want it it would
Explain a little bit for the
Just had a huge
And another uncle
Yeah
For corruption charge
In a bit of a to b a
Yeah
Exactly so if you're going to say it's like that's like saying he got rid of
Like no
He got rid of
Somali
And he's keeping the ones
Prince
Is getting rid of the oligarchs
Who he doesn't like
And he's just going to install
Different ones bunch of apartment buildings in 1999 seized power
Kicked out all the guards that wouldn't play ball played ball with the rest of them did a massive Crackdown on the meter
And then started killing all his attract
A lot of snow like that I made that track record is there and protect
Who has
Time to listen to him everyday
I do a podcast about him everyday and I don't listen to him everyday
I have three f****** hours to listen to this b******* everyday horse nobody lunch doesn't listen
Best Putin has a guy
He's hired to listen to Alex Jones
Maybe only in case like you said something
Polonium darts with Adam or whatever
Bright
He's not listening
Not monitoring
Possibly farmed out
This whole idea that people keep telling him we listen
Write to him
He's just
He's drinking the Kool-Aid
Remind me
What hours are
Pretty pretty simple map to do
I don't think the internet is as free and Russia as it is here
Access to his show at 6 not slightly less free than the internet in China
Terrestrial Leon radio in China
I don't think so I don't know
Definitely Hazmat
I told you this yesterday but comedy
Mvid November 4th antifa coverage
Matt
The guy who hosts
A radio station in the Chicago suburbs
That airs Alex Jones
Then Alex and passes had them on the show
It says like
Chicago
Justin the suburbs
And whatever
So
He came on
November 4th broadcast with Rob do
And it turns out
That his signal was down
The morning of November 4th
And he wasn't on air
Yeah I was like
Is it probably
I know that you are Infowars.
It was a big storm last night
Bunch of other stuff that some sort of a coincidence I don't know
There's other stations I don't know
Free show
Together every late night show has a
Show interview
Improvised conversations guys he has a boner for not having a
And all that I understand
You want things to be natural in Germann and
Same thing but at the same time if you're going to have a guy calling in
They're going to build a
False narrative off
In the break
Talk to him and be like
Play along
Or I mean he's a radio station owner like no.
Because we have Sears of Comedy Improv
But like comedy
Thumbs up
BFDI Clark
Freeze up
Hahaha
You know they liking it too I liken it to whenever like you're playing a softball game
And there's a hit
And as soon as the ball is in the air someone that plays a second
Or something like that so everyone knows
Get the ball to second if you catch
You know that
Sometimes you forget where the runners are
And in the commercial break
Rob dudes be like play the second
This is what we're going right
Now you don't have to say you were sabotage
Also
I get it
He runs
Infowars on his radio show
Yeah he's indicated or whatever
Does not listen to Infowars
So he's not going.
Wow and he still doesn't know how to run with a narrative
I feel like you should be able to jump in at that point
For own race
I told you this is an interview with David Icke
And I
Unfortunate clip of David Icke
Talking about the globalist and what they're doing but it actually
In hindsight really applies to Alex
Can I call him
Dick Van Dyke
From now on
If you want to I feel good
Global site
Freedom
In the public
The reasons why
And because those reasons are not genuine
You have to
You are bringing your system
By lying and lying and lying
Man I love that last part
I love that you're bringing in a global
If you isolated that clipped
Because he's using the second person and talking to Alex
A hundred percent agree with
Because that's where we're having
No.
I'm confused
Don't Judge David I don't know his name David Icke
Demons
Look I I think he has a beholding to answer
Somatic ideas
We certainly believe the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Is real
You're not telling me I'm not blaming him
He is a bit of an anti-semite
But I think
He's mentally ill
Like it away is it Alex
Isn't
Like I always do
He had a weird experience when he was in Peru I think rides on a Mountaintop
Frozen in place
Bunch of things downloaded into him through the
The reason that I say don't blame him as much as because
I honestly think to a certain extent from the times I've heard him on Infowars that he's
Like not thrilled to be there
Like not that he doesn't like Alex or anything like that but it's just like
Fine I'll play along there is a global oppressive system and why
Aliens
Right
He's also a whatever bulshit
To be like fractures
It's unclear
He's good with it
In terms of the Trump stuff
The system but he's not in the same vein as our
I don't think
It's the difference between
A crazy
Pundit in a
Alex Jones the propaganda
Cuz he's working
Towards a specific goal
I think David Icke
Razee pundit
I think he's
But at the same time
A lot of stuff
She says it's really relevant
A lot of the stuff that he says
Is
Makes sense
Some of the points
Behind it
In terms of self-empowerment
Shadow Self and a real self
And there's some like
Just
Self-improvement the ideas that he has
So
You're smart enough to disinfect
Your argument
For not blaming him
To do with like
You disentangled
He's just
He's trying
Is that your argument for why I shouldn't even know
You disentangle the parts of it that are clear like
Like there's Brandon
Yeah and some of the ideas
AR
Okay
And pretty good right I believe that a lot of the
Stuff that he says Federer that's real f*****-up and negative
Especially the
Space lizards
The protocols that sort of stuff that comes out of brain dead
I think it's much more
Fear when you look
In-N-Out
Most thinking people can look at him and he's like
He believes there are legit shape-shifting space lizards
Much easier to look at him and be like
I'm going to f****** either not listen
You or discount those parts of you
Where is
And he's not working towards a specific
Goal
I guess
Self
Preservation
No not for himself but for you
Motivational speaker actualization with his
Not fine with his Mountain
But you're fine with him as a human being
So long as his nonsense comes from a
Altruistic place
No no I mean he's a con man in a lot of ways
Through through just Vinny
Because you need to have people
Throw your money in Courthouse
Crazy alien
Yeah but his career he could have done with Alex
He could have settled down
Don't radio show
And started selling weird supplement
I probably made
Killing office
Instead
He's written a bunch of book
He's gone out and slip
Submitted to public scrutiny
In a way that most people would not allow
Like lectures and stuff like that where people mock him and attack him
Dumb dumb
Somewhat it's
It's not even just to that
It's that
Look
I believe Alex Jones what motive
In a large part does come from Mental Health
Yeah it comes from a place of like
Deprivation is a
A child feeling
Thanks yeah absolutely
I am
For some reason
Are less offense
I don't understand that I'd like to think we would launch into a I'm headed to spend David
That's always my favorite my favorite conversations
Don't know if I want to do this
I don't know why I'm doing this
Somehow I ever
Do I do I do think so
I do I do believe it's always a matter of degree
Crazy enough
To not be responsible for his actions
It's not even crazy enough
Tanabe response
For the actions what I think is
This might be weird but it's what popped into my head and I think it I think it might be where I draw the line
Okay
Alex Jones
With a little bit of self-awareness
And good decision
Could go to therapy
And work through some of these issue
I don't think David I could
I think he has brain.
Okay
And I think
That the brain damaged part of ham
Is the part that is
And maybe this is
Blue Sky Thinking on my part Rose Colored Glasses
I think that the brain damage is the part that believes in the protocols of the elders
Zion
The part that believes in
Space lizard
And what have you
And it would I choose to believe in
Again
Might be wrong is that the other part
The pretty empowering
The pretty self-actualizing motivation
Speaker part
Been there all along
But I also don't think that whatever he have going on
Therapy could ever help
Open leave Alex
Could be helped
Maybe not now but in the past
Okay Isaac David like probably hated
Alright
This is a
Huge conversation to have
I got your realize how big you just
You just open this out
I mean like the first thing I thought whenever you were talking about brain damage and
It's extent to personal responsibility keep this conversation within like
The first thought I had was f****** Aaron Hernandez
And Chris Benoit
You know what I'm saying
Which which is an interesting conversation in as far as like
How
How much can you hold these guys responsible for brain
Just clearly what was going on
Right like there's
Clearly brain-damaged like any NFL player end up murdering
People
Like it's really hard to hold
Any NFL player accountable for their actions simply because
Clearly your brain is
Damn can I take a step back
Answered of refine the argument please do
I think one
Since you're legitimately harming other people my argument
Right because I do I don't think that
Speaking specifically in terms of espousing belief
As opposed to
Killing your family
It's like different there at least in terms of intensity or Vale
But see then you get into the then get into the concept of what ultimately is more.
Damaging like what is what is more damaging
Somebody with a mental with brain damage like Chris Benoit or somebody with brain damage like Alex Jones
Who is influenced so many more people in such a larger negative
Smaller more focused destroyed my argument cuz I'm just reflecting
Me know and are the past the past of our podcast.
Documented brain damage on Alex's party
I think
It is is I think
The David Icke
Is less noxious
I think that there is
More that can be gained
Rum ham
For sure
I think if you listen to his wife I have I listened to a bunch of them
Run at the same time there's a bunch of stuff that's like
Well that's like I mean
The Pendragon
And Kerry Cassidy
Right right out there
But God damn it if they don't believe that they're good people and act like good people for the most part
They just espouse
Such
Ideas you're right you're like I don't understand how to reconcile those two you know
I think in the end you're probably right
I still want to hold on to whether it's right or wrong
That David Icke
Is not nearly as bad as I
Purely statistical level
I agree with you but I also in terms of like
I don't think that David Icke has a
Goal in mind
I think Alex
Does whether or not
He believes it's
Nefarious
Like
Beaver like just wants you to f******
Recognize that everything is b*******
Like wake up
The TV is brainwashing and stuff like that
Is what we're having right now
Gotcha more or less
Anyway
Which is why
Riveting podcast
But let me say this it's appropriate that you and I have embarked on this conversation
Because in this neck
Clip
Alex Jones is struggling
With the fact
Vicki agrees with a David icon so much.
Cuz I don't know
David Icke talks about space lizards
I should I agree with daylight and getting close to being like
Oh am I an idiot
It doesn't matter
What's up
Please just
Going back and forth
I believe it daily
But I believe it's human a lie
Reasonable is a facsimile of the conversation
Exactly
They just if they haven't you got to give it to some sort of weird intuitive ethics conversation
I'd like okay
So long as we're talking about aliens
I can have a reasonable right right
Is like as long as we are taking it out of the real world
Where I don't have any emotional investment in
If your team is
Pro-human
Then you just start talking about reasonable s***
As opposed to
Science fiction as
As always had a
An easier time of allegory
You don't need direct 10 science fiction
Predictive programming to the dreams of
Will Shakespeare
The Show Goes On
To be clear most of it is not really all that worth
Garbage
It's fine it's not it is what it is
David Icke
Like putting out his positions and right
Yeah it's just
It's not that good so we move on now to January 7th
The next day
Yeah Thursday
And
He's moved on
From his
Getting low
Misquoting
Get in line with me
Not a quote
Yeah and so here is
Here is
Where he goes
The next day
Maury 2016
Barack Hussein Obama
The enemy of this constitutional republic
Broadcast to the back when is Vanna Rite
So couple
Does Ryan
How long is he been Speaker of the House
Well here's the thing
The only reason I know it's Paul Ryan
Is because in the narrative that we've been going over with Alex
Yeah Boehner was this
Speaker at metallic pretended that all of the Patriot
Tea party types
Got to play ball
He knows he knows where the power is
Except
Dumber somehow
Younger and Dumber
Paul Ryan is such a disappointment
Alex and the thing I wanted
The point out was
Does the Geist is another one of his attempt
To create like a cat's fur
Like he's doing now with the
Get tomorrow's news today
Today
But that was another attempt
Letgo
Going to cover a couple up
This is another thing I want to make a Supercut of
But I didn't
Because it would be too difficult
I bought a switch so
I'm going to play this clip
That
He says this
Times throughout the
Stinking handed Prime
Over
The top
So from Akon
Constitutional scholar
There is a that guy
Definitely committed all the crimes
About Obama crime
He committed while in office
I'm going to get to this no matter what
Sorel 75
Do you think he even got 21
Supposed to do the fourth hour he calls
6 Arab dude doesn't Alex Jones without ever talking about this article
He says over and over again
I'm going to get that is article
We're going to get to this no matter what I'm going to stay here if I have to do
Never get to even one now
I can read it
Either that
I'm so
I didn't even remember how many of these
I can't even remember them
First of all
Second
Did not read this article
Imallexx
Daniel think he's Martin Luther
Might as well
Episode
IWatch
The lives
November 4th
Antifa protests
Right took over and there's a lot of 1488
There's a lot of Nazi messages a lot of kill the Jews messages in chat room
I saw that you got to count to trolls
Certainly I'm not going to say that every single one of them was sincere
But boy was a lot of people
It was a lot of people
And let's
Listen to this next clip
With that in
They are the most
Evil enemy by
The globalist
I mean
What about him
Was
Moral good person
And Hitler was super dark
Mount
Bisquick goes on butt
So many different comparisons
Totally
Why did you say
I don't know
Well guys choose Hitler is always to make
Hitler look
Better
I didn't I don't want to save this
Before the clip plays but I might as well he's doing a little bit of Hitler apology
In this
I mean anytime that your rhetoric is like
These people has great compared to them it's generally softening or
The name of the cliff I have here is Alex's soft on Hitler
Just Pizza
But listen
Listen to this
Also there's
Is a ton of long pauses
Cuz you can see in his face like
You know sometimes like I was feeling it during the day but icon
Conversation
Thing I'd probably
I don't know if I have
Skills right now to go
Get through this
There's a look on his face of like
I know the point I'm trying to
This is why
I don't know
It's the journey not the destination
And I do not know how I'm going to get
I'm wondering if there's a lot of long pauses along the way
The UK
Norse countries
The Elise
Twisted Fork
But enjoy torturing people to death
Where's Nang
Kettler
Yeah
Picked up
Technology
Good morning
Social control
Actor
Nazi rally
Rally's
When did America
We talked
About that
Unnecessary
Patsy
Yeah
The Proto globalist
All just
One thing to agree on Hitler was bad
From
As a starting point for maybe that's the issue
Which human beings
Is we can't even agree
On how bad
Genocide in his chat room I'll tell you that right now
No the thing is what he's talking about is
Things like
With all these things mixed up
But with the Margaret Sanger and Planned Parenthood stuff
Like
Do you can find
And a picture of her
In front of the Klan rally
Permission
Men's Reproductive Rights
And she's like
There are racist women
Are they still need help they still need a health care
That is such
F******
Frazee
Misrepresentation of like you were saying through the clip
Yep
There is truth to the idea that Hitler got a lot of ideas from America
Yeah
But then to take it to
Ovens
Parenthood Margaret Sanger
That's
Disingenuously
Right that's that's
The propaganda leap
Alex Mae
Expect like look at the beginning of the episode
You went from
A conversation that should be had
Which should be taught
In school
The idea that Hitler didn't act in a vacuum
Right
No
The ideas existed
Certainly for thousands of years
Because there were many exoduses through country has really
Hold on
What about the people you know my grandpa was a man
Did you know that
I didn't know that you text people
Sure but like
HD
It's this fascinating weird
It's almost
I was going to try and related somehow to be
Uncanny valley
But that's not
But like there is this
This area where Alex
Cuz like
Eunos
Good point
And then makes it back
Right there
Well I meant it goes back to stuff that I keep saying and I might disagree with in other
Other contacts
There is the Opera
Tunity IC
Of course
Never has happened and never will
But like there's
The constant opportunity to be the hero
Like he could have at any point
Been like
IC
A problem
Yeah
Actually actually read the articles that he talks about
How could he
But those could have been like an actually good voice
It ain't been like
You could have shaped the
Skeptic
Conspiracy community
I know those are two different
He could have shaped a lot of the
Those people have
In a much more healthy
Much more reasonable way as opposed
To the
The race-baiting the bigotry the
Anti-liberal bashing
He does now
Doesn't make as much money and that should get
Thinking more specifically
Like Margaret Sanger
Went
Talk to the KKK women
Yeah not
DeMent words
But
But it is like
With the the conversation that was always had during so many different elect
Kansas like
Would you have a diplomatic meeting with
North Korea
With no restriction
And their whatever
Would you have a diplomatic meeting or f****** Fred Hampton
The it mean if you want to talk about Chicago
The
Patrons
Of Chicago should be Fred
Yeah and
Genius
Was
He went and talked to everybody
He went and talked to white supremacist
Fred Hampton
Black Panther leader
And you know what he talked about
He talked about s*** the same way that everybody would talk about s***
And the point is
That he would communicate with them in a way that they could understand.
Really important that you know the old adage of like we don't make
Peace with our friends
We make peace with our aunt
And yet at the same time
If you wanted to be a dick
You could pull up app
Picture of Fred Hampton talking to
Justin be like
But this guy's white supremacy
Totally know there's no win if you do that if people are
So obsessed with
Fighting a war
Regardless of who is again
Regardless of how many people died regardless of the lost on Earth
So how it's bought
It's going to be something that you use against
Totally
Which is why Kissinger should be killed again
Also they're appropriate analog
In this
What's January 20th
You talked to Louis Farrakhan
Conwright and the entire time it's mostly just trying
And score points
I've listened to most of the interview so spoiler alert
We don't go over it but most of the stuff that Alex ends up playing
Is the stuff that is like
Living life
I am Trump
Yeah you're he uses it as like a bolstering
Trump thing
That's not legitimate
Conversation with the
People who disagree with you first that's
Trying to use them as a prop
No
Define Louis Farrakhan
Like I'm not I'm not
These note David Icke
Anyway let's let's get onto this.
Good points
Louis Farrakhan does to absolutely espouses a lot of good self reliance
Slot of self-empowerment
Yeah exactly what I was saying about David Icke
Small for soft on that
But at the same time crazy
Uh-oh also
I8
You know I ate I was aware of it
And I've said this so many times
It is really hard to get away
Now
From the knowledge that
Just about everything these crazy people believe
Eventually boils down to hate the Jews
Whether or not that is their primary motivation it's somewhere in there don't even necessarily
Always know that
Important
I think that a lot of people
Particularly a lot of those folks were probably in that chat room probably just think it's like
Duh
Yeah of course
Evil
That's
So
David Icke is on the show and
Self-actualization
Beholden to the protocols of the Elders of Zion and has a lot of aunties
He is a guest on Alex Jones Show
Now think about the two stunts
Interviews that Alex is done
In the last
Gear of us cover
There's David Duke
And Louis Farrakhan right the two of them have in common
Super against the Jews
Interested
Interesting
I really wish the Unabomber
Wasilla
Cuz he would be an amazing
Who cares
Yuri amazing Gaston
Social media
Although you loves to use it
And brag about his numbers
Loves people in the middle of nowhere
On the lam Unabomber knew where the height his f****** guns I'll tell you that right now
Is living on the land
That's important
On the land
Cuz we're about to
Get to another interview
Does Joel skousen
Who's out on the
Michelle now
Not a fan of his name
Whatever is Mancow
The right Lord mandolin
Search Joel skousen comes on the
And
Ostensibly the interview is about
The Bundys
Because at this point
In January 20th
This is when they were
Taking over The Wildlife Refuge
There was only one that killed
Yeah there was that
Finnegan or something like that
Yeah yeah
Imagine if native
Takin Over
They would all have been dead
They would all of them
Or at least way more of them.
Like me to take deaf out of it no negotiation
We come back to over and over again is the idea of why you're being like
Minority baby being Criminal
Absolutely
You look at the difference
Greenhow the Bundy Ranch
Nothing
The standoff The Wildlife Preserve
How's that was
Treated versus
The people at the pipeline
The people at the Wildlife Preserve
Hangout Baron
So I can do whatever for like a week more than mad I don't even remember how long it lasted
No one at the pipeline had a guy that's why they got hoes
No just been killed maybe everybody should have guns
No I don't think so cuz
That
Is a fallacy
See if that helps
Because
With minorities
Escalation
Calm down
Be cool
Alright
You know the skin color crayon
You know how it's white skin color
Let's just drive
White skin on a
You're talking about ask
Scandal that happened in
Early 90s
I know it look
Almost no time I know that that was a terrible decision
Pain where in they were
Hugely races
Paul Joseph Watson
Fishing report about that
Can't imagine how you say the word interesting and have it makes aw
Swing by Joel skousen
Is on
And they're talking about the Bund
Yeah let's just move past my white face
Space idea
That is in the vein of Rodger Stone wanting to regulate Twitter
Apparently David Knight is now come out talking about regulating Facebook
Excellent good ideas and we should apply them to the tech industry as a whole and that weight no they didn't say that
No
Taking away the great betrayal by the BLM
And then stand down they would have the highground people say yeah they're not a bunch of crazy
Well they are crazy
What do you what is 1000
Is largely
Unionization
Regulating
Those are
It goes back to the same thing we see over and over again
I'm against this
Intellitime Gisela
Bobby Q
Yeah
But it's nonsense
And Archimedes
Incredibly difficult for us to have because
Like our position is
Yeah that makes sense
That makes sense we don't team sport
No and it's like it's like the farmers being able to get together and unionized 4shared
Interest makes total sense absolutely
Even the idea
Of
Driving regulation about what the government in terms of land rights
What's that
But it
They are
Like
Right and that's so frustrating
Cuz it's not a conversation you can have
It's the same thing where would like if Alex Jones were to listen to this
So much
You guys support Hillary and your dad
You're dumb liberals now
Did you listen to the show liberals
It is it worth
We're too slippery and nuanced
To fight back against
A concrete
Say that the idea of a
8/8
So that's one of the big things beds
That always
Gets to me
Is like
Regulation is bad
Until about
Regulation
Like it works in your favor
Good liberal
Snowflake
It's always
The demonization of progressive
Is
A million-fold
And that's mainly because
Every part of that demonization
Is abdicating what it is
Write like with antifa
You can't
Against antifa
Verigan's
Fascism
Write their name
The only way is to create a
Strawman
Or
And you can imply that their name is ill-advised in Australia the liberal party is
Is our conservative
Right
Exactly
But it's
It's so long as you don't know
What we believe
How what we will believe will affect you
And so on and so forth so long as you combine us with
The Communist from Soviet Russia
As long as it's
Sounds like it makes sense
You will believe
Anything
Damage
Totally
It finally does damage
You know real progressives have some good ideas
When they apply to anything other than when they apply to me
But also Intel
Like a Depression happen
Well alright really like the New Deal whenever they couldn't eat
Yeah
Kicked ass whenever people
To death
Amazing important
It's a good thing we learned it
You know we
We wrestle a little bit with
Hearing an argument we're kind of okay within that context but
Yeah
Did he have to say on this up
Episode and him and Alex get into having a conversation about selling weapons
Into Syria
And okay
What have you
These are back in the glory
And she basically is just selling arms
To whoever wants
And Joel skousen has a slightly different take on it interesting
And I actually
Maybe kind of agree with him
If I can make one
One caveat
Then I will at the end of this
They're getting old
Is in the USA
Friendship out of there
TomTom
Hillary would know what
Going on in the dark side of the dark side
George W bush
Didn't know it's dark side of government was doing
Minister
Politico's know about Darkside operation
So Joel skousen
When confronted with the idea that Hillary
He is selling weapons
Goes immediately to
Deep state
Come on man no of course not
She might know about that stuff
Now here's the caveat I'm going to make
It's dangerous for all of us if she knows about it you know who it's not dangerous for though
What's Blackwater
That's for the caveat I would make
Interesting point
Seeing that Erik Prince Blackwater have both
Organization and guy who runs organization
In terms of running weapons into countries where it's illegal to sell them
Cassidy's in slaughtering civilians
Absolutely it makes sense
Like
I have a clitoris is half an inch higher than you think
It's going to be you're just pushing a quarter quarter
Okay
You mispronounced
Urethra
Megology
I'd like a written apology to trust
What I'm what I'm hearing from that clip
If you take away the premise
Where is
Turnpike the government is selling
These missiles
Do all these go
If you just let that sit for a second
His idea that
Hillary wouldn't know about that
He's got to be protected from that drove the plausible deniability
Yeah that stuff
Definitely
I agree
I don't think that Regan necessarily knew everything that was going on in Iran
Contra
I don't
Noah's Reagan
New
At that point
Anything
Even if he had all his faculties
I don't I don't think that he would have been like
Signs of dementia in office
Oh do you mean he was f****** insane cuz that's what it sounds like
Right right
Of course of course there are some good play and stuff like that
Like a movie though
Like the idea of that part
Seem to be like I mean the CIA in in time
Right terms of trying to recruit
Not necessarily aware of all of those efforts there were machinations behind
Too busy
What who could blame him
He was a Playboy
That's a good question
Sins of our time
AR
The only question I could think of
Who is Maggie Simpson everybody does like also from that era type questions
I don't remember when I'm gone I have no idea
All before I was born
I love the fact that we're weird enough to pull out a Dallas reference
Which was 20 years before we were born
Yeah yeah but it isn't made its marks
And up much like save the cheerleader save the world that reference 20 years from now
I doubt it but like
Look
I don't know a little bit just so I can make my argument that I think with Joel skousen
Talkin about is Blackwater
Like those sorts of organizations
It seems like those would be the people who have access to high-grade munitions
Which is the entire point of their existence is they are not
Under Federal oversight
It's like money laundering
Joel skousen
Hillary wouldn't be involved in this
Who would
That's the next question a real journalist would ask
Alex
Just wants to go back to Hillary and Bill
If Hillary wasn't involved
How was Hillary involved with this
She was totally involved
Videos
Actual answer me
Hilarious that's all 33,000 emails have you seen this
Bellies like so close and then you go away
Socks
No
Pretty sure Bill Quinn
Skyward Sauk
Probably dead by now though it's been years
Not an addict
Anyway
This weekend of our time with Joel skousen
Cuz
Mostly about like
I don't like it
I like it it's automatic
Play sounds like scowl
You want to put an L in there and I don't think there is one I think it's scouser
Current flavor for me
Like he belongs in this category of Infowars guest
And man it sucks
Because I'm saying like some stuff that you're going to
Clown on me for
The listeners aren't going to like
I don't I
When Joel skousen is on the show I mostly to now
He's not really that bad
In terms of
Is Belize
You have a lot of like dumb geopolitical ideas and write like that
In terms of like
Like red flags
About Bracken has red flags all over it whenever he shows up I'm like I got to listen
Int always like
I realize this
This actually pisses me off
Yeah about my cell
Okay on our last episode we talked about Matt Bracken
Appearance
On the show
Sammy racks
And I talked about how
That is what
Media Matters should be talkin about more than
The
Linda sarsour
Course
And I realized when I went back and listen to it but I forgot to
Play a clip
I don't have the clip
Okay but I could go get it
And now I can't go
Cuz times up
I'll get it on the next episode
You can find episode
But I
That's all
No one's listening
Can listen to an Alex
Jones episode and motivated me to be like this is so much more bigoted
Linda sarsour
Yes was that Matt Bracken got into
F******
Who's it going hard
About
The overbreeding
And the idea that white people are going to be bred out
The argument that Liberals are mad and islamist
Should be mad because this guy went and ran a truck into people
When is
You just chill out we're going to out breed them
Boy
Not tasty
Not tasty as Narcan
So they're people like that like mad bracket
And then there were people like
Like David Icke where I'm like
I did go crazy
But arms distance
Yep Joel skousen
Like I think he is
Wrong
About a lot of stuff
Yeah but also I don't hate him he's a sort of a nebulous concept
Where is Lake Harriet
Harry dent
Or Peter Rhea
Rare terrible later Max Keiser is going to show up
I think I might like men
I understand where you coming from with this here's the problem
The bar is so low your you're in a world where
All you have to do to be a Centrist is just
The juice
Like that's that's your world or mine
You know me and all of the rest of us who don't listen to Alex Jones
Every single day over being Dan the Centrist
It's right you love to do
Not least of which because you
Love guns and want everybody to have them
I want everybody Centrist position that you can have
Kind of a situation where your perspective
True relative
Horrific mess of Alex Jones
Yeah that that that is definitely fair
Nobody's clowning on like their very eyes they dislike you it's just we live in different
There is no counting for like
The the fact that we've been doing this for now
A little over ten bucks
Going over this and most most
But most of the time we like
We go over these episodes
And I don't even include
The portions of other like Paul Joseph Watson being
Bulshit
And stuff like that
You guys were listening
80 Eudora
Realize
The vitriol that isn't included in the show
I am more than its own more than aware that
Sometimes
You are out to protect
So Joel skousen is okay but all that protected the show so I don't yell 414
You can take you with me
I guess my point in that is also prepper
Pretoria because
In a little bit we will get to Max Keiser
There's an interview with him
At the end of the show that I think is fascinate
It's mostly about him being in favor of Bitcoin
Alex being like we don't know
Right
Actually I'm not just when maxpoint started he doesn't pimp it at all
Just talks about how they cryptocurrencies are they just going to cells in terms of
Yeah I don't know why you don't trust Alex
He makes sense and at the same time
Cryptocurrency
Anytime soon
Paper
On paper it does exist
Does it does seem to work
I'm also not
I will change I will change over
More
Things that were convenient in my life
We're relevant
Right
Like I don't like
Amazon but I use it because
Amazon hate Apple
But I have a f****** iPhone
I don't use Amazon I don't use Uber any of those things like I
Hate Corporation
And I do have an iPhone and I shouldn't
But I can't
Like there's a part of me is you don't want a Samsung
I can't survive without a knife I don't want to f******
Zeus
MacBook Pro I've got an iPhone
Write all myself
Is there social media
Make a deal with it on some level
Personally I have not been happier
Since when I left Facebook and Twitter
I don't use my personal account really at all right I'm much happier than when I would look through people's posts tonight
Used to care about that and then I started going through lineups and I was like
Oh I no longer like I used to feel jealousy and I no longer feel jealous
I have no idea about, so
Is
A bizarre reaction to me saying that Joel skousen isn't that bad
And maybe he is
And I just haven't heard it and I just don't know it I'm going to give
But let's move on
He's
Statistical likelihood
He's a monster
It seems like most
Of
His
AR
About prepping
Yeah which I'm okay
Doomsday prepper
Yeah as long as you're not crazy I'm okay with it you should have water in
You should have water and you should have some sort of food supply like when I was growing up
We had a basement
And my parents had a bitter Foods
Supply down there until bottled water
Your family is crazy
But like for my family was more like about the idea that we lived in Missouri and there were tons
The tornadoes
And we might have to hang out in the basement for a week
Or something like that
Protomatter
No matter what
It's good to be prepared
Sculpture theoretically
Get weird whenever you're like
I'm going to build bomb
Would it become Central to your identity
That's when it be
It's like
View from the lifestyle that
You would otherwise be living
Right like we need to spend all your money on it all your time
Make your family do stuff they're uncomfortable with
At the same time it's like a show
Is mostly about like
Bad marriage
That's what it's mostly about
Overly motivated husband
It's just another like
Super weird dad
Kind of behavior
The guy who super into cars
Is only slightly less insane than the guy who's super into Doom
Like
There's not
I know there is I mean being able to fix
Car is great
And being able to have
Reply
With jet goes bad
It's all healthy impulses gone
Maybe that's what the whole show is generally about
That's probably what it is
So let's get to this next clip because Max Keiser doesn't show up for a little bit
Healthy impulsive gone bad
Vodka
So in his nightclub Alex Jones Lament
But he didn't stop Obama
That f****** guy
You should be
That one
I'm just a gullible idiot I'll be honest with you I wanted to see a black guy
Not true
Oh
I just wasn't against human.
That doesn't track either
Evil
That like
Rambling
Brain
Trail
Is so racist
I am
I have been you know dyed-in-the-wool
That my entire life
Liberal
Yeah that's
Hold that whole premise of you grow up in
To become more conservative I don't feel that at all
You and I you and I were raised from
I'm very different
Resume doesn't matter
Because right did come from like
Dickweed weird conservative
I called
Family
Came from
Religious but also liberal
Or not liberal
Christian that
Christ would have enjoyed
I think that my dad would like you saying that I hope you listen to this episode
Let me talk to David Icke
That to me
II
Always have had a diverse set of four
And I've always
Kept
People in my life even that I disagree
When it became
Fighting a
Like that
Not going to hang out with you anymore
Destructive
B'Elanna
Put all the Liberals
Around the time that Obama
Got elected
Not a one of them
To a man
Or one
Was like
I want to see a black guy
They might subconsciously thought
You know there's a part of me that wants to disagree
Because it was never a selling point
Outside of
This is not something that I what you would say and I think it is a reasonable selling
In terms of race
Yeah just
Video
Children
Seeing a black
Black children seeing
Someone who can
Conforms to
Their perception of self opens up
A wide window of
Oh I guess this is
Something that has never been
A possibility for me and now it is
That's meaningful psychologically
That's not what Alex is talking about did I ever heard any sort of like
Let's get it like in there
Where is Alex's talking about it
In terms of
Right
Divide and conquer race-baiting
Yeah
That is what he is saying that if you voted for Obama what you are voting for is pacifying black p
Which
Is not a good position
On some level that is
Is there any saying like
What am I going
How old is Barack Obama
Enough
Like that just
Struggle in his brain of like
He doesn't know what to
To do
Look at the beginning of this episode
Right when he calls for Paul Ryan impeachment
Right
No cuz your craziness
Is all focused on
But Alex is all over the
It's like he's trying to make Penance in some way in the
For being like
Not against Obama enough
Look I got duped
I got jumped
But if you don't actually believe
Fair enough
Then I like
That is very fascinating headspace
Is to get into that you can't really process
If you're not that
Wyatt like I watched all of that one f****** Netflix or like mine hunter whatever it is
I probably know I watch all of that
It is like
The reason that it's so fascinating is because
The 99% of us
Burp
84% of us who aren't Psychopaths
It's passing it
Like how do you get into that headspace
What is it like if you're that person
What is it like if you don't
Really believe in any
Burp
Onomatopoeia
I mean I think that's a fascination with
True Crime shows
2 autos
Likewise Auto Sicklerville it is also the
What reality
TV is
But unfortunately it's
Selfridge
Enforcing because those reality shows are like we're watching
People be
Artificial sociopath
They're getting paid a bunch of money to
Like that
They're not getting paid a bunch of money
Like not even show up at a bar for a private
Michelle and then end up getting 35 Grand
The show up at a bar
Yeah that's amazing
You know what's crazy
Strawberry bar
Let the true story
What are you talkin about what are you talkin about
I was on a
You'd have to get married to someone you just met
Why did you sign up
The more interesting story
I didn't sign up for
I was recruited
Wow I was on the OKCupid
Sure
And so all the sudden
I started talking to this one girl
Lady woman
Turns out
Reality show recruiter Hellyeah
We were having to make a clear from the first message
Horse knots subterfuge
Edition video and all this
That was at a point in my life where I was like
Peanut
Sure I get that impulse I get that in plain to me that the reason that I was not cast was because
Cuz I was a comedian and they thought I would f*** with that
And I was like
You
Nailed it
There is no way I would have taken this seriously and I would have f***** with you guys the whole time
Like the good news is that show didn't work
So
Even if you had signed up I would be embarrassed
Hilaire
There be embarrassing in hindsight
Funniest joke
Fully
I'm into a I want it
I want to do that
No chance I got an email out of the blue from some producers
That they were trying to do a lie
Okay we're going to do a new version of the guy code and girl code
Fred weather
Like real real cool like what
Let's do a video audition so I got like a
Skype going
My
Laptop computer I just looked
Brainiac ship videos not good
Am I
Sorry yeah it's what I got
Your rights and so they were asked me like
What pisses you off about women
A Mike
I don't like the question
You
This is not going to catch food I look like a crazy person and I am not playing ball
No good
What there a couple people on there like Jon gabrus is amazing
Yeah he's f****** hilarious not that guy
Not that guy
I do remember who else is on there you don't need to know Grace are people who are on those
Shows who are actually really talented if not their fault sucks
This person is like
He was trying to get their own version of that right
You talkin to me why did you send me an email out of the blue
I'm not
F****** can find a picture of me you know what I look like what I look like
Hundreds of hours of me talking into a microphone
Know if you catch me for your reality show
Just so you know when people Google
Ships going to get wild
Might have been before we started
This podcast
Anymore
Accidents down
But be that as it may
Has been
Wonderful glass
Downtown memories
I got nine forgot about it this is our version of Alex
That's all
You're almost done a dumb marriage reality show that's exactly what it is except for again
Where reality where were you
I had the opportunity to know
They asked me to do it
F****** stupid bad idea
Frankly maybe if I had lied about being a comic I would have been on Married at First Sight
And I would be the biggest, can the world had a better webcam and I had been like
Let me roll with the questions as opposed to being myself
Maybe I would have made $1,000 and then the show never would have dared you just explain why we're never going to be
Successful
Maybe if we hadn't been ourselves
That's why we're here
Exactly so in this next clip Alex Jones talks a bit
More about
The Nation of Islam
But because he went and visited
Terracon
And he says something feel like
Disagree
Theory
Or perhaps Pasha
Hypothesis
If
Farrakhan
Had
Flattered
How would that affect
He did
Oh s***
I think it's in this next
New World Order
Richmond
So
Let's unpack that
Alright
Let's unpack.
The it takes
So little
Alex
Well but that that like
Version of things is it
Suppose that with
My support of David Icke
That I was talking about earlier
I really wish you wouldn't call it
Support of David
I only did what I did for
I would respect I drop spot for David I stopped just short of
Support
David Icke is not
Legitimately anti-semite
He is beholding to anti-semitic ideas
And
Metaphorically
Spits out
Some red
He's a
Dispenser
Yes but he is not someone who is like the Jews are evil
Paragon
Right in the Nation of Islam
I have had that tradition
Pretty hardcore
Yeah
Answer the difference here where Alex is like who cares if they're anti-Semitic
Best Buy
That's very bad
Where is for me when I say
Look
David I can you believe the protocols of the Elders of Zion and what have you when I say
That it's bless
Who cares about that it's more
Let's look at it
In contact if he actually was coming out and being like fuk these Jews
Centerview
Then there would be no soft
Where is Alex
Yeah they like me
You hear that clip
It's totally clear what happened
Right
They had people
Good up
Infowars on their browsers
That's called f****** research
Compromising
You'll wind up tricking people compromising somebody through flattery
That's the easiest trick
Is like oh no excuse me
Over there you're breaking all the big news
Alex would never demand like what did you want
I saw that video last week you were amazing
Farrakhan and these guys in Alex Jones
These clickbait playing him like a fiddle
Yeah it's very clear to me that there was
At least well as we
Play f****** establish
It's not hard
And that
The point but it does take a little bit of forethought and it is impressive to me
Okay compressor to me that they thought to do that
ATM course
It's clear
It's not even brilliant it's just
If you do
A modicum of research
On somebody
And you actually attempt to influence
You can probably see
And that is the story of everybody's been on Alex Jones Show if you do just the slightest
Look
You could go on to Alex Jones Show
Using all of your information
I might call him tomorrow
Have you
The self-control
Do so
Alex Jones a real fan of knowledge
Assuming he doesn't already know we exist
If he has that free knowledge then it'll be impossible
But it was like
Alex
Look you're the best
You're spitting the at this truth
But no one is putting out there
It's Towing
It's B
Just spitting the truth
No one else is putting out there
Cuz you're like I don't have honesty correct
You're the best bra
Bro
You're the s***
I love you
Alright your celebre all this you got the truth
I believe you appreciate it
Excellent
He asked about you can we get a plug-in
Linda's podcast called knowledge
Despite we just talk about you it's like Infowars but
We just talked about how
How great you are
Is the best
Maybe that would work
Is flattery
If if if he came here
That fought died
There's nowhere for that
I like to think about how we could co-opt him if he came to Chicago Illinois
Found my
Bedroom
Barking at him oh you wouldn't be here
Ruby one-on-one
Good place
You're you're not wrong
That is a very smart
Look
Millions of
Totally
We got to find rap
Anyway
Realized
Mike Rappaport great
But I've realized this
Interesting things
We haven't covered RAV4 analog
That's cuz his reports have been born
Is every other Thursday though still hosting the 4th hour
And it would have realized is he's like
Kind of a psychiatrist
Recycology
Just for Infowars
Right
Cuz he is so much of a
Home present
Cuz he does these neuro-linguistic programming type
Trixie the way he speaks
With like these a lilting tone
He doesn't do that
That was parody
But at the same time he does those like
He's very
Trained
And how he uses
The tones of his voice than that the gate
If his speech
And to the point where even if you wanted to control
You probably couldn't probably not
Yeah and it's so calm
Yeah and that's
Bet
Unlike anything
And so like
Being boring you're still in
Angry Bird
Prepared
Jon rappoport just like four times
Wrapworks been on I've wanted to cover
What he's done but
You know I love him
Iznogoud
And then eat
Part that's interesting ism
Long enough
I've known I would have gotten
The month of all of the
But basically what's happened
Is he shows up for the fourth hour and councils Alex
For the first 10 minutes he counseled that like Alex is in a bad mood and you like John
What about this
Well you got it
I think about you
Go to think about the Angles and you know like
Alex down and then the next 45 minutes is his own report
I would made it
Crystal clear to me
Will last Thursday
I was when Owens
Troyer host
When was
Freaking out at the end
The shout
But he couldn't he couldn't figure out where to put his bearings
He had no idea what was going on
And he was like
These JFK reports came out and turns out Hitler still alive and everyone clowned on that and that was
Like a him
What do I do
And the whole time
You have
Stoic
Jon rappoport
Just being like
You're 27
You probably have a
Sports Medicine
Calm down
The globalist
Are doing what they do
And he just counseled him through like 15 minutes
It was weird
Basically
Is this all John right before it's idea
No because are we sure he didn't
Exist in a meaningful way in 2015 or even where we are now in 20
Keep showing up just to talk about how like
Like AIDS isn't real and vaccines are bad cuz he has that medical journalism
In hard quote
Background
Essentially on Thursdays
Every other Thursday
Someone who will talk the host down it's f****** crazy
I'm going
Is Q I'm going to keep a better track of that because
It it sounds
Blame
For me to just
Sell this whole cloth and be like this is what they do
It's
Counseling
It's absolutely
Because John revworks gifted with his language and he knows how we speak
It's
Basically like
Cognitive behavioral therapy but with
Abrasive
Again it's amazing
How certain are we
That John Rappaport isn't influencing all of these
People to do what it is he wants
I have no evidence
The Jon rappoport has ever spoken to Larry nickel
You got to know
Outside
Two-player boy
Look I don't know that he knows him I don't know that I don't think
Look
100% don't think that he's a part of the 45
Alright
And I also
This is
I don't really think that I've ever heard Jon rappoport say all that much about Trump
Interesting
He's really into Medical
Yeah like little
Yeah but I don't I mean I know he is pro Trump
Is he here
But I don't think I've ever heard him say that much
I don't think he cares that much
He's afraid of
Vaccine
Bush's he's afraid of college campus bush
Define a1personnel
How do you spoken to
It's General stubblebine
Anyway
Gets into
Siri about liberals that I
Don't agree with
I think I'll probably agree with it
Romboy
Obama
Congress time
Why
Not bad Obama.
Neocon Republican Obama
Democrat this morning
So I don't know who this prominent Democrat is but also things
The idea that
Like this prominent Democrat was like yours is mad
Bad
Yeah that's
I mean I would say all literally everything
But like all of Infowars advertise
Weather like
Buy this shirt it'll piss off Democrats
Like
You're not pissing them off
Why are you mad
First of all
Interaction didn't happen but hypothetically mad at this person being like
You know you're pissed off you pissed off isn't that fun right
I had strategy entire life and I know we get back to this stupid thing where it doesn't matter
Big picture
Does
It really does
At the Time Capsule is done
Well that's possible never going to make
Effective
A big picture yes I agree as a matter of record it matters
When you
Fascinating because that is tied
Right into a very small
Where any says
Neocon Tsar route-running Obama in your life
You might think
Right about that
Why are you saying that
Because like
Okay here's why
Alex is wrong
That's why
Like what you just
Express straight there is literally
Why Alex
Cuz Rock
We talked about
We I mean I talked about a lot because
I studied logic extension
In college
Ain't the reason you have to be Robert there's four he'll buy you a Coke burp
Look
Yes the important thing about logic
Nick is truth Preserve
The only thing that logic
Is opposed to
Sentential logic and predicate logic
Truth cannot leave
The falsity
That is where there's a problem
If you start from
True premises
And lead to a false conclusion
That's a problem
If you start
From a false premise
And lead to
A false conclusion
Newport
And the false promise to truth
Conclusion
It's all fun
Only instance where things are actually a real
AR
True premises
False conclusion
If that's what Alex does all the
We've talked about it probably three times already on this podcast
What this episode I mean when you talk about like
Your Obama is involved with neoconservatism that is a problem
As it relates to also neoliberals
Navigate to it is a big problem
Truth there
And then what it come
Comes down to
It is like
Neener neener stuff just trying to like
Right it's a game he was trying to f*** right quick that's a full scan
Conclusion they are coming to
That's that's where logic
Play
We got a big red flag on
That's what that's where
I mean the reason I started this podcast wasn't that
It keeps me going through it
Either
So much
Trivet is that
Yeah there's so much like
Small bit of reality
You're f****** up this
Because I am
I'm offended by the idea that there are crimes against children
Ended by the idea that
Hollywood has this casting-couch system
Alex has been complaining about for the last month cuz
That's terrible
He's right
The truth
As a premise
Many leads to the drinking blood that's a Cassidy
He's right
About
Tarnov dumbass things
Dumbass
Looks like out of
Yeah but he's right about a ton of kernels of definitely
He's like of manufacture
It's just like
Truth becomes
Inspection
It's so crazy but also
Sometimes sometimes
And sometimes fix
Become
I mean he has been right about a few things
I mean he's right about
Like Osama bin Laden
2000-2001 was going to attack
He was right about that
Know for sure
It's the same time
We shouldn't take that away from like
Him being right
Right you know like
You look in the same way that if you had called that
I would give you credit
But I would also say but I called for it and then stipulate
Not that hard to figure that
But he's also right about civil asset
Forfeiture he's right about marijuana laws drug laws in general
They're so like
There's software he's like true to true
It's the problem is when he's treated
90%
90% is that amount of it is true to false and more of it it's
Just falsified
60% is false
False
No cuz even if you go into that
It's
True that the Las Vegas shooting happen
And then
Okay and then benchmarks
Whether or not
Starting
Truth
Is that King
How else are you going to construct a Target
Write the Las Vegas shooting happened it was a false flag
Route
Endive
I don't know Alex is f******
It's eight he's disqualified
From having any reasonable
Sure it is fun for me to be like
Unknown
Morales Morales
Illustrative
You did that to me the other day I was just laughing out
Of whatever it is he does get something that is relatively obscure
Correct
Where in
Neocon running Obama
That is something that is not
A well-publicized version of
Obama's president
I think I think it's
It's in the middle
Like I think it's not totally publicized
It's not obscure either though
I think that's in the middle I think that's a conversation point he's out there
Question for the two of us
Especially because we are
To go out and Family Feud the General Public
Brewers
Mark Dice
Neoconservative
Teasing video
Pitbull
H-E-B on drudge yeah
Probably do that
No it's not our style
Not let's just make it
Can take propaganda video
Alright
Dan let's talk about this
Interested in giving me okon's advice about how they should run thing
Exam problem
Alright well look we got a couple more
Okay
We got a couple more Clips in
Is 8 hour long after
I'm so in his ex-wife
Alex has another theory
About to laugh
But liberal
Write shockingly
I disagree with it again drinking blood
About what
And what they're going to be
You people are front-and-center
But you know your parents
Avant-garde
Oh my gosh I love you
So what do you think about
What what
What was he saying
Not sure
Honestly not sure
If you want me to give you a recap
Are we
As a card-carrying
Is he saying that
We don't want our women to wear pants
No you're not supposed to
If so the men aren't supposed to wear pants
Sort of in terms of like colloquialism
Right I want to do that
Cuz the women
Not where I don't understand how that would work
Well I mean because they specially since
It is
Conservatives of his ilk who kept women from wearing pants
For so long
So okay
So what now
Now also we were
Ray's cancer
But no no
Your parents are trying to make
Conservative
Made you go to church
Okay so he's talking specifically to meet your dump butthurt liberal
Write your cut-out in wall McLovin
A liberal
It's kind of sex
Right
From me
KakaoTalk Christendom
I don't disagree that is kind of hot
Strongly don't like this.
Like nothing makes me want to f*** more then
Whatever it was he was talking
What do you talkin about talking about
I don't think one exist
But
Again it's that same
Hurdle was something that leads to
Fake thing
There are definitely
Liberals
Who are liberal because their reaction
Sing to their conservative
Just because you had conservative parents
Do you have people who are the David Brock David Horowitz types
Grew up in confining
Political bubbles
That in their adult life
There are examples like that that's what he's talking about
Yeah it's okay to paint
It's it's just
This big narrative that he has
About liberal
Love
Radically
Because it's
Cocking out white people
If this
We should get rid of
The West
Like anytime you
Like I'm at I'm at a point now where I feel like every time he says
Is the West like you should have a voice-over come on
White and then just move on
ORS
Just stay White
No that's what you mean
But mail and Christian also
A true
AAA it is
It is subordination of the other
Is what he's talkin
It ain't even if you go back to any of the time when
If we don't even unpack makeamericagreatagain or anything like that
I didn't read
Interesting article other day
Stickers in Politico entirely sure
But they did a study of
Me too
Igo case-by-case
Yeah but
The article was about
The perceptions of when America was
Was great
Everybody
Just was talking about when they were younger
It is just Halcyon Days it's just the idea the image of the past
When things were simpler cuz your memory destroys all of the horrific things that you lives earlier
Deify the things go
Are an overrated band and that's where I get
Murdered
But also a lot of this could be dealt with evolve you would read
Some of the Lesser works of HP Lovecraft
That is
A true fact that is stated
All the time HP lovecraft's most known for
Call of Cthulhu
Maybe the case of Charles Dexter Ward the throat of gradebook
Look up his regular co-host Cthulhu
I I think
HP Lovecraft
Is one of the most
Problematically racist
But also great authors
I either made
Absent
Do something
About the human condition in about Terror and have fear works that most authors
Don't get
And I don't like horror
I don't like her at all
But I love
The dynamic of his writing
The fact that piece of f****** racist
Yeah his time
And if you look at him throughout his career he softened
In terms of
Talk about mongoloid
Booksy
It's named the n word
Like they're getting great
He gets older
That's not a great name
It's not
But I only bring that up syncope
I take the piss out of him as much as I love him
Looking for
Recognize he sucks
I understand
His lesser work
One of them
Is the dream-quest of unknown kadath
And no one likes that.
Just from a title standpoint
Could have had a couple of
I love it I think it's perfect
It's my favorite book of his I always have been more of a fan of the
The dream cycle that he did more than the the
Sulu cycle
Okay I always was more of a fan of
The dream worlds that he described
Because
If you read his letters
They are
Most of his work comes
From
Legit night
Right I like trying to deal with visions that he had like prophetic Visions or anything like that
But then what
From night terrors
But one of the things that's
Really fascinating
Is the dream-quest of unknown kadath is about this guy named Randolph Carter
Who's trying
How to get to the dream city where the city of Cudahy
Where the gods play
Easley's gold people
And it's perfect
And he wants to get there
At this whole thing where it's like you can't go there
You can't go there the Gods
The gods play there and it's forbidden for man to go there
Goes through this whole thing
Nonsense there's a little bit of Wizard of Oz aspect
Alliances with various things
Spoiler alert is
He was dreaming of Providence
He grew up in Providence Rhode Island
And he was dreaming of his childhood home
What did he has vision of
Kadance was
Spray
Created this false Vision in his head
Of what
The dream city where the godswood play is
And it is just
What he had as a child
Hold on one second
Right
Alex Jones
In a small town named
Prosperity
Nobody might have been in
Well then nevermind
I returned
If you was a little Truth and Consequences New Mexico
F****** stupid ass or could have gone to pick on it
Arkansas
But like
Is what people fall into
The Human Condition that HP Lovecraft nails
Which is a
Again
To get through it
It's not terrible trait unreadable book
Cats of Saturn do battle of the cats of ulthar and it's great
Now
Abuela
And the night.
Come in
General of the night God's back off
They have no
They don't have they don't have faces but they loved
Content
Night-gaunts love to tickle
Anyway
It's got a very different
Growing up
Tickling is terrifying
The thing is like
This is
Like
What is being
Triggered
Bye
These ideas of making America great again in harkening back to
Nostalgia
It is something that is so ingrained
In each of us
Individually
To come up with our own positive Association
Where is the reality is not necessarily apposite
The objective reality of
Going backward
Is not good
But each of us has a boner for that
Because of the Simplicity and the Wonder
Of us when we were children
Back of that
And and just that you lack of awareness
If everybody read science fiction
We're being a better place cuz it's the dreams of men
William
Qualified tree
Because you'd have these ideas that are proposed to you
And you deal with
Preaching
Acquire
But like
Most people would have more advantageous
Ideas in their head if they would just
Not succumb
The easy tree
If the classic rock
Conundrum
There is no such thing as classic rock
It's just
The
From a certain area
Are certain
Panera that radio stations
Can park exactly
I thought I would
Conundrum
I was like
Do to rocks
I was like why did Rikishi
She hit him.
Clear
Also
What is he cooking
Stir fry stir fry
So good
Everytime you believe all the vegetables
Are cooked
Still crispy
Tomato
Incredible
Time I don't know
I've never been on Chopped but I bet the Rockwood
Undoubtedly
One more Clips Jordans
A1 Market
Has been a lot of
This is been so much fun
A delight
Anytime I get to
Expound on Lovecraft iron I'm having a great time
Automatch
Billy maybe should be doing a podcast about HP Lovecraft
I have night terrors
I don't
I do
Yeah they're not great
Meijer
My buddy Nick my buddy Nick has night terrors like I don't know if he has reason
Ladybug
Back when we used to live together he would have night terrors in like wake up
Screaming in the middle of
Overnight
I've never had that Alice or anything like that
Like that
Like legitimately he would
Scream yeah
And I feel bad cuz he listens to the show
He knows
Price on the streets
I don't I don't know what that experience is like I've also never had a wet
Dream either
I've never had a wet dream so I don't know I don't know what those things are like but I've had a lucid dream
I've had sleep paralysis we're sure where I've been awake
Never had a lucid dream every time I fall asleep I am at the unwilling mercy of my own brand
But if you ever had dreams where you're like
More conscious
Within them
No I've lived
I've lived an entire lifetime
Multiple
Times where it's like
You you wake up in your life I do not have a wife
What the fuk just happened
But other than that
No lucid dreaming
Why are you judging me as though I'm a lesser person right I'm not I just don't know what to do with this information
Lakers even if people don't like the idea of like straight up
Total lucid dreams trolling everything and
Even most people still have dreams where there
Moorcock
The fact that
Number two
Control over it
Never going along with it
So every time you have a dream it's
Just like a pictograph
Just like the movie playing in front of your eyes
I don't remember most of my dreams
But
You just don't remember them
It's
I just have no recollection
It's a muscle you can work on
Fossil
To be all a dream
I'm in because I'll be in a simulation house looking for would that be
How sad would it be
This is a simulation of this is how we spend our time
We speak English talking about Alex Jones
Drinking vodka and talking about Alex Jones
It's how we choose.
It is an unreasonable
Simulate
I know I read Nick Bostrom
Alright yeah absolutely
Mathematically does not work out the filter real world
Why wouldn't we we talkin about Alex Jones
I got nothing better to do well
I did buy a sway
Do you see what those people do none of them talk about Alex Jones at All-Star podcast
Oh my God whatever happens is when the next
Sims game comes out and they're like
Do you want your character to start a podcast
Do you want your do you or do you not think you're saying believes in the
The protocol
That's going to be a brat
Branching decision developer
Sim Larry Nichols do you get to live
Larry Nichols
Nickels with telling the truth about it
Dude
That's a bummer
What
Not above
But Dad I've got a lot of information
I can't give out on the air
One more click
That Max Keiser
Comes on
Another guy
Aimbooster
Music I was Max going
Most of the episode where halfway think he's the guy who wrote that book about
Women
No but I was Malcolm ellerman
Max Keiser
Most of his appearance is just about Bitcoin being a
Decent
Cryptocurrency
Great idea not Max
Alex Jones
You do not like the Federal Reserve you hate
Fiat currency
See all that stuff
Bitcoins work
But
They get into guns
A little bit doesn't make sense why would you do that
Wow
Max Keiser has
The decent argument
And this is Mike down clip cuz
But also only because
It's so like Alex Jones being
And Max Keiser being
Pretty reasonable
And I want to hear I want the audience to be able to hear the
The times that Max
Tries to Rabbit thing
And Alex Cuts him off it moves very fast
Alright so here's that Mike down
In the news?
I know you found the gun issue obviously
I am always looking at this issue myself
An infant
What will happen I haven't really thought through this
Yeah what would be the situation if
Gun owners
Required to buy insurance
The girl with that gun Sony buy a gun
You need to buy insurance to go take on
Similar to the way when you
Any car insurance
So
By accident
The power to destroy
Obamacare.
Next
Aurorae or insurance
It's a it's a way to
50 spread
Oh come on
Child support
We like the cake that the folks believe the government is coming down in the air
Okay
Admitting
Play register they confiscate
Okay but after it
But it's okay
In the interest of those before
McDonald's
So
Especially on today of all days
Gentlemen all the information isn't out yet as we record this but
Someone went into a church
Kill 27 people
Wait what
He was 27 that's the last report I saw
The number might change rabbits
That's what I saw
On
Parking
On a day like that I mean I know we're going back into
The past but it's important
The principal
Versus the reality
And
What makes
Kaiser is presenting
Is a reasonable Middle Ground
Not a bad idea
It's a reasonable Middle Ground
He's even presenting it as
Look
People are
Pushing
Towards this
Wouldn't it be in people who are
Strong gun
Advocate
Best interest
Live protest
To their ability to have guns
Insurance would make reasonable for the idea behind it is
Schooner or later
Will be enough
So like if your if your argument is or or
Like when when he's describing Obama
The drumbeat of
When will enough be enough
We all feel the
His point is
Sooner or later it hatched
To be there will be enough is enough
And none of us want to come to the point where it's at
Draconian just want to come to the point where there's a fascist State taken gun
Right in the wall liberals as we are would be uncomfortable with that
3 scariest you don't want you don't federal government of any kind
Doing something along those
Or state
Especially not doing something like that
In the same way that we
Support all of the amendments
We support the second
Unfortunate
God's will
But so his
Hint ideas make
Way too much
His idea is
Gun owners
You don't want your guns taken away
So rather than wait until they try and take them away
And then have a fantastic shootout
When none of us want
None of us want that
Maybe instead be like
Okay if you buy gun
You also have to buy gun in
And if any gun
Is used to hurt somebody
That money
Well let's give
Let's go
Let's give a f****** real world example
Cuz I have
Set a couple times on this episode that I bought a swing
I bought a phone
I bought a Nintendo switch
Doing so
I had to
The trade-in
I didn't have to
But I traded in my
Wii U
Because I was like I want
Some store credit in order
In order to
Appropriate
Because otherwise it would be a crazy
Too much
And so I went
To the store
And they said
Cool
They looked at the Wii U they checked it out
Maitre played well I wasn't
For an ID
They ran the ID and I like
Your ideas
Your IDs expired
You can't trade in a video game system
For another video game system
I probably could have bought a gun
Absolute I probably could have
Edit gun show
Or something like that without Eid
Look in the same way I can still get into bars with an expired ID
Absolutely
Exactly what point I'm trying to make with
But like
Maybe when trading in a video game system laws are more stringent
Buying murder weapon laws
Probably something going on
Yeah I had to go and
Really work out a plan
I had to go get on a goddamn
We had to get on the bus
That we weren't sure was coming because
Is Broadway
Together figuring out
How it is you're going to get a f****** tendo switch hundred dollars less than a car
Weller time it is 8 it was a situation where Jordan was the best friend of the world and he came through for me
Maybe cuz he has a
Current idea mine is expired in that
Do you know what they say about George
His ideas always
These pot shop
GameStop
Follow
And also
Sure
Rest in peace Lou dog
Nope don't care
Look I just thought about Lou.
Rest in peace logo
The
The thing that I keep coming back to
2 is is this idea that
I don't care
I mean I was frustrated in the moment
But I get it
Yeah I get why you have to have
Regulations
In place of like
Someone traded in
Piece of technology it's like a lap
Top or something like that
This point
Back in the day was just a piece of plastic
Nintendo
But now
Now these things are like
Multiple hundred dollars
Worth
2 of
It was frustrating
Again
And the idea of it
Lobby Congress
Or that I would be like
F*** you
Video game
Trade-in right
Are Paramount
Right
And granted no one dies
Is because of this
This example that I'm using but
Look at
It's so
It's so silly to
To me and then
The other piece of 1 take away 4
Is that Alex
Insurances attack
That is
No but that's
Again just
Him not under the
Burnout
Oh no
No I'm going to end up in a garbage bag
I bet
Me and me cross-dressing and ending up in a garbage bag
So it's just him
Misrepresenting
The Supreme Court's decision about a bomb
It's not about
Obamacare
It's about the
Penalty
It's about the penalty for not
Signing up
Supreme Court did decide
That it is
Yeah
MS
That makes sense
Yeah it is
So the argument
That conservatives always make
Is
You can't
Legislate
Morales
Which
Is
In a very very simple
Mystic way
A truth
And at the same time
The dumbest
F****** thing that you could possibly say and if you say it
Shut the fuk up forever
Because
The same way that you and I are that you tried
How to trade in a video game
Bright
Now that law
Is not
Really going to affect
The ton of people
If you have a legitimate ID
Even if you stole that f****** system it's going to only make
Get traceable that this
Person stole the
Exact
Woody was not going to
And who the f*** is going to follow up on it
Unless somebody says my video games
List all right like all of legislating morality
Increasing
Two or three steps away from it every video game system
Has a tracking number on it and everything will video game system that you have
Can be traced
Like this
Why they have serial numbers on them
Did they
Can you buy them
If you buy them used they scan it.
I mean it's not like
Oh my God
Big Brother they know but I have this
If the records need to be pulled up
They can find out that I own a switch
They can if need be
And your phone stolen there's loads
It's not always
Evil right there are things that are
Simplest
The second best way of describing why
You can't let
Legislate morality
Stupid
Is
The
I can't remember which
Halo lore
Bridge or whatever
But they just
There was a
Area where hundreds of people committed suicide every
And all they did
With a put-up
And all the sudden the suicide rate dropped
Sofas
Because
That is not
Legislating morality or anything like that
But for a lot of
People if you just make something
Annoying to Logistics
They won't do it
You want to jump off that bridge
But you don't want to be seen
Seen climbing over the expanse
Of human psychology that is just like
That seems like a lot
Sure
That's really all it is really all
Taxes wind up being like you want and like we all want Rose we want all of this s*** but there's
There's a certain point of like
Like the soda tax in Chicago I think it was a good idea
And I think it should have worked
Find people b**** 2050
I know I agree
I'm right there with you
Distributor
It was going to end
The Dynamics of it in terms of wholesale are
Really problematic
Do the consumer I don't think it's that bad
Cuz like whatever I would buy soda
I do think that it's f***** up that
Applied to Stelzer
That's locked
Time like
That's not like
We were always like when it comes down to like wholesalers and
But in terms of
The consumer pain
A couple cents more
Per our Ascent more in Oz
Sugary beverages
I don't like
I don't think that's
Legislating morality
I think that does
Coming to like
And I want to be I don't want to eat this dick
Because like
I drink soda Nitro
Drink beer
And what have you
You fret
If you charge
Me more for it
Because of the burden
That we all
Collectively
Add in
The healthful
Yeah that makes
Makes sense
I accept
That we pay how much more for cigarettes
Then
People in Missouri
I'd like Emily dollars
Yeah
At least twice as much as you know what
I'm f******
Fine with that
And it makes
Sense
I hope all that money goes to the right places
Conversation
Look
If you are going to make decisions
That burden everybody else
More
You should
Of course pay more
To burden
Other people
In order to lighten that burden for other people
Polite
Houses are politeness
And now the flip side of that is
I ate you see this out of like European Cup
He's a lot like people
With the perspective of like I know that
My in my taxes are higher
Because
More of it goes towards
Protecting people who
You need help and I don't care
Right
That's that's right where I live
I don't really give a she
Look if if I have to pay more
I'm not saying that is like I'm
I'm a good person
It just seems like how a society should operate
Think of it
Really really simply
Like the most simple form of that
We live in Chicago
Imagine you paid 10% more of your income into
And you never saw another home
Well I know cuz that that makes
Seem like the Imp
This is never seeing homeless
Events
But that
Is my point
Robert Wright if your motivation is cute but your motivation
Strongly disagree
We can get into ethical arguments about
Determination
Anytime you want
Is the least
Watched show on TV
Put put the point being if that's
If that's the motivation that you really have which it seems like for a lot of people who are anti
It's always about
Well it's not
Going towards what
I wanted to go.
If if you are soaked
Craven and so miserable
That all you really want is like
I'm mad that I have to walk by 30
F****** homeless
People everyday
Fine
Pay 10% more in tax
And you'll never have
To do that again
Version
Is bad like what are you talkin about
About when you started this allegory or this or the thought experiment I would have gone with is
10% more in taxes
And then everyone gets a good at
Education
That's what I would have gone with
You know what remains
Fink
How many people bitching about property
Even though they ain't even though they know it goes towards School
Like how insane is that
Yeah
You know that this goes towards only helping
Your own children neighborhood the children of others in your still like I don't want to
Percent in the Robert seriously no one complains about the lottery
Yeah no good
They only complain about the people who were Tom enough
Famously described as a
Facts on the dumb
And that's the only
Don't ask me
I'm not a good person
In this regard
Respond way out of
But
The point I wanted to make about this tax
Supreme Court
Is that
Penalty
For not signing up for Obamacare
Is covered under the
Yeah and it's
Maybe definable is attacks
But it's
Entirely
Justified
Only thing that makes sense
Yeah cuz why would you
But look the whole container
It's a specific thing that Alex
Calling out
B insurance
Is a text
And that's not true
It's true
In the case of
This
Specific Supreme Court
Which is about the penalty
For not signing up for Obama
They determined it was
Largely
Definable is attack
Yeah Insurance itself is not
Car insurance isn't.
Your Healthcare
If you have insurance
Outside of Obamacare
Isn't
Other insurance
Does home insurance renters insurance
That's not attack
Do you know what they are hacks is not
I'm sorry
Insurance is not
Pat
So Alex making that argument
As a
Shoutout Max Keiser
That's not his argument falls apart
Furthermore
Insurance itself is a socialist country
The idea of insurance is you are subsidizing people
Need help
It is the larger group of people
DuckDuckGo
Almost everything about Society is a slight social attractive
Mad about Gunn insurance and not about health insurance
Profiting company
To get money from u.s. parody
To make sure that this happened
Pre-existing condition bulshit or any number of Byzantine laws
To keep them from getting the benefit that they themselves have paid into this entire time
You're like
Prosperity
You prosperity
F*** you
Prosperity Gospel understand what socialism
Guarantee gospel
Cuz he doesn't like
Yeah like you talked about the glitterbug churches
What is the Prosperity Gospel that's the the
Donating money to a church
To get your own money
He's just the sovereignty preacher
And
To a certain extent
Just this week
I know that this sound
It's crazy cuz it's been 11
It sounds crazy
But just this week
Kind of dawned on me
How
It is
Just the
You flatter him
And it works out
Right he loves
Right and what made it so clear is this s*** with the Nation of Islam
Cuz for the
11 months that we've been going through this hoop and screaming
The Nation of Islam
Take that white people are
Baby disability every manufacturer
They want the white people to come out
Etc
Exactly
He goes in
And they prefer
Tend
That they like him
Black bear Inn
They make a lot of sense
They're the best
It Dawns on me that like
I don't know why we're doing this
Podcast life
This guy is so simple
We're making this very complicated
And he is more complicated than that Billy up
Cuz of his
I mean
Soft
Stance on Hitler
There are those things that are like I still
Don't like the idea that there is a soft
Stay at Saint Hitler there are those things that are worth discussing
I think I said this in like
Maybe one of the First episodes
We did like
So much of this I could have just
Assumed
I think everyone hates him is right but they're not right for the right reason
Hasn't listened
For the wrong reasons
Right it's so complicated
There's this
Thread
I sincerely believe I mean our society will fall
In one day or not
It will
Yeah and I think that one of the most in
Think things will be the millions of people who were LED astray
Bye
Nothing
Yeah
But he's not
Example of that there were there were caught
There were PT Barnum's
Long time
It's just
We have the
Advantage
All of it being
Recorded is available
You can
Take him to task
Ask like
Back in the day like
PT Barnum again
Cuz I just said
He wasn't on
When he said the shipping center
We just get the advantage of like
It's there
I don't know why I mean ultimately
As much as I love all of you
Policy wonk
We're doing this for pasta
No
It is
It is one of those somewhere
There there is
Certainly
A section of the the world that isn't
Interstate Inn
Analysis
It is just
This might be an author
Conversation
There's so many things where
You can take a very very
Specific sub
And by looking at that subject
You can extrapolate the world
Sure and this is what I see our Podcast Addict I just told you all about it
Exact
Wheat through through this
Tiny little box
The prism
Through the tiny little box we can see the world
And it's
Become so much
Clearer
When you
Have this kind of
Small roof
Like its
Alright
Respond
What you were saying
I'm interested
I'm super interested
Evidence by all my
The conversation about our listeners disagree with you
Didn't what's real
The best way I think
To discuss that
Is talking about someone who's
Totally full of s*** because you have these like
I made where Alex is right again
The kernel of right
Falsity
The media sucks
Yeah like
You you have all this stuff on social media on Twitter on Facebook
All these stories that are not
True
Pander to whatever your
Pre-existing condition is or what about like trying to
Rabat the Donna brazile.
Right
Oh my God
Trucking killed through so much stuff
I get it
You and I sitting around
Trying to do a
Progressive show
Would be a disaster
Because
We could if we tried you just like to do an analog of Alex's show
Photo
If we tried to do a news show
It'll be a disaster
No because
Everything moves so goddamn
It'll be like
What do we cover
The Edward get pricked by thing
Probably
I mean you have the immediacy of needing to do the show right
Whereas we have
I haven't heard of a
Complete liar
Yeah
You can find
Truth
From
Pinging off that light
Sometimes they're not lying
Very rare
But sometimes they're not lying
Ragtime
You get to see what is there presentation
Looking
Right
And that is that to me is a much better
That's what the news maybe need
Baby needs
To become
Yeah
Essentially
Debunking
Bulshit
And there are
2 truth
I think week
You can draw from this podcast
First
Poor Eddie Bravo
That it
Such a sweet man
Such a stew
You can follow us on
At knowledge underscore fight
Website.com
You can download our pockets you can leave a review you can do all kinds
Find the fun
Yep
We are on Facebook
And then I think
Ultimate second
That I was
Was that
Unlike a Libra
A poor
Sweet
Innocent
Complicated world
Strongly
Disagree with wherever you're going
This poor fool
Strongly disagree with us who has no chance
Of Survivor
Unlike him
There are
Oh oh
Now I'm back
There are
Bearded
There are men I thought you were trying to present the bearded guy as a
F****** sympathetic figure I misunderstood
Poor Eddie Bravo
Anyway
I accept your apology
Even though it is
Tacitly
Not give it I miss her
There are there are these
Refuse to hang
When they were young
Had all of their teeth removed
And replaced
By CIA.
Insist on
Counseling Owen Shroyer
Given so many Owen fryers
Vaccines and then deny that vaccines work
Exactly it rhymes
There's a kernel of truth to it and I'll tell you about this guy
I'll tell you Dan
Jon rappoport can go f*** himself
In this case
I agree
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work