Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones dad
Pretty much every time
Terrible Rhythm for the day
And I told you before the shoulders of reason as a group and maybe to attack
Make.me a patriotic team
I got me a patriotic themed can of rip it one time
And I went to the store I was looking for a novelty fabric
Energy drink
What's the temp
Almost all of them have sexual names
This one is
Three-way
There's a bunch of like really suggest you like
Curvy energy drink names
I did not know I was like we got to celebrate that starts
Yeah indeed
I speak of something else we got a rip
Also you just rattle of the name of a modern post
When I came upon
I am a modern-day poet
So
Before we could go in at the show we got to give a couple shout out
We got a couple of new donations
What's up G
Thank you for joining up with the team
I also
Alexa call James donkey wrestler
Any of those like
Extended wheelbase problem is the next one's not going to work
What's going on out there Chris
Christine nearly as well doesn't work nearly as well
Welcome to the ranks of the
The policy wonk
You like to become one yourself you may go to our website and I was right. Com
Quicksupport
And then you can pick up
What's basically that Temple
Anyway
Like there isn't a long there's an along
For me there's no delivery no rebates
No news.
No return envelope nothing
Just like boom like that your policy wants
It's a very strange arrangement we have
Is it legal if you get out of line they will pick you up
Send you back to us
I'd like you to check out today is out of context
As producer
Control
Hey dude
Because
There's real I should hire people to do this
To do a good job babe.
I am a fraud
The 2016
We are
January 11th ended on January 7th
Mendieta couple days with David Knight
Brian skip over those
How do I get to with the 11th
On January 11th
Because
David Bowie
Passed away
Alex Jones
Beginning of the show.
Eulogize David Bowie weird it's not as bad
As you might expect
Very weird
Stephen Curry
Amor English
We're sorry to see him go
Condolences to his family
We just talked about
That's Amore
I wonder why my
Most common
I want my dad to be around as long as you can
Situation
That's your angle
There's no there's no moment where he's like condolences or like
He made a Monumental impact on Art in the world
I'm good lyrics
I don't want
I experience what is the biggest celebrities of the last 50 years who happen to have the same name
My dad died
And the only thing I can think about is
So my dad doesn't die
Do all of the millions of people who have been affected by his music
Which key is change genres
Multiple stops
He has extended rights for people who
Really didn't have them
Representative
He's done
So many amazing things
More than
More hit records than you can possibly imagine you know what I just don't want my dad
Fair enough and if you think that was just a stray thought
To revisit the liquor in the show
How can you make David Bowie dying about y'all wait no nevermind there whatever David Bowie
Everybody made it about that
At first I thought was I want I know where I was when I got the news that David Jones
Oh my God I'm glad that we can have this kind of fun
Buffoonery but I'm just glad we can have these Flickr
Hours of Justin Bieber
Amidst
Very deeply problematic things that happen on this episode
Like I said we're back in 2016 because we're trying to figure out the transition
In from Trump
Around the middle of December 2015
Do when does he go whole-hog into
Renaissance 2.0 Americana return
Yep
I believe it happens on January
I think it took him two weeks
That sounds about
Narrative transition
Yeah you're going to hear a couple things
In this episode that I think are like well to jump his happen
He is
And I think it makes it clear what the jump
Because Rodger stone is Gaston this episode again
I think that Alex accidentally make
Way to clear
That all of it is
Just Rodger Stone
Spittin
Interviewer
Wormtongue
Also on the 11th
Today
That we're going over and the 12th
Classic narrative
Who created Clinton
Cast
On
And another
No it's a book about the Clinton the Clinton family's dirty
Deeds Done Dirt Cheap
Bon Scott
So I hope he doesn't die
We we have
He can comes on and he talks about the uranium one deal
Answer that narrative gets introduced on January 12th
Right now let's see what
It stayed right where it belongs in the past
Because I'm the garbage there's really nothing to do with it I'm sure that there's no way that they run with that narrative
What time is it
Narrative
On January 11th
Pieology
I have seen similar articles
And from
Other procedures Publications
Brag about reading
Not renewing
Probably 50
Have you been listening cuz it goes excited to be f*****
Yep
You got nothing
Animal
Us research Farm
Came out on January 10th
Okay so he now has a headline verifies all of this stuff he's been yelling about going out
For any claims that he comes across hundreds of articles about this and I can't poop
Cuz the only references this article ever
Brett
Did you know that was inaugural every headline has the exact same headlines
Every newspaper in the World published
We gotta stop at with these national days
National
Pepperoni pizza day National ever headline matches day
That's the name of my dad I don't want him
Him to die
Let's finish up this
Charles
Just like
Embryonic stem cells
Thunder seven-month-old
I was the only time Facebook live it's just Mercy
Love that
Riveting
100 +
Let's not exaggerate
Inside
Growing humanoid
250 + 60
Inside cow
We know what's going on
Because when I learned about it
Declassified
This is a math problem I don't care to do
Alright
So you're growing human
Do you want them
Look
Humanoid
He does say that it's humans without heads at some point
All right. They don't want to have heads on them because it's freaky to the research
Chris
Second are ridiculous
Nevermind
5260 lb
Alright
What's the average human birth weight
So this would be
3 year old
What kind of gestational.
Would you have to have in order to get something to
Why
That's not what it's about none of these articles are about that
Other than like
If the scientists were just like
See how big
Grow a person without a head
Diane over there
That's the only legitimate reason for doing whatever it is
Because his whole thing about the chimeras
They're not humans they're not animals there the middle that they have no rights
Animals have rights
We've got dumped
It's well see so you're actually being like
This is a good reason to do it
It's not what's going on
Going to be clear about that
You can justify it
In the budget I'm all for growing headless humanoids
Yes on white genocide
Okay with headless
Chimeras being creative
I'm just excited that we found the day that that article came out in the it sort of became a very big
Piece of Alex Jones's narratives that's
So that's nice
Attract
I'm glad we have
The rest of this episode
Is going to be a bit embarrassed
I think a lot of it is going
To demonstrate very soul
Does taking a certain piece of bait
His perspective is starting
To get overblown
Like
I think that
I don't want to get biblical
But I think there's some sort of forbidden
Fruit
But Alex is taking a bite of
And he seems the world a little bit differently
And it's not real
You starting to get
An illusory view of his own importance in the world
And his
Place
And
Describe it is
He's come to a point where there are too many people
Manipulating him
Then he doesn't know what the wrecks
The chief manipulator the
It's driving him image
Pacific Direct
Is Rodger Stone
Write this next clip
I think you will be able to see pretty clearly
But he has 100%
Taking Rodger Stone
Whatever Rodger Stone dangled out in front of him whatever promise
Of relevancy of making social change
Gotcha
Hillary Clinton
How do you spell realize
We have here
No campaign
Nope that's incriminating
Whitestone
In the country
That's why works for Trump and he's gone.
World
Operations
To get people elected
Other countries
Yes real serious
So
Rodger Stone has presented himself in a certain way
Cuz loving
If you parse
Through
What Alex
Little piece of Truth
Did I believe you left
The campaign in order to do exactly this
I think that's true
And I think Alex is a
Expressing it
But
Siri obviously
Which should not
Express
Terms of reality which is Rodger Stone left
The campaign 2
Flip me
That's what the reality of the situation is
Not that
Hey he left
To do good
He left
The left
To help the world
Political campaign
He left because if you was involved with the campaign
He couldn't be an arch propaganda
He couldn't remember you could actually
I don't know
Is that legal
Legal form to work for Infowars
No it wouldn't
Was that a media Outlets
Something like that maybe
Do you have to disclose your conflict of interest
They don't follow any other
Ethical rules at Infowars
I don't know why they'd have a sticking point there
Be that as it may would come off as like if you was still involved in the
Campaign there's no way
The credibility would be there for the audience
Is of course
I was just
I like the ones with the with those people
Can steal a
And the rich guys who
To conceal a
Write himself
Credits Alex just listed
Are stealing election
He's gone overseas and help
Run
Paul manafort of course the classic
Example is
Ukraine
That was not good
General Flynn and turkey
Sure now that's starting to get flip
By the right-wing media
Dictator we love them here we love them there we loved it towed taters
Flicka the argument
Is being made by Alec
And that means that I imagine Hannity soon or maybe already and I just haven't
You know heard
The cleric who
Blue Flame
And the other one work
To expedite legal
I've heard that
Because
Remember
Seals that guy
Part of Batman is predicted
How to go to another country and extradite somebody illegal
I think Adobe a huge international ranking Bank
I think adults have always looked at Batman is sort of morally Gray
It's always been like
A grain of like
Little f***** up
Yeah
But I mean in this regard
Sure
At least the president
Stone and his associates have been involved
Wearing out
That's perfectly listen to on the last episode
Rodger Stone telling Alex
Trump played him
This is
Stone playing Alex for Trump
As the interstitial as the way of getting in the door
In the present
Because he gets to openly
And you can't even say anything about it because even if you knew you were being tricked
What you don't reveal
Because what's the most important thing to your ego and your masculinity you admit that I've tricked you 42
That's the most humbling thing in the world
Is Rodger Stone going down
Through some of this Russia stuff not being
Indicted
Yo
Secretly fighting against I believe he well
You could you could play that as like I got tricked FBI agent
Globulin
They sleep
Within the global Excel
That's been pretending to be
This is not a good angle
It's not like WarGames our way accidentally into a strategy that could work for him
I believe that at this point
The beginning of January 2016
Alex doesn't know what direction
He's got Rodger Stone pulling him in one
He has all sorts of other
People who are pulling him another Direction
As you can hear in this neck
Text clip he's being f*****
With by every
Shooter Philadelphia police
Muslim
But you watch Boxing
Heather calling extremist
Milwaukee with Muslim country
I don't think they're all
What the folks
And by the way coming up
Paul Watson
3 minutes from exclusive
Flashlight
Next Wednesday
Muhammad was a beautiful
I've changed
But I don't want a Civil War I don't want to race war
Louis Farrakhan
I just got
Listen listen
Listen
From Jeff Bridges
Kurt Russell
Successful
Thoroughbred
Yesterday
So is this
Nonchalant
15 minutes
A million and a half
The Sunday show reaches 2 million people dressed really
Twenty-eight million people actually tune in every week.
So keep that in mind
Inflated
Stats that are coming
He has
Vladimir Putin listen
Which we know, probably
From his contact with Russian intelligence
He was going to an interview with Artie
And I turned out to be a bunch of people
Listen to this next
Flip
Because it explains
What happened with the Nation of Islam
When he went to go visit
This is embarrassing
I want to contact some of it
I disagree with
And and
Trying to build a better world
Because he's one of the leaders in the world
He's a big deal
I like that
New World Order
That he's been watching me for a long time
Computer on
Leadership
Businesses with big companies
Super serious super Focus
I was shocked
Why
Barber shop
Vaccines
Break
Like a fiddle
Computers and computers
Got to see through the Ring of like a
Rent out an office
It's torn down and put up
Exactly
Exactly this is
Plastic
Softening technique
If there's one thing that I know about
Louis Farrakhan
It said he's not thrilled with the G
If there's two things I know without
About him it's video
Avery's fairly media-savvy
He knows be the sort of that he's survived this long
Fairly hostile media landscape
Yeah he knows some tricks
He's not going to like
You not going to go into an interview with Alex and not have like
Some little tricks
Along the way in order to make it a more hospitable situation
So
He's got
Russia f****** with him
On one hand
You got Rodger Stone f****** with him now he has a Nation of Islam f****** with him for no reason
Like there's no endgame to that one
All accepted interview Mauser why I don't understand
I mean I imagine he might have had the same agenda that Alex had in terms of the interview which is maybe we can
We have
Very different audio
Maybe some of your people will maybe we can
Yeah but
The only problem is that
Louis Farrakhan
His positions are
So
Specifically
It's fairly black Supremacy
Analysis position
Play Loft
Alex is Lucifer's solidly wife
Supremacist
There's not a lot of opportunity for cross-pollination
No so that
In terms of that strategy
I don't know why
The other Russia Rodger Stone makes total sense
Imagine that if they were to sit down and talk to
Heather
Other media Outlets would pick it up
King Louis Farrakhan
More media exposure Alex Jones gets more media exposure
It's a win-win for everybody yeah Fair times
But then I think there's also a small part of probably both of their minds
So they can reach date aunt
By convincing the other one of something
Really good I think they're probably I even watch the whole interview
Display
Let's just both agree to hate the Jew
I think that might be what they agree but just by calling
Next
Alex
Does Louis Farrakhan impression
Now I'm in
I think
I'll Trump baby the answer
Save America
I don't know how to say it because he's
Pinky really
Is outside the system
Donald Trump
So you talked to Paul Joseph Watson
Is on the line there is Farrakhan
Privately
Endorse Donald Trump
Interview with Louis Farrakhan from the final call
Editor Richard
This is a question
Assalamualaikum
On behalf of the Final Cut
The Final Call newspaper
Our staff and our readers we thank you for granting us this interview
Many news outlets have reported or perhaps Miss reported that you praised
Endorse the portador commended Donald Trump
What did you actually say and what's your view on Donald Trump
Farrakhan
I never endorse mr. Trapani
Can't do nothing
I never endorse mr. Trump or any of the candidates running for the nomination that would make them the leader of their party
I said if mr. Trump that I give him credit as the only wanted
I'm stood in front of some members of the Jewish community
And told them he did not need or want their money
You know what
If you're Alex Jones
And you hear Louis Farrakhan say I'm glad
Job stood up to the Jews
You're like
Love Donald Trump
Wait until you see all the other things
He does to the Jews
He finished his answer by saying I could never endorse any candidate because
Which would save America from the wrath of Allah
Is really concerned about the wrath of other gods
Right
I was really bummed out about God's Wrath seems like gods are getting wrathful imagination
I'm soft.
Imma do it that's why
Okay
Okay to be the god of Earth
Lex Luthor
Fugees like Thor
From now on
We worship poochie the dog for Thor
Except
Okay
Play whatever you like
I'm going to stick with Cthulhu for now but I appreciate your perspective
A
You down in relyea sleeping any religion it's like I don't even worry about it
Stream so I know to be
Scared
Look
Is like
The board game don't like
Right that's what got a hundred percent
The whole string of
Got to get the Guess Who
The different company
Call Joseph W
Great tradition again he comes in for an interview and it's about the Muslim Rape Crisis
What's going on
In Europe
Broken down into
Detailed
Episode
Allah is over blowing
Statistics
Issues certainly as there are in every country
Stuffed a lot of that
Fairly traceable back
Two Russian propaganda Outlets
Because they would like to
Destabilize
The European
Like to demonize Muslim
Difficult
You talk about
Because
You can't just be like
There this is b******* with
And this is
The problem is everybody
Men problems not like us being there's no
Christ
There's no rape
Like that it's all propaganda
They are twisting it to make it look at
As if it is
A certain religion as opposed to an entire gender
It's the weaponization of misrepresentation
Statistics
All of these immigrants coming in or military
It's a fun game makes him a lot of money
It's not
Not trip
Is talking about
The particular source
At the end of the
Deeply problematic
Just the report
All right-wing people on internet
Message
Libertarian
German Shepherd
Defend themselves
Do you know who that is
No
Christopher Cantwell
I think I've heard the name you obviously have
I don't like it
He do I get to stealing of
Greg when you say that
Was the Nazi
Vice interview today
Well
Of 2016
Case happened to Michael Brown
Black a******
We'll get back to this okay
Alright I would like to stipulate
Follows him
As a Libertarian blogger
At the beginning of 2016
In this clip he's asked
He says
Trayvon Martin
Before 2016
And he gets himself in trouble
I might have
With that myself a white people
Oklahoma City Oklahoma
Okay
Alright
You can remember Dylan roast
I'm I'm here to
More capable
Will come along and do that somebody like Donald Trump who does not give his daughter to a Jew
The Donald Trump
More racist McDonald's
Kushner faster walk around with that beautiful girl
So that's him before the Charlottesville rally
Up to it
That's Christopher Cantwell
A source of information for Paul Joseph Watson
Now let's listen to him getting interviewed after the Charlottesville rally
Somebody like him
Say what
Most
Republic
Android
The kind of thing that I
Of course I am his employees are following
Information
You can take different roads to get to the same conclusion
It's the universe
It's always struggling in life
When you agree with the point that someone suck
Agree with someone who sucks at someone else talks but for totally
It's a disaster
So here's Christopher Stevens
Spielberg and the whole Indiana Jones franchise went off the rails
Excellent
I agree with
Return of the Jedi know alright
So here is Chris Cantwell
The Charlottesville rally
Just to give you a taste
So how much of a douche
This guy is strong enough of a word
I'd say it was worth it
Resistance
Define that nobody on our side.
Points for us
I hate you
The fact that
Not a bar
People
We showed
We showed our Rivals that we won't be cowed
But the car that struck
A protest
Unprovoked
That's not true and you know that it's not true you've seen the video
Seen a video I don't know much
Santa video.
Okay
The video
Appears to show
Someone striking that
Wendy's animals
And he sought no way to get away from them except
Hit the gas
And sadly
It because our Rivals are a bunch of stupid animals
Sprint pay attention
Just get out of the way of his car
And some people got hurt
And that's unfortunate
Great
I am glad you're not
You don't plan
Cricket it's not good
This guy this Chris Cantwell
Come up with these feelings
A week before the Charlottesville rally
He had them in the beginning of 2016 when he was a quote libertarian blogger
Talking about how to arm yourself against Muslim rape gangs
I don't know man
I don't know
It's not it's not like I wanted to know what your answer is
Know it well okay I like that
I like that as a
Application of
The absurdity of what we do but
And I know this
Break everybody's
I like to believe in pacifism
Yeah I don't think violence is the answer
Chatroom to drink
With that guy
World War
Is not justified is not the only way that we would have sell things
Was the is there any diplomatic solution to a group of people committing genocide
No I guess I guess that really is the only situation so if
You're that
Guy
The only solution is
Tear him limb from limb Anita's finger
That gets me to my next
Point
Eating fingers is good
No there was a group called The Radical
To the group
Poland
That had a nationalist
Fascist rally
Over the weekend
Ironic
Polish not
They grew to the rally was in about 6
60000 people
I mean you'd be hard-pressed to say that all of them are straight-up not
But a lot of them were straight up not
Yeah
A quote from Wonder
The counter-protesters
It's getting more and more vicious
Jacob
I can't do it
That doesn't counter-protesters stand behind a banner that read we are polish Jews
And surrounded by people
Quote we are really in fear
The radical camp followers argue on their social media that the influx of Syrian refugees
Into Europe
He's part of the conspiracy driven by the globalist
Who are working with Communists in the European Union to bring Muslims into Europe
And with them
Sharia law and homosexuality
Men are they getting American news media all right hold on
It says that the
The same f***
Can Shed Annette
God damn you just
One word out you have exactly the narrative that Alex Jones pictures
It's his entire worldview
Just change the word globalist for Jews
And it's coming out of the mouth of legit Nazis rallying in the middle of Europe
So
Man
We got a problem
It's like a brain
Something
People got infected
We were texting about this the other night
Is Justin
We were texting about this the other night the realization that I had that
I do believe that
Given a week or so to Pivot The Narrative Alex could convert all of his audience
Not all of it but a bunch of them into straight-up not
You could say something along the lines of like
About it there's just too many in the globalist
Structure it must be something about them
He could use some sort of rhetoric like that
And pivot his audience into a legit Nazi
Tea Party
And it would not
It would only probably turn off about 20% of his audience
If that
So
That's that's what is underneath
The surface of
How
Scared I feel
Motivated I feel too
Two black people
Cialix for who he really is
Deconstructed where they come from
And why he's lying
Really bums me out when people just want to laugh at him
Hitler
Before he rose to power
About him you can find looking through the Alexis Nexus yet and what have you about that
The password now apparently socialism for LexisNexis password
So I mean
Coming out to you later I'm just saying
Actually I don't think he would do
But it wouldn't be hard
No it's a very closely Pretoria
From where he's at
And how much is radicalized is audien
To follow him I mean we're seeing this
In the beginning 2016
How easy it is for him to go from
Trump is
Con man
Casinos in Baldwin
His audience called in and they all mirrors
He gets on board with Trump and his audience
Right but wouldn't
You say that
Essentially his audience already is not
Like he's just using
Hey guys
I don't do that
But he was like hey guys we're going to wear upside-down swastikas now
Which coincidentally look like regular old swastika
But they're outside
Cuz we're we're anti-nausea
Bright
I don't like the word is what
It's
It's really just in the America
It's just the word Nazi
That is bothersome
All of the things
Still believe and say those are all fine
But if you call them Nazis
Being like
Twitter outrage I'm not sure if
Thinking people on the writer Baker
This argument
I don't see no people coming out and saying that like
Nazism
Just a word that's being used to almost as a racial slur for white
And
Right
And the reason that I wanted
To get into this is
We throw the word around a little liberally
And the reason for that is because
To take a moment to recognize it when there are examples
Like this
And the weekend after this
Madrid Nazi rally in Polish
Is a terrifying number it is a terrifying
Alex
Mobilized his audience
In such a way
Theorizing could happen
60000 people
Probably most of the Maria mobile
Small town
So
A large group of white knots
Suddenlink
Let's say Let's Move Along
Who's Rodger Stone
In this episode
Latest talks about how like
Clinton
His victim for high-class people and so that makes them more deserving of
Attention
Talks about how I
Clinton as a love child
Cajun food
Hubble is a
Chelsea's
I like that so
We are going to listen to this
Plugs Rodger Stone the book
And in doing so
He accidentally
Reveals that he knows that another one of his contributors
Their book
With Ally
By the book
Talk show host
The other shows
Rodger Stone
Trump campaign
Bushes
Swift boat deal
This is a real swept out for the clintons and the bushes
You need to get the book infowarsstore.com
Lorenzo the slide plug for the fact that are selling the book
All that b******* up butts
Did you guys before with that course ebook I'm definitely not aligned you guys now
Next election cycle course he comes out with a book
B m whatever the Democratic candidate isn't his last time
John Kerry
Bye-bye 2020
Remember it's so f***** up he's admitting
Gorgeous
Reality is fungible
Absolutely
Turn on here is the clip that made me realize that Alex has
He has transition
That he is a full-on trump propaganda
On January
I was about to say
They're just Democrats who want to control the Republican party and that's why I finally about 3 months ago
Trump
Because there was any other strong leadership there was anybody telling like
Ensure our jobs will go but the coup de gras was
Money doesn't lie
He's not getting any big hedge fund money
Are tons of money from Robert Mercer
Wow
All the big money's going to Hillary or Jeb Bush a Rubio
Trump
I'm sorry
That was shot I hope it comes from sweet pea
It's just proof it's a fact
On the sidelines
Because
No I'm going to do the Cowardly thing and let everything I've ever stood for be destroyed by this f****** orange
Monster I will let my entire reputation be cut
Essentially
Be that as it may
Is it the beginnings of it we don't have Americana 2.0 728
Better in that zone Proto x80 Proto
2.0 Proto 2017
He's there already
Just because I don't know maybe they're trying to impress Rodger Stone whatever whatever the case is
I think that
I'm going to play it
Episode
I think I have
A pretty robust
Theory as to
The reality behind all of the
Definitely rap
And the Raptors game in Alex's skin weird
Top-heavy
The globalist
A bunch
Eclipse that I think
Football sort of spell out what I believe is going on
We have two clips
That are
Call them fun
But they're Alex just getting lost
It isn't closest we get to fun
Athletic
Just like what I've been
Working
20 miles away
Another time. Later I'll down there working on a ranch
Discount
New truck
And then we all pulled out our KKK Hood
Good Old Dairy Queen
Peanut buster parfait my friend funny names
I mean it just goes to Alex's fun narrative about all the trouble he had because he was too hot growing up and
We know that you
You can't eat a peanut buster
Parfait wearing your KKK out over everything
Playing Roblox with a bib
Everyone knows that
Everyone knows that that's a clan BBQs
Why do they wear
I would have suggested wearing something darker
The stains better but you know what guys
Nice a nice bit of Clorox bleach on there you'll be just my pain out
No timeshare
He's like I'll beat you guys all up
I see that in like the
Dystopian future that we're going to live in next year there's going to be like a Target ad like
Are your cute KKK hoods a little bit Rusty Sunny did you use your robe with a bib again
Honey I got baked beans
Yep with that same bearded guy that every commercial now
I shouldn't say back into that lost it
Memories
Absolutely not the point of this memory was I'm not in the KKK
People up I like Spider-Man
The fight
Mexico play came from
Not very long after this
Because Dallas black folks
Oh boy
They just lay on the ground
Ford truck
Wait
Water parks that are friends that are love motorcycle
Think about that for two more seconds
What's the gang have more guns
Wouldn't it be more important to have a
If everyone had guns
If you want to pop it
King Kong
You said the n-word
Your kind needs to go I'm so glad
He goes into a long treaties after that
He goes into a long treaties
About how long
We're going the wrong way don't know how to Rusk
We don't know how
How to clean a stove
You're not allowed to have the internet
Go Unabomber it somewhere else make millions of dollars selling nootropics
A bizarre awful science
Listen nobody knows how to clean up
Borat
Can you text brainforest
Back in caveman days
Back in caveman days they drink real bone broth Stanwell to be fair he wouldn't make that are
We're coming to the end
Hear this
One more
What I think is going on
Is Alex's living in the beginning of 26
16 and a tremendous influence
Of influenza
Does that he doesn't know how to negotiate
Beyond that
There are forces at play
He doesn't realize
I don't know how to do
Describe that
Exactly
Without playing this clip so I'm going to play this clip and then I'll explain I thought I could do a setup but I can
And when we have
Iran
Quran or we learn
Russell's approach
Effexor
Conservative
I'm 1776
Yes I mean miserable.
Just shows how
Popular
Did you sound so crazy
Even more wild than that
Jasper's coming to look at it all
The graphs are like this last
Straight up
It is Meteora
So
Listen
Like it's more wild than you could ever imagine
Cuz it's like 10
No it's like Dave
Andy
Frankie B
French
Wahlberg and Mark Wahlberg
Call being a good parent
Mark Wahlberg is actually Donnie Wahlberg
So when you talk about the ratings
He does this
He doesn't
90 degree angle 45 angle
Let's not descend to
We could pin the rhetoric
Literally that bad
Here here's what I think is going on
He says in the last six months the numbers have
Absolutely
That was you go to sites like Alexa
You go to sites
Like what
And you go back to that.
There isn't a meteoric jump
And you know why
Those sites
Use verified
Statistics
So what you might
Be saying is that right around the time when the Russians
Started
Fearing with the elect
Perhaps they created a signal boost
Of people who had
Pro-putin ideas
Therefore in
Blading there
Influence the numbers
Gas
That part
Perhaps
Alex doesn't really have that many though
He is in
Stead
Hold it
The Russian Bots
I like to see English
Yeah! Jump
Statistics around the time are intelligent age
It was when
They started these operation
Influence campaign
Right in that window
I do not think there is a coincidence
Did Alex Jones
Is one of the most pro-russian voices
Outside of Dana rohrabacher
Ania in Media
That that is not a quince
The Russian people telling him that Putin listen
Rodger Stone
Coincidentally coming in
And giving Alex
Solve it like it
Too it's too much
The timing of it is alright
Very very suspicious
Too obvious
It kind of
Hurtful yeah
I still don't know how to work the Nation of Islam into
Investigation yes I think that's a weird anomaly
It just happens I don't think it's relevant
Sprouts
This is an old man murder have
Yes okay
Because
I think
At this point Alex
Hayirli oblivious
And I don't I don't know if he ever becomes aware
The extent to which
Scared
In the present
Isn't there
The beginning 26
He gets way more like in the lead-up to the Megyn Kelly in her
Today's
Use of being
Parasite on an unlikely let's not put out this interview
As if he was aware that something
Come out right
There's a part of me that believes
He is afraid will come out is what he's
Come to learn about what happened
I think he's aware of all the
When Breitbart release their revised numbers after they got rid of all that s*** there was an article in
I believe in Vanity Fair
I have that up here right now
When they went from
Like 500 numbers
In the
Top sites on the internet just overnight
That was December of twenty
16 coincidental and then dropped
And the reason for it was
Switching on and off
The tracking of artificial numbers
If you look at
Obviously
To Alex at that point
Andy should have been like
That's you might read headlines let's see what the headline number is it
Analyze this dumb child is like
Okay we don't need to read any articles that all let's just read headlines
To see what he knows
That's Trump's problems Mount breitbart's numbers are crater
He could probably come up with another explanation
I mean it's not a coincidence that that's December 2016
December 2016 is when Alex
Flips and ends up going with drum
That's when he starts
To see his meteoric rise in numbers
Stop
Anyway
I'm glad we've been doing this for a year
Our anniversary is coming up
Is it
Something like that so does right the beginning of January
I don't know what had weather
It is madness on one hand but it's also like I think we figured a lot out
I think no one cares
We figured a lot out
I got I got a I got
I've gotten some reassuring messages
When the last week cuz I have a little bit of a downturn in my mental state about
What's the point of the
Bed sores
I appreciate listener Mike
Sent me a message I'd like to give you a public thank you
There is some hope that I have
In my bosom somewhere
Like
Eventually this will matter
Boy it doesn't write
It kind of suck
Yeah
It is what it is
I think
Really just a certain
Kind of like
It feels like what we're doing is
To small for what
They think they're supposed
Big Freedia
Sitting on this one
One small thing
When it what what
Actually doing it
Kissing on the large step through a small lens
To make things
Clearer
Easier to understand
Probably think it's undignified to listen to Alex
I agree with that perspective to some extent but
It is amazing to me how much
You can see
Clear pictures of
The bigger picture through the smaller
Does that make sense it's really baffling to me that people don't understand
One of the reasons is because the only glimpsed it
A lot of
Spokes
Who are crazy
Get into Alex Jones are the things that are posted on Media Matters and rightwingwatch so they don't realize
Time these narratives
Is it end up coming out either from Hannity
Or
In the past from Glenn Beck
Banned from Donald Trump
A lot of them have their roots
And Alex
It's one of those things where is
You can do a huge invest
Navigation ultimately if you're trying to build a puzzle
You take one small
Corner of it
You know like
Talking about what kind of effects of the Russia
An influencer
Really had on the election
A guy like Alex
What kind of food have on him and his list
Easier
Exactly 10 pieces that fit to perfect
And you just put together
Nazi sympathy
Sit other corner is
Complete white supremacy using different language
Together timeline
Combine that with the other timelines that we know and you start to see obviously that Alex Jones is
Regardless of his
Knowing complicit
One of the perks of the Russian influence
Absolutely but look at his profile and how it's raised
And it's impossible to split
Rodger Stone
From
IDrive
I believe he's inexorably tied
What was going on at that time
I cannot be a coincidence
He shows up
And starts influencing Alex right around the time
That Alex's numbers take a massive Spike
Yep
Throwing around
Have been fairly Russia positive
For a long time
For that it becomes
So much more pro-putin
And the lead-up
If you want
Before December
It's just
I don't know man I don't think it's the whole story but it's big
It's a big deal
Who cares
Yeah yeah
F****** obvious
Go fuc
Where if you spend a year listening to you do all this research
Anyway you'd like to check out our website
Howardstern.com
That's where we are the kind of research that we do and the things that we cover
So Gone
Sport the show button we appreciate it and you can become a policy wonk
And you would like
Signal booster
That would be awesome we support that you can follow us on Twitter at knowledge
The score
You can go to iTunes
Download
You can leave a review you can again if you're a Russian
Download the same podcast a lot
And talking a lot about it and tomorrow
Where will Heaven episode
Dedicated
Two covering
Little bit more about Alex's
Bizarre relationship with Russian meme
Did you just do a PBS promo I might have
I think you just pulled out of P vs bro like
By his age
Seems like someone who should be watching PBS but probably isn't this evening so probably in
Can't read higher than a Sesame Street level
Yeah it possible somebody who
The children's Workshop
Garbage
Maybe like a garbage can
The lid is never on
Write a note that is laying on the ground
Someone close that garbage can
Kind of drives you to say
Alex
Birthstone colors