Alex
Birthstone colors
I can understand why that would happen
That's also a very relevant possibility we are disgusting human beings like to sit around
But Alex Jones is there a reason why you
Is there a reason why we would record to episodes
Work done some sort of like
Travelers style slash
Stephen King Style
The reason is
Play the world is
The terrifying place I happen to know a lot about Alex Jones
And I see it is my duty to
To teach you who knows nothing about Alex Jones
About this before it's too late
That makes me sound like a buffoon as child
Do you know what I'm saying
But does not Alex, I happen to believe it's one of the most important areas of State in our time and
Whether that's true
You know what here's the other thing
But
Even harder we shouldn't be looking for any kind of
Media grants
Let me tell you something you and me
Adjunct professors I like this
Alex Jones
I think we could teach that at a junior college
I bet we could
I bet we could get at least twenty grand for it
Do a little bit of research
And if you would like to do that you could become a policy if you already donated and you want to bump that number up you could be
Become a foreign policy wonk
Like a real one of our new to Chicago
And we had a great time hanging out with him over the weekend it was a blast
Over the next day
Very but like to give a shout out to our new foreign policy want what's going on out there
Four Star
Aprilia
Yeah super cool dude
One of these
Very very few policy want to have everything we do stamp
I apologize
If you would like
Peewee do stand-up
Follow me on I don't have any social media and I do not post any of my
I will find a video and send it to you
Please don't know for real it was super fun to hang out and meet someone who likes
Michonne is a very interesting guy very nice guy ever in town
Even if you are a serial killer weenie like
Well this is a bad way to go
We would be so I don't think we need a serial killer in private anything like that
It's great it's so it's really cool to me that you know we have
Cool fan
Everybody that I've interacted with online and I'll chat rooms and live shows
Girl super cool and not dick
Even to people like sometimes we get Alex Jones room and then
I like that I like that they're not assholes to people and I think we've done a good job reasonable fanbase
Think we have any
Reasonable intelligent fan base
Reply not so much larger
Is the price we pay
Running low
If we pics
We would be much better off
Jordan
We're going to be going over
Is a little bit of a look
Alex Jones and his relationship with Russian
Because I take out a telescope
Alright alright
I might not understand the bit
I wanted to get a look at
Alright screw you
Screw you Dad don't you dare tickets
Hazard lyrics
Explain the
Moderately terrible B I just gave
What I do
Jordan
And I watched
The number of in
Instances of Alex Jones
Disappearances on RT
And then also I have
Put together a montage
Alex Jones
Songs when he was a gas
Alexander Dugan
Right after Donald Trump
I'm not sure what a lot of this
Proves
But it's an interesting glimpse
And I want to add this glimpse
Into
Even before we get started
Yeah
One of the things that I learned
From this
Exploration
Is it there's a high incidence
Alex Jones regular
Who are also regulars on RT
People like
Paul Craig Roberts
Is on all the time
Gerald Celente
Peter Schiff
These people
Often go on in RT
And make
Barely anti-American argument
Like listen to this to start with a clip of Paul Craig Roberts
Who's the guy who is on Alex
The show very regularly
And I would say this is just talkingshit on America
So
The American economy is just
Play Third World economy
In which
The only jobs available
Are domestic service
Such as
Starburst waitresses and bartenders
There's probably more than that
A superpower
Some extent
Well I mean
Using his particular example
I do thank you
Correcto
I don't I don't I do not agree
We're descending into a third world country when you look at our infant mortality rate going up you got to be like
Maybe some arguments we had though because of the vaccine
Sent right
You got me
Here's the thing
Our economy isn't
Descending into a third world
Steadily better since 2000
That argument is
A lot of jobs that are available are in service Industries
That's mainly because manufacturing has become robotics
That's not the job
That is one Snapchat
Overly simplistic View
I don't think we're sending it to a third world economy
But we're not we're not what we were
70 years ago or whatever
That's a silly argument to be making and at the end and saying
We are this is not a superpower
Is not justifiable based on the numbers
Based on what
Examples
Think you're correct
Based on the overall reality I think you might be wrong
I think we are
I think we are watching a former superpower decline
That may be in the same way
Predicting the future
A little irresponsible
Future which I think is
But if everybody understands history you can cut things off at the pass
Right but I mean if you look at the way that Roman
Fairly similar
There are there are some similarities
But not least to mention so many different states
With in Rome
And its outlying territories starting to break away from each other ideologically and
Really
Having these
Thoughts
You having these you know position
Yes is pretty reasonable
You know what that's fine we can
About these things
If you were to go on Russian television
Russian state-owned television
Save it America is not a superpower
And descending into a third world country
It has a different
Flare tool
To me a little bit
Wealthy but the way that I would
Is that
,
Like you
Is Russia interested interesting strategy
I realize this is a little bit of a small example but it is the trend among all of his
But end up going on
The Robert David Steele the Gerald Celente
Peter Schiff
They go on and they say negative things about America
So let's start off here
Gander Outlet
You are not going to give
Both sides equal View
Like like if you were save some sort of
Massive Media Company
That has a hard right bed
You would definitely not give
Equal view to climate change
I know you would absolutely
Absolutely in
The weakest and most
Idiotic people represent
They're in making it look like you guys are the smartest
Let's go let's go have
Fox News as opposed to
Tomi lahren go on
Talk s*** on the scientist
Right it was a better game
The clip from 2008
Going on RT
To discuss
The Georgian conf
If you'll recall
Georgian Russia
To war over South ossetia
Another area
Well they were not selling as many colorful suits
That's that was that right
Okay thank you very much that might have been a little slow
Who is Delphos area in abkhazia where the two regions
Separatist Rebels
That Russia gave us
Support to a flared up
Started
Fighting
Not interested
Very similar to what happened in Premier similar to the arm
Conflict perspective it's
Neighbors
It's small degrees
The whole time
Here is Alex
In the wake of the Russia Georgia conflict
On Russia
Intellivision
While the shooting at maybe over the war was
Biosphere
Display Russia
Infowars
Cam website
Change
Conduit
First off let me say I am a chain
American I'm a loyal American
Love my country with my country has been taken over by private International
Military industrial complex
They watch the sneak attack on the Russian
Enclaves of abkhazia another area does yuno on 888
Using the cover of the Olympic Games in a dastardly
Make a jack on the order of Pearl Harbor
You know it's real when you use the word dastardly
Used to do this
I was watching Farm news and I knew this
The us back Georgians israelian natureback George's that snuck attack viciously Amber
Civilian
The peacekeepers
Unprecedented crime
Who do you think is talking about when he says the foreign media I was watching
You
Are modern-day the 21st century
Reporting that Russia it was headline
Rock candy
Sneak attack
And our leaders went on television and said that we would have to have a new Cold War
It was such an insult the American people's intelligence
That the United States back Georgia and I apologized
Like this
This is not
All states that I grew up in
The New York Times
NHL in the US and Israel
You have a new Cold War proof in Georgia
So no more sneak attacks can be long
Because the dictator in fraud
Fair in Georgia
Last week to attack
Answer please watch it is not need to leave
Where is Italy part of rocket
Because we don't want violence
Don't want this one
American Western New World Order system based in
Of course London and New York and DC
U.s. cellular
Implemented
Gear up for martial law
1/3 destroying our Republic
They're destroying our freedoms
Coming after the Free Press and feather using NATO
Expansion
The way to widen the war
Central Asia and then to the west through Eastern Europe
In Central Europe
Can I really appreciate
Vodka
Has been restrained in all of this
Jesus Christ
Tesla
Narratively
Did the leader in Georgia that he's referring
Western sympathetic
Power
Not a dick
Dictator
He was leaning towards trying to join the UN
And you wanted
Protection from that that
Guide
Didn't want to have that guy anywhere near us
Didn't want to be there because it got they took away from there
Competition
It's all exactly
It's all a very very simple calculus never have been allowed in the UN
Because Russia can
Negotiate on this
And be like hey and other members going
And you guys don't have the balls to say
And other members of the security Council
That would being discussed the idea of putting forward a map
Of them join
Their position was insult
Or an attack on Russia
That didn't move forward but what did move
Quote undo attack on Russia
No it's so we have we have this we have this situation where there are areas
They used to be part of the Soviet Union
And some of the people there identify with Russia as eight
Bordering
But it's
It's not a part of Russia
That's not their country
The lines are very clear about
National sovereignty
It's a ghost
To Alex's like
His belief that secession is okay
Right now it's significant
Huge blind spot
Because I never
Really even thought about
How were the borders drawn up
Immediately after the fall of the Soviet
Were they pre Soviet Union Borders or District
Everything right
Well in the 10th Century for the first time in merge doesn't
Concept in the territories were the Georgian language
Refused to perform Christi
Chicken ritual
So there's this
The independent Democratic Republic of Georgia was invaded by the Red Army in 1921 in Soviet government wasn't
Installed the government of Soviet Georgia created an autonomous administrative units for the train
Caucasian
April 9th
22 called
Self-obsession
Autonomous
O'Brien
Such as Steven F
Lance motherfolk
Believe that the Bolsheviks granted us autonomy to the accession
In exchange for their help in fighting the Democratic
Republic of Georgia
Tempe area had never been a separate entity prior to the Russian invasion
South ossetia
Subway
So the Democratic Republic of the Soviet Union
With all of the Soviet territory split up after that but
They predate it so there's that I don't know all the boundaries of all these other countries but there's that
You're going to have to
People who identify
In the Soviet Union never lived with anything else
Sure like from when they were born they've always been
There's that
So let's say a situation where I was a sneaky
Sneaky power
And they were trying to bolster the
Credibility
The remnants of the
Confederacy in our country
Could be like you know Alabama was really more importantly part of the Confederacy
It wasn't really part of the United States
Just ended with us becoming two step
Countries plenty of people in the woods North America
Incredibly complicated Alex went on Russian television
Supported the exact Russian lion
And that's kind of common
Kind of common
Is one of the other things that it is a big thorn
A lot of a territory that it lost
Union brokop power
A lot of the money that they could be making for oil reserves and thread
It is a complete disaster for them
Because
Encroaching
No so here's another clip of Alex on nrt
Talkabouttd
What would you do to fix it is it possible to feel
You know
Is there any solution
For fraud
No it wasn't
Did they write that down also
And show you
Goodwill
Used to set up
World government
It's now come out
Not really setup
Operative expression
Yeah that's really the mission that is set up for was let's not have another world war
Guess what we're all hanging out
Come on over we'll talk it out
Maybe you guys want
Right and even with
Whatever excuse
Scream nationalist version of the world Alex
Wants to create
And these other people want to create the garage there has to be
Coordinate your dump
Because even if you have these nationalist entity
Unilateral treaties with each other
Eventually you're going to butt up against each other eventually there's going to be some need
For collective bargaining with each other cuz otherwise
Nothing will ever get done
Guess what once that happens if you have this National Collection of nation that are getting together on
Slightly different name for the exact same
Is there will be inadequate
There will be times when atrocities take place and they're supposed to stop it
That's going to happen no matter what
Yes
The situation
Countries
Eventually you're going to get into dispute
Just like we talked about with the Soviet Union
Your American National
Mexico was part of the United
States rights
We on that territory part of the United States
We have we have reached a stalemate
Is Mexico in the dark
Nope
I'm afraid not know
We can't let you do that right because Mexico is too chaotic
What have you to get there
Frankly I think in this.
It is actually a police action
Benevolence
Nationalist United States to Annex
Write in the same way that
Absorb
The Ukraine
Quick more Nazis in
Poland are the Nazis in Germany
You really brought up a
Listen to when you get into Alex's
Reviews about
Do you want cuz
What day were created for obviously
The world will end up being
Mario donut
So him coming on to art
And saying that the UN is beyond fixing and its only function
Corruption
That's Manna From Heaven
People
The propagandists that are absolutely
He's really describing his FIFA
You don't get that
I didn't have time to
I'm sorry would be International apps
Yeah that's what they're really
The United Nation
As much corruption is I'm sure there isn't United Nation
You know they they hung out with Silvio Berlusconi
Happily to report
Is making a comeback
VIXX comeback
Any of these
Talking bodies
Is it you have
End up lending themselves to corruption
And legitimately the only way
That you
Work again
That is regulation and oversight
The only things that are
Goodman applying the rule of law
You can say like we have a federal government and it's full of corruption that's why
Look at the state government corruption
Anytime of any kind of organized power body is.
To have those elements within it
So you get watchdogd
So you get
Strict regulation so when people are
Caught doing things they are punished
Appropriately
How do you spell that works
How do you stop the financial crash
2008 or the one in 90
29 or the one in 90
You put the people who caused it in jail forever
Forever and ever
Because it's cruel and unusual to use them on live TV
I mean Alex even uses the example of the bankers that
Fox yeah and he even uses that example and I think
Keep takes the wrong lesson from it
Necessarily
Appropriately Iceland's economy has recovered in the
And with appropriate oversight and
Reasonable application of the law across-the-board
Are possible
On a national level
With that's what we should be working towards not the dismantling of the UN that only really serve the
Purposes of hostile actors
That's not what we want
It's it's
Even more than that it's such a simple psychological
Concept
Everybody
He feels infinitely more safe
When the law is applied
It is
Small thing but
Think about how much more comfortable you are if the law is
Oh
I'm not treated any less fairly then the richest guy or the poorest
Yeah
Everyday you wake up
Far more
States
Everyday
Every black
That wakes up
Never worry
About the cop
Cuz they know they're going to be treated the same way that a billionaire
It really seems like that would be a good way to get
To sleep wondering if the next
Yeah also equally and I am the leader of roving band
Coyotes
Literally
I have them pull
And I just go from Fortune 500
Company to the neck
Hypothetical
Sport
This next
I told you that Alex Jones a lot of his guests appear frequently as Gaston art
In particular
Has for years
Max Keiser
He is we know him from his cryptocurrency max bucks
And from that one time he tried to get Alex to be reasonable
About the idea of gun insurance and Alex freaked out at
Here is a clip
Is Max Keiser and Alex Jones have a conversation
This is on our
Texas show
And let me tell you this
Alex's smiling
The biggest smile I've ever heard
This person
Beginning of this clip
When Max gives him a little bit of news
Discuss
Crazy
Governor's dinner
There's assholes
Cuz you're from Texas
He made a picture of yourself on a horse
Turn off Wi-Fi
Much like calling Obama
Sure
Heterosexual and so therefore
Conair
Especially in Britain
Class B classified as
He's bringing peace around the world he's a Statesman piano and and so have a Russian Asian
The greatest
Alex Warren
Has completely
Stop listening
The moment he heard Putin
Says hi
I am just going to be the happiest school girl in the world me put up a picture where I am
Maybe he'll see this note
Do you like Alex Jones
Did about Planet of the Apes
I guess they did another parody picture of something with Planet of the Apes
The person Scrolls down immediately has to get off the Google image search
Bunch of Life ones with crosses through stars of David
Ono Ono
The subjects text
We don't want to air that we're aware of how people are audio.
I mean like
It went when we really get down to he's beaming
When New Year's Day
Like someone wants to say hi
Wants to come out and talk about hunting
Whatever the fog lamp
That's just indicative to me of how
The most days
Is it
South of Section 8 is actually building
Okay
He do a one-man show now that was movie where he gets Hunted
I remember that
I would I just got conflated cuz the only thing I can think of when I hear John leguizamo's that he did that one man show where he played all the Care
There's like a bunch
Two characters
Super Mario Brothers
Best video game
It's great
What's the best
John Leguizamo movies
Where am I
Sonaze
It's such a
Great movie
You know what it do you know what happens in it
And you'll never believe
Alright love you
Keanu Reeves
He is an invincible assassin
Do they do Gun Kata
That's cool
Pretty close to it
Someone else
Monterey transmission
We've talked about this
After the election
Alex Jones
Almost immediately gets an invitation
Over Skype to be on Alexander Dugan show on Russian
Let me know Alexander Dugan
Is a philosopher of note years
I mean the only way really to put it is he is
Had a lot of foundational ideas with Auntie liberalism
Liberalism for not talk about liberals
The American system
He's against anything that takes people into
The collective
Or what have you
TI-84
Retails back into a little bit of his philosophies as we go through this because
This that we're going to play a bit of
Alex's appearance
Show
I think it's fairly telling
In the past made reference to how much
He's getting his eyeball sucked
On this route
Haven't heard how much
The entire time this is going on
Most this is going to be these Russian
People talking
Alex looks like he's going
He looks thrilled
To be getting the sort of accolades
But like you did a good job actually Alexander Dugan hire somebody
Found him underneath
Okay that's possible
Anything's possible
You know what sound
I do
We have a special program today because in a few moments we are joined by a legendary American journalist
Alex Jones
But before that
Mainstream media
The fourth estate
Is molding us today
Before my worldview our perception of reality
Depending on how the mainstream media presents the information
So just a quick
What's going on
Visual
Video package
About how great Alex's
The Voice you hear is Alex's Russian
Unemployed
Doing the translation
In the western world
The dictatorship of the liberal Paradigm is all too obvious
When it comes to the media during the u.s. presidential race
All the big media Moguls openly supported the war criminal Hillary Clinton
Round the Clock
Distortions and fake poles they praised her political platform and assured
Hurting when all the front pages of every other publication
Portray Trump is a loser intentionally exaggerating his
Supposed dark past
Words taken out of context
Over and over
On all media Outlet
On November 8th the mainstream media operation
Already prepared their November 9th issue with Hillary's portrait on the cover and headline
I would like
Just to rebuttal
Against that they also had
Version prepared where Trump won
That's kind of how it works it's like
Super Bowl t-shirt exactly they have to do that
Especially with an election that ends up going into like before someone can seat it was like 3 in the morning
Getting that to press
The idea of getting the copies out of
Of course they had pre-made graphic
64 everybody in something
Horse it's embarrassing in the same way as the Dewey
Defeats Truman right kind of s*** but that's what people do
Every single presidential
That is ever happy
I guarantee there is some facsimile of
DeWitt loser winning
Exists
It's not worth
But punching about instead of a
Instead of
Underprivileged
Wearing
New England Patriots
2004 Super Bowl champs
They're wiping their ass
Underprivileged propaganda
And television programs reports
Praising the lady Kingpin of the World Financial
Something went wrong
And all the pre-scripted news.
Turned
Complete BS
They put everything on the line and failed miserably the predetermined Clinton
Suffered
The numbers
Spoke with themselves
Trump won
No one in the US mainstream media believed or wanted to believe in Trump no one
Except for those in the scientific dynamic
Highly passionate energetic and unrelenting journalist and documentary producer Alex Jones the director and editor-in-chief
Infowars news
It is this journalists who had the courage to show the truth of what is really going on in the United
Five states fighting the false Narrative of the mainstream media information
The globalist liberal ideology prevailing in a totalitarian
Style of the modern Western media fraud
He reported on the financial Elite
Their steaks
How to choose during the election
Alex Jones believes that behind all the world's media out
But there's an idiot logical liberal agenda
You're welcome
Nazi
Building a unipolar Empire
This world government manipulates all the prominent media sister
For the sake of their own personal info
Use all the cast
Hillary Clinton website suffered
Repeated denial-of-service attack
But then
Couldn't
Stop him videos continue to gather hundreds of thousands of views infowars.com
Was practically the only resource
Where do you lessons were covered thoroughly and objectively
Criticism toward the FBI and they discuss the weekly
Infowars
Has built itself
Distill with the intro
Of the American people
This media organizations showed its independence from the world financial Elites
It showed its sovereignty, So Below
Promedia have utterly Bendis
Credit revealing themselves along with credits
Are becoming powerful forces in the new era a new paradigm
Which Usher
So that is a long
Cooking intro
But it's
It's essential
Buttering up Ally
He's already on this is like the payoff
You did a good job song
Basically just like
Do you know
You believe this to be true
Yep
Stick with us we get it get it
Everybody's happy now I really do truly believe that
Got a phone
Time to say it something is lost
Translation cuz the Russian but I do think
But something is lost
On Alex
In terms of
When Alexander Dugan
And the Russians
Liberalism
And when he liberal
Because Alex Jones
Libertarian beliefs
Still rely on liberalism
They still rely on
Our systems of freedom
Or Western ideals
You disagree
I don't think Alex has any idea what
What
Ideas are about
You can expose them only once but now he's a fascist
Propaganda Outlet
America America know he's clear lights clear whatever goes on rtu the American Patriot
Comerica
The Constitution
Cuz it disagrees
Allowed to have gun
Like systems
He doesn't think that there should be checks on time
When liberals are in banana
But generally speaking
Service
That he wants to
Make
Law for everyone regardless of reality or fact
He's on board
Yeah I don't think he likes America most of these people actually like America
I don't I don't
I don't think they do either but
I'd still think
That in his head
The future he conceives of for America
Does still rely
On
Liberal is
What's the future in his head before we go any further what's the Futures that disconnect between what is rhetoric
Because I don't think like we can very clearly see
Reach the logical extension of most of the things that he espouses
You would end up
Pretty quickly descending into a white ethnostate where everyone's armed and everyone's afraid of each other
And everyone is disenfranchised
No social
Safety nets there is there is no
Serfdom is unregulated children are back in the
The cave
Smog is only taken
External View and look at it like that
But I don't think
He thinks that's the end result
The delusion that he dwells in
I think that he believes
That
You're still going to end up with an equitable system
Where
People have freedom they have Liberty they have
Can still vote
All that stuff
You're just going to have businesses that are Unshackled
Like he doesn't understand
What historic Lee his
The end result of that sort
Coal mining accident
Even back then in the nightmare that we lived in in
20 right
We still have a religion
Women because they didn't bother having any safety equipment
Textile mills that we still lived in a liberalist system
We still lived
In a western democracy
Right
Is what
Alexander Dugan and his ilk
Are opposed
They are opposed
To Western democracy
Alex doesn't realize when he's talk
When he's talking
Alexander Dugan
Liberalism is a cancer
Even these vests
Digital images of America that Alex
He doesn't realize I
But he hears liberal in there
Right and that's enough for him
Right
That's the point I'm trying to get you
You clinically I can never I can absolutely
And there's another disconnect
It is
Alex Jones is f***
Eddie doesn't realize what he's up to he's in way over his head
Isn't so far over his head
But the other thing that gets lost
Translation is the idea of
Anti-American
That's going to come up
I believe in this neck
Text Cliff
Explain on the other end of it would I
I'm very happy that Alex Jones is live with us
Right now
We have been following you Alex
For many years
Including myself personally
And when you became
In this new era of Donald Trump
I marveled at
That you the fact that
People as yourself
Embody
Search free
An independent points-of-view
Which are shared in reality by millions
The people
American
And worldwide
The millions of Russian peep
Did you have a giant
Hero of this campaign
How you told the truth
Everyone else lies
How you held your ground
Fearlessly
Against
All the dirt that they were throwing your way
Example of a true American man
The true American Spirit
Alex Ramirez elected Hillary
A real American
Is
With the American people are anything like you
Attitude toward your country
Toward your people
Will be radically
Donald Trump won
School music Portage
And whom we were also in solidarity with
Not a good thing to say in hindsight and him
And all of us
I said this
Anti-americanism is
Over
No the people of the free United States
Free Russia
And all the anti globalist
Powers worldwide
How to build a new world
New architect
We are exceedingly glad to see you on our program broadcasting live
Right now and from the bottom of our hearts
We thank you
The genuine face of real America
Call Alex
Alex alright was great having you on our show some more nice things about you go home
And if you noticed whenever he's on the Russian television he doesn't act like he
Acted on that BBC interview
Sensible
PX
Like someone actually who respect
The person he's talking to
It's very strange can't think of any reason
No
Americanism is over
I think
Then how Alex
Here's that
I know this because he's talked
He hears that and he's like
I have solved
The Russia America problem
They don't hate us anymore
What he doesn't realize is
The subtext of what Alexander Dugan is saying there is
We won
Americanism is over because
We don't need to psi
You guys are pro-russia you guys are
Serving our interest
Yeah we have flipped
Entirely
To a point where our problem is with the unk
Keeps telling us we can't do this s***
That we want to do
We can't take
The Soviet Union
What he foresees is the is Eurasian ism
And Eurasian Union
Soviet Union
Been his
Fantasypros
Underpinning of his philosophy that you're raising Union
Start to have a lot more sober
Do it but it still be your raise or even if it doesn't need to have that
Can still do the same game that Nazis Alex does Nazi ideology
You can do all the things you want to do with just changing one word
That's simple
Eurasian Union
Is Enron still around
Hey man there's a
Guillotine folk right there
Folk with the guillotine on their names now you're wrong Alex Jones thinks that's enough for me
So you're getting a full dose
I just
This is the sort of stuff that you imagine Alex's keyring behind the theme probably the entire time
Restorative like
Through intermediaries they like you
The only voice that's really telling the truth
The rest of the world knows it
Elvis store
This is a thousand times
More effective than just
Louis Farrakhan having a
Couple of people with
You could have just said
He was really good and he would have been exactly as in
As You Are
25 minutes
Where is the culmination of
Love so much
Galaxy probably feel slighted if they didn't
Because
When you are someone
Like
It's easy to imagine
Your influence is greater than it is
Sometimes you need those things
Make
Your internal perception
Appear to match
The external reality
Like having Donald Trump on the show
You should probably didn't Merit that
But because his involvement with Rodger Stone
And working it out behind the scene
Donald Trump
I won't let you down
You're going to be really very happy we're going to talk a lot in the future what have you
Jones Ascent of himself
After the election
Alex we heard him on
Election night drunk at 3 in the morning
Sing I have served my purpose
Then he goes on Russian television
A couple days later
And they basically mirror that back to him
You can imagine that that's how the rest of the world field
I have saved the world
From global
I have done
Such an amazing and that's why he looks like he's going to cry the whole time
Which I'm all yours during back
Cuz he's realizing
Oh no they said nice things about me
And now they want me to go back in the corner
You said I was Alex's done a little like
I don't think he has
Because I ate I'm doing research people that are flattering him actually
It would be
Incredibly troubling or is he ever looked at the chat room
All of the all of the Alex talk about
Why the Jews are evil
All of the n-word flying around
I knows it like we
Maybe they are
I don't know if it's
Gringo's on some level even for us to be like
Everyone is
Cool
If our audience
We're like
If we went to the chat room one night and we saw an Edward I think we might cancel the show
Celebrated Alex Jones doesn't read the chat room than what have you
Part of him that he is either in complete denial about that large
Chunk of his audience
Or just
Do you have to shy away from
Entirely and only listen to voices
That are like
You are the true version of America
You have saved the international
Singing
And now we will rebuild
International order probably the most
Reasonable
Relatable in humans
Though is that
Of course you make compromises if you want to make a s*** ton of money
Part of the game
Specific to Alex it's unfortunate
It's
Piece of s*** he's willing to become the consequences Fortinet
Cuz he's willing to make
Uncompromising
This to your ethical or moral
Ideology in order
To become a
Very wealthy man seems a very common theme with everybody
Becomes wealthy I think that's the trajectory of his entire
Career the compromises that
He clearly made when he infiltrated Bohemian Grove
Happy quotes
The the willingness to lie and misrepresent what he saw there
In order to
In his mind
Take down the banking Elite
That probably
I want to
Noble goal
You know what I mean like
Is there is an element of it
You know the end goal is
You know reordering that to some extent and making sure that people are punished for financial crimes in the same
Someone with a joint is punished
I can't imagine
But once you go down the
The path of completely lying about them
And saying they're all sickness
Amping up that rhetoric
And
Adopting so much of this washed over anti-semitism
What you do is you ruined for good
A suit that you have
And all of the
Become so much more important
To your audience
I think that's the story of his career
Brilliant move
Classic move on the part of the people who wrecked
The economy
We're all pretty much
That be, Spock
And it's unsustainable in
Market continues to rise
The only thing that every reasonable person should be thinking is
Boy how bad is
The crash going to
Especially as the growth rate
What has nothing
To do with real wage increase
Every time
Ever happen
There's been a spectacular crack
The Dust Bowl was a thing
You know overvold were a thick degree iron
This is this is Maybe
Because what ended up saving
The world
Maybe the world at least America
The depression that we had was the New Deal
ER and it was Democratic
It may be
Socialist
Can't figure out the USPS
Great ideas but I'm telling you the actual nuts and bolts of it difficult
Alex Jones wants to go back to the Pony Express
Work better
It might be the most important thing
Now
To build
Voice
In America
Before the coming
Disaster
Because those are the ideas
Save us from
The inevitable crash
I don't know
I don't know that's just a thought that be kicking around in my head
Prescriptive
Prevent
Better now
Build up
To start when the crash happened
This is the way to go
This absolutely is what we need
To do an align ourselves with
Instead of a national party that's like
You guys are right
What if
We don't do what you say
Aaron said keep getting a s*** ton of money
You know what my theory is like I work this out a little bit
I believe that
Democrat to Republican
Because they are sort of Warring versions of
The same sort of
Massive corporate interest
Slightly
Banana
But
Literally
2 years ago
They were
Sides of the same coin
The GOP itself is still a largely corporate beholding
Special interest party
And so are the
GOP is already crumbling
To the libertarian Patriot Wing or whatever of it
Like the defensive Roy Moore
That's weird
Is bananas
And the fact that they're fine with it but yes it is
Because
The part B
Supports him
Are the libertarian
And Patriot
Wingding
He has the support
If you was a Mainline
Conservative GOP member like Paul Ryan
Tumi
Espouse
What we will see in the coming
I think in the next few years
You're going to corporate Republican established
Completely destroyed in
Replaced with this
Hyper nativist Pro libertarian
Party
And if the know-nothing
Powerhouse
The dangerous part about that
Is that libertarian party
The Proto libertarian
The protos not the right word
Right
Democrat
I can fight much harder it weighed
Republican establishment
To maintain the Democrats as their foil
Wouldn't
Scary because those Democrat those corporate Democrat
Are going to fight back I don't understand
They don't
Yeah cuz they're only they're only there only ideology
She is ultimately compromised think that it's
So long as
But
Like that
When you're fighting against
People like Alex Jones
Everybody who doesn't agree with us
Fox kids
Yeah you're not going to like you're not okay
Well we will give you
A harder border
Chuck chuck shoulder Lost Empire
Compromise
Stupid
And there is no like
It's not like there's no compromise
It's in the minds of the Alex Jones
Libertarian
Patriot right
There's no interest
10 compromise
There's only interest in like what you always
Growling
Nothing to do with
If you're ostensibly
Constitutional geopier
Can't
Vote for somebody who's violated the
Katusha
That's something that you can't just
You're voting for
Position
Violating
Intuition that you f****** love so much
And then you're like
Okay
Yes you did. He's done that we're still going about
And then you're like well we hate
What is a pet
What's going you can't be like oh
Well
We're still going to vote for
He loves guns and he's into the Trump agenda
Quotes
Call Maria
Guess the bottom line
The political correct
Age of consent law
Bad
The point that I'm
I'm trying to get to Ibis
Is that the last
Needs
To get on board
With that
Knowledge
Immediately
And they don't
Will come
I think it'll come within the next few years
The dance
Of back-and-forth
Aspiring to reach across the aisle kind of stuff
Is not it's not going to have any stock in trade
There's a denial. Ann Obama wasn't
The best even with
The aspirations of
Compromised
Mainly to his obsession with
With
With Republican financial interest
The point is
That game is over
And it's not over because
I'm saying you can't compromise with the Patriots
Or would anything like that I'm saying it's over because that will not be on the table
Do you know how happy I am to hear you say that
I don't know
Because you have
Disagree with me on that very point
4 month
Finally you have come
Well realization though there is no further compromised available
I still believe that there are
People who identify as conservative
Out there in the world citizen
Who are not
Is the problem that we're diagnosing
And I respect and I get ultimately has been kind of a miscommunication but
Matter of scale
But we're both in agreement
Not just unwilling to
Ideologically
Hosed
2 compromise
There's no possibility
I am I so much as there is a part of it now but what I talked about more
Wait what
What I'm talking about is there will be within
A matter of years
Probably exacerbated by election
Michael's Tucson
But I believe as we get closer
You're going to
A horse swing
End of that Direction with
The people who are on the right
And if people on the left don't
Prepare for that in some ways
They're going
To get to steamroll
Well here's going to be a complete disaster may be the simplest
Explanation of why the Democratic party itself
Something that you
Should not trust
Appreciate
And that is that
Imagine
In 2018
That we wind up that the Democrats wind up taking both the house
And the Senate
And actually getting a supermajority
Which is very possible at this point if you start to look at the Alexa
Results that we've seen entirely possible
That the anti Trump
Fervor
Will absolutely Propel the Democrats to majorities in both
Won't
Well and they haven't fought for
Voting rights
Even with
Results that were singing
The clear sentiment
The large portion of the population that
It's not going the way it's right if you have people were
Franchise did you have people who were kicked off voter rolls
You have these extreme gerrymandering
Situation
You're not going
To be able to
Have the people's voice
Accurately displayed in the vote
Complicit
It's very easy to blame
You know gerrymandering on the APA
Opposite party
Both party
Ship negotiation
No ultimately whenever the
So you can you can always find this s***
Somewhere where it's like
And people say there's no difference
Between Democrats and
Republicans when you go into certain social
Which is absolutely true
The problem is that the underlying factors which
Contributed to those social issues
Those are the things that Democrats and Republicans
Have ideologically agreed on
When you talk about
African-American rights in regards to
Just police shootings and the way that they're incarcerated at a higher rate
Yeah
Democrats
Don't want that to occur
That's part of the reason
Like that's the reason that people say there's no difference
Between Democrats and Republicans
Is because sure you can reactively say
That we don't want all of this shift
But if you are part of the reason it happened
Then you got a lot of s*** that you should be fighting for
Much harder
Yeah I agree
Agree
Wholehearted
I will see what happened
I hope everyone gets on board with
Something
It's going to be reactive Americans always
To be proactive
To the next clip
Andis Clipper Alexander
My name is Andrea Fantasia and I'm the host of the Russian dancer my show is about geopolitics
Strategy and diplomacy
And we regularly follow you
Can you call Lisette Infowars including your presence on social media
They should be another translator with subtitles
Coming from the swamp
Kevin Nealon
But after Clinton loss
They weren't able to accept it
It seems they don't have the
The strength of mind to recognize their defeat
Facts about somebody else's involvement
An independent American Patriots media
What they're really winning a bit Americans underestimated Russia's abilities
That's what their product is happening in America
The same Civil War
Is happening in Europe
Which was started 16 years ago in our country
Also been Victorious
That's why we understand
That today we are all in the same situation
Weather at the Russians Americans or Europeans
The globalist
Represent America
They are the enemy of the American people
And when you tell me
Address in your supporters
It sounds like a call to
All the people worldwide
To shake off
The dominance of the globalist delete
And established in each of our countries
Our own
American order in America
Russian order in Russia
Turkish order in Turkey
Elvis Warren struggle
Is what unites us
Interesting that turkey was your third and turkey was the other
You realize they were all
Briar true certain point
The global Corporation
Transnational corporations
The globalist elites
Were presented to us as the voice of the United States
But thanks to Trump's victory
We now know
That there's an RV
Between the American people that's you.
Those who are the resistance to the globalist dictatorship
Which organized
Color revolutions against
Still not regular paper
The soros's
The Clinton
The Obama Administration
The so-called
State
Call revolutions against Trump refusing to recognize the Democratic victory
Of the American people
Well but also
I mean you want to
This this argument of
Lamented
Color Revolution
Another country
Is not accurate
But that's not entirely
Did there's a difference between cement exam and supported people
There's a
There has been an attempt
To make a color revolution in America
Trump
At this point in history after the election there was only the women's March
And the immediate
Anti-trump March
Color Revolution
Which is
Pretty well covered under the amendment
We only like the second
But you understand what I'm saying this underlies
Of course we'll visit underlies that
There is a
There is a there's a perception
Peaceful protesting is a color red
If you believe that you have to believe that
What they're complaining about in these other
Countries
Georgia for example
Iran Ukraine
Color revolutions that have
Probably we're just peaceful protest
Cuz everybody
Wilbur Ross
Oh man I can't wait
And all of us
United have to think about how we can resist
This Elite
The people
Values
Have to engage in dialogue
In terms of what do we want to build instead of globalism
Another globalism
Not in a position to Russia
Not in a position to Turkey
Each other to protect
Are narrow national interests
Which is what the globalist imposing us
The fight with each other a civil war
We have to avoid
Still not allowed and dialogue
Between us
Exchange of ideas and different values
Oh man he must be pissed
No he looks like he's going to cry
He never let people talk
Saying you're the best
Probably can
Fused
Is there being espoused
Even Alex doesn't go that far but he triggered like there's a lot of words that trigger have my globalist
I've also realized
I should just kill myself after this
I love how Alexander Dugan says globalist
That's what I kind of said global
Whatever I say
I kind of do that I kind of do a little do you like to do a little
He's triggered by those words and when everybody's just saying there's a
What is snowflake
You guys are so right I am awesome I am awesome
It's like he's getting a Lifetime Achievement Award
Culmination
His career mode
Most likely
Not realizing
Not realizing that that's a
The bad thing
Want to reach the culmination of his career this way exactly
The end of his career as well
Want to wrestle with the fact that like
He would be a
Ashamed of himself
5 years in the past
Looking at what you've become
Yeah I do believe
You think so is because we go back and look at the 2012 version of him before he was Hawking these weird
Supplements
You just had these fun
Big Berkey Water Filter cam
Movie Pitch
Alright
This is all a dream
He had
When he was underneath that
House is toxic
Exactly
Christmas Carol
The ghost of Buckley which by the way
Buckley is never Buckley's been dead since Alex
Goodnight
Then we got the other three ghosts Larry Nichols
Ghost of Christmas Past
Ghost of Christmas in Arkansas pass
Totally
No knowledge fight grave
Goodnight baby I think Stone in pieczenik should be present
Location of script for A Christmas Carol
Bring a little bit
Because the old guy like Statler and Waldorf
I'm Sam the eagle
Christmas Carol
A muppet nationalism Christmas
Mascaro
Alexander Dugan has
Really just hung the balls
Play the Nazi
The Green Room
Jean-Luc
Patrick Stewart
Reminder highly recommend
Alia shawkat
Shock Hattiesburg
Development fantastic
So eventually Alex Jones Doug
I don't have a crystal ball
The public like
Actually how they end the books with
The maniacal laugh
Dugan has got to be laughing in the middle of this energy
Because I married this from this big think article
Dugan might Advocate specifically we can look to his best-selling book the foundation of geopolitics
Particular success among Russian military
According to foreign policy
The book outlines a vision for Russia in the 21st century they would lead to your formation
But also include specific strategies for defeating or neutralizing the United States
These include destabilization and disinformation campaign
Using Russian Special Forces and asymmetrical Warfare
Never happened
In France
Never happened as well as for the country itself specifically singling out race relations
M367 of the first edition of the book
It is essentially important to introduce geopolitical disorder into internal American activity
Separatism in F
Mixed social in radical conflict
Actively supporting all dissident
Couldn't match
Sectarian groups
Destabilizing internal political process in the United States
Also support isolationist tendencies in American politics
About this
Alex Jones is going on 20 years ago
If we had
Has Alexandra show
I mean there are Russian companies that paid for a troll account that
Specifically fermented
Race division on website
Facebook setup so no that's how many of them have come out
We got money from Russian sources Movin no
Is Ebola
And a lot of this
Suspiciously
The philosophies and the
Plan laid out by Alexander Dugan in the book that he wrote in 1990
For Russia in the 21st
Century
Also I mean if you want to talk about these like asymmetrical Warfare
Kick it better than Infowars
No in terms of what we've been talking about your enemies as demons
But when you start talking about literal asymmetrical
What else could you describe Syria
Russia doesn't
Really have anything
To gain from fighting in Syria or even
We're not going to do this
I don't think anybody would really notice
Except for this area Do or Die
Right.
It would be it would be like
Because we really don't have any
Nothing to gain from it
Not just that but where you to depose
Hydro putting somebody else guess what we would still be able to negotiate a contract with
Guess what you guys don't f****** live near here what are you doing here
That's the larger question that we should be asked what is
Find a note
At the same time
We f****** bombed hospital so what do you what do you say about America
Beyond
Geopolitical reasons why
Incredibly important
Got a comical in a certain level
And a lot of it is laid out in Alexandria
And Alex saying
Getting on the show and talk about David Rockefellers book brzezinski's books
Or you know that the job Beholder in textbook that he always busy
These things and lie don't say what he act
Like they say
So the fact that he
He's like talking about how these globalist put out these things about how they're going to poison the water supply and I think you're too stupid
To read them
Alex you're misrepresenting those
Meanwhile the guy that you're talking to
Didn't put out a book
This very clearly unfortunately we couldn't have known until now has laid out
Texas last year
You were a part of it
You are a f****** part of it Alex
That'll be
Interesting to see in the history books written by of course the
People who survived in our post climate change world
No more humans are on their face
Will have lifted up the sea-level to the point where they can live anywhere
Believable
Planet of the Fishman
Totally forbidden zone.
Different the underwater
End up a bit
No
The history books it seems like
Dugan should play
Such a huge
In this
Just in case we're trying to
Mastermind
Nothing like that.
More important
Figures that I'm unaware of who espoused similar things
That's entirely possible
The only the only reason comes up so much
In terms of our investigation
He is a very legitimate
Philosopher
Putting out
Philosophy books
Geopolitical strategy book
And
Exist
Infowars
He exists as someone who Alex Jones
Clearly is interact
He's on Alex's show Alex has been on his show
The fact that he's on
Alexander Dugan show Fairly
Close after
The election means to contact
And
Like not it only that
I have to assume that other people
Did Alex Jones is in
Who is the reward in touch with rice
People like the Paul Craig Roberts
People who are they
On our team that Alex also has on his show
Those types of people will probably
I can't
SeaWorld
Where there isn't
Some communication between
These folks
Conspiracy
It just means
They were in contact book
Before the reveal
Depressed doesn't work which is Alex going on
He should be in the Heinrich Himmler role
You know music like there's a certain part of all of this that can be
Traced directly back to
His
His idea
Yeah and if his
Building on other people's ideas of course course
It's tough to get away from that
These things
Vicky has espoused
Since 1997
I mean it's a solid
Planets
In the past
Hanna smaller-scale this is what
It's been pulled off on a global
I would I would
I would not think
Venezuela
Yeah like it's essentially the same
Exactly
I thought we got that
Is my lived I'm very sad
Everybody
One last clip of Alex's
Appearance on Alex
It's a it's a
Just the Wang Chung
Because Alex
Baby Alive
He switches into Alex on Infowars mode
Okay because we get to see some of the narratives
But he spouts on Infowars
Unresponsive
You can hear stuff in the background that's cuz
They have a translator
Does Dugan doesn't speak English
Speaks Russian
And some english in the background from a translator
Apopka
Yeah it's 41
That's why it's so exciting
Does she
Information Age
And seeing the internet
Control
I'm sitting at all
Blow up in their face
It's a very
We have the initiative
We just can't
Globalist
If you would have had nukes
Psyche
In their power
Like
Child
Calling Jojo
Dictator who is clearly
Cleverer than most of the other
World leaders that were dealing with
His
Rampant James
He's bonvillain ass.
But also
This underlies something that Alex
Talked about
Hitler
Metaphor unfortunately
Presupposes Trump isn't going to behave like
Also
Proposal
But if Hitler
I'm ambiguous on whether or not
I care about whether or not Hitler
I'm inclined to believe you didn't
I liked
In Brazil
I'm inclined to believe he didn't but if you did
Cool if you did
Also I mean we have much bigger issues
Project Paperclip doesn't exist
But that was real
Hitler is still alive
We have a timer
Oh no
You know what the bed
Best way to
Yourself
Become Russian
Is holographic Medved survived
Actually you know what I'm going to go with Rex Tillerson
Boys from Brazil
The clone of Hitler
Wallpaper
The idea that like
Hitler did survive and live
We have
We have so many
People who should have been punished
Because they have scientific expertise and
Russia to absorb them
We did we did a ton of that in the idea
In in historical hindsight but if it did happen
They just sort of Falls in line with
We clearly weren't really
Jefferson punishing anybody
If they had something to offer
The Nuremberg trials
Like the CIA would have lied about that I don't really think of
South America and lived out his years as some sort of like fake money
Or whatever
I believe that's what some people
Believe
I haven't done
To deeper dive into
But if they did lie about it and say that he died
I really think that's
I think history should correct it
But at the same time
I don't think that's my fair
Right because for National morality is a good
Thing to believe
That he died
So you're saying that Osama bin Laden
Yeah
Even South America getting it tonight
Whip It
That the TV show
That's like a real world
What happened
End up living.
Quest
Control
Then keep on willing German.
Too drunk
Military
Another such a dick
Russia
From there
Selectivity
One question
My question
Over
Type
Russia
Great question
No
Voided
Corrupt
Power in Russia for a Time
But Didi idea
The longest-running
Stretch
Government
And continues
Man they are amazing
I want to point out the
True,
Alex Jones
Being on Russian television
And some guy asked them
How do you disabuse yourself
Of the wrong notion
That Russia is still the Soviet Union
On the show
Who has exposed the creation of the Eurasian Union which is essentially the
Re-creation of the Soviet Union
That's bizarre
That's almost in incredulos question
From them like
How do you lie to yourself
About what we're doing that's how I heard it
How are you so stupid the most obvious
I scroll back and possibly too far but let's listen to the tone of that again cuz I don't think that's kind of
Hamster correct
How do you free yourself from the nose of the wrong notion
TriHealth
Question for you
My question
How
Ever
Over
Type Russia
Study hits
You know I don't understand the question
Play a couple
You coming out
Not really
You know how you get up from the bottom of pool
Suppress
Everybody gets guns
You fly up
Yeah that's really smart that's very smart
Cuz if you might not
Come along,
Nightmare
Welcome
Fundamentally
What we always
Oh you're so close
Well
Those
We want our
We want we want
We want a Russian
National
And only killed
What you guys don't talk about that
Missouri
On birthdays
Jumbo jet
We fundamentally
The
Bus schedule
Kevin Nash
Where is gabon
Boswell
Weird
Real world
So Barry Goldwater crazy
Ron Paul
Deeply racist past
Also some good ideas about non-interventionism and I would have you
Makeup
Live through the gulag winner of 6
Stacks
Strange
Eclipse that we have but as a little bit of a punchline I'm going to go through some of these
IRT videos
From because
I can't I can't
Eclipse put out by Arty
With Alex Jones
And these are the headlines that they've given
As if they're using him
As
Again.
The UN is a Nazi movie
The UN needs to be abolished
Alex Jones
Texas secession
Where's the one who was created by the CIA
They just posted a clip of him getting in a fight with anti-trump protesters
Them calling
Gay rituals at Bohemian Grove
The media put a spin on wikileak
Total control grid design to predict the future
There's one in here
Related
The others in the same way
No I can't
It's not scrolling
Was a mason
Pepsi
Oh that's true
Are you f****** kidding me now that's
Anders Breivik
Not a Mason first movie
It's a Wonderful brother
No beggar you set up a bomb
In Norway
Other people have hailed as a hero for his
F****** white supremacist Bowl
Yes after him like he's been
Supremacist movie
Call Joseph libertarian blogger
Free bloggers I don't think that we proved anything necessarily in this
Exploration of Alex Jones As Time on
Russian television
Proof
Where you at where you at
So
You remember if you haven't heard any of this
Remember
Duck season wabbit season
Looney Tunes
Remember how eventually
Get to the point
Where
Elmer Fudd
Daffy Duck
Okay has put up
A million different
Print signs
All shaped like arrows
Pointing directly
Play towards Bugs Bunny's hole
Rabbit
Yeah hell yeah
That's where I'm at how you feel inside of the rabbit hole
A million sign where one particular rabbit
Maybe sitting smugly
Chewing Auto Care
I mean it's not
The rabbit is
The dumb idiot
Confused by whoever saying rabbits are Looney Tunes
Metaphors going to fall apart
That's all folks
Every nuke
Go off in the background
Roman I mean it's
It's a bummer but it doesn't
Tumi doctor Infowars or how I learned
To stop worrying and love the
Like all of this
Just
Just mirrors all the stuff we've already seen on his own show
But it's interesting to look at what
He is willing to say
Where he's at
14in
Enough just for it
It's foreign media run
In this case by
Stayed on propaganda
And a
Philosopher who has espoused
Plans to crush
America or neutralize America parents
Resemblance
Two plans that were affected
Correctly and when you look at
The fact that he is willing to
Push the Russian
Version of history on Russian television
And
RT
Is now
Been forced to
No signup
As a foreign agent
Right
It's it's
It's bad it's a bad look
Well when you talk
About
Collusion
So what
What exactly
Is the difference
Between collusion
And cooperate
Right now collusion with the
Suggest that
Prior to pulling off all of these narrow
They discussed
And
Bright
Similar Thai
At the same time
Cooperation
Suggest
See this person with similar motive
I'm going to amplify
She sees me with similar motives
Ivan app
Amplifier
No it's not a crime
But in
Fact
The same result
Yeah
Cares
What is whether or not it is collusion a cooperation
They need to be fought at
And destroyed in the same regard
So whether or not the one
Whatever you want to say that Alex's
Is on the payroll
Immaterial to actually solve
Tissue which is that Alex
Is beholden
At least
Ultimately is on the payroll
Like whenever you get an
Inflated viewership number
You're going to get better abs
What
Bowser in the same way that Trump got
Two billion dollars worth of free advertisement
In the same way it doesn't matter
Where or whether or not it's a direct payout it is
Still a payout even talks about that like if you go and watch MSNBC or NBC
See your feet
It's for Northrop Grumman
And it's like what they're trying to sweat
Consumer can give them
Okay Alex your
Think about that take a step back
So yeah I mean there are
Different ways of
Of looking at it
I agree that the
Nothing both of it or not super important
What is super important is that
Yeah
And the fact
Unfortunately
Where we are now
To why the Democratic Party
Such a
Virtual group
Was people at least at the top and a lot of them
Yeah exactly because this story
Right in front of everyone's faces
Two billionaire
It always comes back to the Oliver
Take me to be dis
Stride that's ultimately what democratic socialism
That's the goal at the end of it
We can't have this level of inequality
Because that leads to an inequality
Yeah that's the whole point
Well it's one of them
It's one of the main point
It's from it's from which
You find so many other
Socially are social justice
This platform
Once you once you
Span power
To a farm or equivalent
You wind up finding many of those other issue
Are solved along the way
Unfortunately we can still
We all can kind of diagnosis like we can all
We're all aware that
The problem even news
The issue is
Like with the opioid
Prices regardless of whether or not you are on the right or the left everybody is aware
People are overdosing
That there was a massive advertisement
Based on these company
Movies that wanted to sell
In their pocket
We all know that
They're just
So smart
At least there
Never enough
They have a low-level Cana
To convince
A massive section of the population
That it is in fact
To the people who are trying
To help them
Who are the cause of their
The sleight-of-hand that will disc
Destroy the human race
Well the sleight-of-hand to Alex's
Portion of it these ads that are all like
Conservatism
Is the counterculture
When in reality
Even with Trump
Really
It's just the maintenance of Agro status quo
It's not really eat Trump isn't
Counterculture
He's not really
Fighting globalist
New
Like he's he's on board with a lot of the things that I like
Nevada
5 out of his eight cabinet
Members were Goldman Sachs people
Yeah it did
It's nonsensical.
Dangerous
I think he does agree with that
Exxon
Some of the geopolitical ideas
He has in terms of power
Right
I came to me we've gone over this already even in this episode
Problematic
Come up
No matter what
Alignment you have right
Nationalism globalism
You would have that body
In some form or another
What were
Finding out with
Trump
Is that
We can either fight
Domestic policy
We can't
Successfully fight
Like on domestic
Policy
We're fighting really hard we're trying to keep
Healthcare
We're trying right
Keep them from destroying the tax
At the same time
They are dismantle
Yeah they are
Dismantling who are literally people who got there
Facebook
Which is
And that's something
Thing that is in the news that we won't even remember neck
No I have no idea because we're going to be off on why is the why is he
Why did Roy Moore still win
Keep going
You can fight one or the other but when were fighting both
We're going to wind up losing on both front
Yeah
Noel
But that's what that is
The neutralization
Of America
Yeah that is sought
Exactly
Auntie globalist powers
That really aren't against Global is so much as they are
Against the encroachment of the UN
Which is
Holding up International sanctions
Against
Encroaching on your f****** neighbors like you did in Georgia and Ukraine
Which is even crazier it is
It is kind of interesting
Because many of the UN Nation
10 states
A spouse that very similar center-right policy
It's just they don't get their countries back
Yeah that's the only reason
Disagreement
At the end of the day between the klepto fastest un
Congratulations
Let's wrap this up
Let's just not let's not try
Okay Farin
I can solve one problem
If you need to go to a website I have a
It's knowledge fight.com
Yep that's true
Garbage
Rewrite Pez
Bingo Terraria Twitter
Subscribe
Internet with people who'd like to support us on our website
We would appreciate
Foreign policy wonk
And globalist is coyote
Oh, you're going to join my group
Become part coyote
About this for years
Beyonce We Appreciate You
Absolute come up in my research that I think is weird
Yeah
I could not
I could not find
An instant
Larry Nichols
Being on art
Is there Berry Auntie Hillary
Like a lot of times that
These people who are Infowars characters are
Empty Hillary should edit call Larry
They just give him a ring
Call Larry probably call
You think if that's weird another person
Find a monarchy
Even even Artis like
What the f*** do we do with this guy
That's got to be like
Did the Russians one thing or tidy people
Prefer if you hang up pictures
At the breadline
Pictures are always helicopter
The bread is really wish I would have prepared
Anyway
And learn how to say Go fuckyourself in Russian
Rapoport
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color