Alex
Weird couple dudes
Sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Today we're drinking
Spark
It seems to be a go-to to ascertain
Maybe
Today
Couple ship bars
Three or four shitbox
It was not great
And I know nothing about
That's the premise of the show I know a lot about him you don't know anything about him and we try and work through his weirdness
Play game of Scrabble last night at the bar but it was non-canonical
Non-canonical from the Furious
Forever
To make it this far
Complicated
Put it in the fryer and then hand it
Stick
Fry's
Yeah we should have known
There was vomit like right outside the box
Juliana
Fizzy water
Which is delicious
To be back
Dear Alex
I'd like to a couple things
First
I don't I don't go to Paris
I mentioned this last night it's one of those things I really really hate about bars at some bars
Big open windows
I think that some people
Persuasion
Exactly
They have a performative aspect
To their nights out
People get really dressed up and they want to be
Look like they're having fun more than actually having fun
There's a large group of people that were spending most of the time they're at the pool table you wanted to play pool
Couldn't because of them
And they were like doing
They were just overhyping how much fun they were having David Busters
Exactly that and I know it's because there's a huge window to the street there they knew the people could watch them having fun
It was sponsored by the
I mean by theory that these people were dicks was like
Very well-established by when they came over
And a guy lectured you about low fives
Reminder of business wait for our food
You gave your girlfriend a low five
No ma'am
This is a friend
Is this that what's going on are you trying to be or do you think is going to be
What's going on I don't understand that mentality
I don't connect with people
How would that break the ice
Just like
Low fives are bad
You are right most interesting man in the world
Elders of Zion
We had approaches
To dealing with this guy to cuz like you
We're kind of like you're an a******
Very over-the-top fake laughing
Neither work
I think it's fair to say if you've listened to our show you understood the dynamic of how we react
Exactly
Page right now and started we started the end of last week
Started to post a lot more blog
Content about Alex Jones
In the immediate
So what I'm listening the episodes I'm cutting clips
And writing up
Debunking
Articles about f*****-up things
He says in real-time right
Appreciate everybody's like them
Shared them
Interested in the show
I would really appreciate it
If you could go and
It makes such a big
Books algorithm
And it's not one of these Alex Jones
Right it's just how it works
If you have us like
Make a fan page or whatever
It. Your contact doesn't get pushed all your fans unless you pay for it
But you can organically get around that through
Like three or four or five people sharing thing
The ball starts rolling
It gets shown to a wider range
People
Help in terms of
Getting the word out
About things that we think are important about Alex
So if you could do that I appreciate
If you don't want to jump to it cuz I understand what it's like
I don't want to share a bunch of stuff on my I don't want my page getting cluttered up with a bunch of crazy people talk about Alex Jones
And if that's where you're at
I understand and frankly it's not where you're at
Who are you
Do you like your average bear
Alright
Let's avocado
I think it was the
The compound
It was the stuff please do and also
The second thing was totally ever saying
Alright alright
Policy wonk give this one out to you what's going
Ryan
Thank you so much for joining up with Team absolutely
I don't think you would call himself Ryan I don't I don't know
Accounts to attack people who made fun of his
Who knows
Anything is possible call Ryan is itself
Hating Republican
Listen to
Astro
So you want to be compulsory want to do that by going to our website knowledge fight.com
Sports robots
Now he's done all kinds of business here with the top 5 minutes
Yes thank you
I appreciate it keeps the lights on
Lowe's
So this is my house
Yes sir I will give you a loaf I'd like to propose a metaphorical for the fact
But today we are back in
Thank God most recent shows of Alex's has not been fun
Not really all that interesting cuz he's mostly just going hard at Alfred
I don't disagree
Did you get the pass
And anyway Alex
Presenting it as like
The Liberals won't call the road to tasks and I cranked off everyone hates Lena Dunham
Everybody's mad alpaca
Yeah they're better than mine in a much more complicated way than Republicans
Impossible
Disappointment
And
You sorry you f***** up you got to go disappointment of like you had done some good things
The Senate you seemed like you were Yogi's real sharp in a lot of categories
The grilling people about climate change publicly helpful toward the cause of
Just women
It's unfortunate but the reality is the reality of Bryce dealing with reality
Never give men any sort of power
Because chances are
Perhaps
Complicated way Alex
Dealing with it isn't based
In reality
To score points
And the whole time he's
Stocking with all these
People about like about Roy Moore and his whole perspective
Yeah it's weird
You think
The time to talk about a joke
She absolutely raped
You know it and I know it.
Came out and said
He basically like
Grabbed her head through to his crotch
Can part of a parking
I mean that's not weird
No
Let's Criminal
Yeah and it's so
Yeah it's possible that you could do you take right over that I do have one thing I wanted
This is sort of an out-of-context drop this is from the November
You chose this is from the present
And italics trying to
To score points
About his
Sexual tastes
No no no no
What I like
Oh no
Girl
From the fifties I'll just sit there like an hour
Now that's weird
Waitress in a
Feel Like a Woman
Really where
I mean there's a lot of things to unpack there
H2 sexual contact
Like let's
Let's be clear
Do you like the fetishizing
Pin-up girls and that sort of aesthetic
Often is
Maybe a fetish
Is Asian of like women without power and are aware within were very subservient
I think there's some weird element there any ideas
An hour
Just like
It's very much an uncomplicated life
I like women who cannot talk back
Only smile and who are never ever matter
A mannequin mannequin leg
I'm not.
I've also not
Blow up doll
Charisma
My friend Sal from Columbia Missouri
Decided he was going to do a setup
Hilarious
Forwarded
Pipefitter
He's an awesome guy
Now I'm super onboard I want a million of him
Blow up dolls
Play blow up
I love it if that's that's always the best part best part of any kind of open mic
Look
People who were working on jokes
I'm happy
Yeah
Lunatics
Now I'm now I'm excited he's a good kind of limited
Some of the other sort
Yes
16 we last left off I believe online
The 11th
After the 11th there's a
String of boring
Because Alex
It comes out that Chris Carter
Is rebooting The X-Files
Okay is restarting the X-Files and one of the characters
No
Not the Vikings
The guy who acts
X-Files was Loosely based on Alex
Hehehe
In an interview says that Alex Jones
Isn't
What he would consider to be super
He's more of a libertarian
And Alex takes that.
B a b positive
Work
Whatever
I don't matter to me really
The most important thing
Fair but he goes on for about 2
Today's talking about how the X-Files is the biggest show of all time
Even they know
Guys from The Lone Gunman
Promotion
Email hadn't even started on his
It had like maybe up was about to air
He goes on and on and on
Two days straight just about how like X-Files loves me
Chris Carter
The show
Best show of all time
The guy from The Lone gunmen
Spin-off of The X-Files
And how one of the episodes
The CIA
Contacted the lone gunmen writers
And told them to write 911 as a plot in the show
In order to prematurely inoculate the public
From thinking it was fake is like
It was in this episode
I don't do this I'm just listen to the episode
I meant David night host
A couple days
No so I jumped the next day that was
Imagine what if we
We did David Knight episode
Would that even work
The audience would Revolt we would lose our walks
Halfway through
Rage Quit like a online video game
Olive Garden
Our will to live
Which is amazing the David Knight hasn't done the same to info
Display
To do a well-trained
I want honest rest
I mean this sincerely
Because
Our last episode that we covered was like on the 11th or the 12th
We're covering January 7th
Don't think of that doesn't mean I still had to listen to 15 hours of Alex Jones for nothing
Covering it all
But it took me
All that time
Get to the 17th of January
And boy was it worth it there a couple things that we're going to find out on this show that are
In terms of
Proving
Fast and Furious that we had about Alex and then Beyonce
He's crazy
Sunday show so he's over
Some soft narrative that's what's about to happen. Especially one of those Sunday shows
Those vets are the audience
Is be smaller and
More engaged audience
Is the refills free
Let er Rip
I think he thinks he's a
That sounds good
In terms of the NFL
He's a little bit of an esoteric preacher especially when he's really really wrong about what
About what we'll find out if
I imagine it is Alex's
Today that's where you point the broadcaster will join
Well we're on the 17th
Right around Superbowl territory
February beginning of February was the Superbowl
Carolina Panthers
Unmanly
That I don't even know who played in the earlier playoff
Today
You did it
Dallas Cowboys
Cool
But you know
When I realize that it's used as a propaganda tool
And that the patriotism
Millions of dollars
Well then I assume you support Colin Kaepernick
Taking a nap
It because the patriotism is clearly paid for
And in fact the government pays the NFL
To pull all that b******* they started doing that around 2065
American Americano
So since he knows that it's just a money-making
Maybe he supports people
But like the other thing about it is like
The idea that he thinks that that's
Some sort of like
Arcane secret thing
These presents
Idea that the government or the military pays to promote the military
Of course
Of course that's advertisement
Haven't you seen the Army commercials
Anybody could see
I don't understand why it's like
How they secretly do that
Classified that's David
Commercials
You guys are screwing everybody commercials
What are the military services
Real athletic
Tone to them
Video game Soldier tone
Yeah it's
It's a different issue that he's complaining about
For those reasons
I'm glad that you can enjoy games
I'm glad
I guess it seemed through the b*******
And now doesn't want
He doesn't get into
Whatever from from dude male vitality
Exactly you know who does that
Demasculinized
One of the more prescient films of our time
Really hate that man
Unlike
Robin Williams in LL Cool J, he thought that that
TV segment was wack
I don't disagree with it
Replace about sports
You makes this revelation
Absolutely no sense
It indicates
Something other than
Enjoyment of sports and sports leagues
Be complaining about
Sports
I get it
No I've been awake
What year was it
The Red Sox finally win the World Series
10 years ago
I was working on a film of the director who was into the Red Sox
And so I started
The office working late and then
World Series
It just took like a month or whatever but
I was calling my wife saying you know I'm sorry I'm going back out to
To watch the Red Sox I mean I get it
Within
They
ESPN
Bombast
Do you have an addictive personality
I've been there
Exactly
I think it was gambling
Behavior is not really
When
They like Cubs were in the World Series
Why would you just randomly there's no reason I mean I know he's hanging out with the Sox fan
Lifelong Texan
Is no reason for him to like the Red Sox
The time that was an amazing team Pedro Martinez
Throw fireballs
Remember
They came back from 3 down to BPM
Monkeys that was
That was pretty much
Bead shop that happened
In my life
What was great
Real bloody Beats
Covered in blood from the roast beef
Okay
My buddy calling
Buns
Is butter the buns and put them in the toaster
You should have switched job now exists Superfund slow on it was always you
He got you decided he was going to make a rap album
Waiting on bond
That's not a little update for good
Cuz I was like
Cardinals
In the series
I like a gamble I like I bet you $100 that the Red Sox win this thing
Nothing I'm sorry about that collected from me if I had lost but
I did not
Or not.
But be that as it may. What else is describing is not normal Sports washer behave
Absolutely that is like I got money on the spread honey I'll be home later I got to I got to watch the game
Yep use my prop bets hit
You have someone in the morning track
I get 20 bucks there's no
You're going wild
Or just like because Sports
Such an excuse
Used to drink
It could be like an alcoholic
Best type of personality that's really all he's revealing their the problem he has with sports
Is the problem he has with him
Sports reporter not the issue here
And that might be why he thinks
Sports takes away people's like
Virility in there
Enthusiasm
Because it does for him
He gets f***** up by him as we have found elsewhere he's a world-class
Yeah that's true
Eastgate movie theater
Your job and put the projectionists
A little bit about science
Okay
That's why he's wrong
And the systems written countless books countless University
Studies white papers
Research studies they had others
Able to get 9 out of 10 or more
People
Subject
Will come up
I did
We're students believed they were killing Subs
Took a week or so
That's not how that works
And most people with the
Kill
Under pressure
From the 40s
Ocean Avenue
Pacifica
And that's what this is all been about
So that's the one that's about the Nuremberg trials
Actually is
Okay sounds good
Is it possible that these people were just following orders
And so what they did is they had it set up where One
Subject
The test subject was in a room with an experiment
How to dial
No
Had a button fairly certain that was the dial one or they had it was like it would turn up every
Turn up the knob knob
How work was Yeti experimenter and you had the subject
And in the other room the Next Room
You had to be
The plant who was working with the
And supposedly another subject of the study
So you and experimenter the role the subject was
To be a teacher
And the this
The other subject in the other room supposed to be the student
And is
Setup has experience
The subject
Would be sitting there
And they would try and get
The other person in the other room
Guess a word based on another word
There was a word game they were playing
And whenever they got an answer wrong they were supposed to shock the other per
Now
The experimenter turn up the volume
And if the person who was the subject of the study who's asking
Questions
Teacher
If they said to the experimenter I don't think we should do this
They would rub them for time
And if they made it past the fourth rebuttal the experiment would end
That was the whole idea to see how much people would push back against party
And they did find that most people very unhappy went along with it right the other way the experiment ended was
You did up to 450 V which is enough to
Theoretically
They were told it was enough to kill regardless Central piece
Experiment misrepresenting
I mean 65 V
It's not electricity
Not about voltage
It's about current
When it comes down
Electricity
And it also comes down
To like you have a wound
Skin is a really good conductor
For the most part of electricity but if you have
Cut or something like that
Is going
It's going to be a disaster
It's not
DD works together being like
Kill this man
Or something like that
What they learned was pretty shocking
Here's the other most important piece and Alex
Cuz not talkin about
The Milgram experiment
It is historically seen as not that great of experiment
Here's why
Every road was dude
Yeah
No s***
Well I mean if your Ridgeway was all do
If you are going to test that as a Nuremberg Trial
Situation though
Not a lot of nuts
Female Soldier
In that regard
Was it was at the
The time
Military
All dude
Except for the Russian military cuz they
Needed everybody
But yeah right but you can't experiment goes
I don't think he is
Misrepresenting it and getting a lot of details wrong
But based on what he is saying
I think he
He's got the spirit of what he's trying to take her
Which is that it's weird that people would be willing to murder
Because of
If that's all he's trying to say in the first set of experiments 65 Briggs
26 out of the 40 experiment
Participant
65%
Do you vote shock
Though many were very uncomfortable doing so
At some point
Participant paused in question
The experiment some said they would refund the money they're paid
Participating
Throughout the experiment subjects display varying degrees
Stressed subjects were sweating trembling stuttering biting their lips groaning their fingernails into their skin
Nervous laughter
Yeah it's a relief
I'm passing he does mention
That he also brings up another super f***** up one
There there
They are described
Less as experiments and more as kind of philosophical question
And
The Stanford Prison Experiment
Is a
If it were
If the strictures of the experiment were applied elsewhere
It would be immediately invalidate
No no biological science know any of science any of the hard science
Would ever accept those
Rules as well as a valid experience more or less anecdotal in nature
Still
It is
The Stanford Prison Experiment
You can still draw some
Conclusions from that but you can't draw conclusions
You can just notice
Hey human beings are f***** up
You know what they almost are
They almost are good ways to inoculate people from that behavior
You're in the future
Quote experiment
It's they're done the demonstrated point
Can see it Illustrated in real-time though like I hope I wouldn't do that
More aware of the influence
Authority figures or in the case of the prison
Experiment
They're more aware of the idea of US versus them mentality is a Breakout
Artificially it just naturally wherever
Well and the old the only problem with that though is
It doesn't seem to matter you know we have a very good experiment about how Nazism works
Apparently people are still fine with it
Yeah that's
That's really true
Oh well really interesting studies
Again because they are invalid
There's a note just by the very fact
Being you being aware that is
Experiment
And you're being paid means that you're you know like if I'm in that situation
With a
An experiment
Bababababa
There's also the part of your brain that goes
Well there's no way they would allow me to kill
So there is a artificial
Whatever
That's f***** up
You want to go back to the f****** Tuskegee experiment they're fine with killing people
Yeah that's true
That was back when science was more of like a
Somebody go f****** whatever
Is wrong about
He's writing a small sentence wrong in a big sentence about these
Experiment as it so often the case when we say he is right
Is generally speaking a very very small
F****** fool you okay
The history of reading
Brain magazine
In different Publications that work
Ugly
Beautiful
Destroy the discrimination
Factors in the brain between what is good and what is that
Brainy Publications
I came to I don't know if you guys remember that one go back to the March 30th episode
For that sucking
Super fun time
So his idea
So as he understands
The cia's plan
Yeah it is to
Put out
Right
Credit good
Yes
That
Is a great CIA plant
And I would have fun tomorrow
The idea of like hard what is beautiful in
What is ugly
Anecdotes
I actually just let a monkey paint piss and it sold for a million dollars
What are you what are you talkin about going to discredit our
The art world is already fabricated
There's a truth
To some of this
The CIA did
Help promote people like Jackson
Kampala Mark rothko in Willem de kooning
Diesel abstract expressionism
Back
In their time
They did and it was a
Piece of the Cold War strategy
Okay
The Cold War The Artist
I'm reading here from an article in open culture about this the artists themselves were completely unaware that their work was
Being used as propaganda
On what age is called a
They participated in several exhibitions secretly organized by the CIA
Such as the new American Paint
Which visit European cities
And included the stuff
Modern primitive works
The surrealist
William
Basquiat
A 1951
By Adolf Gottlieb
And 1984
Super f***** up painting
Like a Bazaar
Okay
Next question
And this is very serious
What's the CIA behind the data
They were behind row Coco
So the idea that what they were doing
Is
You have this art
And it's not really
Casein is all that great over here
But you have people in Russia
Gore used to
Very conch
Play because
And there
Totalitarian
Berber control over Arts
So you had basic
Sickly the art that was approved is like
Realistic paintings of Stalin
Like that that's what flies over there
Promotion in Europe
This
Very bizarre American art is going to lead to
Positive America
Because they're going to see America is
Avant-garde
I got to try to be so different from what they're used to
That is the strategy that the CIA was employing as a way of culturally piercing the Soviet Union
Okay
Is what they were doing has nothing to do with trying to warp the minds of good and bad and
If the CIA was exporting Super Mario Brothers to North Korea right now
Yes
Sometimes I wish we could go back to
Cold War the stories of what the CIA did during the Cold War
And how they had
So little oversight
All of theirs
All of their plans were we're Rube Goldberg machine
Expense
Aztec how silly they were
So much rooting through garbage and like
Okay what if we implant this thing inside a mouse
It's a little recording device
And maybe the mouse will go into the boardroom and windows
What is this are you guys mad scientist
Happening
Action of desperation and like
Early technology
The military-industrial complex run-amok
Technology
And then you add lack of oversight
Because of Desperate Times
The real
Severe
We could argue all day about whether that was
Overblown
The fears that we had about the Soviet Union back then
Uno's
Is all imaginary
Not gotten what I would call close calls we had with the nuclear warfare destroying the Earth
Here's a really good but those fears should have been more toward
Okay wait so we're giving nuclear weapons
To a bunch of
And we are a bunch of idiots
Nuclear weapons through a bunch of idiots
They leave like 5
Documented Indie classes
Defied
Instances of like one dude coming down
Press the button or not
A couple but
Assume that it's more than I'm aware of
Just died in
Yeah
The Russian guy who against all orders from a superior
It was like
Save the world. Never allowed
Speak of it
That's what happens
We've not got into today's being yet
Behold episode
Football
No restarted
The Reds
No
Lose a lot of money
He's betting against the spread stupid
A bad idea
Basketball
He has
A very bizarre
Lead us through most of the rest of the
Episode and boy
Strap it in
Real
Yes
We're going to end up
Where does it say that in the Bible
Say that many of my Christian list
Viewers get extremely angry
Yep
Someone disagrees with
About something
The deity of Jesus Christ
You got a problem with it become a Pharisee
If you want to believe
Your business
I don't think
You have been
Grievously
Bible
Very excited about that next hour
Does he not get the irony of him
Somebody disagrees with
About everything
You got a problem which implies that if you have a disagreement about the Trinity or Jesus is Divinity then that's not a problem
Also
Does it say in the Bible do they ever talk about the Holy Spirit
A ghost is in there come on.
I don't know I don't unpack that
I don't know if you guys have no I have heard
Interesting might have a problem
Well we don't disagree on the Holy Trinity by like the most best bibles if you look at number of verses
Especially
I kind of just
Count most of the old.
Jesus
Arrival
Sacrifice invalidates
Frank creates a new cover
And yet somehow we're still listening to people tell us about the Old Testament
With all due respect to the Jewish Folk
Do have a lot of the old
In their in their holy books
But it should just be historical
And not because of Jesus literal because of matter all because of Jesus
So did the things that I really resonate with
Bible if you want to talk about it
It is Jesus being
The Rockin that that that sort of idea
Says things
To be effective you will do what I do and greater
Difference in Houston
If you look at it that way
The idea that Jesus is
Is God
That sort of divinity within him is the Divinity that
It's within all of us
I can buy bond that
If you want a Vibe I can Vibe on that
You can't though
Because Christians do not believe
Too busy talking about the Wrath of the Ulta
Alex
I'm very
This episode
F****** bent out of shape about the rapture
Furious
And I think what has happened in the in the Pro or the con
He thinks the Raptors real rhino
Oh he thinks
The pre-tribulation rapture
Alright
Let's get into this I want to dive in here I don't know if you've been paying attention
But throughout the last like
Baby
1012 episode
There's been a guy who key
Keeps calling in
Yeah there's a guy who keeps
Keeps calling into Alex's show
When trying to explain the pre
Tribulation
Keeps like telling about I want to have this device called
Voices like I will talk to you later
And I think this guy has finally gotten to Alec
Cuz get on the show spent almost the entire time talking about how stupid pre-trib
Rapture is
Great
Find me up for that as well
Ovulation Rapture is
So Alex Belize post-tribulation
And that's because somehow
Even dumber
What's because in the Bible or at least in Alex isn't
Interpretation of Revelation
And I guess
Video
Somebody prophetic books of the Bible
He believes that they're all right
The Antichrist comes
Yes and leaves us to real bad time
Real bummer almost as bad as Trump
Dude really worse
So we go through that lot of the world dies out
Amman God comes back
In the battle of Armageddon
Exactly
How to lose a lot of money
You got Jesus and the field
I'm not going to take the field not going to gamble in Armageddon
And he's Furious that I think a lot of his listeners
Are trying to convince him of the pre-tribulation Rapture in the Antichrist comes
The faithful go to heaven if they don't doubt this whole trouble
Write the troubles as it were
He's mad because
Alex believe
That
Is a globalist
Yes I wish
I wish I wasn't all right I wish I wish I was joking I wish I was just like a good bit
It's not
I think you spelled it out in this next clip and I'll just play this and we can discuss it on the other end
God would protect
Providence
But you have to go through the fire first
Until dawn
Like the Christians
Take action
Spread
A billion Christians
And do not be involved and let the devil take over the world
That is
Crises and Evil on this planet that they should just
Lucky 13
Out of context
So
Alex believe
This interpretation
The pre-tribulation rapture
Is something that is being taught in the
Glitterbug churches in what have you as a way of taking away the
Activism and power of the billion Christian
They could be fighting the devil
If you devil and eat the does imply that it's the globalist or doing this
He got a caller calls in all of the world religion
Like Islam Buddhism Christianity they all met in Seoul Korea
Seoul Korea South Korea conversation
All these religions came together and decided that ended
Comedy of it is
This color is listed off the religious we like Christianity Islam Buddhism Alex
You guys keep going
Worship in the trees or whatever
Shintoism
Very very small population but I love the idea
Throwing something
Myself sound smart
I've never read the gospel
Like the synoptic Gospels
Happy birthday Ken Jeong
Word hey
Let's not
Fight
Assholes
Turn the other cheek
Slade
Yeah you have them read the book of Romans 13 and maybe go back in if you just refer
Pressure course it's really actually pretty f***** up because it is
You should submit to your rulers
Because their representatives of God
It's one of the reasons it's one of the
That they've used for
Slavery
Over many many years
Further Authority is God's servant for your good if you do wrong
The sword for no reason
They are God's servants
Crafts to bring punished
Turn on the wrong door
Therefore it's necessary
To submit to Authority
Not because of possible
Also as a matter of
Next paragraph deals with that give everyone what you owe them
If you owe taxes pay taxes
Is revenues and revving
Respect respect
If honor than honor
It's almost as though
Is written by somebody
Vested interest
Maintaining power
Crazy
Wild asparagus
To all the Commandments
Can be summed up in the one command love thy neighbor as yourself
Love does no harm to a neighbor
Therefore love is.
Fulfillment of the law
Great
Part about it
Starting at verse 11
Understanding the present time the hour has already come for you to wake up from your slumber
Because our Salvation is
Is nearer now than when we first believed
Which
Is altruism
If there is an end eventually
Then right now
Sooner than it was earlier
The night is nearly over the day is almost here so let us put aside the Deeds of Darkness
Put on the armor of light
Let us behave decently as in the daytime not a rousing and drunkenness not
Sexual immorality and debauchery
Not into sentient
Jealousy rather close yourselves with the Lord
Jesus Christ
And do not think about how to gratify the
Desires of the flesh
Almost counterintuitive
The night is coming tonight is almost over and
And the day is almost here
Means I should go f*** as much as I want
Cuz the nights about.
I got to go to work
Something's coming
Practice
Being good
Piano easy the first time
We got to practice being decent
Or something
I don't understand exactly how that Passage
Does weaponized outside of
Literally
Interpreting it as
Submissive Authority
Yeah which is their events in your holy book
So
Deal with it
Deal with it that's not a Miss that's not misrepresentation what that mean
Nope it's
Actually literally what
Salsa
Don't think so
Is the mark of the beast real Jordan
Maybe your headphone
Is your headphones off
At this point
Do you believe them
World where to live in
Under the sea
Everything everything
Distorted
A false reality
Sports in our consciousness
Even the elect
The modern
Antichrist system
Thomas in my life
Still
Academically
Boy I tell you it is bone-chilling
It's not
Very bones
Alex is on his tip
Is that you
He's worked up about the Revel Revelation in biblical prophecy coming
Beyond that later he does sort of spell out what the world is going to look like in of course
It's just
And then I'll be on that key
The other thing is
Just
He reveals that like
Anna
Yep that's not that's not great
That's the way it's supposed
Yeah after this point
Alex is a mother
Now we got to talk
Thank you
Look up a genetic engineering
Look at the elites
Brown inside cows
Logan
Can I look at
I just thought of something
Responsibility
You going to get
Just like Planned Parenthood infiltration
They are committing crime
I know that I don't
Nope you guys.
Cuz they're not
Mor Furniture
Helen Clark keeping babies alive for harvesting
No
Physician retired and I remember
Dentist
Going to get my driver's license
We're back to the story as but I do want
Just take a second before we move on cuz there's another minute of this clip
I do want Alex to go save those kind
I agree that would be the best
TruTV show ever
Absolutely make a make another season of Jesse Ventura
Instead of Ghost Hunters Chimera go to Bastrop
Alex Jones dad being a f****** weirdo
My hardship license because I have a job in a small animal vet
This one is picked out of school
Don't
I would say Dad
I would say why would you say that
Here's why
Drug addicts
It came out with Jon rappoport
Pretty well debunked
No this is what we talked about that yeah
Dentist father wonder he's f***** up his
Only affected black people a race specific bioweapons
Who's getting more
Is because the applicant the way people use drugs
Come up with are so much more complicated than the reality
Season if you share blood with somebody
You're going to get the disease
But be that as it may.
That's crazy the response
To Alex's like hey why shouldn't I sign my organ donor card
Is even Wild
Hold on
What if we look at all of this
As just
Alex Jones
Dad
Was f****** with his son I don't think is working with
You think he's nuts
Forget the front
Sure
People listen to it
Alex Jones is the CIA
Yeah
Like
It was just dads
Dinner table talk
The hospital for your organs
What is your printer
So now we know where Alex do we know where Alex gets that
My dad didn't think it was important to
Prove the claim that he's making that are wild
Clear
I mean
Much greater understanding
The science can debunk all the
Just for you if you want to go look
Go to Jon rappoport site
Thanks for
That helps
And then you'd be like
No that's
Dumb also
This Chimera ship
Is wild
Because it is just a
Like the article just
Scream out
Human human chimeras are
Gestating on Animal Farms
Google headlines
And what have you
He's going to ramble about it
For a little bit here and it goes
To some crazy places
It's just
Something like this
Human-animal chimeras
Gestating on Research Farm
Is it
Is it is it
Why
That board
Fast forward
So now let's pause right there and discuss the science of this
I think Alex Alex think
The only reason our our organs aren't Biggers cuz we don't have enough room
Okay
Alright I can't do that
They want to put human organs in the couch because cows have more space
You want to do.
Maybe that was a design flaw with god with God's plan in the first place if he knew we were going to drink so much
Ezekiel now that's your pre-trib rapture right there
I think there's some comedy some value in
That being said right after the HIV is a race specific Style
We want to use these human animal chimera
The question
Exactly
Sperm whale and they're still mammals we could get us
Liver the size of your f****** whole body
Exactly I love how you always obviously review
Sing by saying he's not doing
Listen and I'm not bragging
Exact same thing over and over again hundred articles but I only talk about this one ever
What a dick
I was reporting on this out of white paper
It was 10 years old
That's when they admitted it
Takeoff
Cheap
And go to the part spider in that they
I said okay
I should know you're a liar
But yeah I did
Which is why I know that when you go
I just so you better get out of my
Coveralls
Been in hundreds of Publications
That
Time
I have the CEO on
My show
Running program
The first of all spider goats are real but also I do love just the way he says that's it
The
Video with running an apartment with the goats
The goat for the employees reading the Department of Defense or whatever
Leadership
Is another question another population between the leadership
Crossbreed
What leadership is not accepted
Chords back in the day
Yeah but if they could go discontent together
I got to do
That's what I can't deal with
The emergency centers establishment Act
The civilian inmate labor camp program
Is it
FEMA camp
It's all for political dissenters
Well if you if you would like to recall that episode where we did the the
The
The speed lightning round and discuss all of those FEMA
Alex
Just making stuff
Very much
Except for the civilian labor camps
We have a private prison
Industry in our country that is enslaving
Rexall
If you
If you want to talk about both
I support it
Going to talk about one not the other
Talk about the private prison
More big deal
Now
But wait dan private
Absolutely oversight
No regulations
What they should do is give those civilian inmates
Totally
I don't know where we're talking about anymore
In a little bit
There's some more thought rest in peace Malcolm Young thoughts about the devil and about the rapture
But this next
Clip
This is Mike down clip
Alex Jones
Make like
This next clip
Is basically like
I have been looking for this clip
4A
So you falling in love
No
I found a woman that you want to marry
No no
Something like this
Come out of Alex's mom
Can you deliver
Desk lamp
Is so f***
In hindsight knowing what we know now
About the Russian
Influencer campaigns that we're running from the summer
Of 15
6 months later
Listen to this
And Obama gets up on TV and says everything's fine
Everything's wonderful. Wonderful
Ladies and gentlemen
I meant on your 21 years
Volume level one.
Profits went up to find the op
Double the last 6 months
Fastest growth rate
We got so many Lester's that makes my head spin
And profits are flat
Even finally operation
That's why we know this is serious fact
Scotland
Purchase high-quality products
Delta
Our voices
Then ever
Oh s***
Oh s*** idiot
First of all nights at pivot
He just revealed that
They've doubled
I guess that must be the economy that must mean that Obama is lying about all these statistics that pee
People are putting out about the
Boxer listening to the show.
There's not a
There's not a chance
In my mind
B on some subconscious level
Buy now 2017
Alex knows
God damn well that's what he
Really he has to
I think that's why he's fighting so hard now trying to make the Russian stuff
Casinos
I have been a
Is evident
No
But it's obvious
Right it's like
I don't know how to come up with a good analogy about that but
Apex it it's like
Alex talking to his hypothetical friend got tricked by the Nigerian
I'm going to make a lot of money
There's nothing there
Alex is talking and playing like we have gotten
Weis the listeners in the last six months as we had before
But no one's buying anything
We can hear that and we're like
Oh dude
We literally know exactly what happened
And that that to me
That's that
Game over game over on his
First of all his audience size secondarily
That he was not being
Specifically Target
Biopsies Russian
Royal Farms
Yeah been compromised by Russia in
So many ways
You've revealed it all on your own and all we had to do to figure it out was paying attention to your dumbass
Wow
Congratulations
Now look at BuzzFeed
What an idiot you have to be like if we saw a doubling of our numbers
Buttercream
What and that's why it's so easy to Hoodwink him like that cuz he expects
Of course my listeners double because I'm right and of our listeners double would be like
Listen to this God damn show
His version of it is
Finally people are waking up and thank God I've been doing this work all the time
Coming home
What have you robots
What a f****** idiot
I love it when I heard that
Nailed it
Cuz every other time it's been very
Nonspecific and he just said that the numbers have gone up
In that time
Yeah but the fact that he's
The numbers are going up
Sales
What exponentially the numbers have gone up sales
Have stayed exactly the same he's right those two numbers and think something is up the wrong thing
And now we know he knows
Now we know he knows exactly what happened
Cuz he and he hasn't revealed that
Pinterest
How would how old how do you think
His listeners would respond
If they
New exactly
What was going on
If I don't
You just learn
That
A hostile foreign power
Who's artist
Officially inflated the influence of an Alex
Different right-wing thing
Exactly how would you take
The Russians are right
Because Alex has the built-in narrative that Russia are the good guys and what I do look at it as I
Really trying to help the patriots and that's the way they thought it was best to it profile the one guy telling the truth in the
This country
And they could save us
Through working
Sing with Russia
Call Trump elected
That's probably what they would say
And the fact that Alex like at this point
In the beginning of 26
Clearly oblivious
Because I
I can kind of tell when he is
Goodies such a bad liar.
He seems like he's like why are all these people listening and not also buying
Restart to seize
Search hard desperate pivot towards sales yeah I'm really ramp up the commercial
Clothes and stuff like that
Yep there's that
Area of a circle
Them
Then we'd be
Enrolling and not realizing
Wow
You do it like
Before but you really have to give it up to the Russian
That was a brilliant
You don't have to give it up to them
Give It Up
To the I mean like
One of the main reasons that it works
Nobody saw it coming
Nobody saw this massive
Media landscape
No
This is one thing where America doesn't have the same
No I don't know I have no idea but what I would say is
It would work
Work
I think it was a very very
Good strategy and it was
Like if you are if you're fighting a war on a battlefield that you can't win
Choose a different Battlefield
That's all that they did know they can't do any number of propaganda things
The same way that we
They know they can't fight us
Physically they know they can't do
Chose the one spot where they were like
Here's a flaw in this
We can dance on this
Memory as hard as we can as it was brilliant
Useful idiot
Congratulations Alex
Nicely done now let's get back to the
There is an attack on humans
A political global system eugenics
Comes to kill steal and destroy
And behave
Joseph Campbell Whole Nine Yards
I've experienced
Providence
Many things that are private
I can tell you what's real
I've interviewed many people are
Expect
10 minutes
Beyond
Genevieve
Christian
Amaya found that
The
Phenomenon
McDonald's
Judgment
What people say
Is after they die
Mission liquor
The future
Sophisticated
Quantum mechanics
Hold on
Thousand Years Five Hundred Years 20 years
Post-tribulation rapture
People having the death experience
They're going in
Incredible
Once you figure all this out
Sacred geometry
No it's not the Bible says
The proof of God
Design
God's creation
We can do
Level stop
It's very
Living and non-living
Again how
We experienced what
Chepachet memories
Stop same thing
Who are children genetically as well not really built
What we do lives on
Striploin
By the way
By the way Infowars is doing
We're not in financial trouble
Talk radio
And other media.
It's stuff
Shirt
It's script
Starpoint
In the face
Responsibility
I really try to get as big as possible
What were you trying to do before
15 to 16 million people
Deaf people
The ruins
Is killing
So I really want to be able to continue
Infowarsstore.com
I wanted to keep that part at the end they are in
Because it is
Drinking the Kool-Aid about these new listeners
Wii maker
What the f*** is going on
He is out there
He is out there so I've never heard I do understand
Mechanics you'll realize that when people die for 10 minutes
Yuma golden gates and the judgment is real but it's totally real
Angry Birds post-death judgment that you go through is real
Albert Brooks
It's like the movie flatliners
Defending Your Life it's much better movie
I am
Flabbergasted
I f****** love it anytime somebody like him says quantum mechanics you can already tuned out
Nope nope you got nothing back, right the pronunciation
Quantum cuz you're just going to hurt yourself with that
Awesome
For me it's like okay
He starts that clip by saying the debate about the devil is over as far as I'm concerned
Okay
Then all that stuff about you know Joseph Campbell all these cultures and
CPR
These cultures they've
Michonne
Judgment and all that
Science has shown
The when you die
Your Consciousness goes forward to the post-tribulation rapture
You know it's real because when God said what
16 MI
He said look around
And then of course it comes back to Ed's it's just like what is going on he's a losing it there's just this like
Ratably
Like
This
Point
He's soaking
Confused
What what do you say to somebody saying stuff like
Well I don't even mean about that
You should be saying is on there that's
Read up on sacred geometry
Blogs about it
Spiritualism and stuff like that
I feel so weird about it
But I would never tell you what I know I would never sit here and be like oh yeah
Dudedad like list off specifics
He needs to be less
Specific that bilgrami
Experiment Milgram or talk about the electric shocks or whatever
I can't
Disprove that
That I can disprove
He's too specific here
This is what crazy people do
Island is a crazy person
This isn't religion
Former Department of Defense psychiatrist
Who have become Christian
Officially proven was probably pechanec that the Golden Gate
I did not know that
Does he has a state psychiatry
Right
That's the only person I know of it that qualification
I don't know just cuz the name
Okay so does he think that the hurricane
Through happened because I got to buy the father's Jewish cuz he lives in Florida
There might be a bias on my part and I apologize for
I don't know anything about his life
Population Florida
So let's in this one Alex is talking about how the Chinese have
I decided they're going to start a new program
Where they have
People do the golden
Smoke now. Quite they have a Facebook
People and you'll get a social credit score
It was an idea that they were throwing around I don't think
Great Black Mirror
Basically
When the next two years
Political
Possible
Social media
Social credit score
Before he gets through not a good global
Can't buy or sell mark of the beast
Before he gets into talking about how like everyone go
Going to do this and they're going to think
It's cool
They had a one-child policy for a really long time
Salt Lake
Works perfectly and everybody
Oppressiveness in chili kit
China this is not surprising to come of these ideas
Be coming out of a pretty authoritarian state
Doesn't
The restaurant is not going to be
No
Good episode
If you do you get lower prices
Now it's pure pressure
How is your friends aren't good communist
You don't get a good social score
So now you stun them together
BBC China social credit
What he's describing is the current credit system we have now and it's only it's only incredibly offensive to Black
People in minorities and end the life
There's a threat of that
What is only hurts minorities
The other something to that let's get together this club cuz it takes a Twist you're not going
What's described in Revelations
Whether or not
Cosmology
Selfish truth
But I don't want to be associated with the establishment
Pharisee
State-run churches that are 501 c 3
Now even got it right to their credit
Does chilling plan
Do you social credit rating
Human soul
Sometimes I tell the truth and amazing
Sup
So now he also knows that
Yeah either where of that knows that Artie is run by the FSB
Purple
CIA agents tell it they're not good at running
They do but different job
With the contact that they
Indicate
A clear awareness that Alex knows that Artie is run by Russia
Outlet
For propaganda last episode
A bunch of times.
What does that say Alec
What does that say
You dumbass
Dumb dumb
Prick he's like he's like
Movie Avatar
Like
Come to us from the cognitive dissonance
Planet
In the same way that Jon Hamm
Is an alien who
Stardust what true hands
This really is
So is Alex teaching as what true cognitive
Can do to a purse
It just baffles me the way that he reveals
These things
Like
He thinks it all make
Since it's a wife wouldn't tell it to you
That's that mild schizophrenia the ordered worldview that he has
Luso
Worked everything
Despite the fact that it contradicts
Itself at every turn
MC and this is the other stuff where we're talking about him being a performance artist
But this is he actually believes
Yes this is real shity beliefs tribulation Rapture that your brain goes to
Do when you die
If you die before the tribulation
Yeah it may this is not like
This isn't
In the strictest sense this isn't
Propaganda
This is why this is a lute
Is what it is this is what we've all thought Alex Jones
For the longest time it's f***** up is it like he can have
That half of his audience that are robots
Are there like this
Just fun
That's true actually I've been working on it.
I think that I don't believe
You can find Alex Jones
Funny unless you subconsciously agree with him
I don't I don't believe nothing
Possibility
Some people
Former AJ's
I know people who are like
Island
F****** hilarious man
Or you agree with him and you don't want to admit you agree with him because then
Do you look like
Oh really you want this
Everyone knows that's too hard you don't f******
I Love Lucy I think
It's hilarious when Alex Jones
In flames
Anti-semitism
And everybody but white people believe
I think it's hilarious
All the time we do laugh a s*** ton of
Colors that but it's in a different we laugh a different laugh
1 filter
Rage revelation of what
Actually talking about
Back to the Rapture being
A handle
Text clip
Enjoy
You can read
John the Revelator on the Isle of Patmos
The Beach Boys war against the Saints and will overcome they'll be there
Great falling away before with greatest
The God ever
The whole world turns against the baseboard more
Population
Columns of flame
Mountains
Huge metal insects
Huge wall
Russia and the Middle East huge compensation
That's what they called
Themselves
Then Christ comes back
Five-year-old
But yourself
That's true
Because the last year the World Council of churches
Globalized
Christian faith
Dogmas that were not known in Christianity ever
In the forties
Christian didn't resist Hitler
Thought
It was the end of the world they thought he was
In the 27th
American Christians
Didn't resist
Hitler supported
And your preachers wrong
Pre-tribulation Rapture I'm not saying he's a false teacher
You are
Fair enough
But yes
I mean it's imaginary arguments to argue against your argument is probably right
Weird for us to sit here and have him
Be like the post
Versus pre-tribulation Rapture I don't care
Why are we doing it I think what we're doing is a weenie
It's important that our audience
Knows that he spends a lot of time on stuff like that right
Because it is like
There is way too much
Super Focus
In the manger
Stream I believe the coverage of Alex Jones on
I mean there are important issues the is hucksterism is is
Desperate salesmanship and rap
It support of trump
Those are two things are important
It's to him but he's religion
Which is not Christianity
Big picture of who he is
As a broadcaster
Right
Sunday show man
It's not that we're like
Alex blazing post-trib let's just for the pre-trip for fun
What cuz it's f****** Wild
So now I'll do want you to argue for the pre-trip
Course heaven before
That was a lot of fun
That's very that's a very dickish God
They'll be like
Why would God put anybody through any
5 to make them
Stronger
Walmart clip here Alex
Is bucket like in this clip I think
We get the revelation
That
I got it
This whole day's show
Okay we're all of this comes
From this day of just rambling about the the Revelation tribulation and what have you
Think it's because someone
Bothering him
And then he Rambles on for a while about
I'm not on some high horse but if I get lectured one more time
Miles French
So real and files
I know my heart's right where's yours
Icpj
I don't know where
You know what you're doing
Almost
Midwest by Concha
Even studying the enemy
I wonder why that is
I just saw the great evil is upon us
254 the decades coming forward
Get maybe 50 years 100
Tommy's
We could get a reprieve
But because Jonah didn't want to go
Seems very arbitrary
Archaeology
Archaeology shows in haven't approved Jonah was in awhile and have
God gave them 100-year rest
What's this doing in the fossil record
The reason that this is important
I left
Blue kind of rambling and nonsensical but
This is the beginning of a narrative that will be
Become very important
In his support of trump
Let me so you could argue that this is a softball
I got some ways
This idea of a reprieve
Like Nineveh
He uses those
Pacific languages
About Trump
Trump is that reprieve
Has God given us a
To get out from under these globulus
Got you
Get further makes it more robust
Extended metaphor
That what Trump is allowing us to do is get our head above water and take a breath
Before we have to go and fight this
Shark I guess
I'm not entirely sure where works in the metaphor this is the first time that he has used that metaphor
In the contacts
Like the globalist and what we are
Right we're doing moving forward and he will co-opt it from this religious
Perspective
Entrepreneur
People God's sure are we
If they appreciate this
Status
That's a God who who's not paying attention
That's a God who checked out
I'll tell you that right now it's not buying caveman
That's where all the ad that's what the traffic coming from. Didn't have any dollars
God's God got his own holy Bop Farm
Bought
He knows that Artie is a propaganda outlet and it showed bickering about the revelation
And our various forms of the rapture
And doing that whole game where he's like a if you believe in a pre-tribulation
Preachers not
Nesco was involved
I want
They sound a lot like collaborators to me
Pick a side if you're Pizarro nonsense
God I want it
See now I want him
I just quit Broadcasting
Write your own holy book
You get a look at f****** Joseph Smith can get a worldwide religion f*** you Alex Jones in ism
People would do that s***
I just don't think you could write a coherent thread I think you need a Ghostwriter
Alex
We are available
Website.com
I'll try to gmail.com. Your holy book Alex
Mileage underscore fight Alex and like I said there's a lot of
Writing contests
Also your blog every Thursday and there will be little pieces
What the f*** Alex Jones to talk about that day if you can help boost them out there and would help a great deal
You could also go to
It's true that's where our podcast
You can leave a review
Give us some Stars preferably five
OSHA
What
So we know about
Sing
That Alex Jones
One other guy believes in
Oh s***
These guys even hang up pictures
No
What f****** person would believe in do both of those
Ice-T
No reason
Monopoly
Jon rappoport is Alex Jones
Oh s*** now think about this
The teeth
Come into play
No
Is a dentist
Bits of depression he's knocked out all of his teeth and that's why he needs dentures
Okay okay alright
Oh no
Anybody need a replacement Daddy
Alex's dad wants to live forever
How do you live forever
You download your consciousness
Into some faulty Trace memory
Exact
And then implant those teeth
Into John rapping
That's probably what happened
John Rappaport I invite you to go fuc yourself
Alex