Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Hey everybody welcome back to knowledge
Doesn't talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Seest of beverages direct old style old style cuz we need it buddy we
We need it today is a weird day this bucket where I know a lot about Alex
That's our Dynamic that's how we like to have fun
Clearly dance got
S*** to say cuz you ran through that bet real fast I want to talk about Survivor series
No I do not really
I do got a lot to talk about it a little bit
Pre-show a lot of shows have
Okay here's what we're going to talk about today
Know about Kevin Owens f***
MSNBC will be cancelled
Immediately boilers
Past wrestling pay-per-views
Have we considered killing all white
Well we're going to get to that later
I'm going to guess it does in a very interesting way
Covering the November 20th 2017 episode of The Alex Jones Show
As we're recording this
You can always
There's trouble
I don't know how else to put it
Yeah
Incredibly shocking
About today's episode
You're going
To be as mad
If you've ever been
Is a
Predict
I want to
Year that we've been doing this podcast
I think I've got some stuff in here especially once we get into
What the reality of what they're talking about okay but
I just asked you in
Courtesy to my network
It's been I've just been reserved
Furious
That's not true
For me I feel like I said
I know exactly how much you were yelling
I have a hard time with
Yeah that's fair
The episode of
Be trouble
I'm so to start things off I have an out-of-context drop that is delightful
He's not wrong and Alexandra together
Coming out of break just Eastbound & Down
Subhuman moment now
We are going to only descend from that High Point into hell
Yes indeed because I will tell you this
Listen to text message
Between you and I are earlier today a lot of the show
Put on today was
In reaction
To the death
Charles
That's why I said I'm sure it has something to do with race
Yes
The biggest part of the race war
Stuff
There's another Charles Manson not the biggest or the race worse
I had a stretch where I was actually very interested
Boy howdy
Yeah
He was really afraid of black
You have a lot of awareness
Yes I know it's about Charles Manson
Well for this episode of him but I will be the first to admit that I've never
Doncic deep dive
A couple book
Documentaries
Human beings Leverage
When you have more expertise and thankfully that is
It's because
Alex has a narrative
Dell and let's start
No it's start with how he wants to get things going how you going to present
The death of Charles
I've already
Also this is the music that's playing is the cover of Helter Skelter a little bit
He couldn't get the right to Helter Skelter on this one
2017 well Charlie Manson
Also spoiler guys
But I have 100% at the drums on Helter Skelter on expert on Roxanne field
I realize that's a lie
Actually you were telling the truth
You don't mean to brag I got gold stars on it I did not in hundred percent
In the interest of honesty
Is in the chat
It was really weird crazy that somebody
Running around
Beauty queen 70s Villas
Coffee baroness
It was a big big deal
Everybody's crazy
That is a Charles Manson paraphrase
This is the Godfather of the antifa movement
What is a Godfather
Abba modern environmental movement
This is a man that wanted 90%
On the world's population to be exterminated by a world government
Who's wanted to ignite
Different religious groups against each other
Concord strategy
Level CIA
Control program
The highest levels of rock and roll
Movies he knew all the major folks co-wrote songs
The list goes on and on
California on drugs
Devin the Dude door was ordered to carry out the murder
We don't know still this day
Sure.
100%
What is your immediate reaction to to that
Reaction
It was very obvious not not in favor
Okay
Not try ends
Cuz erase work
He was paranoid and terrified
And one of the main things that he did was he use that paranoid
To control the people in
Inside of his car
Wouldn't allow them to escape he wouldn't allow them to go anywhere
By stoking their fears that they would be killed if they went
The other thing
Was not co-write any of the Beach Boys
However
One of the Beast
F****** sorry we had to do with why they ended up breaking up
Hung out with one of the Beach Boys was not because
They were friends
Because
Sex
Yeah those drugs for some people
I just want to be right
What's his f*** I don't remember which beachway it was that an Wilson it was not Brian Wilson
David Jones
David Wilson just hung out at the place because
Charles Manson
Through women at him under a wonder if Alex wants to talk about that
Think he does
Yeah it was a sex called for David Wilson and he did that part of the reason that he had the
The call was just so he could get more people for David Wilson Ave sex was in the correction
Correction from the
Okay alright
Could I have that I run into all the time is the length that Alex will go to
Excuse white violence
It's astounding to me that every time there's a white person
It has to be some sort of a
INR CIA operation gone wrong or something like that
It's never that they actually wanted to kill beep
It's never that they actually had malice evil or anything in their hearts
It's always someone else's fault
Dennis Wilson not David Wilson
David Wilson was a guy who ran a film festival in Vikings come out and was not involved.
Azurite that is
You're doing that
Whatever that was I got going on is I know that this is going to make you so mad that I'm trying to
No I'm just trying to be like
I'm going to have my fun I got you
That's fine I will try and play off of that
Owen Wilson
Drillbit Taylor
Luke would never been involved
All of the best songs on pets that's true
And future man
Andrew Wilson bottle rocket
And of course
Best character in
Any film
In history
No
Volleyball
Wilson
Talk more about future
What's
Future man is which ones that do you was the guy who they lived with
BottleRock
I'm not going to lie to you
Never saw a bottle rocket
Yellow jumpsuit on
Future man pulls up
Makes fun of them
Little banana
One of the funniest lines
Cuz afterwards after he drives Leon Wilson like
Anyway rocket talk
Okay brother was a
But movie really come at me chat room
Alright
That's that's going to the list of things did find reasonable I think BottleRock is a very reasonable let's move a lot
Alright wilson-read
60s
In the car
He wants to talk about the the environment the people were living in
Season what was taboo and what have you and it's devil worship
70s telling me what happened
This is what this is about
What was
60s to the Puritan America
Devil work
You can get people to worship the devil that sex with
Superhot
Movie stars
Next it was
Charlie Manson was about
He was wanting carry Altra
Yeah
Popular culture
Where is so cool
Being hippies
That's always the first thing is to peace and love and Nirvana and
Make the play
In the shadows
We got a couple of problems
Charles Manson
Was used
In the sixties device
Because as the narrative goes
Literally
Everyone else
Charles Manson
Was the end of the six
Yeah it was the story where everybody got into the flower child
We got to figure s*** out
69 right everything that happened to the beginning the seventies of kind
I love trash
Teachers Charles man
Listen to all of it and the connective tissue
It's not really in a lot of these clips
Cuz it's boring
Is that he believed the Charles Manson was a guy who was Batman is drunk guy
And he was trying to
To get people into
The drugs and then compromise them into devil worship
But not even the family
He's talking about like he says specifically there's one
Charles Manson
Campus around America
And Charles Manson was just the one that went wrong
He went off the reservation and Alex will explain what that means in a little bit
You have a question
I see you raising your hand
I have time for one Quest
No follow-up
I think there's this guy named Gabe
Who is realreal
You would walk around with a big
Bush bleed
New strain
You know what I'm going to go I'm going to go
I don't think he had a cult
You got to start loading every student
It's for Action Group or something like that have a following
Yeah
Picture of George Washington
It was like a joint
Entirely true
So in this in this next clip
While discussing all this devil worship
Alex accidentally makes
A bit of akka
Confession about what he's version of Christian
And what he looks
Let's
Is
For the real
The real Atlantis
Now
The real rosicrucian order
Esoteric Christianity
What she's just every flavor of rebellion
Gas station
Program
Horrible things
Ohio
Man
Wanted to say at the end of that last load we kind of got off track but he said he's saying the Dino Charge
Girls Manson there's always a Dracula in the background or whatever like
Like he based his career he started his career building
Like a new church
At the site of the Branch Davidian
And loves Waco
Koresh all that s***
Huge David koresh
Interesting
I love the way his name is David koresh
Love the way he was Jesus okay that's true every buddy knows that strangely enough
Fine with everything he did
Moving lock
Very apologetic
Begin
Esoteric Christianity
I do like I do like the degree of difficulty on
About that you got like okay
It's like in the Olympics
You know anybody can do a straight dive
Make it look pretty good your degree difficulty
David caress your degree of difficulty is way up you already start a little ahead
Bonus point
Start not there's no doubt about that but if it's at the same time does not nail The Landing Golf Course
Blows around
He just goes on and on about that like.
Gennarino did killer
It's not the most important
Important
Esoteric Christianity
Series about gnosticism are pretty close to right
Call Thomas Jefferson a classical liberal in Liberal all the time
Christianity is
Logical
As you wish you removed all of the The Pretender
To the Bible
Those miracles
B******* like the Gospel of Thomas
Sprite
If you look into most-liked version
Who's the best character
A lot of The Interpreter
This is one of my favorite piece
Most of the interpretation
I don't
That's what a lot of it boils down to
Is like the tree of wisdom of Good and Evil is an orgasm
The fruit of the tree of Good and Evil is an orgasm
And so you should never
It's so weird how
All religion
Are obsessed with Zack
Yeah yeah yeah with controlling and regulating
Because it's such a powerful force
Well and it's not a bad idea like if you're trying to get people to Channel all of that
Look up frequently
Rio cuz it is another base
You get someone to
The control that through your
System then you're way more likely to
I mean the other thing is
If everybody's getting laid all the time
Nobody's going to work
You know
Now back to Mansion where is if everybody
Repressed insects
Actual you're going to build the system
Chapel
Sublimation of Sexual Energy
Play death
Admission
Not real Christianity not Mainline Christianity
Nice to hear it from his mouth
And that means straight up
He might believe in like
Lost Books of the Bible and forgotten books of Eden
He might be into
To the Apocrypha
The pseudepigrapha
He might be into all of these like
Banished book
No and I'm not talking about any kind of like
Logical reasoning
They're just
Looks like I would totally if you had an illuminated text of the
Jesus fighting dragons and murdering kids when he was a kid
I'm excited about that
The perfect man
Tim killed Sharon
Do you know that
Alex knows that to Reformation
I spent a long time researching method
Wait he did what are you oh my God
Take back everything
So he got that probably the only thing we're going to
Agree with him
Equip alternate
Explanation
Now it's better so Tara christiani baby
Alright
Podcast
Banana Joe
Was jealous of the cultivating
What he do they were never billed are high priest
Do people eating doo-doo
Kildare
Number one woman
In the Hollywood cult
Roman Polanski
He was out of town
They showed him what happened
Charlie McCall
Riverhead
Jealous
French story
Charlie
Little man Manson
Garrison Keillor
Okay
Also I like how you just takes man
Who was telling the truth that's probably reference
Things that I'd say about like wanting to
Kill
Celebrity because
Be more attention
But that's our thing it's not like she's the goddess of a
Illuminati cult-like
At this point
Charles Manson is a Renfield but he wants to
To be a Dracula
React like a Dracula
Okay
Read all the requirements of being a
He was a
Paranoid
Co catalog
Who just wanted people to like
Inexplicably that was how we chose
Like he was he was
At the same time
His motivations are so
Stamboul
If you just get into work
You know what I'm saying
Like you do
No structure records
Raped children right
And they've been any history of like
Boarding
Houses in
Just like that
Kid yeah he was he was definitely sexually abused from the mon from the jump
Like he was
To start with also
Very short man
That's no good
That's bad
Those people those people
I mean I know this guy ran
You told me that you have no reason to live
Ready Paul Newman
Sharpie forgot Google
Loveboi let's move along
Discusses how
Drugs
Armstrong
He's saying that there are there's like marijuana's that are going around that are hallucinogenic
More less
Marijuana
About like psychotropic drugs
Medicinals and then he gets sidetracked
80 weird
Deconstruction of his own voice
It's very it's very
Look at it
This is a very very serious
Situation and is part of a larger operation to put you into a near dream-state
So you're not really conscious
Row Row Row Your Boat
Down the stream merrily merrily merrily merrily life is but a dream
If I wanted
To come on this show
And talk to you
Like they do on NPR
To put you into a trance I could do it
But on purpose
I have a grating voice
You out
Your coma
To shake you free out of it
So you're revealing the invoices
I could talk just as sweet
Justice pretty
Has all these fake people
I don't do that
Are you trying to share my real voice
Is everything they hate
Masculine
Grading
Copying a Marine Corps drill sergeant drill sergeants are trying to Encompass the classic
Status of a male instructing people in serious Danger
The affect their life
Android
Bring up that stupid
At the end of the show
From the
Quote unquote Chicago affiliate supposed to host the fourth hour but I think Alex doesn't trust him to host
Cuz of course not so he cuts into the
The time and just Rambles about how the globalist
Aren't having
Kids because they don't want kids down to their underground Arts
Stuff like that
I like
It's too it's too nonsensical
I wanted to bring it up
Okay I'm actually kind of interested in very fast
Is it in what his take
Already is on mantle and how it's going to go from here
Yuge
Nerd about certain types
Pics of things like that
It's going to be fun
Perfectly clear
This isn't the stuff I expected you to yell about
Later
Alex
Makes his narrative
About Charles Manson
A bit more robots
He starts to try and deal with the eye
DIA
The Charles Manson had a
Environmental
He basically says that he was a globalist
He's basically saying that he's a Proto globalist is also a Proto antifa
The grandfather
Yes absolutely first-hand knowledge
Globalist plans
Doesn't sound right now
Charlie Manson
Is only just one guy
Not just one but several songs with
Beach Boys in Outer Banks
Not just from the CIA on the drugs
Hollywood
How things ran and who really ran the world
Probably took LSD over a thousand times
Looking completely looking like a crossing a homeless person
And a guru
This you say where is he good at
Alright
If true
Like traveling
Well
If not true
Which it is not
The globalist have any
Breaded eggplant
Write his
His fear of what the world is going to be
Yes he thought 90
90% of people were going to die in a race war
Which by the way
Fears of stuff
Recently watched
In Bruges
There's a part where
Dwarf little person
Wow I was never have never seen a little person
Got2b Dinklage
He has a cocaine binge where he explained how there is going to
To be a race war
And that's based off of
Manson's idea exactly
Is what a Neo-Nazi said about that is going to be erased
No that's a dumb dumb dumb but it's also Alex Hawking
About the idea of like climate change and saving the environment
It's all those things
Incongruous
Actually Galleria
People on the planet
Tell you this
Sew-ins
I do respect Charlie man
Don't Call Him Charlie how can you not
Delaware also familiar with him
Also here we go this next at the next web lays out what I mean
It's not just the race
This is what Alex
Who the guru's over the universities in every city
All that is coming
George Soros
Now
This plan backfires
This plan backfires when Alex starts playing some clips
Yeah kind of sound more like him
He doesn't address that at all but
In the meantime Alex starts talking about
Sort of generally discussing what they are about and
Spreading some fears fryeri thoughts on the other side
BOCES a bunch of pedophile
Devil worshippers today
Sex with hot chicks on altars
Hy-Vee
And you got to
So that's the globalist
Children
Taehyung age
Roy Moore
Well I'm not just that but the entire homeschool
Community
Like one of the big things that they do is
Is they create the
He's child marriages in order to 1
Subjugate women
In order for it like
That way your father has
Complete control over your future and
The weird. Is that your betrothed
You're supposed to be betrothed like that and married at like 15
But before you actually move in with your husband
Your dad is supposed to
Teach you for a few years
What year
Duties
Like it
Batshit
Insane out there
Go around and give these
Talks at evangelico
Meetings and Conference
That are all vaguely like
You know this is what women are supposed to do and then later on people are like wait are you talking about 14 year olds
And they stopped getting invited as much
Is very uncomfortable
Abor what I wanted to bring what he's talkin about there
Blood God bless their drinking
That's the blood libel
From the children
First air
They're not doing that but that's that's
That's all that is
That's all
This idea of misinterpreting stories to say that they're trying to
Blood supplies
Right whatever
Or the putting fluoride in the water all of that are examples of
Choose another form of archaic
All of the stuff that Alex talks about
With the globalist
All of these beers
Traceback for
In the most part about 11 or so
And it's pathetic
And the fact that that people don't
See-through that is
Troubling
And it true
It's a true
I'm so in his next clip Alex wants
Do not be afraid
Oh good cuz he's been stoking my fears for a while now
He wants you to not be afraid of the fluoride in the water watch anymore because
Do we have found in China there are levels of fluoride
Unless you live in
Know that people know
As of now there's a new
What's a system
Fall out of trees
They can make you go to sleep
Flip the switch
Moving away from that program
They're going with 5G technology
So this is how the photo shoot going on
Cell phone
Group has been doing good job
Merida's on the show lately
This is like my favorite crazy
Crazy his spouted lot of his ship and Alex brings up hamamoto store
As well dr. Nick begich
We've gone over is not a doctor
A lot of those clasica
Traits that he was describing about University
Like I'm a little bit
But Nick baggage is not a doctor
He has his degree from a Sri Lankan University that is
Diploma Mill making up all this s*** about electromagnetic waves and what has
Have you it's just complete pseudoscience
Attitude teacher
Do you think I could get one of those srilankan degrees
Weed out
I have
Diploma Mill that I run
This shows not making enough money
But if you got a diploma Mill I like one
That you're expanding your Revenue
Totally credits made already
High today
I'm just a to prepare you for what's to come
A show later is like
Deeply troubling and
But before we do it turns out there's big news
In terms of the world
We're all going to
You know one of the problems I have
Hatred of
Theoretical universe
The gurus
Was that
Generally speaking
All of them
We're trying their best
React to what they saw as the 50
And the way that the eyes
Ethan Herrera
Destroyed women
Like
Exactly what they were going for
Unfortunately a lot of them continue that in a different direction
One of the big things they were trying to do was create a
Amor
Expansive
Society and allow people
Open up the Earth their minds in the same way
Kizi in the Electric Kool-Aid Acid Test
Would go around and do that
It's frustrating to me that you would Moline
Them the wrong reason
Are deserving of much-maligned meant for many other
I think to a certain extent what you look at is
Like a macro version of someone who's going to
Through therapy
You are really buttoned-up and
Never speak your mind
Speaking up for yourself and being assertive and all that
I am on the way
Health
You will probably scream at somebody you'll probably on the path to getting better you'll do something wrong
Or you'll go too far
And perhaps
60s in a response to
The 50s
Right
Help
Trying to fix the woes of society to end up you end up
Metaphorically screaming it said one of the biggest
Groups of the biggest influences of so many of those
Was the burgeoning
Therapeutic
Community at the
He's one of the
Great chroniclers of
Why
Cease all went wrong
And his disillusionment when the the 70s rolled around
After he did Time in Mexico all of that stuff was
Was very fascinating and that he did start
End of deconstruct
How many of those therapist
We're basing themselves off of fall sign
I'm assuming the chat room is going wild for there
She just wants
Attention
It is something that comes comes out of that
And the way that he is
He's portraying these people
Is so wrong
Because they did so many wrong things
He's missing the point because the things that they did wrong are the things that
He supports them
Right where is he's creating this false Reality Bites
Why so important
She's just making a drop in Camarillo
The worst and the best
Now it's
I don't know
I don't know what to know how far to go in
Widest picture
Charles Manson
You could make a lot of arguments
The Charles Manson was an offshoot
Shoot of
The worst tendencies
He's of the sick
A lot of arguments that serial killers going to serial killer
Going to happen
The particular details of them are worth what
Downtown
Down the road Alex's the Zodiac Killer
Completely distract
Give me from whatever I completely lost track
I tried to start setting up the
Which means everybody gets a drink this weekend
There's big news
About the world
Religion
This weekend
Akon worshipping AI
I think I'm actually okay with that
Play play for a while
Impression
Not a good one
Something different about this
What do you want must warn you last few months
We're back to that
Rebecca that from
Elon Musk
Sub tweeted a guy
I have probably a goof
To worship at the AI godhead
All of which is most likely a tongue-in-cheek b*******
What kind of idea you are not the person
All the people who shouldn't be
Making
A religion
Bulshit is manufacturing dialogue in one of the most disgraceful is there
Is that is that a I would be the closest thing that we've ever come to that is actually
A real God
Bright lights
Do you know the ways that technology
Expands exponentially
Not on a nonlinear fashion you like what we will end up having
Will have access to within the next like
The growth of Technology
It's almost
Some people's modelsim futurist model
RNR insanely like
You noticed everything being able to communicate with each other all with all knowledge by all centralized
I don't know self-learning self-perpetuating
Computer would be
Would be on Mission
Essentially
I'd be fine with
Like
I always think like Janet swim
Is 1 good questions
Second question
After we figure that one out
Would a thinking robot
Like if you could really
Sincerely
Have them
Be able to respond
Rudimentary work
Call mom passed the Turing test
Sure something along those lines of experiencing boredom
That is a very
Does that is a lime
Because that's a line for me
Well here's the thing
If they were capable of it
Experiencing boredom
Boredom
At
The same exponential level
So one second of boredom
Something along those lines
Would be infinite
The search for robot novelty
Would be
Deal with boredom is generally
Find something interesting
Robot Chicken Robot
Novelty could be
Now we're getting into an episode of Futurama where Bender goes on a bender or Black Mirror
So that's the future
Yeah but now let's go to the park
Alright Alex Jones has something he wants to say about the past
And then I'm going to have
Serious
Rebuttal
Afterwards
Bedtime
So he's saying that the British Empire was the ruling system of the world Italy
But let me tell you let me I put together
Not much to do British Empire
Well first of all it was being explored California was becoming a state
Expansionism was on the March
But there's a war in that crummy us again
The Ottoman Empire was still in play
What a great range of power is going strong
Years
After this
That's why I thought
Those are some things that are going on there was the Indian Mutiny against British rule
That was dealing with it was the Opium War
Brittany was not
The colonial rule in the world
It was like
Dead center of the
Complete collapse
Of the British Colonial
Yeah yeah
Republic
Just given like the setting
No
I am wrong that was
American
Fair enough
Decision
To establish world.
So any government the scientific Elite in the British government the colonial British government
The empire
Global government
Could have swore they thought about the sewing machine
Hey don't knock that
Very hard to do it's cool it's cool but the scientifically we're not doing all that much
Does Macy
But everybody else
Militarily
But culturally
They barely understood pass
Where
That's the final Revolution
Just what the globalist technocrats calling
Book
Conferences
60 years ago
They didn't
You know what he's talking about
I figured it out
Charles Darwin wrote the origin of the species in 1850s
I think that's what he's really I think that's the only thing he's talking about
That's like the scientific should he hate
Write the idea of evolution
Evolution of
Have to hate
Revolution number one on the list
Can think of that was relevant
1850s
The Western world
He could be talking well I don't know my history but I'm
Pretty sure that's when they found out
Heliocentric
Is that right
Okay
Nachos
Feel like Alex is still mad about that
Definitely
You gave me a second look like
Hold on now
So
Earlier
Alex said that he was going to play some
Yeah Charles Manson
That they were going to
Show
The Charles Manson
Charlie if you're nasty
He's like the Democrats
News like Al Gore
Here's the first clip
The first one
Is like algo
Here's the first language
What's up with the family
Salvage outdoor
Bio-weapon plug releases
This is where normal
I know you don't have enough time
If we if we weren't doing this episode live I feel like you would have spent an entire weekend.
That one clip
Just gone like
Buy sentence
Superman
Pull together a clip of Alex saying
Exact same f****** thing
I don't even need to cuz at the end there is a m being like
Crazy
Keep saying that stuff about
50 million people
How can I buy this
It to shock the guy
None of that sounds like
I guess dog or likes trees
So there's that
Now here's exhibit B
Alex Jones believes
Is there Charles Manson
Super into a one-world government
Okay
One World Government
Man doesn't back up to his fear
Michael Strahan
One World Government
The bombed-out little drug-delivery got
When what you look like
Looks like an ant
Eclipse lighting
F*** you. f*** p***
God damn it if you don't support us
George Soros will win Stanford
Now
He pivots to an ad
Not just on like
Be afraid
It's our enemies are goddamn Charles Manson
Accidentally
Like you playing these things
It's very clear
Subway
It sounds exactly like it sounds very similar
Back in the 60s
The idea of a unified world government was a very popular idea
It's not like he was the only person who ever is paused
That was pretty big hippie idea
It was one of the end it was also coincidentally
The time when the UN was maybe the most
Popular it is
It's a bit yeah
Like that was that was shortly after they were afraid that way shortly
The Cold War was just
Really starting to ramp up in all of the proxy wars I hope really
There's the hope of being able to avoid
Yep
Entirely possible that at that
You sound like Charlie
Charlie obaugh
I prefer spider
Alex I don't even know what
He's trying to make but it doesn't work
I hear you talking about man-made global warming
What the f***
Search for slogan it goes on from here but it is definitely worth stopping
History of the world
He is really f****** lucky that
It flashed away from his face
There had to be more easily
Oh
I really should have
Before
You playing the clip that Paul Joseph Watson put in the dark
Infowars
Send it starting to troll Alex he might be
I think you might be working on the next
Charles Manson was an environmentalist and all they need is Cherry Picked
These tiny little pieces from interviews without looking at the big picture anyway think we are
1776bank
Throughout the rest of the
There's so much
Play horses
White papers
Fluoride
Constantly talks about free association
From your words
It's clear that you were
Westbury
Alex believes that all of this
Yeah
Chimeras
There you go
If you want on the street
Flipping her off grabbing the microphone they all have that
That that that stupidity
Broadcasting
The correct spirit in the world
Turn off themselves
Great way to respond to that because he can't deal with the content
Biggest reveal is not all of the s*** that he said that
Is exactly what Alec
Orangetheory similar
Especially like that
You know
After me I'll kick everybody's ass me like Alec
That's you that's you have left back to him screaming at Adam Schiff
Paranoid fancy
Disease of somebody attack
Which will give you the right to do whatever it is you want
The biggest thing though that
I felt
Was a huge
Reveal
Listen
I'm not a devil but I'm a devil in
Which outside
I have evil inside of a good
What Alex
There's there's so much there
I meant also
Quick Quack
Did Charles Manson
Trinity
Pretend to be Bill Hicks for a long time
Okay let's actually do with resumes
Had a swastika
Tattooed on his forehead
That way you could differentiate
Differentiate himself from the real Charles Manson
Charles Manson was now living is Alex Jones rehab
Exactly
Interesting
So Alex
Who's there
Mansaf
Call Charlie
Hold on right now
Alex last week
I feel like there is
Got Rusty
Life
Alex Jones
36 hour
People
Vice did an article that we discussed
Yep that's covered all of the wrong
Mostly motivated out of spite
For our live broadcast next week
Because of ice
That's just I need money
Why would you even try and hide it under that veneer of like
We're doing this
Not because I need
Because I wanted
Trolls
Tooth tooth questioned behind me are in Factory foods that should not eat
Together
That is what those are old-time freezing point reference it'll never be explained
Episode where and we explained or at least we talked
Maybe
Through the archives maybe you'll find a way of talking about the food that you should
With ice Lolly
Let me tell you
Ice cream
Ginger salad
Dead there's a bunch of things you can't eat with jingle be
I know that much I don't know what to drink anyway
I don't know what a mangosteen is all I know is that
Baby
12 years ago Ludacris was on Twitter yelling about mangosteen
And Aziz Ansari was trying to get
But not take mangosteen
Anyway
I'm just a big fan of
Neem leaf and chicken egg giving you
Rheumatism rheumatism
We're done with Charles Manson buddy that's not a good thing
Are you sure
I'm not even going to introduce this clip
This is Mike.
Roshan
Who is a prominent
Activist
Individual
Exposing
Genocide in South Africa
Zimbabwe
Weimar Republic inflation
Because they
Conquest
Black Monday
Protester white farmer murders
CBS News
Epidemic of South African Farm murders
Elderly
Your grips
AMC connected
White Converse
Jubilee
This
Trouble
You can pick your mic back
If you like
Alex has a guy Simon Roshan to talk about
Capca
My girlfriend actually grew up in South Africa
I have no thoughts about it whatsoever
Price
Z
Call
Even
To even be like
Hey
I can't believe black people are angry at White
The Chrome plated
Balls on these f***
This is
This is astonishing
Bright
It's pretty it's pretty crazy
Look look
But I also want you to know
That the situation they're talkin about specifically
He's crazier than you think
If there is
Any place
In the world
Where you could look at white genocide happening and be like
I guess that's why
It would be snow
How to be a little bit like okay
Guys you shouldn't do it
Okay
I'm going to read an article about
This black
It was a Black Friday Black Monday
The thing that ever
Who cares
It is
And he is
Being misled
By this guy who's
Who's coming on
Right who is apart of
Would amount to a militia group
Very heavily armed and will get you some of their craziness here in a little bit
So before you read it
Just recap the story that we were told okay that farmers were killed
4 killed by
AMC black militia groups on black lives matter
Blacklivesmatter worldwide
Protection and I guarantee
Perfectly with truth
Nautical from al-jazeera are most across South Africa John black clothing and gathered on motor
In A procession of tractors and trucks
Interpretive response
To farm murders
The racially-charged protest
Comes days after two white farmers were sentenced
More than 10 years in jail for assaulting a black man
The case that is also stirred racial tension
Interesting but that's what the protest was about
Not what Alex is actually even describing
White commercial Farmers have long complained that they bear the brunt of rising violent crime and save the government
Ignores their plight
So what do you think so far
What I think so far
Apps
Alex
Did not read
Earlier in 2017 Africa
To the fact-checking political organ
How many people working in Lebanon Farms
I am impossible to calculate a farmer.
It also laid rest accusations at a
Unfolding in the country after Mike cernovich
American white supremacist
Freda Dale 2016
The quotes white genocide is real in South
Here is that interesting other quote
Some guy named Garrett
The head of governance crime and justice
System
I got it so just got Gareth newham is the head of the government's crime and justice
Division of the pretoria-based in
For security studies
Quote within the white farming
Community there are white right-wing sense
Belief that these attacks are Orchestra
And they've been lobbying European country
Which is only resulted in the political
Politicization of the issue
But they think it's only them
And that's a mistake
Of course their concerns
Visa V murders
Violence
Their concerns are serious
They also need to appreciate that it is a national issue
The claims are white genocide continue to circulate on social media with memes calling on the World to act
GameStop White being murdered in
These have been met mostly with ridicule by most South Africa
Last week to South Africa
Complete service
Released its annual stats of crime
I found that there were more than 90
18000 murders in the country
Or 34 murders per 100,000 people between
A 2000
Not bad quote if you want to ascertain through
Statistics who are the most likely to be murdered in South Africa benthos are young black males Garrett's do him
And told al-jazeera for some context
White South African make up 1.8% of the country's murders
While being under 9% of the population
Statistically
They have a shockingly lower
Then expected murder rate
So
Mike cernovich
Vets
One of our cast of characters
By being a f******
Racist pilot
Right I don't have this article pulled up anymore
But I found a very interesting
About this guy Simon wrote
Apparently what he is done
I'm here the part of a group called The sweet land
And I'm not pronouncing that correctly
Nice already I'm already out it means Southland
They are a group that is
They believe that our race war is coming and that they are going to be
Comes of it and so they're basically
Charles Manson
Yep ironic on the day after it dies
This is an article on a website called
Angry white men. Org which is dedicated to tracking
Connections within the white supremacy
It's alright world
And it's very different
Beyond the other side of it it's really interesting I'll post a link up to
Cuz I don't have time to go through all of it
Is if I
If you do the kind of research that this
The website is.
You see
Focus
And intentional campaign
On the part of Simon Roche
And other members of
The Swede Landers
To approach
Really really f***** up versions of the right-wing
To try and publicize
Fundraise for
Spend that they even have a recording
Ava Ava of a phone call
This guy
I'm sorry I really sure
Twist Australia
It's very similar to the Newsela
So
I'll just read here from this box is this is this is
Specifically about Simon Roche
The founder of the Southern nationalist blog Occidental
Brad Griff
Is Panda number of inflammatory articles under the suit
Hunter Wallace
In 2012 for example he wrote the quote Hitler was justified in conquering Norway
And claims it in 150 years mass murderer Anders Breivik will be
Viewed as quote the European John Brown
Don't
Support
Anders
Rough
In a March
19 post Griffin Road that he was contacted by a representative of the
The Swede Landers
He explained
Several calls from an unknown number
When you finally answer
To the found a gentleman by the name of Simon Roche introduced
Himself and inform him then
Pastor Griffin
Number to him
Later he revealed that he accidentally recorded the conversation but
The audio on his blog is
During the call the person which is included here on this website
Rose explains that he another sweet Landers
Roche says that he was hoping Griffin would cover the sweet Landers organization on his blog
But he has been going on
In southern Africa
So there's a bunch of connection
Intentionally made with white nationalist blog
Nautica winter
Really it's really important to remember and
Really hard drive
Is that
Apartheid didn't end along
Time ago
My girlfriend
Live through the end of Apartheid
Yeah she's not
40 years older than
You do like a mole
It is insane because of course
Listen to be
Listen to these ass
Can tell that it's that
White victimization that comes
From its
Oh no
We don't run the world
It's so much more f***** up
So I'm going to finish this article in algebra and then we'll jump back into Alex's
Jillian godsell a lecturer at the school of governor
Is it with a gay
She told al-jazeera that the claim of Red Rising
Farm murders was a
Proxy for
Something else
Quote I don't think this is about murders
The number of deaths
We don't know if there are whites or black farmers were killed
Some say 30% of those murdered were black workers
People seem to be grieving for much more than these deaths
People are grieving about change in this country
The end of a
Now here to things
Bitter Berry
Very relevant
A lot of these farmers
We're flying apartheid-era flag
That is not
About
Farmrite
Again whatever is about wanting to go back to where you had
All the power over another group of
Even if it wasn't
I get it
Here is another
Stacked in a stat that is very
According to a recent land on it
White Southern app
Africans are 8.9% of the population
And they own 73% of the agricultural land
Still
The still
Which is
Which is a very interesting thing that's f***** up
Even at the end of Apartheid
The
Fashion
That was shown very very small minority
It's ridiculous
I mean again
What are the reasons I'm a soft no on white genocide is because of that every time that white people have
Finally had to relinquish
The power and only had
Most of the power
They've been treated with touch
Compassion
It's bananas
So they would never have
Which they have historically
Never show
Not when they needed to not like how I'm calling white people
I think at this point I've proven that I'm a self-hating white person
The issue comes down to this is
Not about any kind of ID
Video of white Janice
Even though
They can find about
Farmers that are red
Down
Did the peak of them worrying
Late night
Well in the same way that crime in the United
Significantly dropping
Ever since
Yeah like it is been consist
And yet one of the
Easiest ways
Stoke White
By acting as though crime
Splash
Black crime rate
Really cause a good scout game
Describe this is against the murders of
Protest was about
White people hurting people and how that should be fine
We don't like it
Against
Of course
Nonsense
Play again
I completely agree with it
The concern over violence
Murder rates are real that's
That's something that's real but
Personalizing it making it your victim narrative is wrong
Because it's
It's a national problem
Statistically
Show there
1.8% of the murders are
White people
The same thing
Hear it
Pixar not interracial
Murder as an a
Generally speaking murder is
Is within
Each
Incretin 90% +
Likely to be murdered by
That generally people you know
Anyway
This interview is
Hot garbage
Included most
Thank you
Things ever
Emergency plan because
I already
Population
Ism
And I got to ask you why not just evacuate
Very sad these folks will just kill each other
Very very sad
We'll be right back
F*** you with your very very sad nonsense Ali
Hey white people
Evacuate
You know what that Independence
That argument is
No no look we don't want to
Cleanse the racist anymore
That
Europe should be for European
That's almost in reverse
Literal white nationalism that's a new state
Also that is nonsense also if you want to talk about rape
Issues in Africa
Do you want to know the largest number of rape cases
Causes those races
Raven Africa if it's not f****** racial or child bass is really Chris
American
Go over there okay I'm sorry I'm sorry Daddy
This is something that really f******
I know
That f****** brand of Christianity
Sanity was no longer as except
Even though it's still very except
Did hear what it was
Those f****** decided not. You know what
We're going to go to Africa
We're going to run this f****** place it's kind of like what the pilgrims did here
Hold on Sarah made a really good point
What's that I have neighbors
Fair enough I'm sorry so I'm actually more sorry
That was probably one of the things I was going to set you off the most
F****** idea
That Alex wouldn't have the wherewithal wouldn't have the awareness
The knowledge
The self
Reflection
To know what he was saying
Like I don't believe that I don't believe he would be
So glib
And loose-lipped as to say
Why do white people just leave and then the blacks kill each other
He knows what he's saying
That's not a stray comment
Guess what
That's a big part of the Swede Landers
Sort of ideology
Dino or
No they believe that at some point
They're going to have to evacuate
Especially
That's part of why they go around and raise tons of money cuz I need to have enough fuel
I need to have gun
And all that s***
Hazel Alex is having this guy on
And he's not reading the Articles or the statistics
Anyting
About the underpinning
Of the
Or at least he's gotten the call
From
Cernovich
For one of these guys
You got to talk to this guy he's up on chair
Tommy Robinson gave him a call or some s***
Asda Tommy Davis
This sweet liners are bigger than p'zone
Okay interesting products
Also to the chat room roommates are okay with people who live upstairs for me probably not great
Children
I'm sorry I thought that was the Airbnb Castle
Not always
It's only nine 12
23 they can deal with Target
But look at the weeknight
Good point
Right
Okay
Thought
If you are a white Nash
What if we just
A viewing
Because in all honesty
Like think about this very serious
No French
Ardiana where did
You can have that place
I mean in reality
Most White
People aren't White
True most white people are at
At the very least some sort of late
Like
Are you there's there's no way to it completely complicit
Conceptions that
To evaluate your
Self as you go through
Experience
Forms of race
Cousin within me and I got
The way that you were raised in
Culture that your race
The people who are out-and-out white
If they're arguing
Is when we leave
We'll just let the
Them kill each other
If we let them leave
With those people trying to kill each other
Help me find a new version of Separation with blue eyes and green eyes or plaything
People who are going to get into a small group
And then go well we're not racially
Right there's going to be some new division
Alex Jones
Won the
It still has to be the victim and have their own car
Country Maid still be like
Scapegoat
Ginger over there when your entire audiology
Is based on
Purity
Then there is always
To be in Esco
What Purity is
Store speakers.
Never exist without
Pure
And that's that's always be issued
They're they're always going to
To try and come
Continue to
Escalate their purity
And find that
Perfect little Diamond of white rental everybody's dead but the one guy
So if their argument is everybody else's going to kill each other once we leave
What
And then when they kill each other will be like
Haha
I got you guys
You're the one
I mean no matter what we can just
Put a pin in it with a
Champs bigotry
Like
Is no leg to stand on
In terms of
Not harboring white nationalist opinion
Pretending that he doesn't
No
Driving
The guests that he has on
Commercial
God you have curated
You bring me up
And then down
So
If this is from a commercial where he reads reviews
Of the product
Alright in the website
I want to I want to throw something everytime I hear this place like three times per episode
At this this little snippet
Is just like
F*** you Alex go f*** yourself
Was Silver Bullet the highest quality
30 parts per million colloidal silver out there
Elizabeth
Every time he does that
What a dick
What a f****** a******
It's so weird how it's
Do heat pumps
In-and-out of self-awareness
Like he's the leader
See I feel like though he
Asked you on some level.
When he says that he's doing
He's doing. I'm not rushing cuz this is 1takejay
Okay he doesn't have time to record this
Glass door baby
So now it's back
To this South
Jordan
You might think
This is so true
This is so hard for me because I just don't know what's coming this is very hard for me here's the problem
You've built this up so much I almost
Have to not get angry and
Response to that
This Village is going to battle for his broken
In terms of this part
There's something else to make you mad later
But in terms of the South African stuff
Yeah I think we're in the clear
Hey now we just talk
Pronounce like that
I don't care to respect them either quite frankly
Are based on
I don't know
Misinterpreted history
You might think that they're based on
Pure racial hatred
You might think
That they're based on any number of things
You could never guess what they're based on
We hope to a series of of prophecies that said this
The prophecies given a hundred years ago we looked at a time
When a man with a price
Will be in power in the United States
The power
Man
End
Ancient culture and
Who is Buddha
To be fair Simon roaches not in
Charge of the group
Who wrote the prophecy
And why doesn't he have all of our money
Okay that is
Venice Beach
Most
Prophecy I have ever heard in my entire life
This guy's name is Nicholas
Peter Johannes
Did ramsburg
Also known as
Beginner
Van rensburg
Which Theory
Let me give you the block
Dan
Do not ruin this for me
Batman
Is unequivocally a genius
If you wrote that profit
That is
The most brilliant thing anyone has ever done I believe in Clairvoyance right now dance
Book of his prophecy
Are you still at when was when did he live yeah he died
26 and he still writing books to Prattville were still writing books probably someone collected something or other
I believe in this
I can't find that proper
When a man with the head
That looks like a wig
He takes over for a black
I will give you 10 years one of his 1916 August 19th
60 years one of his prophecy
I see a terrified Woman in Black
And the interpretation of that is
The death and destruction of communism
Level of Prophecy
It's that much of a stretch
Yeah
If you got the dude with a wig
I can't find that
Let me believe
I don't believe in ghosts
I don't believe in God
I want to believe
In this almost certainly racist by Algarve
He was a South African guy
He was involved in the Boer War
He was on the right side
I think so but you was sort of not he was not a good soldier and he had to
Visions and so you got sent home
And then he came back to try and warn people
Any games of a reputation for being right
He had some hunches about military stuff
And ended up being right about some stuff
Any amount of
Research you could you could
You could certainly
I don't want to get too into his
His whole history because it
There's not a ton of information that I can find
It's all
It's all cockamamie bulshit
It's all just like
If you're say
From the people who want to support him
But like
We know again that replacing the black man
Like a wig
For a black man
I cannot find that prophecy
But also my Afrikaner accent
So here's our
Thing
Is interesting
Throughout
Most of
His prophecies
Just real quick
The way to an Afrikaner accent
Just a flick
Play do you have to do
You got it
Okay
I got a new year
You liking Alex Jones of impression
So this guy was
An African
He died in 1920
He was making predictions
Threw up to his death
What are the pretty consistent threads
Throughout a lot of his prophecy
What about
Germany
I mean
In a positive light
As a good thing yes
Not just like a
Hey these white dudes are going to f****** rise
No no no like a very positive
No
The interpretation
The interpretations given of a lot of it is that like the US and Germany will have to be on
Same side in World War
That's a way of getting around the idea that it had everything
World War
But you saw there at the end
Basic research
You could have expected that the us would have joined the
Would have joined Germany in World
It is kind of surprising if you look at the United
History
To see us
The right side
So this guy named Gustav Mueller
He was a guy who was in the the service they have in South Africa
As it were
Back in the back in the day
Houston
Hugo who started
Based on a lot of the prophecy
Please of this
Sinar darensburg
He started this
Extremist religious group called
How do you pronounce
Die in German
Btd3 Lambert
You started that as a
Paramilitary
Non
Connected to a state
Action Group
Protect White
People in
Faced
Prophecies
From this guy
Based on
Prophecy
And now
Their representative who has spent a lot of time contacting alt-right figures in United States
Purposes is it Gaston Alex Jones Show
This is crazy
Gustav Mueller
You know there's a part of me that's always jealous
Like imagine
Who would join a group
See now this is where this where might sort of
Dysfunction comes into play I thought you were jealous of me getting to the
Discover these things
Oh my God
Where this is
Not anywhere nearby I want to talk to you about Gustav Mueller
I would never want to say I found an article from South African newspaper
Let me tell you something about
Hats
Good idea
In January September
I'm sorry January 2008
Using courts
Laredo's
Mueller was arrested on December 13th 2007 at a caravan Park in mosul Bay
You been on the run from police for being in
In possession of an illegal submachine gun
His co-accused
Hank Duprees
Are currently held on respect is bales
Mueller has been remanded in custody until January 21st or formal bail application
The Swede Landers shocked
The public notice
Behind the Nelson Mandela hoax emails
Feverishly circulated on the internet
Do you know this song
A bunch of emails
That were a hoax
That went around purporting to be from Nelson Mandela's Widow
She had a large inheritance
But you needed to get out of the country
It was the Nigerian
The Swede Landers did that
But just with Nelson Mandela
Really
Why are idiots
So much better
They were tricked by black people that's bad
God District
And that is so insane like I don't understand I just don't get it this is
There's so many problems with this
And what genocide fears are
I mean through the most important there they're the most
Evil the only real
I don't know what to tell you
Somehow
I was about to say that's the least dumb one as if being afraid of white genocide
Is the least
Dumb of those
It's far more reasonable
It's Farm
Yeah and the chat room is about to
It's far more reasonable to
To follow somebody based on profit
Opposite than it is to believe that white genocide
When the two come together
Chocolate and peanut butter baby
And so he tells him more about the prophecy
Find a prophecy with the wig
In this again I agree with Alex
Alex takes a turn in this next clip
Even better I don't I don't think it's real
Further when he elaborates on he just repeats
There's nothing new in it
Interesting
Prophesied
Is a little bit self serve
The God put out the
Personally
Deals like this
I've had experiences
We talked about this before
That's not
Radio show it is like
That's great prophecy
Let me tell you about them
It's fantastic
Specific about
F******
Course not
But man oh man
So we've now reached the end of the Swede Lander portion of the show
On the show
And it's generally someone who don't like to talk
No fun
Essentially a cult and there are support groups
The people who is I had
Free of it
Encourages people to break ties with people
Who are ride abusive
Is Scientologist
Is it worth you also as we played in the past that clip where he
He says that women were
To blame for Elliot Rodgers
Attack
His shooting spree because they didn't f*** him
Alexa Rivera
Knew I was born
Stefan molyneux told them
Well well after I was born
Because they cut off all contact
When my family is in there
Nobody knew me and my family knew that I was even there
Yeah this is going to get home
Yet again
So
He has
Stefan molyneux on
To talk about
Downloadable
We're already coming in at about an hour 40
And Michelle
We don't usually our lives are shorter than our
Specific time to get in
All the
Stuff right
Lancaster
Talk to f****** mile-a-minute
Either he's a piece
The garbage
Here he says something that I
I think is really scary
I kind of agree with but
If you understand the kind of code
They have missed
The opportunity to crush
You know you've been doing this longer than I have I've been doing it about 11
But it's too late
We have become too big
Freedom lovers who is supporting each other
Now if they try and smack people
The profile
Virus by friends
B contains
Please do not
The Overton window
Has gone so far now that was impossible before has become commonplace now
What was Radical
Context
What are you talkin about
Window moving that far
It means just talkin about
White National
Disagree with
What do you mean
I mean
Like the idea that
Or that this is
I just know I think in this to the extent it is now
I just
I don't think that years ago
You could have Network
Full of mainstream
People
Making these sorts of Art
I just scream okay please make your case
Okay I think the biggest
I think what you're I thought you were
Staking
Is that
Vista
Mainstream
I think one of the big issues that
People are
Discovering
Is that
One of the
Problems with white Nationals
Is that for so long
It was assumed
It wasn't it wasn't something that was publicized or talked about because everybody
Assumed
Because it was such a normal thing to be
Like
Nationalism
Soupremacy
I disagree
Give me a deck
In American history
Give me a decade
1850s
Alright
White nationalism brain-to-brain
Scientific control
I mean what do you think is the most
Recent decade
White nationalism
Wasn't means
I don't I don't disagree.
To some extent with what you're saying but I
Degree in the
That
These ideas were
Okay too
Make money off of it speak out on
Platforms that reach millions of people
Okay I mean maybe
Maybe the millions of people less than the mess
Stefan molyneux in Alex Jones would not be allowed on television
Or in the present
Because of public diesel
Mtstandard
That's why they've created their own places there
Weird corners of the internet
Supremacist and white nationalist
And have built up their fan base
The Civic Center
I'm at what I'm talking about
Walter Cronkite was a
The secret white nationalist
One of the big problems
That I have with
The way that we are
Maybe the way that the media is
Covering it now
Is the idea that this
Explosive
New issue this is the exact
Percentage of
Patient that has always been
In fact I would say this is a lower percentage
Which of the
That is white
Said it was
Staples
Just so much louder in
Signal is so much
Amplified
Because of the
Not because of
Greater
Number of
The population
Experiencing or or having
Let's put a pin in that for a second
What I would like two more respond to and what I when I said that I kind of agree with what he saying
No I understand
What it really got to me
In that rain
What is
The freedom virus
Is gone airborne
Write any white nationalist viruses
You know because I always do
Conceived of this globalist idea is kind of a brain
The idea of the globalist which
Is just antiques
He's a brain
The kitchen to you and you start to interpret the
Entire world
Through this prism
And that's why you can think that the
The British
We're in charge of the entire world Colonial in 1850 when that's not the reality at all
Curly they were
Or whatever any number of examples to Alex Jones
Rose Colored Glasses
You can pretend
Visit earlier in the episode you can just create an entire new narrative for him
Raised on what the globalist
Berkeley doing right
And to that extent
I believe Stefan molyneux
Correct
Right get his version of
Freedom lover
Is one who believes
In archaic
Somatic beliefs
Couched in an idea of the globalist
Yeah
Tip to ortley ca
When he's on Alex's
Anarcho-capitalist
As we have gone
Through over and over
Regardless of whether or not that is
Central or
Specific to your otherwise
If you go on Alex
You disagree with him and say the show
To hear in order to get
Your
Perspective
I'm not giving him any credit cuz I don't
Tufted attic
Are you don't really buy
But he's a bigot he wants to get his voice
Not long ago
When apartheid end
There was a huge population in the United States who is like
That is
Wrong
Population of the United
And thought
Against
It was the only way
To contain
Control black
Peoples
Aaron's urges
As if that was
Implicit in Alex's
What's really new
Is the idea that there are so many
People who are
To me that's what I find
NBA news
Development
Because because and that's and that's part of the rewriting
The American
Legend
Is the idea that every time
Time we go back to
History
We rewrite
How it is
We thought most
People in
The United States now imagine them
Themselves were they in the 60
These they would have supported
And you have to go back and remember
That doll model percent
30 /
So to me the newest idea
Is that people are on the side of
You're wrong
It's just that their boys allowed because of
Response to the
Exact you have more people were shocked
And they realized
This has been here all along
Right it's like
Tearing open your wall and finding out there like
Is mold a male can I get
When you pull that Rocco
Yeah and that's what I think that's what we're really doing
And that's why this
Like
There's an argument to be made
That I don't necessarily agree with but
It is that
Wendy
People do come
Because their signal is
So many
People
Examined
Themselves and go
That is raw
So if you are going to say you know is it a
I'm not going to argue that it's a good thing
But their voices are so loud right
But it is something that has made a lot of people who otherwise would have
Have assumed their race
Actually
Examine that there
Is not okay
Because they see these f****** assholes
There's there's there's no
But also I think the other thing that I
Stefan molyneux
What about is the idea that there's too many interconnected
Did networks now
Of these people who are self-aware
If you know someone were to attack
Spawn molyneux Alex Wood
Sobia co-defendants
Rebel media
If he still even exist
Gavin McInnes
Yeah people would come
With their
Social media following
And try and make it the biggest
Story in the world
Well in a way that if they weren't a team altogether
It wouldn't work continue my metaphor
In this
Disregard when you
You pull up that rock
All the bugs don't
Scatter
They're all
Connected and the Reddit
Fight you
The Rat King
We have discovered we have
Discovered a nest of rats
Cooking unified witch
Terrified
Bonbon
But also
There's one last clip that I I told
It'll be fun to make fun of him
So the most important thing I think of this area Alex is something called the perreito
Principle which everyone needs to become familiar with
The square root
Of the number
People free people are producing half the value
Right if you have 100 people 10 people
Juicing
If you have a company
I want to stop already
The Pareto Principle is based on the idea that
Any rule where 80% of your outcome
Output
20% of your
Input
It was Italy
Realize that 80%
Other people
We came up with this observation universalized it
In a very
Add square roots
Hugo
F****** dumb
Well but even his numbers are wrong he's telling
Familiar with him
Smart people start to leave for whatever reason
Smartest people leave it means that the company productivity goes down ramp
9-ranked
Productivity is gone
Western Civilization
On the brain
Thousand people
Maybe too fast
Scientific
Machine
Then if the top 1% of smart people from third world end
The first one
With a complete disaster and everyone migrating to Europe the destruction
Could not resist the temptation
Absolutely beautiful
Absolutely beautifully said
Alex Azar
I mean it's fitting that he ends it with
Ideas about white boy
Just washed over in Rambo Smith
Representing the Pareto Principle in order to apply it to this weird
Randy and vision of
And if it looks
Clear about this
This idea that this
Hundred people at this company are responsible for
Half of the productivity is a cockamamie nonsense idea
Be at that idea if you want to apply it on a macro scale to civilization that like
Only these two thousand people are really responsible for the productivity
No it's not they're the ones who were running the system wherein everyone is working super hard for nothing
Yeah do you want to do get one of those f****** people through what really happened
What really happened
Is you find out
Connecticut
Meme
Right they are worthless this is what happened
Easiest
Examples for that are the NBA's
Imagine that
Because they control the leaf if the players actually have a
Strong union
All the sudden you find out
But we don't actually need those
No we're the ones who provide revenue and
Blood off
If you want to go by
And in that example
80% is creating 80% of the productivity of the basketball team
80% is creating 100% of the value not really because they're all the people who are like you know
Maintaining the court
And running
Concession
Calculus
Bring them in with
The player
Like that they would think about biggest lake
Specialist unit again to a I feel like we should have a universal
Union at this point
I don't give a f*** about Governor
Commence I think we workers
Like outside
Imagine
Collectively bargain with the rich
Like that's ostensibly
It's supposed to
Debate
It's supposed to be
Large
Collectively bargaining with the rich
With what
You would call the ruling
Out of the world today
He's some sort of
You know connection between
Them supporting each other much in the same way
Total gym membership membership
Can you stop
No but I did that that's true but at the same time there are connections being made
Between various Union
Supporting each other the most recent the most recent things that I read about the AFL-CIO
Supposed to be
Is that everyone
Confused
Sty Union member
Even as they don't realize that they're not doing a
Outreach
And that the boy from the rich and the big issue
Within those
Often
Job-specific
Like
Pipefitters
Should strike
If
Mason
I mean like bricklayer
No I know
Like if the car manufacturers
Strikes
Pipefitters
And all the sudden
See a lot of
Like one of the
Is that as
Union Spa
Wages for
And nobody
F****** talks about that one because the talking point is so much
Easier that you have to
All that stuff which is right
Concerned that people have
Makes
Feel like I will make less money not looking at the longer
Every every right-to-work law has led
To lower wages
In the Union
Indian
If
Pictures make more money
You will win
That is
Always the case
Trickle around
Exactly when you go through town is
Ineffective when
You go bottom up all the sudden
People starts at
Wealth
Is no longer
The end of this episodes
Stefan molyneux sucks
I really think there is a really interesting narrative
Vascepa
Episode accident
That's one of the reasons why I really needed to do the app
Episode even though
Today's
The reason I needed to do it was the idea that like
Started with this
Weird
Apologizing
4 Charles Mann
Kind of
Narrative
When
The reality is that
If you was
Someone who maybe wasn't
Entirely motivated by racism but had a bunch of it in
Crazy cult leader
And then later he has this looking South African guy who's afraid of
There's such a weird mirror there
With added looks
Exova
For a black prism
Those two things
Mega saalam be
RNC
I don't understand why
This show is
Zip
Badflower show a show quite frankly
Yeah
His bosses
Discover.com
Considering the way that he knows where the growth
Growth that spawned out of that
Ignore 9 million
Are fake
Because it's been such a rough
Road
Making Union
Scream through a bit of it
I didn't
You're going to have to
You promised that later on the episode I would get angry and I did not
Okay I got
Angry but not all the way
2 minutes
That's true
But anyway I feel better
The song
Stars go home and call your mother alright Alex
Nationalist
Website.com
More regular concept update
Yeah we are on Twitter if you'd like
Acknowledge
Underscore and then there's
After that
Can go to iTunes
Yep that's
You could leave a review because apparently algorithms matter over to vote
Beyond the show
We have a new policy walk with some food
Next episode I feel bad about that
If you would like to be forgotten next episode
Then click the support the show about the bad self
Is good as I can do right now
So
I mean
We've we've run the gamut
Anran
Mutators
Cult leaders from the 6
Union talk
You people
African
White nationalist
South Africans
Not good cult leader from the 60s
Also not good
Cult leader co-leader from
Now Stefan molyneux
Call leader from now Alex Jones
It's a bad group of people that we're talking about today
Quick question
Within our podcast
Who is labor and who is
Knights against you
I would not let Ivan has been neither of us are being painted that's true I would like for you and drop
Rusty to Union
Cthulhu
This m*********** we're going to come together
By yourself
Cthulhu has been here imagine if there is no Cthulhu imagine if it was just one camera of Utah
Put something else
I don't know what
Your entire room
Even those the food that should meet to get to
Doctor
We're going to Union
Insurance does better donate
Unionizing with Cthulhu
Better picture lyrics
Oh God you know who that was what I was trying to get you all right
Do you want to take the reins on this one
You were going to cuz you asked me do I know me
Intuit
There is Guy
Notorious Union
He got into so many Union Bus
Scraps
You be out there
Heat up that motherfukers getting
Beat up I hate every picket line
Okay now
The unfortunately also in one of those beatings
But he took outside
I want to be
Please pick up line
He lost the ability to raise his arms
Further than this high
Is John McCain
No it's not it's not but he can only do this high and if you want
Like picture
Exactly
Couldn't get it up there
Although I have sympathy for
Your physical ailment
They have come from your union-busting activity
I still must say
Go fuc yourself John Rappaport
Alex
Bose neck