Alex
T-shirt dance
Going on that was a very aggressive way to relieve done this show without a button-up shirt on
Let's not a little spoiler alert
That's okay in my room it's kind of warm because I put up
Plastic over the
You have done a good job
Yes we talked about home insulation and Alex Jones
So I applaud you
You and your
Improvement I appreciate it
Some trouble though there's some trouble
This morning here at knowledge fight headquarters
Maybelline got into a fight this morning
Alright Claude through by
I might have called her the c-word
I threw up a matter
It's one of those things
It's such a
To hassle to put this
Jessica but don't want to do it again you're such a
I'm bad right when I wake up
What time do discover
If your washing machine is not working properly and you wake up and it's that time
Time of the morning
I will burn this
Whole f****** place
Everything has got to go
Disaster as we do all the time
Interpersonal connection
We might have to
Yes I know a lot about Alex Jones special episodes
Keegan out there
Thank you so much for saving us from the present
And this is in honor of him
Four Star
Intelius Brillion
Someone someone sodomites
Thank you so much for being you like to donate to the show in any way become a policy wonk
You can go to our website, appreciate it
I don't care if you just add an extra penny for like 4 months
For real
Just allow it to hear that soundbite again I'm holding a hostage
It only comes out for globulin
But anyway
Tegan requested
That we go back
Was interested
Yes and so the theory was that if we go back to St Patrick's Day
We would be able to find drunk
It is even though he's well not Irish
Wet vac
I started to listen to them
St patricks.day is episodes Cinco de Mayo
Interesting
Let's cancel the show let's just go through what holidays you think Alex
Arbor Day
Saint Patrick's Day
Going to be drunk
Noon Riley's Broadcasting 2:49
If we go back
Can we look at
The day after
I think we have much better likelihood of hungover Alex
Usually esoteric Alex which room
Great
Sometimes
Still drunk
There's a chance of that delightful 12 a.m. still drunk Alex
He instilled
So I went back to 2014
And we what we have here is the March 8th
18th episode
Gets into
Witnessing
Hungover man
As well we were discussing
Stop does he do it
What was no recognition or Patrick's Day had come over when
Space f****** Potato Famine pieces of s*** coming over in our country
First immigrants that the reason that we have these Muslims to begin with
What's the trouble
Little weird
A little weird
He's mad at 8
Pacific
Athlete
On the gcn radio network
GasBuddy gcn
Genesis Communications Radio Network
Owner also of Midas resources gold sales
Just a reminder
The Marriott become more and more relevant in the future
Maverick I'm sure there's no reason that you left
I just like to remind
Everybody knows Dan
Does not leave things into these clips it's definitely has no purpose behind
And no live from Austin Texas Alex Jones
Responsibility
LeBron James
I believe it
Actually dinosaur media
Attorney
Basically
Sports figures
Known as Ron Ron
Because
Piranha
Hang out together constantly
Steven Price
Bullying enslavement and it's no longer free infected cost a lot more'n
If you're really feel
Really does he sign up for
LeBron James
Literally
Better than anybody else sign up for the Giants
Obamacare
Today
That's it
Who thinks he's God and let me be clear
He plays it like three more times that's all
Further education from LeBron James
Here's the reasons that you should
Sign up
You should go get signed up McDonald's commercial
I was waiting for those
Where was pretty girls
This clip isn't done
LeBron James
Sam's Club here is where his head goes
This is immediately after
Give babies acne
That would be a weird thing for Obama.
Would be more honest peace there
If you watch the video his hair is
Wyoming all over the place he's screaming he's going in Real Performance mode
Not feel stuff
Kind of counteract that cocaine
Probably little hair of the dog on top of it if you want to talk about Obamacare in the
These shortcomings
Sound variance
I don't feel like you need
Need to jump all the way to
To be covered in blood by Satan because of abortions
The Killing black people vaccines and
Sure I feel like it's muddying the Waters of the debate
If you do a lot of people would say
You can't be like okay well yes
It does cover.
Well yes it does
Expand the number of people who will get help Ensure
Which then of course will lower health
Cost for everyone
U-Pull-It people paying
Health insurance
Is a socialist
Idea so I'm sure that
What he's really trying to say
Is that we need a more aggressive approach
Why is it that only adding an extra 30 million
I'm still leaving
Success
Perhaps what we should do is really Implement universal healthcare
Bathe ourselves in children
I think one of those options
Okay
So after this clip he loses the thread a little bit
LeBron James
Basically
This is like
You're in no shape to be on the radio
Healthcare.gov commercial
Very sad
Special
Constantly
Reflected Glory of their president they're in charge and
They're the bosses in
About to do
I kind of long one
But just right there I wanted to take a second
Universal axon like this is 2014
Flash for two-and-a-half years
The idea of the reflected
Pride you have about your candidate being on the winning team doesn't look great
What's going on Eric Trump is the only person who can save the world
I never heard that before
All right.
On YouTube Mania Philly
We could be that could also be the new Miss the end there
I love to channel judge smails how about you I don't know what to say
Just got to be like
What the f*** is going on this show has started
Weird things the problem there is
I doubt he still alive
I don't have no idea about Judge smile
From Caddyshack
Alex references him a bit weirdly
They look similar or at least Alex
Will look like
It's possible
I honestly don't know what judge MI
I have no idea
I don't remember the exact
Alex Jones maybe like I watch to it
And I don't think I've watched
Maybe I should go back
I don't have
It's pretty good but I don't have time
I'm listening to Alex cut the clips
Got my ears open
Listen to this b*******
Alex
Heart open can't lose antlers
More or less
Obamacare
Cloward and Piven mindset which discussed in the past
People don't remember
Well it was two University professors who had an idea
A system where everyone is
Constantly of all the social welfare programs
Or available to them already
Bright actors
Millions
Billions of dollars
Food stamps assistance
Housing credits
If it's available to people that they don't take
And would help people if they knew they were available
Ratso cloward and Piven is an idea that
These people had
Hey you tell everyone what is available to them
They get all of the things that
But they are entitled to under these government
And in effect
The system because
It's not set up for people to
And which is why in the 90s
They did have a guy wearing a green call Everett
Yeah they're there their thought experiment their idea was not so much
Actual
Listen to crash the system as much
Cuz it was
A way to get people to on
Understand and realize
That there are
So many people
Need help
Believes that Obamacare is
The Peace of this
And it's trying to crash Healthcare
In order to bring in socialism
Many ways
Single-payer
Universal Health Care is
And in this next
Cliff
Obamacare
Cost will
Mainly because when
We have a republic
Looking president one of these
Is that
Executive branch has control over what subsidies
Can and cannot be put
Together
If you don't advertise
Like perhaps if you coming to work louder
And when there are fewer people in an inch
Insurance market cost for the people who remain in
Indian
Market go up
What is
In a nutshell
A self-fulfilling prophecies and Alex Jones himself has helped
Bring about you are in the Obamacare market right now
Blame Alex
F******
And his ilk
News what happened
Whenever you Underpants
Just take the rug out from under the idea well in the same way that and Bernie put this
Bernie Sanders America's
Most popular
Politician currently
Put this perfectly in regards
It's to the GOP tax
Which they are going to destroy our revenues for the god
Then later on when revenues for the government
Are so low they're going
Look at how high the deficit is we're going to need to cut
Spending on this
What are they going to cut
Spending on Medicare and
Ultimately the Jeep
Tax plan
Is attack
Obamacare
Healthcare is
Stack-On literally
Every program that helps
Speedball
What is it not attack on Dam
Lariche
The rich
I agree so Alex is talking about that sort of nightmare socialism
Descend upon us
Yes
I want you to try and think about whether this
Literally any worse than
The reality in front of us
Socialism
Dump trucks
Surviving off a little dribble they give you
So I'd like to compare that to the gig economy
What are you talkin about is he describing that as socialism
Yeah he's
Conception is the
You give all your money to the government they give it back to you in
Small kernels
I kind of
You know like that the reality that we live in now where companies are able to have people
Haven
Nothing in very weird busy
Teen scams bright but they run I think that's probably worse
Then whatever nightmare scenarios
He's depicting even his
Worst-case
Scenario isn't
It's on par with right now
Maybe better than what we have on tonight
Your worst case scenario
How the kind of b******* that we have
To drive for Uber and Lyft
The crazy ways that the companies
Just take
Take from them
Define workers as like contractors
Employees
The problems that Alex
Plaintiff
And it seems
Because
Because they do that
They make more money
And our taxes
Which
The Uber and Lyft drivers
Go towards subsidizing the healthcare that they have to also pay for
Like we are subsidizing
These companies
Who are keeping us from getting Healthcare
Because when he
Fun lies about Obama
Specific
And that kind of comes into it really Trace back to just like
This is not Obamacare this is business
Yeah this is this is business she's one of the issues with right
One of them
What is a couple lies
Next clip
About Obama
Or let's
Just called the Affordable Care
Let's not play games
Healthcare was about $100 a month for somebody under 13
The past
$600
The average person
Unless you're 2611
One way or another
Was going out
Conspiracy theory
It was
IRS website irs.gov
Wishmaster bank account
No it's
Ludacris
Complete abs
Salute b*******
Like
I feel
Sad for the people who believe
These sorts of things
Look into it
The year 2017 so this is
Three years after Alex's
The spelling of b*******
Yeah like this
The penalty for not having Obama
Affordable Care Act insurance
Is 2.5% of your total household adjuster
The gross income
Or $695 per adult and
$347
A child
Up to a maximum
Of 2000
That is the maximum fine
There's literally no way to be 5000-10000 20,000
I can't afford it
So you got to pay 45% of your income to file taxes
Interesting also well the truth is they have reduced besides
Is the IRS to the point where
And this should not be publicized
But
They just don't have enough people to actually audit
And
It's not it's not an actionable thing
Trump has laid out
In terms of their priorities
If you just don't check the box
About your insurance
They don't
Look into it they don't come after
Exempt
Built into the Affordable Care Act
About if it would be
Be crippling
You don't have to pay the penalty
If
The most affordable coverage that is available in your area cost more than 8.1
Percent of your house
Household income
So that's one thing
Or if you are uninsured for less than
Consecutive
Or if you're exempt
From filing a tax return because you're
Income is too low
Or your religion objected to the use of insurance
That's even a f******
Thing you could do you could claim
Do Christian Scientists don't have to
They're exempt for the pedal
From
Given too much credit
I'm sure but
Why they pitch a fit if they weren't
Example.
I'm starting to think maybe religion
I also you're exempt from the fennel tea if you qualify for a hardship exemption do things like homeless
Miss bankruptcy eviction
Or any other of a list
Trying circumstances
Which involve poverty
If you are making under like a point where it would be
Devastating for you to have to pay a fine
For not joining the insurance Market you are the only people that makes a difference
Are people who
Really really should be in there
Poor person is going to be charged
$20,000
He's playing games this is for people like him the people who listen to
Are the people who almost
The people in red states are already subsidized
More by wealthier Blues
Totally because they are tricked by these con men
And they are voting against their own interests
The same way they have done
Since
All the time
The sad sad shell game
Being played in
They purport to be speaking in
In favor of
That is that is the system
That Alex is upholding
Is bizarre stupid patriotism
Deconstructing a little later than episode
He's mad
And in his mind
Obama is a criminal
Yes trying to pull off this
Criminal scam
All over the world
Horrifying criminal scam of preventative medicine Limited
Insurance
Yeah and the rapture globalists
Huge issue
Bike
You know what babe
They don't get
Trouble they don't get punished
But who does
Well Alex
Talk about 1
Kevin Trudeau
Starbucks
Years in prison last night
He was
Borders
Call
We didn't
More
I'm not support that means I'm not going to support
What is that mean I don't know what that means
The point is
Just study the con
Prison
Superman
Twice
Got 31
What's going on here
Daiquiri what is it
Infomercials
John's Wort good for depression
Honest he's good for
Discovered
Kevin Trudeau
Sogo glisten Obama aren't as bad as Kevin Trudeau
Just a deal with that thing to talk about at the end there I Kevin Trudeau had a website called meet Illuminati members
Lowes.com
Where you could join up for $1,000 and he would introduce you to people in the Illuminati
$6 a month
I believe was my monthly
You keep up your Xs
And I'll be an Illuminati member
Torn between wanting to protect
Stupid people and wanting stupid people to get their comeuppance
That's just at the man that's a great
IQs of Nantes
You know you know that something is not true if you see through the b*******
And you want to
People like
Use it
It's making people afraid of the globalist
Was
A bit worse
In many ways
So what time
Weird bulshit
Decatur bunch of books
They don't want
You to know Lex food secrets
And he made
A number of
Really really
How many vitamin C's only one of the things he also
The starbugs the graduation sun doesn't cause skin cancer so but what does sunscreen
So you should
Perfect
Someone who's gotten drunk on float trips I will tell you don't
Not put on 3rd Street
Super extreme sunburn
It was
One of the worst couple days
Is not being able to move
And just like biting a pillow cuz I was so much pain
Is terrible but you also encourages them occult
I'm gazing you invited me out on a float trip
You son-of-a-b**** on sunscreen to be fine
Stolen polonium all over again I got too drunk too early
Do you get to
The more the more biographical.
Details I get a
USAA
Fantastic
Advocated for just like folk remedies
And stuff like that
Whatever
Also has a bunch of stuff about like there's a
It's called Coral Calcium that advocated that was like
Will save your life
The miracle cure ulcers
Which
Very bad people
Reflux is a
The myth
Can deal with it by
Cider vinegar all the time
The whole bunch of claims that he's made over the years
And a lot of close to becoming l.ron Hubbard
Claims
Things are just not proven no backing
I'm sorry
So over the years
SEC and the FTC
Because he's making dangerous claims
Lymphoma
Yeah he's hurting
Right cuz I got a lot of complaints
There's other complaints
Cheplics Loudoun court orders
To stop selling this stuff
I mean to
You got a multi-level marketing
I'm going with selling these products
People and have them sell to their friends
So over and over again that there is Avon for Pure milk or Infowars
He keeps being told
Ensued
Any lawsuits
You can keep writing your book
And selling them
Cuz that's free speech
We can't
Suppress that
But you're banned from making infomercials
Or selling your product
And he wouldn't listen
He just kept selling s***
We ended up getting food or I believe the damages that they they affected on him
Was 37.6 million dollars he had to pay a restitution
Ford
Consistently defrauding people and you wouldn't pay it
Gizzy kept floating court orders
That's such a weird
Okay
You can publish books
Yeah
Can't go auntie
What's the same thing that happened with Erwin ship
But because
Profiting off the book
Right
But be that as it may Trudeau is a guy with a
History
I'll just
Like real f*****-up crimes and scam
Classic snake oil
Yeah he's The Music Man
The monorail map
Kevin Trudeau poses a doctor in order to deposit $80,000 in false check
Eddie 1991 pleaded guilty to Larson
Federal charges of credit card fraud after
Social Security numbers of 11
Customers
Memory product that he was selling
And charge
$135
58 cents on their credit card
He spent two years in federal prison because of the convection
Balls later his interview he explained his crimes and quote youthful indiscretion
Here's the problem with catch-me-if-you-can
The wrong guy Leo was playing Kevin Trudeau I think we would all be honest
He said it wasn't as bad as everyone thinks
That's all I got to say I'm just I'm starting to like the bald-faced lies
It's like a man with way too much
I don't know why that should be illegal or anything like that
Cuz I thought you was a doctor
That was a simple misunderstanding because he jokingly refer to himself as a doctor in memory
Alright
Regard I don't think
Bad guy here he also tried to
Cool a lead Kong International pool tour but because he was just
You know such a con man you didn't end up paying the people on the tour
I bet a job for a while there I was I was actually aware of
And plugged into some of the professional pool playing
Community
I know some people
Interesting late like like the black widow I bet she got she got taken
Didn't buy that because of the disaster of it
Because of like
The distinct that put on
Like fool as a national sports club in like bowling two certain
Poker caught on real hot
A good long while we didn't end up paying people
Except like
Reminder
Parts of what they were owed
National Poker Tour
But a professional pool competitions as a whole
As one commentator put it
Quote the pool Hustler wasn't murdered by any single suspect
But the last man holding the knife with Kevin Trudeau
You know what's so weird about that he could have been present
America eventually what did he do with literally any
Different route
It's f***** up is just worse
He would be depressed
Yeah they probably had access to like or didn't
We made some bad choices of lawyers
Hey if you are if you're trying to pull yourself up by the boo
By lying
If you're already rich
Your but also 37 points
Billion dollars is what he was supposed to pay and didn't
You got to consider that's not everything you made
How much do
I have no idea I have no idea I'm going to be a lot of
Stuff like that kind of like
Weird cons
No
Cuz we ain't making s*** I know right if you think our main issue is morality no
Creativity
We could come up with all these talking households easily
Abreva
What would we have what we have policy walks multi-level marketing
Think about it
For $150 a month we will maybe send you a picture of Celine every now to be tough
Take pictures of her at least one of her tearing up last
Sounds good I just wanted to go into that cuz I was listening
Text Kevin Trudeau
I didn't know so I looked into it
Defending interesting
He wasn't
It doesn't doesn't gated like a guy who commits
Go to bed for seeing an event
Supported Trump seems interesting
And this together
Looks like he might have some of that history in his his own life
If you actually go to
I don't know if I have it pulled up
This might be a subject for another day
But I was reading a bunch of reviews of the Infowars
Which is the Infowars multi-level mark
Nothing but complain
About like
They won't return product they won't allow you to send
Think back
They overcharge you customer service
This is terrible at these people who are buying in bulk and selling to other people
You got to assume that
Oh I wanted the reviews
It was very clear that like
They take down reviews
That's why they have such good reviews for all their products
Yeah I've had experience almost everybody doesn't like
Hunter back to turn over
Say loaded more about him
About their dinner
US Weekly
Putt-Putt Obama and Hillary Clinton prison
Abs
The Four Seasons
I mean
That's rude
Nothing compared to LeBron James
Rolling out
Amora
Michelle Obama Care
Emergency room Hospital
Most of which are hospitals
Caprice
Regular Hospital
Hippocratic Oath
Call Allen
So what
Actually advocating
Is
Government subsidy of hospitals
Instead of government subsidy of insurance
Slightly problematic for his philosophy
Run
These hospitals
Necessarily
If half of the shift they do is free
Unless
The government's UPS
Yeah
Getting back to us fake pass
Right where where everybody does everything for free
Hospital
I would like to believe that they got rid of the Hippocratic Oath
I hear that all the time
I would like
Leave it at some point in history that's how eyesight operate
I think what he's talkin about is like mission
Catholic Hospitals in
Stuff like that
They had
Standards that they put upon themselves
In terms of charity
More than welcome to do on their own
You can't force someone to do charity
Under Alex Jones's Prosperity libertarian
Right
Somebody want
You would need government regulation
Congratulation
I'm proud of you
You nailed it
Kind of he got it
I think it would be a 20 your system
To have the hospital
How to take care of
Everybody have their own
Government-subsidized
Easier
It's freedom of going wherever you want
Do you know if you when you go to the hospital if you're in the hospital going to be free or not
I think this is going to be a hookup and then
Anyway with Deli
You show up you never know
Inefficiency
You could be operated off
That's nonsense
There's no way there be able
Uneven
Even if
You would like every time we go through this though
There is that
There is going to be a fight
And it's going to
Come from recipe
National Health Service
In Britain
Has been
Because rich people don't
Want to
Right
When it comes in always comes back to
We need to
Behead rich people publicly
In front of children
I think that's what needs to happen
Navigate to drink
I guess I don't agree with you metaphorically
If you want to do something like a national health
You're going to wind up having it
And it's going to work
People are going to love it and then eventually the trick that's always going to be pulled is
Well it is working
Sing well
Selecta Fonda
Work is well.
And so then you can say well you know what would work better
And then privatizing it happens if people go this doesn't work at all even though
Kind of idealistic
What's going on in the world
There's a lot of stuff that's half
And one of the things that's
Is that Russia is
Crimea
Still alive
Sure
And that's okay
Not Alex's that can always live forever
Alex
A little bit of steak
Bathtubs
Situation in Peru
Also we're going to get into
Is projecting weakness
Obama
They're not weak they're incredibly evil
Does Obama is just a figurehead
Global Empire
So what's going on in a little bit later
I think I'm running out
I think I'm running out of patience
Driving me insane
Kamiya is not
It's very much
Before we go any further
From what I understand of that clip
He is saying that
The Israeli defense
Is saying that America and Obama are projecting weakness
For not intervening the Crimea
Alex's take on that
Is that no
Obama's in
Instead promoting
Globalist
By not intervening
He later I'm almost there
Defend Russia Annex and crime does not understand that
By not intervening
Obama is not acting as a global defense
Annexing Crimea
Putin is making
Uce expanding your Empire sexy
Yankovic
Adjust flat
Back to Russia at this point
Write the way that Alex is presenting
Is
Boettcher
Gourmia is going into Russia or being annexed by Russia
But Obama is managed
To take 98% of
The country
What to take
Yeah let's get in
That I don't know if you fully spells that out but that's what he gets at
Like the idea that they are for their strong
If they have the rest of Ukraine
It's weird it's weird
What's bet he doesn't get into it right away
Fake news
Before he does backs
The first piece
Just waiting gun store was fun
Infowars.com
He doesn't really cover it and all that much detail but if you go to infowars.com
Find the article at
The quote that he's taking
Is
Basically
Fun paperwork is
That's a quote from the guy
Rating a gun stories
Is exciting
Sitting at a desk
Doing office work
That's not what you say
That's not anything about like I love grabbing guns
He's completely misrepresenting that even
Even based on the article that's on
Infowars
It's not what you saying just read the headline
Giving his own
Now that's
Editor-at-large
So you're another piece of that nonsense
Report
I told you it's a long time
It wasn't
I'm not imagining this
Greece
Insofar as
But you are not imagining it and being right
Interesting way to parse
Mostly and updating of the Telecom
Medications active
1834 which wasn't updating
The
I don't know I don't think more than before
And the reason is because back then 30 whatever
Slightly different
Answer what it actually was was
About regulating
Monopolies
And that sort of thing
Which is a good
Instead
CeCe is allowing
People like this
Sinclair
Two outlets in small-town
But
Forcing people to get what is essentially
Media
And then eventually that it will all be owned by one group
Something that we all know is evil and yet
People are consistent
Bentley voting
Struggling
I love to be shy
Phone call
In the article.
Drudgereport.com
That should be the headline
Headliner
The problem
Let's not
What what's going on
Right
That is not
If you read the entire rod
Canton Post article
NPR article that goes into what's going on
The United States has the capability to record 100%
Of
4 calls
This isn't
24in
This is in response to
To foreign countries
Is that have
Interest
Terrorism invest
It's
In terms of a technology
It's chilling
Certainly
Yeah but also that goes into the
This article
Is that
They have the ability to
Record all of the
Phone calls with Alexa
Indonesia
Or something like that
Deployment collection system
The recording every single conversation Nationwide
Billions of a rolling buffer
The queers the oldest called as new ones arrive
According to a classified
Of this program
I called Mystic
It's messed up
I don't like it
But Alex is misrepresenting
Even even William Bennett
Alex Jones is NSA whistleblower
It was saying
Recording 80%
All the phone calls which would be
Money but that's also not active
Based on information
Come out
I think I might
Actually
Gree with Alex
Spirit
Write-in lyrics letter absolutely not
The
It is it is the absolute
Worst thing
But it's
Not any
Indication that they're recording every American
Phone call
And they're not letting go of them 4:30
The people that we know that they have
NN the more reports we get out of
Snowden revealed is that
They are not
I'm against
But at the same time I don't like
Sensationalize versions of it
Cuz then you're not dealing with the reality
We have Alex's version
You're never going to
The deal with the situation
Exit
You're going to be having this
Scary Boogeyman version of it that every single thing I do is being collected
Good forever
Stand up in it
Orin reactionary violent reaction
Okay neither of those is productive towards getting any
Anything done
So that's why I even though I
Have that capability
It seems like a bad thing for us to have
Developed at the same time
To be honest
Clear that he
Keith Lyon
Yes
Even even wrote an article about it around the same time
Yes and they are like tamerlan Tsarnaev
Boston bomber
But she had a phone call to Chi
Was being asked
About MSNBC
Please have that phone call its
Just a matter of whether she would
Agreed to discuss a tourist
She's going to have to
Deal with it with
Operation
And
The reason that that's not
Not as scary to me as like
An idea like that
And that's how it's being presented
The reason it's not scary
Cuz those dude we're under
Sedation for quite a while they were on the FBI's radar
There's a collection
A phone call
Their Associates
And things like that that's not
That's not that surprising
Use of spyware
And the fact that they bombed the f****** Marathon
Is indication
To me that
But that line of Investigation is worthwhile
Yes
I I don't know you know that's I think that leads us to a very interesting
Conversate
In regards to
Do you think it would be more effective
To have
This kind of got
So there's a certain percentage of the population that is never going to respond to
Reasonable faith
Right
Do you think it would
Be helpful
Do you have a guy like Alex Jones
Sensationalizing what is Anna
In order to mobilize people who would otherwise
Do you still be mobilized correct
I don't think they could I don't think they could either
Reasonable at like when you describe the reaction
Is that these people will have two hits
Sectionalized
You have the impotent
Can you have the
Violent over
Half-cock
The guy
Went to Comet Ping Pong
So like
The reaction that you're going to get realistically other than anti-semitic rants online
Yeah and people taking super male vitality and doing nothing
Okay
My next question
You though is what is the reaction
That people have
The reasonable fat
Free question
Which I feel right now is
Informed impotence
Yeah Thursday
Not just
JustBats
Football people
Lobby Congress
Some Congress members have acted
I need 2015 Obama.
Stop the book collection of metadata
People have rationally taken action
And gotten a lot of this rolled back
Not to what extent that actually rollback is almost impossible without
But
I mean we can't operate on hypothetical information that may or may not be true
I don't know I mean that's that's why I asked you I feel like you took it a little bit defensively
I didn't I just got excited by remembering that
The year that yeah that's true
No I sure exactly how it is that we should know about
Because the other argument dysfunctional government but I mean the other argument against
Is that because of that bulk collection
We do have those recordings of the phone call
All right
Would it have been
I feel like it would be more
To reduce the signal-to-noise ratio which is something that we've I don't do it we've come under Fire for
A million with
Preventing 9/11 is that
We have so many different
Threats that were theoretically monitoring
That you can't give any kind of credence to any one over another
I don't disagree with that so it's hard it's hard for me to say
What is what is the most effective situation
And whether or not and Alex
Jones
Disregard helpful or hurtful
Situation
Answer is
I don't know how you would implement
But I would imagine that's way to get around this
Is
Have
A civilian board with confidential access
Whatever
That would have oversight over until a
Or something along those lines
She's just a rubber stamp
What note 99% of that. What I'm talking about I'm talking about like how they have
Civilian Watchdog group
Veteran place for police
Departments in some
I agree
And you have to have like tops
Clearance for these people that
Ridiculously excited that point do they be
Become a part of this
Security apparatus
Wakeboard almost 38
I can't be from the body politic right but can't be from Congress
They're going along with it
Then we get into the f
Be safe and you can see how they have been captured
The same offices
The bank's that theoretically
Do a lot of good just to move their office
We're not going to solve this issue
Will
I think you and I are going to get to the bottom of this
Tonight
How many more codes to get through
And how we solve the security apparatus
The way you were talking
To some extent makes
It sound like I'm in
Favor
Augustine
I understand that but it could be biscuit
I just find it to be a very fascinating question
That we wind up
I think we wind up getting
That were able to talk about
Insofar as
The same the same question that we often have witches
What happens when Alex Jones is on our side
In a certain way
Can we utilize
No
I can never be sir
In the same way
Somatic blog
That attack Alex for being
A shield of Israel and stuff like that
Do you make some good points about how
Jim sometimes they are never allies
They can't be
Right
It's frustrating in some ways because
Like it in a perfect world
You could
Theoretically team up with Alex
Can fix the drug laws
Forfeiture
But you can't
So you're debunking The Art of War
The enemy of my enemy
Is not always
Absolutely
Alright get in bed with
People and you just
Too much comes along with
Don't get in bed with son to
It's not a bun
Slipper Alex
Explain what some of his
Fears about social
He's not right
Unemployment sometimes when they were
Which is welfare
Godiva chocolate shop
Service jobs
Undercut workers
Your welfare card
Psychological evaluation psychology
No.
If you're on welfare you should not be spending movies
Military
Watch
Sanctions against
That's an interesting sort of a 2B 2C daddy kind of
Through
Yes it's Warfare
Is not
A realistic
Sick pass that
People go down
When they get social assistance
Not really
It doesn't even track gramatik
No but it is it is it does make sense in terms of his fears because it all does come back
The gun grabbing
I'll get it back where it was two sizes
These negative path lead
R2r gun
That's if you are mentally ill we should take
He starts at Point a which is people going on welfare
The path of the yugos from agency
Is it is nonsense
Bizarre it doesn't it doesn't
Connect anyway
That's what that's all fun and games
I guess this next clip
Perfecto
This is so f*****
LeBron
Narcissistic childlike smile
Like they're five dressed up like Batman
Guitar birthday party
The order the five-year-old getting the ride with the cops
Batman
Cystic glow in their eyes
Shell's actuate
Become the wrong person
Narcissistic
More about
Humanity and building system
Honorable
You're still an individual
But it is more
Honor System
Abby
Mickey videos
The Dark Tower
20 starts
Calling about your old books
But
Narcissistic
There's ever been
Do you know who
If you talkin about the
Make-a-Wish kid
Became Batman for a day and everybody
Join them in the sink
The Make-A-Wish kid
Make-a-Wish kid was fighting leukemia
Okay
Alright
That's f***** up
Narcissistic kid riding along with the police cuz he dressed up like Batman
Birthday party
Tv85 leukemia at 1
People fighting it for 4 years
He's a Make-a-Wish kid all he wanted to do was be Batman
So the people got together
And they created a whole scenario where any Stop The Riddler
And people
Did a
Very good and charitable thing and it is Twisted
Tire World part it was one of the rare like viral kind of things
Just like god dammit that's great
Alex Jones
LeBron just not narcissistic
Compared to what he deserves to be placed on being probably the best player of the sport ever
Call Sabine one of the most physically impose
Using athlete ever and this presentation is stupid and all this stuff is very racially loaded
Absolutely you listen to interviews
He is not stupid at all.
Modest
Ford
Looking for his talent level person
Like people have asked him about
Plays
Like 10 years ago
And he remembers not just the
Play he remembers
His thought process through and he remembers how he spun the ball through the like he's a
Brilliant map
Unfortunately 2014 I believe
If I remember correctly that was right around the time he was making
Deal out of his
Decision
I've going to the Heat
Don't even bring it up bring it up if you didn't know anything else about him
Yeah that would give a bath
Taste that was bad
All right but a lot of that is marketing
How much of that was his
Choice or his idea unclear
Yeah who cares at the end of the day
Now
At the end there
He's getting every
Just putting aside him shiting on a Make-a-Wish kid
At the end are you getting into
He's gay.
I wasn't
Sure I wasn't at
At the Ender's getting into like this
Gene is the
You want to be a man you want to go and be with honorable people he's such a
He's such a
Weird f****** ass on here is where we take our jump
Into esoteric nonsense we're going to find
Real f*****-up
Laughing as he says
A couple of
Weird brags about his past
That I can
Handsome agenor
No you haven't
And that was no you haven't
What a fifteen-year-old
Ancestors and their family names to be strong
15 year old
If you are a man by the side and almost every culture
What
25 mil
I want to have some fun first
Only worried about yourself when you lose everything
Collectivism
Free association
Literally stereo
Civilization
Imposed by those that wish to sabotage
Great secrets
Known by all cultures thrive
Forgotten secrets
Revolution
That's why people in every old culture
It was a thriving Noble culture
Noble
Their honor at the fact it like a
Bulldog
Hold on and never release
A all seasons
I think a b**** got over the wall
Misogynist
Senior bulldog
A lot of people out there claim you want Liberty
Contest
But you don't act like
Perennial
Has Birthright of George
So there's a lot of dog whistling in there
It was
But it was it's almost
Too dumb
Lunatic
To really be effective
His dog was other stuff about like
We want to be
Individuals freely associating and that is the real collectivism
Willie actuated
He does not know what the word Act
I doubt it but all that stuff is
Rambling nonsense
I don't see any of
Principles
Place in a lot of pain
Civilizations that I've
Read about
What you haven't read about all of the ancient
Civilization
All of the ones that have right except of course
Free pre-literacy
F*** you
I know that
Especially the
Most
Cultures didn't have an
Idea of the free market
Not a big deal if you look into like Native American civilization
You look into
Bad way to put it either the first peoples
Yeah you look at a lot of South American cultures
Even
Summon Africa you don't
Even have an idea of manhood
That was all about dudes
Yeah
Nothing about women
FurReal matriarchy
Nothing he has no interest in talking about women
Place
In society and you kind of have to assume that means
His vision of it is
Observe
Division of it is secondary to
Twomad
It's just
You need
To be women for men
And that man of course
Pichu
Code of chivalry or whatever that he's old
More about that
Clear as it goes along but I'm
To jump into this
One of my favorite thing
This is one of Alex's weird childhood Bragg
This cannot be true I guarantee please this is my sound
The specifics here
So stupid
Narcissism at about 85 I remember it
Understanding
Imagining I'm a team
Imagining I'm powerful imagining I'm dominant imagining is is a fraud and a
Why then I could see another children
Literally
With the wisdom
Who sings the old men
LeBron James who is literally a child ladies and gentlemen
Liquid death
And poisoned
Do shine up cuz my laundry
6:30
Obama is using bron James like a puppy
A bag of candy
Get the child in the back of the
Torture Center
Nelly weeklyrides unpause here for a sec
I don't know how one individual
14 snuff films probably small logistic
I think the limit per person
But I don't blame the puppy
What is pumping
LeBron James
A weapon system
Great
All that aside
So at 5 let's talk about child develop
This is knock
Do you know what's going on with your cognitive development
The age of 3 when Alex Jones
Old man
I think that's when you first
It was like
All the child psychology
At 3
You are
First learning how to interact with
Other human being
Subway
Guttural
Speech patterns
You were first
Your first perhaps
Define Concha
You have your baby
Now
You are also
Able to access
But only
If you're at
Individual
They have this year from
From the
By the office of child development
Pittsburgh
Children start to pay
Stories
And are able to respond to
In the story
That's how their brain
Is that they're able to understand
At 3
For the first time
Size
Add yellow and blue
They start to understand
Counting on a very basic level at which
All that stuff
Understand
Sound similar
Like
They start to be able to tell the difference
Difference
And socialism
Start to be able to develop the idea of
So scared of like
Things under the bed
Start to have a creative imagine
A tiny bit
In terms of being able to
Play make-believe
Sorta relevant to Alex's
More relevant is the fear of the monster under the bed
Think that's where Al
Haha
I'm so at this point
For your cognitive development
Involved
Where you're able to
That age for your able to
To stretch the truth a little bit
The children before that generally aren't able to
Come up with
Counterfactual state
Children were also able to much more than before work
Cooperative
How's that evolves around
They are
Accessing
Where do we get to accessing the wisdom of the ages
Maui
At this point child development age 5
Irrelevant
Children
Their play is more evolved
Costumes
At age 5
You start to get the
Maybe Alex
You know dates
You became more able to
Stretch the truth
Rabbit 85 evolve
That's my theory and I'm not going
Stick to it
Man what kind of donut
Would claim that it aids
5he
Man you understand
Legitimately
Is when you
You start to be able to understand that night
And they are
And they're on a cycle
Yeah that's the kind of a development that you're able at
Able to understand at age 5
Like
You might be able to count
At 8 spot
Credibly
Developed
Unless you're one of these savant
Right
Is not that based on
But we've been able to
Discern
He is still unable to
You might be able to identify all 26
Might really
I was able to
Look some people are on different scales is
Was just generally generally speaking we're developing
What is at those
I don't know
Steel male child psychologist
They can't
Diamond exotic Diamond gusset saying about it
Steel mills went down south
So like the only reason I bring of these sort of examples to give a generalized sense cuz I don't know if our listeners all have kids
Leaving like that but like there's no way at 8
3 Alex's
Like I don't think he could even
You know I think happened I think he watched a Wes Anderson movie and was like I'm going to pretend I was
Yeah that's how I know a lot of people
That's my that's my best guess
Salinger
Anyway I look for Alex continue
Esoteric ramblings
About
Your honor
Dishonorable
What are you f****** talk
Good for me
Geometry
Been following me for 20 years
And they know I'm honorable and have the blood of Honor
I just accessed
Basic primary operating system
You can access it as well the Hardware's there
You have to accept
Stop being insecure
Human programming that God put in
Or you know you deserve
Score of the universe you're on a plant you want to go to space
Do you want to travel
You want to own the world
Yoorana beautiful
You're part of something amazing
Huron fantastic
Forbidden Planet
World of wonder
The mysteries of the universe fill out before
Transcendental experience
Full spectrum Consciousness with the Enemy
Stores opening Friday
I am not their biological
Replicant
I am
A man I am real
I am free
Nazi Justice
Just one
God wanted us to be free
Did you notice how he switched
Listen to his fake voice
We have to make the decision
Woodside wieser
How was William movie commercial
The universe
They stare at the reflection
As the narcissist
The reflection is not
Reality
Reflection
Only
Dimensional
Facsimile
Genetic research
We have a photo of the grizzly bear
Not the true genetics of the grizzly bear
Not the way it actually works
What is a photograph
Of God
Don't distorted photographs
The real power
It's so hard it's so hard to take him Siri
It's really are bad
It's all her fault it's our fault
Trying to say here about sports
He's on the sidelines right now how do you feel about being part of the Stardust of the unit
So like
He's just
He is just
Trying to
Get through it
Social break
You like
So he's going through this like
Manly Hood honor blah blah blah
Get to the esoteric
Kind of kind of shape you can tell vet
Grilled
And then he's like well
I've milk this for all it's worth let's go to Special Report
I got nowhere to go with it
Auxiliary do we get back to Russia
It's about the next like a little bit
She's not done
Some of that weird heading on
But
When he comes back from the
These regroup
After that
He gets back
Get back into Russia
Entire world
The Obama the secret weapon everything's okay
Nuclear war
Ironic in current context
Not
Can see him be like
Actually I'm going to go with
Nuclear war cuz he's white
So there might be a chance
After he says that
I need to I need
I need the sperm this one up
What do you like
Outdoor
He's trending
Absolutely
Yay so
I mean I have a lot of feelings
I like some of these Noble culture ideas
I have the blood within me
There's a lot of
Vaguely racist
Talk
He starts off his next wife with a
Let's make the subtext
Little little race
Graphic 12 as well
Already
Ocean White Lane
Announced by the way
Watching
Don't struggle
Important before they do the procedure
Your mouth
This is going to hurt there's not going to be any anesthesia
I would like that.
Patriot Supply
He's noticed he's not a smooth with the ad transition back then
Mypatriotsupply.com Alex
My Patriot Supply products
Interesting
Do you know if you if you could make a Supercut of things that he said
And it would sound exactly like
A serial killer
Right before murdering
Thousand percent before he
Yeah but I feel like it's
Because he said those things to evict
I don't think you're the only person who's
Something that I was
Is the idea of the demographic
Cliff
What comes down to is generally like we're not breed
That's exactly what he said
Ideas of like we are not going to be able to replace everybody
Acura TLX not accurate
Can pretend that it's be
Because more immigrants are coming in
And all of that
But ultimately goes down to
White people talk more
So earlier in the show Alex
He was talking about his fears about welfare
Declared mental
CL
Alex
Reveals
That
Being mentally ill is cool
Trendy
Gusting f******
Please don't
No
Hospital
Mongozo
My child has a mental illness I'm going through a lot
It's really the coolest thing to do
Patriotic
Artificially schizophrenic street corner and you can wash your hands
You know we don't know why is a mentally ill woman on the street
Bobby is what
We did the best we could with the doctors will be right back stay with
So
Food
Dude
I mean it's so interesting
F******
So many layers there are
So much
So much hurt in that one clip
So much damage done
So many lives in that one clip
If people like listen to him
You are
Possibly stigmatizing children and their parents eyes
I mean
If you are if you are an Infowars devout listener and you have children
And your kids are
Mental illness
Help
Do you need to get
You need to get
Do children help almost Christian Scientist I had a mental
I didn't do anything about it
Tell my parents
Cuz they didn't believe in mental illness
I didn't do anything about it
Until I was 20
Because they didn't
Believe in mental illness
And I was
Braids
I was
Terrified that they were actually going to stop
Caring about me or they were going to
Send me to some sort of religious therapy
Get them
Type of s***
Hit so close to home today
It's f******
That mentality of that rhetoric will lead
Two peoples death
Absolutely does quite quite frankly I mean I don't want to get it
In-depth about specifics of a lot of stuff but like
If it weren't
For therapy when I was
Am I
Team
Even
Sometime I spend
Mental hospital
I would be
I would absolutely be debt because
Why I went to the hospital
Cool and trendy
It's because
I had
Serious issues
From
Alex good debate all day whether it's red dye or sugar
You know anything like that
In the street and say
Oh we tried but they're mentally ill
People who don't believe in mental illness or people from Noble
Yes yeah
Absolutely
Real and let me see
This
Like
We're getting better as a society in many ways
About mental health issue
In terms of D Stickman
Sensational
But at the same time
I know at least
At this point
People are not
Bragging about their kids
Being mentally ill
That's not something that happens that's not like
Hey Mike it's f***** up omigod you get snow out
That was something like that
Because
There
Most parents
Hey babe
I have two remotes
But I think there's a lot of people look at their children
Themselves
You don't brag about negative things about your kids
Negative
Do not like
There's a bit about
Being bipolar and it's a really old bit and I couldn't
I thought about not doing it at
But everytime I go on the road
In some shity small
I get at least one person who comes up to me
In these small towns
Thank you
Thank you for talking about
I know somebody or my kid or meet
Thank you for talking about this because nobody talks about it and 8
It really means a lot to me
SpeedZone import actually just f****** give people a space to talk about
Something that they are ashamed up that they're afraid of
All of the
The s*** and it is
It kills me
Kills me
Will do this s***
Because it
Mrbeast
Legend suicide attempt
That's it.
This type of s*** is
God dammit I could
I could be dead
I could legit be dead because of this exact red
You're great
I'm in the next Club Alex F
Globalist
Club Alex Harkens back to a time that never
Wonder wonder what he's talking about Austin I run into YouTube football players
I run into professional
Fox and they are just mentally ill
Arrogant people walk Walking pitbulls downtown
Bumping into people
A bunch of narcissistic mentally ill twitch
Because first of all they weren't
To say that I guess that's true
That's again
That's just
I think it's a little race
Real
Only white people used to do athletic
Haha
Yeah all the history of in Major League Baseball
Major League Baseball up until like 5 years word arrogant
Alexandra struggling to not say like
Uppity
If we transition
From weird sort of race
Stuff to gender
And I want you to succeed be successful
Competition with a strong
Society strong male-driven
Society
Patriarchal
Buy 1776 individualism
So he's made it clear there a patriarchy
Empowers women
I know their place
I don't know I don't know
I don't I don't understand what you saying but he's never been impaled ribbon
Society
Clear
That's so clear
Histories
At least of all the cultures
Patriarchy
Are self-perpetuating for machines
That old early
That that's
F****** monstrous world
Through most of them
Pre-market
Yep but
Whenever you give women power
Only good things
It does seem like there's never been a negative result of giving women more power
Look at
Trying to think of one negative result
Societies throughout
No tribal time
Right
Trying to think of one
Sprouted into a
No
Generally speaking matriarchal
Societies always
Prize the happiness of
All members over
They
Everybody got laid a lot more
Simply because women have the power of choice
Send I also that you know all number of
Selfish male Pursuits are better off
Absolutely
Alex Azar
He's getting
Weird rambly esoteric headspace about masculinity and never bring it up
Towards the end of
The show be like
The global tape man
Driven Society
It is all just Victor
But it is all just
I am I don't want to give up my place in
Is there any harkensback to athletes being better when he was younger
Or any of this other ship
Talkin about is when
White man wearing Chargers
Delegate people have to hide
Make America great again
Of course there's no way that someone is on the radio spouting this kind of rhetoric
Who has a history
Long documented history of bigotry who is about to begin
Can't not think that that's what he's talkin
It's f***** up
Really really
Deeply
Deeply troubling
Man
Better example of why women
Should have way more power it
It's just listen to this into
Secure
Same
Piece of s***
No much
Misplaced in
Insecurities
He's a fragile man
Fear their sowa
Braids
It's amazing how terrified these people are under the year of
Righteous anger and positions of power
Doesn't relate to his like love of Putin
Yeah
That's
He loves big dicks
Love big dicks more than Alex
Love's
Besides Queen
Cancer ribbons
Replace cancer ribbon
Pens with
I think
You should do a second
Not a good idea
Nada
We know there's a Eugenics operation
You think that's too long
In the White Stripes
Little messages
There's a program to destroy the families
There is a world government
The New World Order
They are the enemy
Discover the enemy or perish
Giant sticker
We're talkin billboard at this point
People be driving by squinting like what the fuc
Positivity f****** accident
That's a bad idea to write that on Eddie Vegas
He'd start with a big letter a better just get smaller and smaller as he tried to send
He has a lot of spin on the situation
And it's not good
It's pretty bad it's the Russian lion
Broke
He does bring up one thing that I think is
Worth mentioning
And it's an article that
Interviewed Ron Paul
On the subject
I'll just play this
Residence Inn
Autonomous region
Scotland
96.7
That sounds like a
Suspicious number
Very similar to the number of
If you look into it there are there have been
Done after the fact that say something
The tune of
80%
Of the public think that
Warfare
Reflect the will of the people
Suspicious too it's also 6
Per cent lower than the people who voted for it
Then that seems to be a significant percentage
Seemed strange the reasons the International Community generally is called
Referendum vote in
Question
And one of the reasons is that what happened
The peninsula of Korea was
Occupied by Russia
It's on
Clear I don't I don't think there's enough
Information
To say it was
Completely rig the vote or anything like that but there are other red flags
Generally dictators end up winning by
97% very common number generally whenever There Are Places
Is that our voting
Occupied by
Interested parties are me
It doesn't
It's not fair it's not fair election
It's weird how
Huge
The population of the vote was
For Hitler whenever
Invaded
France was like
Vote for Hitler
Yeah and then the other the other aspects to is
Is there were tons of
Reports of
Pre-marked ballots
And stuff like that that there's a lot of
Build-A-Bear in relay
Tow the Russian lion
I don't believe it
Heat would be like
Oh my God
It's so great
Even a newbie like this
Even in Catalonia where they were talking about the vote tally for Pro Independence
Even then
They also carry out of that with
And the other side
Entirely so it's like
Yes independent 1 with 90% of
People reporting but all the other people who would have voted no
You know
Boycotted the vote in Scotland vote
Tippecanoe
Devoted
We believe that the Breck's
I'm going to end up working I don't think it's going to happen
But if it does
Northern Ireland which will be very awkward
So the reason that I believe that Alex
Incredibly biased
Coverage
Is everything I know about it
This neck
Where he is
Super defensive about how patriotic he is
I meant says something right at the end of this two-and-a-half minute clip
It makes me think
You. The protest too much
You couldn't
So also
That's bad
That is also
White
Strength
Confederate
You scumbag trailers
Tell me I work for some foreign government
You know you are you work for a
Can you tell me I'm not a loyal American I will stomp you into the ground for the four years where my answers
Ancestors one
America
Thomas
You are the rightful heir
Why
You want to raise your own children you don't want to abort
Or where you're from
Can push around 10
Also love the Russians
Do we have 50% off sales for joining Colombia's Independence
Same structure
That's f***** up
Yeah I didn't even think about that I just thought of the comedy minutes of
America
You've hit me with enough add pivots
For me to know when a pivot happen
Yeah it's structurally tonally X
A hundred percent
What a fucken day
So I mean
Sure
Russia is a communist country
No
And that's great
I guess
Right
I mean in terms of Alex's rhetoric of being like
You know there are sovereign country in whatever
Economic system has always been
A autocratic oligarch
No it is not
Putin has been in
Power Center
And he has been up to some s*** ever
Before that
I need shown his colors
In many ways
Stripes
And the fact that Alex Wood
Sync
Like
They're cool
To the extent of Love Freedom
Yeah
Anthony
To the very
Stamp if you would
Make that kind of a statement
After this rambly b******* about patriotism
Just shows like
Either he's the dumbest man in the world or he's a foreign agent
Exactly I mean like
I know we don't have evidence of a believe everything except
Andrea Lee
Like on the last episode we
We covered hoping to be the last one that is put out at the
This point on the episode that we did back in January
Where are you
Like my numbers have doubled
And my money hasn't gone up right we were very clear that he is the
Beneficiary of the Russian Bots
And the Russian
Traffic
Bean Boozled
That sort of thing
And when you start to question
F*** would they choose Alex Jones
We have this glimpse
From 2014
She's been
Pro-russia all along
Because he is
What they would want
To push
That is the only
In which I think
Very
It's very reasonable and probably
Legally inexorable in the heat
Probably dumb
I mean word 2014
Yeah
Hey I mean are they pushing him
No because they think
That he's what they want
In 22
16 or are they pushing him because they've been
Cultivating him
The same way that they cultivated Trump back in 2030
We certainly don't know when he had that talk with Russian intelligence and listen
But I think that's instrumental
But he has been going on RT
At least 2,000
Cupboard on the last episode
The state-run propaganda
So I mean I don't know I don't know I don't know how deep back and cultivation app
Aspect of the ghost
I'd be willing to believe that that was Maurice
But also he's clearly
I don't think I would I think
Are flattering him in order to
Create
Willingness tabpro Rochester
Put on man even then you have to
Consider to that like
His favorite politician in America is Ron Paul and Ron Paul's response
Leukemia is who cares
Right
But at least within Ron Paul's kind of operating ideology
That's mainly just because
It's over there
True you could say like hey did you know that
Russian nukes all of Europe probably likes to cross an ocean
I don't know it's just it's it's interesting but I would be willing to believe that
They've done Alex is unaware of it
To the extent that
Clear surprise
About the numbers going up in the sales not going yet
So that I could believe that
The unwitting beneficiary
This
Acceptance
And push
From the the box in the troll Farm
Not willing to believe
Is it Rodger Stone didn't
I don't believe I absolutely don't believe
I think Rodger stone is not a dumbass
No he is part of influencing Alex
And you can't be part of that without knowing the rest of the
And this is Ken.
Is unreasonable
That it is impossible
For him to be a foreign agent
To you and this
Amor amor
Know that
You know the more we find out about how Flynn was a
A foreign agent
How manafort was a foreign aid
How all of these guys
Have all been working
For other gum
Lobbying for other
Not disclosing that
How long
Has that ship
The answer is
Probably forever
Yeah probably a while there's absolutely
To some extent
It's not political
Like I said
That's why I buy Alex Jones
Just want to get rich
I don't know about Alex the more the all the bulshit flies away
White male fear
Absolutely relate to misogyny and racism
It's real
But even then
That is that I would argue is also tied with
Looking for money
Looking for money and looking for power are ultimately insecure things to
Like donate to the shower
Hazard Apartments to Palladium Luciano
Sent up there and shitzu
Please do check it out
If you want to share that s*** on social media to help us out in terms of boosting the signal
If you don't want to totally cool if you want that stuff on
With knowledge underscore
Fiber on Facebook
You could do it there go to iTunes
Because
It was a bunch of
Stars
As long as you're going with the 5-star review you can say whatever the f*** you want a new game
Meet us thing with a visor
I do know it's just
It's just
You can make up a conspiracy theory about anything
I think I would like to make up
About 1
Couch it that way
But I want to make a couple hundred
That's probably probably going to hurt traction
Alright
Okay so
We've already covered the
We know
Reincarnated Alex Jones
Talk about now
Is what he's hiding in that
Probably rations
You know what I'm going to go with
An extra set
I want time went to a concert and hit a joint
In my beard because I didn't had down my beard
Sounds like I had a joint in there
Put it up
People don't advertise this about beard
Very good containers for
Absolutely
Absolutely true that Whalers concerts a tolerable
A guy who I would also like to entreat
To go f*** themselves to go f*** yourself Jon rappoport
Alexandra Thurston color