Holding
Galaxy color with huge fan I love your work
Magic novelty beverages
Question please.
Clamoring
For a reason to listen to
Show podcast we hear it all the time
When I walk down the street first day you're saying
I love it so much
People of all colors and Creeds come up to you give them the answer to that question
Witches
Why would you listen to a podcast about
Alex Jones
Beverage store you are supposed to go into the bed
Wherein you say I know a lot about Alex girls
You just gave them a perfect reason
Tourism
We appreciate you listening for a minute
You walk up to me
Tell you about this
For the show and I apologize
Spring this on you but
We have a episode 4
A foreign policy
Ivar's
That was
He requested that we time travel back to
And I want to listen to that episode and I was going to get it ready for today
But it's actually going to require a bit more research
Oh no damn it is the other level of Alex Jones is anti-Semitism and I don't want to go in
Quit half-cock the blood libel well poisoning kind of narratives of the
Protocols
There's a
There's another level Tuesday upper echelon
Yes Alex gets into some stuff that I need to read up on a whole bunch more before we do it
Sew-in in calling an audible I had to figure out and what a weekend
Can you do
If you say Carrie Callahan
Nowhere I've tried to find some good good Project Camelot episodes lately but there hasn't been any
S*** no but
Do in episode live
On Twitch
On Wednesday
A Thanksgiving Eve episode
I don't feel like I was able to do the
The Material Justice
Okay so there will be a few people who watch this live this correctly dead
Do yourself after doing a great job.
Constructing things
Why isn't anybody screaming
Yes and so you're doing it again
Well there's that that's that's part of it but then the other part of it is I feel like
You are missing out on this stuff too and it would be unfair to deprive you right
Fall behind
This is all we've never done this before like re-recorded something
I'm Flying Blind
So some of the glistening who are in the twitch stream will of heard these clips
But you won't have heard them discuss Ride Like This
Reason number two through the first reason or is 3 minutes
Glistening
This is
Okay
Can we turn this
Into a
Let's call it
What's the name of the movie with Mel Gibson Lethal Weapon
We're in a Lethal Weapon situation
And I'm standing on top of a roof
Hanging on saying let's jump
Lucaya I don't understand the metaphor but yes absolutely
The show with me
Last week
On November 14th
Alex Jones
Posted a special report
His website
He did a little bit of a livestream
Aunt
She was pretty drunk
I'm in
The setup for this what you really need to know ahead of time is
Recently. Right before they said done
A 36-hour marathon
Came out with an article
Write an article afterwards where guy
Tried to watch the
The entire thing
And he reviewed it
It was Alex Jones
Floridan situation
Look and we're not as popular Morgan Spurlock
That's b*******
I'm at Morgan Spurlock
One time he was in Columbia Missouri for a festival
I hung out at
Good dude
He was pretty nice
Actually I made some joke
Politely
Patted me on the shoulder shook my hand
Seem like a graceful guy
Like as you could have been I told the joke that I made
Was not good okay I don't remember what it was right
But it was not good
Yeah or it was just a benevolent minor celebrity running
That's irrelevant ever want to hear the words
Benevolent minor celebrity run in Everett
Oh that's going to be a new segment
I have a list of what I have a list of times I've run into Beasley
Not being mean
Alright
I thought you was not on that list
Shaquille O'Neal 9ice
You been
Matt is a strong word
I want I'm being my dad's knock into
Lakers
Cavs game
The city and We snuck in before the game so I can get some autograph
Cuz I was probably like
14 at the
And so I'm getting
Nick Van Exel I got his autograph
I looked
I want to mute good I like the Lakers back then I was like my dad's from L.A.'s weather
Shaq and Kobe
Kobe's autograph
It was actually
A benevolence weather
Not a minor one
But
Shaq was shooting free throws you practicing shooting free throws out of
He was also not like you it was not an intense cracked
At all
Going to get another opportunity
There's no other like fans around or anything like that We snuck the f****** through
So I walk up
The Shack on the court
Because I'm
So
Shocked by how big he is
He's very large even though you know he's not big
Depth
So I'm walking up walking up to him
And because I'm
I'm so blown away by the call my God it's Shaquille O'Neal
He was like when I was
He was on the magic and Lakers team
It's so I don't see out of the side of my eye but he has a
F****** bouncer
Get a bouncer to guard while he does throws drink
Downtown approach
Not at all
Don't interrupt
I get it it's fine but check looks
Turns around and looks at me
I like my shrugs at me
The shrug shrug
Shaquille O'Neal the gifts from
Sam himself
They was kids a shrug
Screams
What can I do
And I'll tell you what you could do that guy works for you
Jupiter's f***
Consignment it's not going to cause
A like
Bum rushing
Or something like that
Little kid clothes
You can't do it
It's fairness
Is communism
Anyway
Where were we oh yes
Oh yeah we were redoing an episode episode
You didn't already press contact
Benevolent celebrity running
Can't wait to tell you guys next week about how I met Don Cheadle
You know what that actually might Propel us into stardom
International Superstar
He acted like a minor
Celebrity
Anyway I'll talk about it on the show The Farm
Humble
Stay humble
So at 8:36 hour marathon
How to make money
Desperate cash grab
Article and
Discussed it briefly in the past
It's a
What's article was the way I described it naturally the guy writing it does understand but Alex's
Performance model is to just
Scare people in Enfield
I'm bailing.
But he doesn't
He doesn't deal with like the fact the doctor group is on and he's not a doctor I just makes fun of his
Appearance you doesn't get any of the subtext
The things out
There's no discussion of any of the
Actual narratives other than there to scare you
I mean that's fine but you're just getting the surface
Like Bethea
And that
F****** New Yorker article I'm still very very angry about
Movie over the weekend
Gives a f***
Alex
Pretends to be outraged
Or
I guess
This special report is in response to Vice doing that artists
Of course I will get into a first-year isn't at a concert
Angle
Does it very interesting
Let's have an out-of-context drop from this episode to give you a little bit of flavor about where we're going to be going
Alright
That should give you a sense of the Alex Jones worth dealing with here today
Start Staffing
Way better
I'll tell you that right now
Lord of the Rings
Listen
Redo all of Lorde's
Sure
CGI Alex Jones into the Golem Park perfect
Who if you had to recast the rest of the
With Infowars personalities
Well I would say that is going to be
Boromir's because clearly he's the one who's going to take the whole operation down with his lies okay
Prada
It's possible of course
Go fuc yourself John Rappaport
He's our guy.
No way gray there's no way we cannot make him get out of the grey
Rob do review is our Samwise gamgee I feel like sample sizes too effective
I think it's
I think because Rob do is a fumbling bumbling moron
I know I could have
Said Eddie Bravo
We can't do that
Eddie Bravo's heart is too good to be in these values Tom Bombadil
Eddie Bravo is the Tom Bombadil of this
That's right did you think I didn't know Lord of the Rings
Salty about the other night
Me and Jordan
Girlfriend may have made fun of him but not knowing Lord of the Rings
Ferret
Alright let's get on with it
Here is where we start like I said
He did a marathon
Yes Vice wrote an article about trying to watch the entire Marathon
Then Alex.
Good Humor when I see it
Device
Popular outfit to work with HBO
Obsessed
Daily basis
34-hour ever
34 hours today
He don't recognize
Text Tabitha
Cybermen
Unwise right now
At 8 a.m.
The same
Riveting Transmissions
He absolutely is
Night being boring a s*** and Alex
Ghana's basis if to say like
Alex will be in his Marathon
And again like you can tell the artifice immediately from Rob do being like we're doing it
Okay that's the stuff online you just doing this cuz you
Need money
They might have even better
On Cyber Monday
Half of Their audience
The people 50% off
Free shipping
65% off 75 if you get Auto refill
What's 10% off if you get Auto auto ship
CD clubs
I've gone through and look at reviews of
His stuff in like
There's a number of people who complain about
Like automatically getting set up for auto-ship and not realizing it
Hey been making it less hassle to try and get off of it
That I believe
If you sign a product shipped out that's cuz you're dumb
The internet is not that
Strew
Then you get all the stuff
Guarantee
Even if you sells out
You still get it
The auto-ship
That is not real and does not mix
That is not a real thing that you can do
Again to reset
You did a marathon Vice wrote a toothless article about it now he's pretending that in order to
Or something like that
He's doing another Marathon
When in the reality
Threw it immediately he didn't get enough money from that last one he needs to do another one
Cyber Monday whenever I buy stuff online perfect time
Bada-bing bada-boom perfectly
Going to complain a little bit
Places like pie
Articles
Demoralized
Power absolutely pathetic washer reporting on us constantly
Program
Just start going 24 hours
What's pissing you off
We better
Rakuten
It's all frivolous
It hurts my Humanity
You just described yourself as a missile
Well but most deaths
Starkey also maybe a laser
He missed a mixed metaphor cuz at the beginning you talking about other people
Missile
I don't get it but the way that rambling like metaphor goes like that I mean
But
Is there
She was vice
Is the first
Adjectives used
To describe them
Lengthy
They write we all would have been like oh yeah
You would have read them talking about how he
Like using amazing showman and even though the content was terrible
The reviewer was talking about how he couldn't wait for Alex
Get back on because if you watch these other things
It's just like
Cuz he has a brilliant about him within his
No one knows
Better than us
I would say
So B dude if you're writing another 34-hour
Here's my face
Don't watch it
Call Dad
I can help you out more scathing job
That's a bad idea
I shouldn't have said that I don't think I'll do it
Okay
I don't think anybody expect you to do it
I mean I could not watch it and do a more thorough recap the most people put
Although he's probably salaries
But anyways
Coming out when it's
Too late for anyone to pay me to do it
Next time
Where City
The other thing that he's mad at about Vice
Goes into what
He says there at the end
Humanity
So many
People who are getting
Paid to do
Hatchet job so they turn on me
Right
I think that he associate device
With Gavin McInnes
Okay
Proposition
Yeah but he was out real early
But I think Alex
Still thinks that he's super involved with it
And there's some Lake
This publication should be on my side me and Gavin are cool
And I think there's something like that in his head
Advanced knowledge and information so I apologize practice Mexico
Let's see if you change your mind
I've been contacted this week
Libertarian
Money
Are you okay
They'll be a real boy a real girl soon
I prefer velvet
Interesting Lee they'll be a real boy
Yeah
Pinocchio is about
Well your
You got a better
So alright alright if my theory is correct
I think that he
Presenting this
Like
The flip and now this article comes out
You can't possibly be talking about the actual guy who wrote the article
Of course
Because I
I don't really have any idea who that guy is
I looked at his past I saw that he had a bunch of articles
But he's written that were critical of the alt-right
So doesn't seem like Alex should have any reason
But
Gavin
Vice
Conspiracy
I'm listening
Alex Jones
Rex
That's why it's a huge betrayal
His son
Because he loves his son true
All of that is fabric
The backstory
Play something the Alex
Himself helped cook up
In order
Disseminate
Pro Alex
Material
By the way of pretending to be anti
However
So now lyrics
Okay thanks giving dinner reveals all of this
Text Alex G
Thanksgiving
He loves Americana Thanksgiving is Amira
Araucana every night is thank you
Flying fruit
All I can think about is like someone directed me to
A picture of Alex Jones at Thanksgiving
Yeah and it's always liked him and his wife doing the okay symbol
Towards just trying to troll people with white nationalist
Ironic symbology
Sitting on the couch
Looking
F****** uncomfortable
And it made me really sad all the baby really sad York every level
All of it made me so sad
First of all
Might have been poorly time pick
You look bummed
And then
Alex and his wife
Just say Alex
Taking a family picture to try in
Liberal
Nothing
Nothing says family and Thanksgiving more than go f*** yourself people I disagree with how you don't understand it like
I am very little family values
Like I don't really
But still that seems like
Crafts
To me that's still using your family as though
Yeah
Crack
Co-opting what is ostensibly a family bringing together holiday for
Kraft commercial purposes
The point
Into the end of the real job
What's next play palak brambles a bit about
Some cultural trend
He's not thrilled with
Grab
I should say
You talkin about Roy Moore
He doesn't really doesn't really
Come out and explain a lot of the things you talking about but like side thought
And then they develop
Is Alex's narrative about Roy Moore is not sexually assault
A bunch of people
The miners
Various like sporting events looking for kids
What Alex believes
To be the case
Is that Roy Moore
Like a southern gentleman
Might do back in the day he is
Parents if you can date their teenage daughter
Back when he was like 30
Creepy
But he's not ready to say it's bad like you're creating a fake version of what happened
Hey Ben you're still not denouncing
You're still ambivalent about it
It's very weird
Anyway
That was the setup for what he's talkin about there
Okay let's get this correct
He is
Okay
A grown man
Go to the parents of a
14 year old
And says
Or or perhaps
Now my dearest
Paris
Put on your Foghorn Leghorn
Pull the trigger
Beautiful daughter
Great great job.
This isn't meant to be
A purely accurate
If he ask them
Her father's blessing
Ownership
Yeah then it is
But not much further
He is
Lying about the circumstances
To make Roy Moore look better
And no matter how still get too creepy
How low the bar is is that if you look
Hey pedophiles
Attempted pedophile
Do you know what he's talking
Grab
Manchaca
Infowars.com
I love the
Rob do you nailed it
I don't know
Kronos
You missed the punchline.
Long time
Weird
Alright so
Then recently had a national drag queen
Alex Jones video outside
Got them selling baby
You'll say that I went and watched the video that Alex is talking about and their kids
Adult
That are holding up bills
While a drag performer is doing the routine
It doesn't even seem clear that the kids know what's going on they're kind of just like
Sexualizing them it's not it at all
Anything crazy even beyond that one of the things
That is great
Is that you see
A bunch of
They're in the video that they have
There are kids
Who are offensively crossdressers
Who are doing routines with
People who are maybe on drag race roar like their Idols or are
Benevolent minor celebrity interactions for them
But you're also they have they're getting to have a really great experience
Under Armour
If they were sexually assaulted by
Gotcha
$0
A r
That is not a rebuttal
No it's not
What was
Wrong and I think that liberals no just like ya know he's evil but also you're evil too so that means
But it's not evil
No it's not it's not but that's his argument
His argument is like I'm not going to jump on Roy Moore and say it's fine
Although he has a weird it's anti-christian and the proof is that Christians won't let their daughters date until
Till they run away at 18
That's not a great like life pattern
Do you think it's bad to be anti-christian
Even though
Christian music
Debride Runaway
It's fine
Does anti-christian
When women are subjugated sometimes they are give dollar bills to drag queens
It also Alex is going to mix this up and
That's just worthwhile
Makeup on you can scream a lot about dreams
People
The point that out ahead of time
Cuz it's going to get Marquee
Hi
I'd already Murphy I'm not sure what it is he's trying to attack or defend I don't either I watch this
I was scrolling through the special reports trying to find
Hoping it was
Interesting to cover
Yeah and I was like
This video is 11 hours long
That's too long so I clicked on it and I scrolled to like an hour 5
Or something like that
First of all he has a goblet
Caboose
Is rambling nonsense
11 hours
Of Alex sitting there drunk
This is going to be amazing
Cut to just be repeating video of bacon pancakes mixed with New York by Alicia Keys
No it was just a upload glitch it's only like an hour and 10 minutes
So excited
11 hours
Make communion cakes making me so f***** up an hour 7
But it was not to be
I'm sorry this entire thing in like I don't really
Exactly what is
Except Troy Moore is creepy but he's fine and vices
Life is
Abandoned
If it's true I will.
Where's the pretty frock
How old is wife compared to his
If you look at that she was 25 when he was
Are you making the Goddamn point
Yeah here's but they are also missing some facts
Go at different points in life is
Is totally fine
No big deal
But there are some indications
He may have met her when she was
And he was 20
So if that's the case then that age difference is very relevant
I think we did but like Alex
25 + 35
Doesn't have any knowledge of either the actual
Situation he doesn't know Anthony Samwise gamgee right over there to help him out
Not exactly right
F****** insane
Alright
That is gross
Roy Moore is gross
And if you write anything nice about Roy Moore you are gross
If you say anything nice about Roy Moore
You're gross
Doesn't even include the pedophile ship
Yeah yeah yeah
It's very frustrating to me that this is not
It's still not enough you can win
Probably he's going to win
40 years too late
Harps on that hombre.
That's something that I've been sort of wrestling with this
Is it going to be a downer
I think the Battle Is Lost
I think that at this point
All we can do
In some
Respect is prepare for today
Play cuz I don't do it the way that I see the people who could
Help
Not helping
Yeah and I don't mean just Alex Jones
I mean
Big pig
Picture a lot of it
I don't
I do not see
Necessarily activism and
I hope I hope a lot of accept
But like
I don't necessarily see you away that meant
Neutrality is going
Tubi
See how that's not going to happen
Inside the stripping of the
Neutrality rules
And then when you have that you just coming through the internet is destroyed
When I was thinking along the way I hope there isn't going to be rolled back by
If they have any tax cuts
Yeah and that probably I think
I think there's a good chance
That they're going to get that.
Point
When you adding
Here's the hero of the piece of it that I should have realized sooner
Together with
Why the f***
Did Donald Trump
Immediately restart
Is 2020 election
Why did was one of the first things
Is he dead
I was install someone to oversee Alexa
It's because
They're not planning on
Running a fair game ever again
They're not planning on any of that and when you take away the net neutrality
You end up with a situation where all information is disseminated
That is
Exactly and then you will have the tax cuts that are going to destroy Healthcare
Going to be scrambling
To live
That's right not to fix
Society not to make
Active change in communities
Not to help the disenfranchised because they're disenfranchised themselves
That you're going to have a situation where I mean
I don't want to be alarmist about stuff but like modern-day feudalism
Could be
Tears away
Something like I'm here
I8
It's
Absurd to me how close we are right now
When you have a president like Donald Trump
You got nothing mean you got none
I've got nothing
You know Jen genuinely along the way over here I was thinking about
How it is that we could ask
Something done
In the Democratic
Situation that they cannot
Is how angry everyone under the age of 35
Angry we all truly are they don't have any concept
Majority along that what we need is somebody to
For a minor office
Like the house
Somebody to run for the house
And actually channel that rage
Into a national
Every race now is no longer a local race
Is it is completely National
Because we all know at this point
That
We can't do anything local politics because National politics
Has completely taken over
And even if you are in a state house
Or something along those lines
The Republicans control those ledges
Even then
The Deep the people in
In Congress are trying to defund those things
With this very text Bill
They are taking over every local race
And turning it into an Ashley
So we need somebody who is capable of channeling that Rage of young people
And actually turning it into an election win
Because as much as they can
Screw things over
Young people are still a huge majority
To my my
My idea
I generally can't help the person who
Channel that rage
Alright
Starting new party
F*** that s*** party
That's what we have to start doing bro
Even if they have great voting record
Are not capable of doing what needs to happen which is to develop a national movement
I think that if a lot of Democrats
Stepped down or a lot of
Babe just cleaned house
I think that would
Maybe have some
Positive benefit for the younger folk like getting them on board
Weed legit to get rid of people who are 50 and older in government term limits baby
That can't happen anymore
We have some gloomy ideas about where everything's going
Anybody would like to help with my campaign
Great
Let's do it
I'm going to do you know when the next race is
I can see it now
Are you on this December
Sure
You have my support
The issue is that
That really is the only way
At this point I disagree
You don't think so
I think collapses
Alright well see that's where we might actually
If we can actually turn these protests
Into a real
Political party
I think that makes a huge
Because
Is making a big stink
And then nothing
Where is if we can turn all of if we can turn black lives matter into a political party
We're in a different world
If we can turn the women's March
Into a party
We're in a different world
Just
We're just incapable of doing that
Maybe
Still feel so helpless
Due to the position that we've been putting
Maybe I don't know
Let's get off this cuz otherwise we're going to be here all night this December
Three weeks after the votes have been so
Mostly mad about the vice article
And so I wanted things that he doesn't like about anybody you ever reported
And Donald Trump
We don't use anonymous sources
And Alex in this next clip is sort of
Not understanding how that works
And really wrestling with the issue
News articles
Find me Frank Sinatra
Frank Sinatra
Hitters baseball
Lucky chops
Subway
Frank Sinatra
Avoid that lawsuit
I just got a source
You just switch the knife again
Thank you for
So
That was probably the most
Self-reflective he's ever been but while talking about other people
Yeah just want to disrupt and get attention exactly his
Business model
But then he said it like on his mirror he's got all of that written
And then on top
That a to-do list
And then he's like he pulls out his phone and he's like oh what's that buzz
Reptoid
Hey like dude
Funny refuse the switchblade as a phone if he's doing some physical comedy would I be in on that
Beat the thing is
Alex doesn't do that
But what he does do
Is Pretender
He pretended is callers or high-level Source isn't it like that
Three high-level libertarian online people give him a call and say
Are you okay Rose groups are coming after you
What are Soros group
What are they
What's the score of screw their roving bands of soros's
And also they are
Enemies of the reptoids thesaurus is in the reptile
Source of the bad guy then cuz he's aligned with Mark Richard
An hour and trouble
No because the reptoids are the good one
And they're on BuzzFeed
Staff according to Alex's fake stores there the reptoids are fighting the Raptors
So in that case George Soros has to be erected
Okay he's good
I don't care anymore
So I mean he's he's talking about himself he's projecting
I'm into this about talk
People under globalist mind
Control
And I believe it is more project
They're just worldly and take they're angling and think like you're a sociopath
No no
No I'm not
Rebuttal
No I was
Shut up
Current time station
A good thing
If it's emotion and it's what I'm feeling it must be real
Pinterest
Jordan you're having a real intense with in the year did you ever hit yourself in the head with the mic
This one
This one was banana
Well he's doing even when he was like
I'll just do what I do
You're right
Literally
Word for word that is a perfect
I could not have described his job better
Look what I can do and then you're like no I was just giving you an example of what you say
He's at he just described
Sort of self perception of how he interacts with people is fastened
Like his idea that he goes up everywhere I look like I just want to build
Cupcake over and over again
Outlets instances of him just being abusive
People on the street
It's not about your words.
You just want to build what you meant was let's go bacon
Let's take a lovely cooking class I think we all should take a knife skills class
Cooking shows people get cut all the time
It's true
Is very important
Cupcakes with light
Ridiculous
That's that I like when you're banging your head about it like him
Just projecting like crazy
More prone to bang my head about that like idea that he polite
What's that really bothers me
I think it's just
Cuz he's got the booze in it
Accurate about what
I just can't deal with that level of projectile vaguely in your like a lot of
People who are filled with rage and stupid
He doesn't know what he's doing
I know I just it's too blatant
I like it at least drunk at least
How you doing
Little bit
Drunk
Trying
That's what I'm disappointed in Alex
You're better than
Anyway
On Monday Cyber Monday
Name for it
Cyber Marathon
In this next clip they don't come to that conclusion but Alex and Rob do
That's not bad either they don't they don't land on that okay they trying workshopping
Wheel of Vice
Vice wheeler
We love rice we love him
Rodger
So at this point Rob do we love by three love MSN
Yeah the camera on
Which is a good
The camera on the picture that they used in the vice article and
Double chin
Is it ever mentioned that he has a double
No no he's just seen a picture of a
Cell phone
I have a double chin
I mean when I read the article at that didn't even
13 Even
Dawn on me
I looked
Very very Petty
Right he's a very vain man he's obsessed with it
Do the clip goes on and it comes up
More
Oh my gosh
First annual Alex Jones
Stop time worshipping
Misrepresent
You got there
Did he just
Okay that is that
What is that
Goddamnit that's
Set the title of what's her name's album
Have to misrepresent toad Fiona Apple
I mean
Board certified projection but it's inaccurate
Jackson the idea that like
If you want to get traffic all you have to do is s*** on me
The greatest biggest podcast in the world
But
They wrestle with
What do you think we're not misrepresent
Maybe we should be misrepresenting
We should do one episode where Reid is live
See what happens
Buffy did a musical episode
Like eight like actual Infowars
Be drunk this is how we actually do an episode where we
Fish places you know how at the dollop occasionally though her
That's the way that we can do it that way I still don't have to know anything about allergy guidelines
I meant I'm interested in giving it a try fake Alex Jones Clips in my voice
I'll play them for you I will explain what's going on I like this this is not coming up
But before we do that
Alex got talk a little bit more about Roy Moore
Now they're real comedian talking about there is Aldi like brigading that they do with the like
Giving bad reviews to Amy Schumer stuff because they don't like her
And all the alt-right
Communities online that's what they do to make it look like
Nobody likes something
Cranston
Consideration the actual product
As opposed to you guys trying to make it look like
Ghostbusters with women is the worst thing ever
We was good
Yeah I agree
I could do with a little less mugging to the camera but with a little more
The little morzak there is no there's no large enough amount of Zach
Backwoods Pecan Valley character and his evolving backstory
Delightful
Shutdown
Alex Jones
Pivoted on a dime there
Sitting at his desk
Scrolling through stuff right he's drunk and he's just looking at the internet
There's something about
It doesn't
He is worried about it at the other as well as well as everything else turns out
There's an article that talking about how him and Shepard ambellas
Did Defender Roy Moore off the show
So he's getting defense
He's a nice type of
The shambler
Jobs
Break
Charleston
We are literally what you're doing right now
Yeah
Which President is the reality that the early charges were told someone they were pretty
Is not
Not at all
Even from day one that was not the case
The end of the world you get to live in
When your
Alex
Read headlines
And generally only look at
Media that is
Full of s***
You can make stuff
Exact
It's a bummer
What is
Alright
Cuz at this point I quit that stuff
Okay but here's my quick
Quick interruption
And I am sorry about the end
I didn't have anywhere
Alright
Do you think
He thinks he's in a bad spot with
Okay so you genuinely think that right now he's like
He's kind of scrambling to figure out how we're going to elect
Worm his way through these all these landmines going around there
And he's not sure if he can pull it off
So he got drunk
No I don't think
Ahead of us
Yeah I mean it's not a terrible idea
It's like
It's like not going to
Because
If you don't try you can't fail
Right right if we're drunk trying to do that you can just be like
That's drunk Alex what are you going to do with that guy now and I'm sober more stuff in
Episode has hasn't said the n-word
What
The Roy Moore stuff in this episode is accidental
I think because this is just about trying to announce the marathon that they need to make a lot of money on
This stuff is not stuff you means to talk about
And it's so far removed from anything that they do let me give you the reality
Who is drunk to the two of them are having some drinks
You like this Marathon that we're going to do
Do get the camera then that's what happened
All the content is
Drunk
Ivar's whatever pops up is what they like
I don't have the audio
Awful but like there's a period of the show where he's just like
Photos of automatic great report today made it plays like 20 seconds
Powerful interview with Michael Savage
The Alex Jones internet
It's terrible
It again
It's just to promote the marathon
But your question
I do think he thinks he's in a bad place
The Roy Moore narrative understand that like
I'm over a pickle Barrel here because
Come out pedophilia and I forgot
Yes yet at the same time I'm coming out very hard
Pedophilia
The only way to really make this argument
Whatever the only way I can make this argument is to
You say that all the women were making the accusation
Exact
In the same way that he does with Trump
But the unfortunate thing about that
Build a cottage industry out of Bill Clinton is a rapist t-shirt
Right and how do you listen to Juanita broaddrick
And stuff like that and so
You got it
I think you can pull it off if your allergy
And you never let them realize that the two things are
Inherently spiritually contradictory to each other
When you're like no the women who are attacking Republicans are liars
The women
Are Puritans no driven women
Need to defend them
In the same way that like
Liberals defend pedophiles across-the-board
Comet Ping Pong
Now and then
My theory
Disgraceful web genuine
Especially with guys like Mitch McConnell even saying like
I believe
One I know Roy Moore
He's gross
That's all I needed to know
I think one of the big things that is influencing Alex
Is
Normally I think
If you would go straight after other line is politically-motivated it's all liberals
So many women
Have been coming out now not just
Anyone in particular but a
Across-the-board
Because of that there is an influencer
That has happened which is wife
Against their
I guess their political
Like Mitch McConnell his best move is to say
I don't believe
The same way the Alabama
Best moves
The Alabama Republican to support who support right now
Realized
Hey we can't
Give a step we got a lock ranks even harder
And not allow anybody through this war that's how we're going to get that now and then deal with the reality Leigh
Later if we have to
Of women
And he's
Can I be clear I don't take this
I think that the reality is that there are very few politician
That Alex Jones
Has Don suck
Such a load work
In terms of branding
As
Trump style Trump Revolution politician
He spent
Out like a month
Before the
With Roy Moore
He gets it like a f****** Roy Moore comes to things with
Guns out
Alex
I think Alex in order to turn on
Would be a really f****** big deal
Cuz he doesn't have there aren't a lot of
Rump
Agenda people who are actually
Inauthor
Then why isn't he saying they're all liars
He is
Most of it yeah
Stuff that's not lie
Is the idea that he went and asked
Parents to date their teenage daughter
Senior legal in Alabama
Very gross but it's still illegal
Alex says it all the other stuff all the assault all that stuff is why
The only stuff that screw is
Slightly creepy behavior I'm not for it I don't want my daughters being engaged in it
But I get where it comes from it's a southern tradition
That's
Really difficult position
Cuz some of it you can't say correct move is to say it
Unconventional
Alex likes to create an entirely robust picture
You can't just do the most sensible thing all the time in believing a woman
If you're on the right wing
Do not do that you're going to get yourself in trouble leaving apparent woman
I think that's more what he's doing is believing the dab
It's not believe in a woman
That might be even more to the point of what's going on
That's a good point because the dad boo come out and say
To date my daughter
Daughter
Like I said this is a marathon
Commercial
Anthony's next Club
He doesn't do any address
Yeah which is an ad for our add
His professional wrestling level of
Is kayfabe too
But the next clip here he discusses some ideas that he has
As for the marathon
The first annual
Vise appreciation
Jayla
We will invite
Great
You're great f****** man
Martinis
Big sombreros on
He's allowed
Listen to stern
Really ever
Do listen that's not what it shows like
Any more anybody
Howard Stern knows that his entire career
Was fighting
It was all being censored and him fighting against people censoring him
Extant
The use of little people and stuff like that
Was
Make a point
I don't know if I don't know if I'm going to give him all that credit
But there is a rebellion for Rebellion
In terms of defining the lines of free speech
Shrek Alex
If you wrestled with that a little bit would die
I don't f****** step to Howard Stern when you're trying to make your dumbass jokes
In your ad commercial for a commercial
I don't understand how having
People in sombreros Little People in some browsers
Just losing the thread
Yeah he is he's just he's just mad living poorly now
Going back to the drag queen
I brought that up earlier so it didn't come as a side free unhappy with that
Alex
Not good
So unless you think
But the idea of getting little people to come to the marathon was just a joke
I want
I'll have another track
You just talked over him saying extravaganja
You f******
He's drunk Izakaya
We should have it
Can you get hired
All the attacks
Oh my God
He's a patriot he's Pro pre-market
He's on Howard Stern
The first annual
First of all
But
If there's any
Very large part of me
He wakes up
It's not like super hungover
I like that was a good idea
Let's do it
He probably
I've been robbed
Who we don't know for sure is this
Buckley is like
I think it's a great idea
But
I don't think we should follow through with it yet
Give me more years would weep subjugated
And the thing is like
The only reason that I have an interest in him actually
Trying this
Just like
He does not have the grace of a Howard Stern
So just be a
WeedMaps
Trying to use exploitation as a performance piece
Or whatever it was
Hey buddy
No it would probably agree
Spectacle
Like it would be
It would be a serious misstep
It would be comical
Which is where we're really turning I love I'm starting to turn
Really hard toward this is now
Hilarious
We have to
Acting directors of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau
And that is a
Actively hilarious
It's awful it's stupid
But I'll be god-damned popes
Isn't really funny
Pretty crazy
Alex said the special
Is obviously him
Yeah that's obviously him giving up the game
A little bit but he tries to save it you're immediately after
Should we
Liberals are
Olympics
You don't get coffee from your head
You don't get beat up like that
By the way
Media Matters
Jihad Christmas
I forgot about that
He's going to get into it all
Here's Alex Jones
Alex Jones is transgender people
Are usually super ugly
Why the average American Airlines
Good myself I just have a grandson
The Cowardly Dog
Yeah I like how Rob do is playing the salacious
Scrum character right now
Yeah a little bit play a little bit more towards the end
Swig's or something refilling his drink
Maybe doing coke make noise
You know
The issues with free speech
Yes
What about
I don't think we have
Go
Alex
His continued existence is a
Demonstration of free speech
And action
Right
People who may or may not have been plant
Throwing coffee at you when you antagonize them on the street
That's not your free speech being in
Encroached upon
Media Matters writing articles that again or toothless's f***
That's not your free speech being an
Encroach upon
That's just
People responding to you appropriately
And let's be clear that inappropriately
Media Matters did write an article about this and it is
Worst things about trans people in the past
For sure we've discussed a good bit of it but I think it was the same day or the day
Right around there
That he had that South Africa
Apartheid
Proponent
They didn't have an article about how we had one of these Swede Landers on just lying about white genocide
So
This is why
Well that's not going to get the liberal
Twittersphere up in arms man
That's in South Africa
Huge issue
When I when I start had a little breakdown earlier was saying that I don't think we have
Chance
I mean it's stuff like that
Just Like You cover these
These things which I'm not saying
You shouldn't cover
What is about trans people you should
But you also need
To pay attention to
Him saying that
Charles Manson
Advocating for a white coming around
Advocating for a white nationalist group in South Africa that's spreading lies
In alright communities
You're in America
So
We're antifa
Which
Celebrity goddess should
Who's the Sharon Tate of our day
I don't want to kill anybody so
I don't want to answer this
I refuse to play a game come on I wasn't a suggesting that we actually kill somebody World by the media
Delray
Because
You think you love Lana Del Rey but also a Charles Manson probably loved
No no I'm worried about you but see Lana Del Rey is the only way we can truly love something
Thing is if we kill it and it's
Well Lana Del Rey might be past
I do not like the last album as much
She's not pasture Prime
Do you know these blogs online pretend that she's an Illuminati princess
The only reason this doesn't work out now she seems a lot happier now
Where is enter first couple albums it was all like I want to die
A little bit baroque-style that's
Does not work
Unless you're kind of like
Unless you're bummed
You need to be flat and bummed out uplifting songs
No
Not happening
Odd matters covers their coverage is incomplete
That is exactly what we got to do with the what celebrity would you kill if you were at
Charles Manson was your Castle
Has nightclub
Great Alex gets back to the issues with the crossdressers
Yes
Splits hairs a little bit about being a
Complete
And then
Put Gavin McInnes as business
What if I want to
So first of all
Already were indicted did you notice those appropriate language
He's talking about him
Self but not when he's talking about other people
He uses slurs when he's describing actual train
That's a subconscious tell
For he knows exactly what people
Purposely doing it to put them down or maybe in his mind he's doing it to rile up live
Maybe that's what he thinks he's doing
He's revealing that he's
Filled with all of these
Or attention is more important to him than other people's
Felix that's
Everything probably
No matter what I say or what I do
Geology
What about the gay stuff
That one place
Technoguard
It's just crazy
What were you when we get here is what's crazy
Not sure
Picking up women at gay parties maybe I don't know but like what he's doing is basically
Do you know the government has a failed stand up comedian
But like
He at the way Alex says it and this is obviously with Gavin told him
Is it he got kicked out of stand-up because he was libertarian
Kicked out by the HR Department of Commerce
We got together and had a comedian
Notoriously Collective groups if you'd like Survivor when you're happy
Take out that way
Probably was at
In college he met his wife you would probably at
Some sort of liberal party because
Is
What he was when he was younger
And so now he was up
He presents that history of that that piece of his life
Probably just a hack
Comedic products that idea like
Go to gay party to pick up chicks
The old wild women
Just repeating, Diaz
That's what they called themselves as
The classic comic move like
I can get away with
But I don't have to take responsibility why can't I say these words
Richard's territory
That's one of the ways that you can
You can tell a failed stand up comedian
If they're on right-wing radio
Yeah that's pretty much I guess metallic might have wanted to do it
Doug Stanhope
I'm not sure if that's the point the finger
But
Because I kept saying these words I just wanted to say
Watch that Michael Richards
If you take the offensiveness out of it
Really pretty fun
What is not reasonable
Look at it as a human experience
And like
Just look at like he is
Blank slate
He's opaque
You can see into his brain
Do you like
Oh no
Yeah that's trying to say
The dynamic of like the host has to come up after
Is the comedian you forget about that stuff like
Tom Dreesen was hosting that show and had to come up after
When something goes wrong
Never never to that level but
I'm what I'm saying is
I bet that probably wasn't too hard to get out of actually I think everybody at the end
I think so
Did the show I'm pretty sure
I don't know idea though
What you want to be the man I think I could get out of that
Next Comic-Con that case
Here's a new game show
How quickly do I get out of the sweet like it's like Name That Tune
I can get out of this mess
Get out of this mess in a bit of crowd work and one bit you have you have a comedy show that's going on on a sounds
The audience doesn't know they're part of his can I get out of it show have a regular comedy show that's going on
For most of the show
There is a negotiation of I can get out of this in 4 minutes I just got out of
Get out of the truck
The comic was onstage just something
Super f***** up whatever it is
Maybe Moon's the audience automatic
You got to get out of
That's a good idea
What was the other show we came up there was brilliant
Deal or No Deal
That's true
New podcast
Drive me crazy
You get out of it
Get out of this mess
Endlessly watchable
So this next Cliff Alex
Does not get out of it
Not good
Permission
Wrong word
The people act
No one is
Dan is reading all of his responsibilities
I don't think that's bad
It also is not
Real that's not within the video
There's no glittery dicks flying around to be kids
There's not a big official
Evening and over drag shows
And they conveniently went and took video of the daytime
Workshop types.for meet-and-greet
Statue
Pretended that it was part of a
It's just I mean it's it's a ship game
Bye.
Again just beat you can't talk about Roy Moore without
Jumping off the issue I love rubbed coming in and Alex
Not prepared to deal with
You know what he never actually said that and now it could be like
Does not rescue
Knox
Going to have to
What do you say about that
I actually think that is creepy
But I can't say that
Better pivot to drag queen
My audience of love that
This Mech
Clip
It starts with energy definitely when you get out of this
Deeper into it
I don't know can you get out of it like a borderless
Think your way out of a stand-up
Mass
By confusing the audience
Cuz if so then I would be like I can't leave the show otherwise I'm not sure
This starts with these drinking booze
The end of this clip is just labeled
I don't know I don't remember why
I guess you could say I'm
Americana
I don't support suicide
You want to kill yourself
I don't want
George Bush
Agree
We have finally come to agreement
It is okay bro Mark commits suicide
I didn't edit that
No like that's just him his brain straight
Because I am not going to say it
I struggle with suicidal
But he just jumps to that really had
I'm drinking red wine I love the red lady
Suicide Vine but not forcing people to have suicide Liberals are the fascists
F****** Roy Moore
Little bit of a pause
GameStop
And so here's where we go from there
This is this is my territory
Him and his own
Super southernway
Older men were looking
You took care of her but
City Rollin
My dad
Younger
My first wife was four years older than me
Could stop at any point
.
To his credit he doesn't elaborate like you'd kind of expect him to fall into a pit of his own making there with you
I have been waiting for him to
Hit the argument of like
After puberty
Look if you believe in evolution maybe you should
Like that's what I've been waiting for the hammer to drop
This whole time you don't believe in evolution
You liberal Hypocrites think you believe in evolution well Evolution Theory web
For that is the wrong clip
This is a mess
This is a continuation of the thoughts
Say that for the rest of the clip I'm not
CareCredit he doesn't like descend into a beautiful or anything like that
Straight Talk
Transitions into this
Judge Roy Moore
It's all suspects
They can go get
Alex is drunk
I need the computer might hit the spacebar and it started playing the flute
That's so like you hear Michael Savage's voice kick and he just looks over the computer kind of scared
But only because I found
For children
Celibate
I digest I just always wonder what they're going to make up
I do too I wonder
I wonder what they're going to tell the truth about I wonder I like if you just told like
No
Headline
A buck
Alex Jones headline
Creepy ramble about 35 to 40 year old women
Hey
Yeah I have probably sexually assaulted some younger women
Almost but I like I'm old
But let me tell you something I really want to sexually assault
And all of you out there who should that sexually assault 35 to 40 cuz guess what
Spot Suites
He has more to say about older women
I was 16 hours
Spell stand-up comedian.
You're not looking for the virgin
Dingle B from
And Rancho
Live
Who played
Beautiful
So God almighty
He leaves it into Islam's there but also just that that f****** lying the older women
They're the ones who won
Does argument actually hold water with Lana Del Rey
Younger woman
That's so cray
Where his mind goes from there
Today he talks a little bit more about his
Alzheimer's
Who is this
Crochet
Women
That's weird
That's very there's multiple weird things in that like 35 seconds
You can't say that I'm not for women
Because I
Prefer the company of with
Or there's women around me
He claims to prefer the company of women
Very true
There's a decreasing number of women around him at Infowars I will say that from everything I I can tell
Over the years there used to be a few of them
There are fewer there's rainbow snatch
Millie Weaver
No that's one
And she's not there all that much
Busy being a failed committee
Lee Ann McAdoo is basically just over Skype sometime
Never really in studio
Right only confuse Legolas by the way
The only consistent woman I see there is
Is Daria his Russian translator lady
That's the only person that is there all the time
Interesting
And she's just there to do Yakov Smirnoff jokes
To Alex off air
In Russia global
So I talked about for a little bit how I like
His daughters
Croup cough
And
Whenever
Spitfire bedside
No I tell them to suck it up
Congratulations
You are raising your children differently based on gender
That's arbitrary you're probably going to give your kids
Joy
Okay
He thinks
Little lot of his fear of Islam
Is based around
Yeah right
Why isn't he more afraid of Roy Moore
Alabama Roy Moore is closer than wahhabi it's Islam
Claymores in Alabama alexand Texas and Islam is everywhere
It's at the pool store
That's true it is at the pool store that's that's the perception that he has
Scared all the time
Anybody who's not white
It could be an enemy
That's not good
No it's very bad
Very very bad
Now it's bad thing it's called
Prejudice
Family raising strategy
He says this
Buried
And try to get the kids separate
From the parents
Kids go upstairs and play their Xbox
The kids are hanging out with us
It's not less
Under the groove this point the ender portal good counterexample is
Weeknight making a video with him
I don't know where your kids are in this equation
Probably drunk without commercial for commercial
I don't
Get
Like I
Do they just think it's him
Possible for
People they disagree with to share similar values
I don't think there's any hardcore liberal parent that I can
Could be like
No
Togetherness with our children we're not worried about our kids at all but they have to say that
Otherwise they don't get to take ownership of any kind of
Family Values
Abundantly
Clear
Alex Jones and Rob Duarte
Incredibly privileged people they have a lot of money
This pill scam they're running and have been for years
So
A lot of times
Families that don't have a lot of togetherness
Probably a single parent working two jobs is often that or or even
Two parents in the household
Earbuds working exactly is incredibly difficult
Judging a lot of it comes down to like
Their rejection of white privilege and male privilege and that sort of stuff is
It's not understandable but it comes from
There's a pride and ego that comes into it that they can't accept those things
This is just clear blind
This is just clear I don't care about other people's real
And
Why doesn't
It is also a
Complete rejection of the idea that
It could have shaken out any other way
Like their lives
Yeah they don't have possibly understand that they themselves
Could have been born to somebody in a different situation
And have had fewer opportunities
Opportunity
And I've been stuck in that situation and have had to deal with a separate reality Alex Mount 100%
I would have been in prison
If his dad wasn't a retentive
And able to move him around
Don't doubt that for a second
Yeah but I have almost no doubt
Fun cuz Ian Rob do get too drunk and talk about other
People's lives
Implicitly judge them like a bunch of dick hole
But they are doing this live
Periodically checking
The comments
Interesting comment
Comes in
No
I don't
I'm dead certain of it
It might be a glass of wine
But I bet you were drinking at the office
We've seen so many instances of him like
Whatever
There was that one marathon where he got done with his show
And then they had the robin Owen show
Before the War Room
Existed
They came on right after him
And not an hour after he got off his show
He barged into their show and started yelling at them
I clearly drunk at like 6 in the afternoon
So
Hold his booze better
Something along those lines
That's not first drink
His kids that's why Rob doing so good at it
Yeah and that's why it's kids go to bed so early
Alex is just pretending that YouTube
Demonetized liberal channels
Do you like didn't you see this coming when it happened to us
Yeah he wants to be the
First group in the I didn't speak up when they came for a ride
Open demonetizing all sorts of
No it's you too
Yeah they're demonetizing liberal channels
Didn't you know that
That's why is that how they paid for the iTunes album that that downloaded directly to your phone
That is
Is a scam
Get it
I don't know why people are talking about it desperately about U2 song title to make a joke
Two things I know about Bono
Short
Love stealing money from Liberal channels on you
That's what you got
You know what it is
To making that joke streets had known as
Not good
Metal thing when liberal channels
The exact
Time frame.
It's nonsense
Little bit about the marathon here in this next clip
Talking about
And just see what happens
Hookah 24 hours
Is a piece of s***
20 + x
Washington Post
Shut down shut down
No
Monopoly
None of that accurately
Depict reality
Also are any of them
Like I haven't heard the narratives that he
A Russian
Asian from anybody but us
Really
Projecting
Yeah
I think it is just revealing that he is a Russian agent in the same way that he has revealed that already
This way he's like
No cuz they're saying that I'm a Russian agent because
Terrible articles in the past
There was that one recently in BuzzFeed about how you just copies RT article
Goes in the past about how
There are our investigations
To the
Patterns
And stuff like that
Sites like Breitbart
Until there are
It's no one is saying he's a Russian agent but people are saying that he's disseminating Russian talking points stuff like that
Is a Russian propaganda of the Russian
The conversation in those articles which he doesn't read
Does read headline
The conversations of always been the investigation
To figure out our hope to figure out if there's coordination
The no one really knows that no one's making that accusation other than
Probably
Movies listening
Forklift left
Do you know about this but the right-wing internet is really a buzz and has been for a long
About Joe Biden
Groping children
Do you know about this
I did not know about
There's a number of videos of Joe Biden
Grab kids
But not sexual way or anything like pictures being taken in the Oval Office
I just want that is it is actually kind of upsetting you like grabbing
Girls are
Yeah
I don't know
I don't I don't know anything about this
It made the baby slightly uncomfortable but at the same time
There are people who don't know how they're touching
It's not groping
It's not like
Imma get onto that blouse
If it is the case
Did these kids feel that way
I am on their side
Probably say something
If if that is the case in these kids
Feel like they are being assaulted or something like that
Then by all means I'm not here to stand up for Joe
I don't I don't care
We're not playing team sports
If your
Look if you're out Franken
Yeah
You f****** did it hit the bricks
But at the same time there is there are accusations
That are made there are
People who have
Videos that they are being like oh look at him
Look at it that sort of stuff
Did Rob do decide to discuss
But something's on YouTube where
Gestation swatted Away Joe Biden's hands
Like everything trying to imply
But everyone knows he grouchy
Was big enough to stand up to
This one's mine
Well
Here I'll play this and then I'll explain what exit
Sessions
Classic
Back
Girl
So you getting the creepy voice out really taken out
Watching YouTube videos be like
Skates
Cuz they play it
Abdu phone
Riveting
Riveting production value
So they're actually watching
Is there is a child who needs to be
Not where she is
Right now she needs to be
A couple feet over to the side for pictures to be taken
I'm Joe Biden is coming in to Usher her over to where the pictures need to be
There there is no audio
I would assume
That he realizes
That is
Crouching behind her
He is walking up to her
And is blocks to where the picture is going to be taken
The hand swatting
Is absolutely not
It's just a shame trying to straighten out or get
Lint out of the girls hair
And how that's you know that's clear it's because he is basically stroking her hair
And does so after Joe Biden has already walked away
That raises the question
If the girl I deleted her hair
It's not like I do I know it's true waves I was happy
Okay sorry
I'm not immediately accusing Jeff sessions of being a pedophile in a creek
You're not Mike cernovich
I mean in that in that situation
How can
Can you really
Misinterpret that
So confident
Like if you can see that you watched it you didn't watch it like this the Zapruder film
You wash it one time and you were like
Oh this is clearly what happened because they played at
A clear indication for me as if he was
To do another swap
Which to me indicates
Either
Incredible presence of mind
Where he's like
I'm going to swap but it's a cover cuz I know people videotaping this
I'm going to make do it again
Which is not the case
Anybody who's watching that who doesn't have a vested interest in trying to
To create some sort of a narrative would say like
Oh that's
It doesn't actually did that
He would be using that video to fundraise
Absolutely
Like that's exactly how that would go.
Yeah I protected this child or something like that
It's and it's so quick I can't stress this enough
The timing of the second wife
Is after Joe Biden walked away friend pathetic propaganda and again
There are other videos with like grabbing that girl's arm
Pretty tightly it appears
Make me uncomfortable
Not defending
The big picture I'm defending this I'm attacking Alex Jones is narrative
Left
See what they want to see you
Confident
Yes like that's kind of interesting.
Right that's true
But
I do not appreciate that at all
The movie
Gross
So I don't know
Because
Roast people
Yep they like to dwell in in these things
Narratives in the way Alex
Launches
Feet first into
Whatever he does the like trapped in basement
Yeah it's just
What is gross
The first is that it might
Well the first
Is the least
Reasonable
And that is that there are
Deep-seated
Aggressive
Galaxy sort of living out on
On the show into that voice
That's possible but it's less likely that that it's that and it's more likely
But he realizes the
The power of the fear of those things
And he's just using it
Like Wiz favorite weapon
Yeah because it does evoke all sorts of
Scared feeling specially about
Did he brings up kids so often
We have a natural urge
Drive to protect children in so
Really powerful people on your side
Well it is it is
Helen
That
He is so delighted
Yeah the weird is it like
He does not have any empathy for the victim and instead every time someone is victimized by
What he perceives as
Anime
He takes Delight in describing all the things that
You would be afraid of from this person
He enjoys it when the people are victimized you could still argue I think that he's delighted
By realizing how effectively it's going to move super male vitality
Crass
I also a complete lack of empathy
Absolutely
That's taking his red imply
Anytime over here this
Drunk commercial for a marathon commercial
Wherein they accidentally say a bunch of really f***** up stuff about Royce
Alex brambles about his wife and how he likes older women
We just played this entire clip Evan
Good luck
Is constantly playing with that switchblade
Yeah like it's 88 is a child
It's a child behavior a child mine
I got this toy
Oh I don't
I don't necessarily look
For me to judge that what with all of my playing around with a panda and moving my
Leg situation I've got to do all of this stuff
I will buy weapons
No it is not wet
It is not wet
That's true
Texas
Great
So
I love it when you get a Rodger Stone tattoo
I want up to Rodger
They're going to double dare each other to do something of Rodger stones
Back with
Richard Nixon
Tattoo on
Tattoo of Rodger Stones back
Instead of a Nixon tattoo with Alex Jones
Even repurposing
Like I got a tattoo of you with the tattoo on your back
It's like one of those
Optical illusions
Anyway
It's been fun if you let your eyes go out of focus you see both Knicks
And
Alex Jones at
Terrifying sailboat
Scooter websites
Writing contest lyrics
Nation of what Rob's doing on any given day that Terrazzo Verde
Given that you've really written some great stuff if you'd like to enjoy that we would appreciate it
To check that out share it on Facebook help
Score fight we're on Facebook
Please feel free to
Don't matter rap style beef
Yeah I know
You can download it
Either write a review
Great review
I also realize my again forgot to give a shout out to the policy want that have donated
The beginning of the episode
We appreciate it if you'd like
We would appreciate it
A couple of ways what's your way
To become a pilot
Alright
Go outside
And then
Say something to this
This horrible man
With his
Huge hideous B
I understand Daniel for the grave back when he was the stormcrow
You're just trying to show off now at the sky
I understand that if you do that we will also hear you
And you shall become a policy walking that you must scream into the sky Dan
It is
Within a sensitive thing said before it
F*** you John Rappaport
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color