Holding
Alex
We are a couple of dudes like to sit around
A little bit about Alex Jones
Is in the history of twitch
I am telling you what
Audio issues
No never have a bit turns out its staff on that s*** I know nothing about
Audio settings but I do know a lot about Alex Jones
Find are you doing today Jordan
I don't know if you've ever done that by Mariana
You ever ask me how I know
In our friendship I don't know if that never happened I'm very back on my heels because of these issues I don't know what I'm doing anymore
Going back to my freezing point
Just be happy sitting across a conversation
OK Google
No no
Book Two for the people that I
Rent from to know who we are we would also be famous enough
Need to pay my rent on
So
That is what we did
I know is
Too damn High
Shoot Em High
It is November 27th
Also known as going to a
36 hour live Marathon
Disgusted on our last episode
And I listen to Alex
Jones's show during it
I had every intention
The purest of hearts
To cover that
That was going to be recovered on today's episode
But it was all f****** advertise
It was all commercials for products
I just don't know how we cover that
You know there was almost no content and it to the point where I was just like I was getting mad at
I have one clip case we should join his pyramids
Might as well
I did I do have one clip from today and it was just a beautiful moment of irony
Because I turn on
Do you live stream of his show
There was a bad before it
And it's very interesting to
Procure this ad
And see the juxtaposition of the two
Okay
Now available to Kohl's in your neighbor
Everybody around me
Cannot use Amazon
I love that
As far as
It was whiplash
It was all just like
Completely boring ads
We have no reason
To talk about it
A butt
You Jordan earlier today I've never done this
Before first time ever asked you to choose a day from history for us to go back to episode 4
I'll because again I am not prepared to do that time travel episode the one of our policy walk
As I requested updo
How did we go
We went back to you said
December 21st
17th or 18th
December 12th
That is when the torture report
That was that was what happened or what your intention was to see what Alex Jones about the torture report
Brand new year anniversary of when the world
Basically
Amazing episode
Number of reason
No. No way of knowing what's coming seems like I could possibly
Does the Torture part is not really a big factor
Other stuff that makes huge out of context drop from today
You know they just drops in that quickly the number of times you said that on the air is
Elizabeth
Heather Alex
Be that easy
I realize that we keep forgetting
To give a shout out to polity walks
I'm hoping this will get my eyebrow
Chance to get some sweat off of it drive is f****** thing off exactly
People for giving you money
What's going on up there Kelsey
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you for joining up with and also a note
How you choose which you want
You're going to fall off a cat
Old European
I'm a policy wonk thank you so much for joining up with
Thank you very much and Kelsey
If you would like to go
Not not the same last name but you never know could be long-lost twins
Anyway if you'd like actually Arnold Schwarzenegger
Define
And maybe if we get an apology want
Laurel have enough time to run soundcheck before the episode or I'll be able to pay my rent
Yeah I owe any of these things impossible and
Delightful to
God okay so here we are
December 12th
D12 shifts going down on the 12th
12 12 14 what is going on
I'll tell you what's going on
Alex Jones makes
The very weird reference
To his personal life
City almost
Never make
Okay
What's going on
Make it up
Ladies and gentlemen
How will you make up a divorce trial to everybody
No it's the divorce settlement 2014 getting divorce
So it's actually the separation and everything is what he's talking about that's when he's making it up
I guess
Yeah
Because of his new wife
I always think that's interesting
That
Never talks about the divorce and stuff like that
That sort of stuff
Hey alright
I look
That was family issues
Yesterday cuz I was busy getting divorced
Exactly
She's yelling at me about that boat and I'm like I can't give you that but every other
God dammit
Which is the name of this car wash
Probably
So
On the 12th
To the twelfth was because on December 11th
There was a report
The came out about
The CIA torture
John Brennan
To respond about that
Andy gave a lackluster response
Human rights correctly his response was
Hey you know some people do a thing some people talk to you with things
It's
Not far off
UN Human Rights commissioner
It was like you got up f****** prosecute those people
. and everything was better forever
Bagram prison because of it
Tune in to Alex Jones Show and hear what is top story
Where to start
Dot-com
Leadership
First ladies lunch
Camp monsters
Defense
The system
I was calling you
Gruber
Boner
Dave Gruber Bader
This
The naked tracker this Banner riff
It's going to go on
There's no way you can do that it was bad to start with Joe Biden Banner
And he thinks that
Do you know Alex Jones he likes to pick all the meat off a bone
Good Humor would you like this f****** comedy or is just
Coming out this is
Name sounds like we're going to get it
You're supposed to pronounce that German name boner
A running balance
BF
Years ago
There we go
That's right he did
Gruber conservatives tonight
Obamacare
Terminal operations
Open sweep in over 100 years
What's going to happen
Perform
Which Mitch McConnell
John Gruber boner
A3
Are going to be seen as a bunch of
That was a very successful
Record of all that might be the first time that I have strategically edited
We are stupid if we go along with that and then call myself out on it
But I mean
Yeah
Sure
Alright
Sub owner
Established ear is that
It's funny to say boner
Which you're not wrong he's not wrong
This is immediately after
That was an exam
Comfortable thing.
This is right after the November election
That gave us the Republican majority that we are
Just after the midterms in 2014
December 12th 2014
Alex what will happen if they don't successfully repeal Obamacare
I can't think of anything escalation
Yeah it seems like that
Actually Karen will not punish their politicians
Sims 4 failing them
The only thing that they really asked
Yeah absolutely name is funny
Yeah and that there's a spending bill that they didn't
Stop with their supermajority they had the funds the government into that after this next clip
Infowars.com
House passes Government funding bill
Belle Isle
Who added that
But it's not even bad enough
It should be
House passes
Cuz it is
Express
Forgot my work.
What's a sales alliteration of assholes Army
Yeah this is an article from Kurt Nimmo who is the guy who work for
Clearly
You know what the spending bill
Do you know the context
Yeah but government
Call Ted Cruz
Very hard to rule the world
Damage the GOP rep
Butaton so that even though they had a
Maturity everybody hate them so much
Specifically Ted Cruz
Who would later
Come second and many primary
Trillion-dollar spending
Omnibus
Spending Bill Democrats are now opposing several last-minute provisions
Including one that would repeal the Dodd-Frank Financial Reform Bill that limits trade by federal Ian
Insured Banks
Car insurance seems like the Republican
Trying to get rid of the Dodd-Frank
I can't think of any reason that they would get rid of the Dodd-Frank Bill considering that they represent
To just care about
And just
You know getting back to Americana I don't understand why they would try
Destroy a bill that actually
Those people
From predatory lenders that you don't understand prosperity it's Mostly Ghostly
About Banks taking risks with your mind
Real prosperity
When they're doing
Are they more fun if it's a surprise
No I mean the Revolution was a surprise
It's a surprise to all of us by 1776
Also to be about occasionally being Tech
Text too much Maxine Waters Elizabeth Warren both wearing
Incredibly vocal in their opposition
TVs
Are these last-minute additions Republican
Snuck through in
And someone else is talking about the spending bill now this.
And the real dangerous parts of the things that the Republicans who he is
And
I don't know you can always pretend that he's not a Democrat he's not a republican a bipartisan
Be off
He celebrates a lot with Republicans
Oh oh
Yeah
And I I don't know I don't know if that's just an amp
Reno
Democratic Norris
It's just full of s***
Cuz I would say a brings up another employee of
This is right after a video package
It's real like
Fast Cuts things taken out of context with relief swelling dramatic music
Get Nancy Pelosi
Nothing explosive but
Eric Holder
Wasn't nearly on his life is shooting board at the
Colder's in there Obama
12 quarts
Obama saying something like
Let's feed people and then he's not horror movie right
Awakening
Infowars
Funny story rotten long name for that
Quickly about how Alex is an a******
Interested
If I recall correctly he was to Alex Turner
M24 backup
In the David Duke Energy you
Have gone on to say
Certainly don't agree with
Miss B
Israel
That's her to stop using their brand over
I was worried that he actually
Went to the side that make sense
No longer there
Does not like
Do you know what Alex has some Weird Al
This back in 2014 that you would never expect
You already heard him say something negative about Sean Hannity
Best friend
What is the present with God because the future is not going to hold well for him
Are you going to be in trouble he's not pimping
This clip is
Interesting as hell
He doesn't just throw out
Teeth
Ears better
Venice Sean Hannity
Rino Republican talk show host
Support
Drugstore
Police brutality no matter what
We try to look at both sides
No you don't
Not at all like okay I get
Sean Hannity had morphed into a on the same team
Guy at that point right
Corporate Fox News guy question
What happened to Hannity
Is Han Solo's happening to Alex
But I mean more like was Hannity a secret Alex Jones this whole time
The what is crazy
He was always as crazy as radio show
Sensitive like he was a he was really
Unprofessional
I used my grandfather force me to listen to a good hour or
Two of us
Watching him and Usher
Bring him into the
Beyond
Infinite kept me from listen to Hannity I would have been like an hour or couple earlier
Chicken
Hannity
But it's interesting to hear Alex say positive things about
Charles Krauthammer
Whenever he gets challenge
I'm not talkin I want to talk person
I don't want to talk to anybody
I mean it would be hard not to next Shame Shame here are some reasons Alex Trebek
Alex cannot say he supports our greasy Charles Krauthammer
Supports abortion that's number one
Number to believes in evolution and rejects the idea of intelligent design
To support environmental causes and energy conservation
Emphatically support embryonic stem cell research using tissue from abortion
What's wrong with that
Isaac nothing speaks there
Harvesting babies and making cameras
Both sides
He likes to listen to Charles Krauthammer
Hey Alex that's f***
King stupid and he's going to be like
Hey Krauthammer you got a lot of good ideas not like that dumbass Hannity over there
Who agrees with me that they're creating chimera
A great Ally
Got into years
We have our demon Canada once you guys come to me
Krauthammer
You're gone
The rip
In the the the reality
Avail becomes big enough
I will go to Sean Hannity we will come together
As some sort of globular
Ulta media and professional media
Two headed boy
When we get Force
Listen to the dark timeline by Mixel
We have to say his name backwards before we can get into the timeline we're burning one like
Alex is f***** up
That makes
Philosophy a anything
His hubris
Back then
Humorous
Back then nose
No bounds
Listen to this book
Sales pitch for a second
Exactly what he's asking of his listener
Another key
World
Supporter
Become sponsors
Become
Supporters
Disco clothes
I want pay for a billboard
That's an interesting
To call your AM FM radio
I don't know about
Three Billboards three Billboards in ebbing Missouri and they said $5,000 a month
For three Billboards that's pretty close very small town
Yes outside of Milwaukee
You can get one for about $4,000 a month
Three to four thousand dollars
Yeah you bump it up to a city like
San Diego
Right which is not even a large Market but it's not like LA or something
That's going to run you probably about 10 to $15,000 in
Still reasonable if you get a return on your investment Boston let's say Boston
Urban urban area Metropolitan City it can run you up to 23
Yes
Traffic areas is all about how many eyes get on stuff it's all about impression how much would it
Cost us to get a billboard
What are you thinking
At least a $20,000
Boston and
Chicago probably for
Pretty close I'm terms of
Maybe a little higher but probably in the ballpark
Geez
So we're going to do a 36-hour lock Street
$23,000 and it's a you want to pay $20,000 for a paddleboard
Or conservatively $10,000
I know that it's too expensive to buy my wet herbs
Buy a billboard
Humorous
Hubris
Yeah that's not
Half an hour into his
Tipping Point
Finally decides
To the tortures.
Yes we're going to go hard on it he's got a lot of Articles he's really going to get into
You know that doesn't mean anything
Doesn't mean
Who is Alex Jones
Fish report
Tom
Torture report
Torture everyone is
Whatever.
Asystematic
Across-the-board
Court reports
From 2000 I think it's 2000
Torture report
He's the Filipino American General
3-star General
It's tacuba
Investigation
And that was a real one
Launch are related
Military
Federal prison guards
Records on purpose
Whitewash
This whole thing
Yep and not realized
Tacumbu
Here's the thing about that
Slightly off
He said it was 2007 I believe did a report
Tell anything about children being raped
Withings dipped in acid in front of their parents
Have not talked to tacuba
Tacumbu
Extant
No she
Blue
Boys come from
Closest thing I could find is there
Report
General taguba got
Incredible based on the circumstances sodomized
With like a
Light a fluorescent
Flight or something along those lines
Horrifying
But that's not quite
Children getting raped with things
Dipped in acid in front of their parents
Alex's sensationalizing
Quite a bit
It's not that
It's a stupid place to draw line quite frankly
I I mean
I'm not on anybody's side there but I want to back
In this in this race in terms of Alex being a reporter in terms of him actually telling you things
He's failing at that this is the most important
Takupaz report came out in May 20th 2004
Damasteel International put out their report about Abu ghraib
In
Juniper
So his report
Came out even after the atrocities that were reported in Abu Dhabi being
Reported so a lot of the stuff that's in there
Is just
I have substantiated that
Detainees told me these things happen
What's it already been reported
Never want to give it up for amnesty
Or something like that so
Is it weird
We've all known
At this point that America is
Is torturing people
Non-Stop
11 years
And we're like
Brennan
Don't agree with us
You're supposed to lie so we feel less
Complicit in the
It's really f***** up Alex
I would think his position on it would be
Pretty close to what I would expect different though
Cuz I would expect it to be gloating
Yeah I would also expected to be gloating with like
Here's all the times I've told you
And here is you know me breaking the story way before and all that instead of just message Billy being like to hooba
I'm sorry took
My thoughts
On what he would
Think based on his lover
The Blackwater now is
Yeah we're torturing people that's how we should be doing it I don't think you like Blackwater
Cuz he doesn't support it definitely will
Backwater now I assume that you have loved tortures
You saw your first episode of
I'll tell you this
Which I support
Does he know what we're doing now with the Trump regime and how we're killing them
Food around me
Is just going Buckwild
It's just they are
Just fighting a
Total War and burning people alive talk
Fake news
Shout out to project veritas
You saw this
Everyone
Most put out
About project Veritas trying to trick them
Sting operation about Roy Moore
Right I don't know if everybody is seeing the videos
The project Veritas
Out to try and get ahead of it
Was going to come out
That is so funny if you're
I imagine they got reached for comment in the middle of trying to screw the ocean
You guys are you guys are trying to trick us
Can you tell me some
The record I want to be a mountain
Rushed out some videos and it's like behind the scenes
Talking to people watching
Then post it so much nothing
It's astounding how little there is there
This is the real truth
This is
American prophet
Betty's got is
Somebody from from The Washington Post editorial board
Doesn't like
Realtor
Pretty
I think that's pretty salad
Those are not the news writers
It don't like that like
I think there are few
But also in the wake of all this is very important to remember
That's a few years back Donald Trump did give James O'Keefe
He's $10,000
Really
So interesting to remember and that will come back up
At the end of this episode
In a really weird way
Alright
Be that as it may
1120 bookends
I told you
Alex Jones Against torture
He is Against torture
Now in this time.
When Obama is doing against
Because
To be fair to him
When he's critique
Trump
One of the things he consistently says
Orr has said
Especially in the early days
The presidency was
That's one of the only things that he would point out that
I dropped the wrong on this one
Yeah generals are misleading him and stuff like that so I mean I think on some level he actually does understand that
Torture is bad
But
This next
Quip understanding and being against
This mess
Clip
Tells me that Alex has
Eating
Incredibly weird tape
On torture as a whole
I don't really know what's going on in this clip
Okay I really don't write
You better stop
20 years ago
Good
Level I don't
Much less
Where everybody
Here's what I mean
I need you to track the thought
I really need to cuz you talkin about Crimes of Passion right now and the idea that like you just go red and UK
Kill somebody or whatever
Yeah I swear he's going to try and relate this to torture
He's not but he
Baby baby flying a little bit low right now
Throttled
Porkins no
Presentation
Torture
Your heart
Torture is natural
And you're going to be
And in the moment
What it's like
You have the energy
What
The government
That's because you don't do it for
Compassion
Because their barbarous
But it's really interesting at the end
What am I going to save this
Call Grandma
This indicates to me that in December of 2014
But Alex has also been debrief
The Russian intelligence agency
I think we can push that date back to 2040
I don't think so
Inclusive thing right there
Fair enough I'm standing by this is what happens when you torture me before the show and we wind up getting audio
It was a crime of passion
I don't know what he thinks torture is
I think he's just against false confession
I agree with
I mean I'm against
I think
I think that's what you're really doing is talk to Trump about the Central Park five
F****** for any number of people
So
So easy
I think he's Against torture for the wrong reason
Or at least a reason
It deprives you of your Humanity
Surprised the person who you're torturing
And I would love for everyone to operate on that
But if you can't
And don't torture people because it doesn't work
If that's all you got
If it leads torturing people or advocating for people not torturing
Hooray
Yeah
Very Elemental Elementary
Writes very much
In terms of
Yeah there's just there's
In the same way there's emotional maturity and intellectual maturity there is like
Moral Majority
No just going by Golden Rule kind of stuff
Basic level and then
Principles get built-in as you get older and wrap it
Live by principles
And then eventually you get to the point where
You live by principles that must
Like they'd be the opposite could not be true
Alex is operating on
Very
Very childlike adolescent
Equating torture with beating someone to death
Because they
Drunkenly killed her
Kid in a car accident
That was weird
Very much and also that's a crime of passion if you go and get your gun
Though he wants to buy somebody
Like he's describing some
Something that he's done where
Totally
Turn it off
Yeah
That's a very it's very real
At least the feeling
But that's stealing I'm saying that he thinks he stopped
Himself from killing
Definitely could have killed a lot of people
Literally said that before
Jordan
Yes
You know how I told you
But the beginning of the show
Also I think he was referencing the movie The Way of the gun
Probably Silverman gets punched in the parking
Free movie I love it Ryan Phillippe Bonita Benicio del Toro
Big fan
Good Sarah Silverman
Dim screen
Jordan
Yeah
This is the end of his coverage
Torturing
So
He nailed it
XFINITY Live
Check that off the list
Now I told you at the beginning of the episode editorial why
Eye cancer
Torture into words
Punch
Don't
Pleasurable but don't do it
I told you to beginning
Of the show
Do you actually
Episode
I will tell you why there's
There's two reasons
And one of them
Darrell hamamoto
How did that happen
Uc-davis Professor Darrell hamamoto
Get up I started listening to it I was like
Oh f*** yeah
And I will say this
It's not his best showing
It's not that it's not I wanted to
Tickpick my gayest instrument to go infiltrate Occupy Wall Street
Stop
It's really great also
Keep it this bums me out
Cuz he's brought he's like calling him from his
Pretty small apartment
Yeah whatever it is what it is
Through the interview you can hear like
Truck
Like really loud
Interfere like it's clear that he lives
You know Donatos
He's a man of modest mean
Tenured professor
Here is our first clip of
Darrell hamamoto
He in this clip
He compliments
And then insult
Another one of Alex Jones
Professor
Model y
You talk about Jonathan Gruber
It's not important
How the world really works
Inside baseball a BS
Always went on from when I've seen in some special phds
Get on C-Span
Arrogance
The arrogance of how stupid they say
It's arrogance and I was listening to what here earlier interviews this week
Great great
What time is it
Check n Go
Collier
Rates fiction Ghostwriter or collaborator for Tom Clancy's books
Do that
Shooting on Plainfield
Rapper
Clancy's got some good
Most of the writing of the book Saturday the 1st
Hamamoto is nuts
Analyst
That we have
I have no idea I've never read it I would like to Rouses Latter-Day Tom Clancy
Tim's books at some point
Summer reading
Is that
Beach region email hamamoto with like a recommended list
Oh he knows something
How to hide your gun
No. He doesn't know that
Where to keep your gaze
You don't know that
We got them up they got a book on high today in Summit
I told you that I'm a moto nose thumb
Fitness mix
What does
Elaborate
Conspiracy that he is going to lay out in this next clip
And I would like
To point out that the
He sets it up even from the beginning
He's discussing what
He tells professors
To try and get them to wake up
The red pill them or whatever
Even in his own conception
He's talking about
Corporation
Trying to screw over people pain
Not globulin
So hold on
We'll get to that on the other side after he makes
Suitcase that is
Rambling and nonsensical
My favorite crazy
Is an illusion
Going on at night
So when you talk about the weaponized campus
He's talking about the electromagnetic rays
And stuff like that they're shooting
He's not.
They aren't going to enforce it was militarized
That's where I
No I don't believe so and also it's not it's not the
It is because they have these remember he has that in Tennessee
All kinds of ways that are going around campus
Backup
Also the very idea that Wall Street wants
I mean yeah.
Do you like
That's not Google
That's out-of-control capitalist
I don't think they're going to enforce it with lasers
Although
If you use lasers that better for me somehow
I think that's more fun like it's the Pendragon affair
Flamboyant monster
Give me some entertainment
Search answer such as
She's having a US citizen
You have no idea
I didn't do that okay
An international Network
Education course
For the destruction of
What's the destruction of
So
If Linda can
Through the education system in Greece
Economy at that cuz you was so successful you got to be the president of
A bit also
She's so important that she's an international destroyer of economies yeah and was fired for giving her son
And stepdaughter a job
Yep
He's so crazy
Checks out
Indispensable piece of a nefarious International conspiracy
Heading
Petty nepotism
Of our Global scheme to destroy economies through education system
I'm stupid I added he already had it whilst redesign your pensions
Make that just one step
And if Wallstreet eyes your pension than then takes them
Like they did
Then it's a bad thing
Even if you think it's lasers
You're doing so good I like you
Whatever
I liked you earlier when I said this wasn't
To go to have a moto up here
You killing it
In his next clip we get to find out
Some of the inspirations
For Darrell hamamoto
Professor.
He wasn't ranting Alex did like a 3-minute commercial and then Isaiah
478 get back in the day
Questions
Credit First
Alex
Sedation
Wichita course
Or no
Oh no
Are you getting the picture of
I'm emoto's life is exactly what we thought
Yeah
He was really want to go to
Can we audit one of his lectures
We got to take a trip to go on and we can go to you are you kidding me
Proud of those lectures that students go to
You understand I mean what he's accidentally revealing
He at one point was a normal human being and then he caught the brain virus of Alex Jones's globe
Yeah he already had tenure so they can't fire him scaled-back who's
Caitlin his class load your house within the bounds of tenure for someone who's
Clearly off the reservation talks about arguing with students
Gifting system teaching classes about Illuminati Theory and s*** like that
But I mean if you want to teach it from a like academic perspective
This is a real Olympic has
I want to go
How much fun is it is that should be in every University there should be one hidden lunatic.
Yeah
Missouri
Yeah of course
Crazy were talking about
He was a doctor
It was some like Wellington
Somebody named like that
The Greek history
Professor
F****** a******
Music kind of crazy
He was a kind of crazy who like
Expected everyone to do the reading
Not be grateful about calling
On people in class
And then he would clown on them when they hadn't done the reading
Crazy, Modo crazy
Crazy
Let's see there's a guy that this isn't the right kind of crazy either
But he only does classes on whether or not molmed
He is definitely
This guy named dr. Rowley
And archaeology
The professor
Class I took
The joke
I'm self cuz he was like 90 something barely talk
The entire class with me and the guy next to me being like
Everyone pass
Cuz the curve was a disaster
So it sounds like a mystery shows
How to get back on the show he knows how to get in Alex's good graces
Facetious
What the hell
Flickr
This is what happens immediately after
Conversation
Vitamin
Because
International Auto Glass
I mean
I don't know what's more troubling about that snake everything
Everything is troubling about that
B12 makes me feel great I take it before lectures
So I can be slick
Is Joel Osteen
He's being glib there
That's making fun of Joe
Our favorite glitterbug preacher which is a reference to Alex Jones
Insulting these are Prosperity Gospel
No I think I did
I think also there's a chance
Darrell hamamoto has some sort of a personality
Can you can't tell when you're being
Like possible
Tony voice almost never take
Guys always die
In the same motor
So I think you
When I read the text
IRead
Irony and sarcasm I could be wrong but that's what I say
You might be right
I might be right
Either way
F****** amazing
Weird tradition on every appearance
Like one one of the other ones we went over
He was like he's like a Alex I just want to tell you I just got your book
The making of a president
Pikachu
Great
Now probably yeah he has to be
Yeah if you're if you're popping up a book
You got to be a social media influencer type gig right there
Buzz Marketing another level
Just sort of understand where his bread is buttered and he's like I can get a lot of exposure from this that I couldn't get otherwise
If I pimp
Stuff for Alex I know that's what motivates him
That'll make him more likely
To promote me
Bright everything works out
Best of mangle
Hamamoto is got some
A little bit of
Complex
Going
In this neck
Flip
Reference as a colleague of
His
I did
A bit
A research
Listen to this
I can't find any
Look here's the deal
He gives enough details that it sounds true if you're not okay
So few details that it
Possible to search for
Further
Is the ecology speaking of real
I can't
Say either way
My gut
Says no
Ugh
The story is about to tell is
I got red flag
Okay
Viciousness
University
Worcester
Practice with
What do we do with the ideal
So College
Yep
She was declared clinically dead I some kind of alone she still alive
Because her healthcare costs are too high
Here's where the cutoff
Which I'm going to jail
Insurance
That's not how I heard
I heard it as a better estimate
Retaliation
Do you think she race
Healthcare prices
Notre Dame had some sort of an accident
Yeah
Your your your theory makes the most sense
Yeah I wouldn't what did you think was going on
Your interpretation because mine is great
I'm a big fan of him believing that they would declare a living woman clinically dead for a while right
The cost of whatever
Because that doesn't work that doesn't track
I heard it
She was making
If University causing trouble until they declared her dead
Kind of makes it sound being harassed and all this stuff and it seems like
Did declaring her dad your dad now
You out of health care for you either what does he tell them
No
Weather
Illegally
She wrote a great paper that if you email him he'll give you the name of
But I'm what I'm saying is like things
Or like
Enough details belt
Couldn't
Make all that up
Anyone
To confirm
This person's existence
Bright at this point legally
So Automotive
In his next clip
Omoto has a fever
How would they even have that power
They don't
In what situation could the university be like
Okay wait
Her bills are what
Just declared your dad now
Tricked out
Two guys use Social Security numbers no
This guy
As a lot of theory
A little song
But the reason why
My students
ResCare
Earlier conversation with you
Theoretical
Gostream
Enterprise
Have an alternative Theory to the siop theory
Eveni Enterprises
Ever
Put forward to defend
I think the 1970 series
People dropping out of humanities classes
In droves I would imagine that hamamoto sees a lot of people dropping out of his Humanity
And that is a chaotic element to have like giving you grief
Like
F****** Fantasyland class
Little wasted money but it was worth it
I have another alternative Theory
It's not just based on his subjective experience
And that is the humanities path
Generally does not leave
Good salary job
Not in Mike's
Most of the humanities leads
To akademia or social work
Who are those sorts of things from home
Absolutely
Let's say
Ryan study class
Like just asking which classical world
Literature even any of those
The real path that you can go down and become a
That's essentially what you can use that degree for
Like I have one of my
Majors
Minor but I took a lot more than
Who cares took a lot of classes in Greece
And if I were to go to grad school I'll probably take more
I'm the only person that would help you run an auto dealership
Absolutely teacher somewhere
It's Jake. It's just people in a bad economy or an economy what debts
Values people with
Our type of education so little specialized degrees much
People go to those who learned that when you're in college
And that leads you to go away from
Your motivation is money
So is probably a more sensible
New job market
I'm here in Pueblo
We
Tutor
Chemical engineers
Stem field like just all stem field okay
Alright
Kind of going into random stem field people
Homes
Just teach them just AFK
Chat like that
That way we'll never have a theory care of the 1970s again
Bringing these f****** French people over here
I don't know why you got to dig in at the front
Like this guy f****** overhead most of them
French
Conspiracy theory
So at this point Alex is like
Hamamoto.
I got to come with some
I can't just let this guy run Circles of crazy around
Whole Foods
The magazine
It's so cool
Meanwhile Obama's Fire On Air Force One
It's not good
Has a new dark
To stop the
So here's what's interesting
I know that it's
Tired for us
To play him talkin about that Obama
Air conditioner
I'm flying in on a plane
The reason that I kept it in this time is because
What key was saying
It literally what Alex has why don't you say
But he's is why don't you say you could have clean cars and clean air conditioning
And the point that Obama was making was
We can't
Modernize
The entire world the same way we have modernized
The world
The first world we have now
We made a lot of mistakes on the way we have to be smarter about the technology
That we used
Or else the world is going to boil over
I do
It's particularly offensive for me
When Alex
Uses
This narrative to make a stab at Barack Obama
Then give a white of me and says exactly what Obama was saying
I think that does get into something
Thing that is true
What's that
One of the biggest problem
Alex has with Obama
Is
He just doesn't talk like me
Sure doesn't look like
Necessarily think it's not either I think it is smart exactly I think there's this huge anti
Intellectual
Coincides with being on the right
Why you have a professor like hamamoto
There's a lot of really smart professors
Hate smart
Experts
Common sense
Dude you guys are so smart but you don't have
Common sense you don't know how to solve this budget
Sure you know your math
And you're gay instruments
What learning stuff is
Hard
That's why
People like
I generally think that the sentiment of intellectual
That it runs rampant around this year
Country of ours
It mostly comes from people that are abused
In their own head of the with the idea
That smart people are smart people in dumb people are dumb
It's just an eight
You guys are the f******
Stupid you think you're better than us cuz you were born smart or something like that part is what
I'm kind of stuck on people don't they never come out and say
Intelligence
I mean
You can make it nature-nurture
The biggest
Piece of it is learning
The biggest piece of it is
Hard work and reading stuff
Able learning experience in these people know we're going to have to refer you back to the four ways to learn
Episodes memory
That is how you lie was the other one I know that the best way to learn
Is to learn
That's true I do know that
So at this point
Alex is like
Colorado
You got to talk
We got to take some calls
Alright
This does not go with
Doesn't go well
Here's why
Here's the color
How you doing
That was
Great work right there you played just enough and then you real quick turn to the get ready
For you to not have an expectation that this is going to be fun okay this is going to be
Pretty sexy.
I just want to say real quick that I'm in the middle of changing my life
Question
Athena
Powder
My job
We can't give phone numbers out on Air Bud
Can somebody can call me
With somebody else
We can't get up
Phone number
Sorry about that
In the season of a
Illinois they're saying you
I'm get ready for your big dude I'm a very good person I'm just wondering how I can
I pray to God
Email
Nissan
Collapses
Kicked off
First things first unemployment
Is unemployment insurance
Pay for bikes hacks
Second Alex absolutely hung up on me
Yeah
Undoubtedly
You think so I didn't hang up you was in the middle of a sentence
Cut it off with his
General we're done with this kind of language
And then he's like what's your email
Maybe the call screener did it
I would say probably more likely
Real City
There's still traffic and I understand that
PS button
Yeah probably
Hard-and-fast like
I bet he has a dump button
At least the people behind the board No Lie
Someone starts
Cuz there was actually I found an episode
Steel was on me like
Right
We are on radio
Yeah he lied about buying the DNA force in order.
He might have recently
Yeah but essentially what he was doing is
I'm going to give you this so you can give me this
Yeah you can give me the opportunity to put my name out there number and maybe job
Evicted from my house
Hangs up on ya
Thrill City and then he's like
Score points with talking about how like to be losing their unemployment
Program program program that you hate so very very much
That stuff everybody hates Medicare until their own Medicare
Oh my God I'm sick and I've lost my job
Coach was on Fox News
I've been on welfare I've been on Unemployment and those are bad programs because they saved my life like
He just he just pulled Craig T Nelson
If you were talking about coach
Coach
Or if you have a coach
There's only one coach
Okay I was Only We Know
One coach
One through couch
All praise
Call did not go well
This is not what you want but not photos in studio
Bumper collar
But
Guess what we had something
To pick us up
Call
Comes a new gas
Brawl
Billy Corgan
That's why
He is in the airport
Smart guy
Music
.
Billy Corgan
Champs
Blue
It's not out of the blue
There's no scandals
No.
Nothing
Kleinfeld
So
Well I f****** pulled up in this episode and it said the guests were hamamoto and Billy Corgan I was like
Holyshit
Wow
The good
Aldi's Hatchet pieces about Billy Corgan or easily explained by Billy Corgan
F****** a******
Seems like if you just look
This shortest Google search
We'll turn up at least
Ham instances
Of him being totaled Xtube Auntie performs with
Thunder story
I mean
He's notorious
Bush People
What's people say
Billy Corgan affected them through their music
Help them
Kind of grow that way and Alex is like
Shity musician but let me tell you about this guy chemtrail f****** made me mature quite a bit
Vaccination
Airbnb.com
Cooper from the CIA put
About him
A coops
I don't know I don't know how to just I don't know how to
I don't I don't know how to get in
Just get into it
Baby so Cooper had a segment
On his
Around this time
That was called the ridiculous
Salad pun
I'm going to be where do I say
It's the local TV level hacker
You know it's just filler
Subway comedy peace within is actually
Really funny
I've heard him on radio shows like him
Like he's been on E back in the day he was on Loveline a couple times
A couple of like clips of him
On Howard Stern
I need a super personable
Comfortable in his own skin
Present
Funny guy
And this is not
It's not great you know it's definitely not great
Producer wasn't him
Where did he come up with Stephen
Kind of shity
No I just I think it's
I think we are comedians
And when you're looking for a premise
You should try a little harder
What happened what happened was there was an issue Chicago
Which pauses the no-kill shelter Chicago
And Billy Corgan did a cover of the magazine
A couple of cats
Headline
Siamese Dream
Cover of Madden and so
Around the same time commercial for a furniture store
In Chicago
And
The point of Anderson
Cooper's piece
It's difficult to wrestle
Difficult to wrestle with the idea of
Musician
Getting older
Little little
He presented a little bit like
You know it's sad that he's doing these
Ice Cube family
That's because the reality is
Billy Corgan do that cover for charity
There was like a charity piece
Attached
Hey Porter
Taking that money home supporter of the pause
No kill shelter
Positive
But the other place to get ice cube to do something other piece of it too though is that furniture commercial that's
Isabel that way
It is
Out of
Character
You know like a
Beyond the saying you're washed up and it's a money thing
It's also like you are avant-garde you were someone who when I was younger I thought was
Really creative and Rakim
Snoop Dogg
Game show and the cover is weird
It looks
Really weird
If you look it up
It's multiple on its own
You should have taken another shot Billy
Play you the end of this Anderson Cooper
You'll hear that he takes the piss out of himself
At the end to
The internet is a real problem
There was a time that nobody outside of Chicago would have ever seen the cover of Paula Chicago magazine
But nowadays you can't even pose for the cover of WebMD Magazine
Wait a minute cover of WebMD
Okay luck
For the record
I have no memory of posing for the cover Web MD with the apparently I did I gave an interview I don't know what I was doing
Anyway
Stupid like a little bit
It's not great but it's
There is
There is an element of a where he's like
I do it
Yeah I N whatever really being
I need to fill human-interest cuz I hate
Respect you
Because hey we all do dumb s***
The softest of hit
Possible
And oh boy
Almost the entire interview with Alex
Course
Alright alright so if I understand the timeline correct
Anderson Cooper
Makes bad joke at Billy Corgan
Billy Corgan goes on Infowars
Not realizing how much sadder that is then being on the cover of pause magazine I propose a solution
Do this with Billy Corgan
Shut the fuk up no I wish I could have told them about the charity
Whatever
He's not like
Mad
The first one
Alright
Anderson Cooper
But
Torture report
Almost like your publicist is encouraging that sort of thing
Maybe your publicist to copy of this cupboard
No kill shelter
Very proud
Hours for the charity
And I
Magazine
Equator
Where I am
Where is he
Restrain
Between your legs
Be a grown up about it you know
Request for correction even not too far
Off the mature pack
To be somewhat convincing
No rockstar
And he's an aging Rockstar and he's not aging the way that the Rolling Stones
Successful you get
You're always going to feel better about not being more because he's
He's that is the way that Cooper pulled up
He's lived like 15-20 years 25 years pissed off that he's not Nirvana
Is his existence
And because of that there is probably in a
Complex
Everybody in the Infowars
Universe does that he's being held down and it is greatness isn't being recognized
I want to know I don't know I'll call it
Booker on that
Email
It look here's as far as I'm willing to go with you on this
I'm willing to agree that he has a good
It was misrepresented
Yes don't believe Super Bowl
If you are an adult looking at that
Your best play is to not get mad about it
And to be like
It's a human interest piece
They Conover
As an adult promoting your next album
A f****** s*** for maybe realize that you have another out map because
What is the first time I've ever said that
Talk more about it
Is no bad right now
You put a story on your
I wonder if that's why it went viral
Play the game
It's interesting actually pawschicago is this really great no kill shelter and I was
Doing it to support misunderstands I understand maybe I didn't do a good enough job of explaining that when my age
Maybe they could have done a better job for immediate-release Billy
Morgan does cover for charity instead of Billy Corgan does very weird looking pictures
This is all
I'm telling it okay
What if it were Kanye
Kanye gets
Get the same result from Anderson Cooper on CNN
Then Kanye goes on Fox News and goes on he likes
F*** this guy
I'm still on Kanye's side
Information
Krowd
But again
Billy Corgan left on their side of himself is like all these low-information
People who only go off headlines
That's what this whole episode is about
I agree with you that he did for charity
F****** a****** anyway
You're you're biased against assholes
Most of my friends are assholes
Let's talk more about
Uber
Really is he really dead
Kirilli Groove
Of one of the biggest
Nope
He's a little Richie
This this is this failure
Everything
Personal stuff
Except for this example of the other day when I got into the personal stuff
Very interesting
Whatever that crowded
I mean I love you
Really
Realizes
I don't understand it
Sounds a lot like Alex
Okay
So
I understand that correctly
Play gotcha
CNN piece about me I'm going to be all angry about it making me
Act like a c-list celebrity
Instead of saying that I'm doing a great thing for charity album
There's a Great Awakening coming
The only other thing about other than Anderson Cooper
But everyone's asleep
Zombies all around
Billy Corgan did come from humble beginnings
Paid for his first show as well.
Apple Dental practice
Tons of property
Oh really
Wait till this next clip plays but
About Anderson Cooper that I
Alex is probably not
Willing to deal with
How could you not be eyes open
Vanderbilt
Nothing wrong
I wanted the biggest robber baron
Give us a break
And Cooper
Personality
Toledo
Everybody knows
Are all along
Even great Bel-Air Bel-Air you're the best
You're the best
Have you tried this
B12
That I'm getting out of here
Billy
Let me tell you something dr. hamamoto it comes Dexter hamamoto recommended
If you want
To get the morgue a instrument
In your Smashing Pumpkins band
Come on down to hamamoto gay instruments
So
Cooper's mom Gloria is Evander
The Vanderbilts
He's not the last male Heir in the
He's been very clear in interview
Throughout the entirety of his career that he was very young age
But he was disinherited from the families
Well that there was no trust fund
On for him
He's interpreted as
If I knew that there was a trust fund I would have never tried to
Succeed I don't know a lot of people who have
Billions are millions of dollars waiting for them
Is it have a drive to
Disinherited
Yeah but I had no inheritance
Actual
Real likelihood
Is that there is no
His mom did the equivalent of 33 million-dollar
Not just
Translation $3000000 now
In 19
That's a long f******
His mom is old how old is How old is
Anderson Cooper
He's probably 50
He looks
You looks great
I just I like Anderson Cooper I don't get it I get it
Against Billy Corgan
I don't think
Celebrity situation they were running into.
Billy Corgan
Look the issue is I'm telling you that I I think
But it's correct
Not right
Too clearly bring up that it is a parity thing that he did also also in 2009
Gordon
Randolph be the right
Someone paid $6,000 to get lunch with him but had to pick up the tab
Total assholes
Price of the mail along with your charity
Thousand dollars and I would say probably like $142 worth of McDonough
225 and family wrangling over the trust eventually accelerated her
Control
Slightly bigger share
A lifetime of artistic and business
Pursuits presumably help
Independent cash flow
Distributions long ago
9 decades is a long time for a traditional Trust
People of modern on that the trust
Was actually empty by the 19th
It's unclear how much money is
Designer jeans
Perfume line that you put out actually made her
By the time the perfume came out
He was already fighting
Her Partners over a relatively insignificant
Forget 1.3
3 million-dollar
A few years later a Manhattan Court ruled
Better lawyer in psychiatrist had colluded to misappropriate a whopping 1.4 million dollars from work
In the meantime the IRS seize and liquidated her assets
To pay 2.5 million dollars
So there's a lot
So Anderson Cooper
Inherited wealth
Is dad by the 4th generation
Along those lines so many people that are that are in on it
The guy who made all the money generally speaking
It comes from a different
Replacing if you're born into wealth generally
Not going to
Be very good with money there's a really good chance Cooper was a child
His parents told him
He's disinherited and there is no inheritance waiting for him and he interpreted it as a way to stiffen him up and make him more
Thirsty for life or whatever but the reality is that there was no money there or there's a little bit of money
Make a couple million
They had
A lot of property
Anywhere in with social classes
There was the appearance of royalty your luxury lifestyle
When they were really just probably
Pretty upper-middle-class lower upper class
Or whatever like
Old-money the car
Carnegie's
Yeah of older women
He's just trying to stoke up sort of like class anger that he doesn't
Deserve to play with
Cuz
Alex
You probably have more money than
Yeah I know they probably started out at a relatively similar monetary position
Right it's just the image of the Vanderbilts
Right comes with so much loaded baggage
For Alex City
Hi Alex. Come from royalty
Confederate oil
It is next clip Billy Corgan wow he's been railing
This entire time
Anderson Cooper has called him a washed-up celebrity
On this side
Puff piece
Human-interest nonsense missed comedy
Segment
Thinking this club
If you listen closely Billy Corgan
Kind of says that his career is not going
We have to remember those of us that are awake
Screw
I do
And I
Elrond
We just don't know what to do
And I
Everybody
Here I come
He did it
What he did it I wrote down the moment he started talking about all that stuff
I wrote down go to an ad pivot
Just like Alex Jones he just nailed the Alex Jones
That's why I'm dangerous that's what I'm doing so career going once
He listen to Alex Jones he's got his
Talk about buying it
First of all I'm getting very impressed with your ability to pick out these like
Subtle versions of the active you have hit me with so many ads and area 1
Starting to become a connoisseur the education
Show you the way
Look through Alex's bulshit
Tanner class at the University of Missouri you know what how to go to an ad pivot
He did it
I thought what you were saying
And I was going
Dumbledore
Was that
Think he gave away that he
Probably planted
Did the story about pot
Because when he says in there
My career gets going in the right direction again
This blustery nonsense about like
Oh you saying that I washed up my career is not going
In the right direction
It's because not enough people are awake
Not enough people know they got a red pill it and get rid of this CNN
Anderson Cooper Vanderbilt bulshit
And start listening
To the new Smashing Pumpkins album out in 2 weeks
One of the most grandiose and nonsensical plugs for Billy corgan's album
You people go out
Support independent
That are speaking out
Music
Buy your album
It's Smashing Pumpkins
Play it for free
Billboard
Tell
The system down
You've got to go
Further
And decide you want to promote cultures of Liberty
How many kings
Down by
We came
By the
Local band
Guy with his
Is little
Singing songs about the
Corrupt
Organized
Didn't use it in the hands of the
System
6's matric
How do you get rid of oppressive regimes Dan
Well I know this
This machine kills fascists
That is it
Exactly what he's doing right there
You don't you don't go out and do any activism which
To do you wait for somebody to write a song and you buy by the stuff that I promote
I know that you're a student of history as well
Yeah that's not how it works
Do you know of any kings that were brought down by Jesters or song or is that just an archetype vitar
Tell the song
Henry the 8th
Haha
The Great
All right right
Exactly
Let's see
No
Panthers no
Dixie's did
Where's our new protest music new protest
Even gets into that a little bit
Yeah but anyway hip-hop assholes Sono Alex
It's weird because there's already talking about
Potency of Song and all that stuff
Next clip Alex reveal something
Real weird
Facebook
Because he has a lot of Courage
Classified
I'm just going to stop
Really want on and then what happened
What aren't you telling people
You told people everything
Tell you what I know but here there is all of it
Do people believe that
Alex Mae
People believe that the FBI in the CIA
Traditionally do
I mean if you're awake
Hotel
It would have been funnier
I don't know that was all part of the cover-up and they killed him back in Liverpool
With nine people believe that Paul McCartney
You still alive food made it takes all kind
It's weird that
Anyway this next place
Glipizide
I got it okay
This makes represent fortunate
About how
I remember how they got onto the
This topic
Borden
Almost all local news
Pharrell ardc
You tell them local story
Cancel somewhere
You know there's not a lot of
Your listeners know I don't know what even losing to the liver is no local news when you're watching your love
Local news
Whatever it is
There's a good chance
That
They don't know what the
The story actual
It's only from New York or La they are broadcasting teleprompters
So the people sitting around at the desk girl reading for the first time
Local news
Well there's what I mean that's
That's nonsense but at the same time I want to say one thing really quick before I dive in
Going to be damning
The man in the High Castle wasn't it
Philip a dick fan
Don't don't do that is your metaphor I know you visually think it makes sense
If I was gone
That's what don't you remember catching the riots about a dude catching all that f****** ride
Conception of what is going on with local news
Is sort of spiritually correct but it's not correct in the way
Conceives of it Broadcasting
Completing to Italian
Control over all local news everywhere enforcement
People to run their propaganda
That's bad if you look at that what's happened
Sinclair
Since Trump got into office a lot of good things strangely enough
It seems like
They're coming out as a
Winter Monday morning this is Becca and I believe March
Of this
Yes let's go
There's an article from
Just aggregate
Replaces
The fairness and
Recordings
Organization
Monday morning Sinclair broadcast group
The conservative media Behemoth that owns more local news stations
Any other company in
In the country
Just got even bigger
8.9 billion dollars creating with Bloomberg
Play TV Goliath
The purchase which Sinclair
The nearly 69
Now
What's the u.s. population
Violation of ownership restrictions
But last month
Pi
Updated
Conglomerates to exceed the nation
39% cap on ownership
Of media
420 million dollar deal to buy Banton Media Group the very next day
This sequence of events quote sure looks like
Quid pro quo
As Craig Aaron of the media advocate
Jiffy group Free Press
Has noted
Months ago Trump son-in-law Jared Kushner
According
Politico
Sinclair broadcast group
Secure better coverage
The geopolitical report
Sinclair
More uncritical coverage
In exchange for more access to Trump and the campaign
Now
Trump appears to be using
A considerable power of the Federal Communications Commission has his own personal ATM for political current
F****** stupid
He's so dumb guys win
Anyways
Adjectives I as well just recently that I'm not done the one that was just a couple of weeks ago
F******
So you got to take
Consideration that
In
December
For this year
Or July excuse me
This is from an article in Politico
Even while Under Fire for requiring its Outlets to run conservative content
Cast group is increasing
White House official
Asian
10 times a week
The company confirmed money
Yeah you have to run it
The embossed run 9 times a week I have to run to 9%
Of the the coverage in the in the country
Of a conservative propaganda piece
David his mask
To look like local news being presented by a former Trump White House official
Also they have a pieces that are made by former
Trump Communications advisor
Multiple multiple Trump people have gone over and started to actively work
For the centralized Sinclair broadcast company
The biggest thing that dies
Dead is
Allow local
There used to be a rule that you had to have at least six or seven
Local media outlets and they just got rid of that which means that Sinclair media is only going
Expanded
Total Domination
Turn up local news
A nightmare
It's interesting
As far as far-reaching
Consequences of dawn
Ajit Pai has been the most
Damaging person in
Indy Trump
Cabinet
It's
In terms of the future I think I'd reprise probably going to kill us all
It's real
Stacks field
Real tough to make that kind of decoration but it looks bad
None of this legislation is really got
His Muslim bans have been stopped by the courts
There's a legal challenge to just about everything
The only thing that has
Apparently unilateral control
Is the FCC
Yeah and I G Paez
Singularly
Destroyed net neutrality
Destroyed
Against monopolies
The power of media conglomerate
More than I think anybody's ever done got rid of the need for equal internet access
Is giving a huge boon
To your Comcast
In order to make sure that if you're poor in the middle of nowhere they don't have to serve
With you
Idea that there was
Some sort of the deal about coverage
Xxxx
No but just the idea is the predicate
To the antecedent they were seeing now
It is not fine backroom deals you got to give a little
I don't I mean I do but I don't
Well I mean
Is that any different from a guy like Rodger Ailes
Who stands so much more money
I just think it's a bigger
Con okay
Not as good
But it's not as good a situation there there
Local news
I was making sure that these are
Not
Centralized reports
From bias people
Is going
To do
Incredibly in
Insidious job
Radicalizing people in smaller communities
You're going to have the output of that beats
I mean I guess that's the same thing if they would just watch
Watch Boxing
Houndstooth
Yeah it's all bad
The same thing as
Rodger Ailes
Stan's two games
So much for Trump winning as opposed to do
No not him who's there
Who's the f***
Who runs
Who runs Fox News
Is the guy who owns it
Rodger Ailes
Murdock
Nikki's dad today
Who the f*** is my remember any
Remember
So this is all bad. Trump wins
Because he uses his bottle company
Run propaganda
So bad but we have one more clip left
Guy who's
Going to make everything
I'm going to leave you with a punchline
Play something that I learned
Screw
Something like that
Coming down the road
Alex
It's bad
Just having him say that
It damning
You're such a strfkr that you will agree with Billy Corgan saying
Literally the opposite of how you conceive of yourself
We don't have to be guys like us
Things that on the Alex Jones Show
That's probably true amazing f*** all of you
Knock knock
How did you do it
Celebrities are allowed to be assholes
Disappointing
Power ranking
Animoto
Still the number one
F*****'-a how is it that
Strfkr
Is anybody else
Like if you even if
Stephen pechenik or somebody like that
Who is
Smart enough to know that he would never
He would never challenge
Listen Alex you're not accurate all the time even when I'm wrong I'm right
Exactly has the New Year's today
Right like that whole thing
Buddy
Anything you say
L week later when he listened back to this episode he had a thoughts
Like this
That's probably what you would like to think about
Solid punch
Congratulations
Just out of an out-of-nowhere choosing an amazing day to go over
There's a lot of episode
I think I'm back to the present
We'd never find what we think this is when this big thing happened I was like
Hear what he has to say about the torture report
And you're like
Yes
But
How about hamamoto Billy Corgan to
Shows ridiculous
Anyway I could love it has been fun
Do you guys want to learn more about a particular
Sure we have a lot of news on have a lot more
From now on
Material ever
Time now
You can also follow us on
Yeah Pat knowledge
And then there's an under
We are
Libreview couldn't hurt
I don't know if it helps
Rock You
Website is knowledge fight., pretty good name for a website
Name wheel of mainstream media attacks
He's actually sitting on the domain
That I wanted
Really no way
What
No more fake news. Com
Angelfire
Go to Squarespace John Rappaport seriously
Tell advertisement Squarespace
We don't do ads for Squarespace unless they pay it
I use Squarespace and it's pretty convenient
Jon rappoport user really update that website cuz it looks like a hot pile of garbage
Until you update that website what
To tell you that you can go f*** yourself.
Rapoport
Thanks for holding
Alex
Person coloring