Alex
Christian coloring
In this case gumballhead
Delicious beer
Asking me how I'm doing this conversation
Grown-ass people
Thank you very much
I think we're going to end this podcast
Acknowledge about Alex
So it does
We are going to be in
Present today
Oh yeah but sucks
November 30th
2017 Thursday if you're nasty
You know
Stuff happens Wild
Before we get into it I want to know you know there's no
I can't I can't I can't explain mystery into it
Give the people what they want amazing
Crazyshit that have to go to show the alright alright
Success on a road trip
Episode first of all I'd like to give a shout out to what I do foreign policy walk
What we did on the last episode
You know just
It's so difficult
It's difficult to interrupt our flow in order to thank people
You're so kind to support the show special thank-you out to new foreign policy walk
Thank you so much
Tell your brother thank you so much for joining up
If you want to become a policy wonk
You click support the
Yeah
Reconsider decisions up to that point
Not giving enough money to this Del Taco
West Bistro
We don't really know exactly
Sonia is on her way so very much
Follow
Today's episode of covering the 30
Yes I want to tell you a little bit about what happened the other day on the
There was a
Amazing comedy
Accidentally
Well that would be the only way it happens
It's for the entire beginning of
Alright I got
We have some big news out of Disney
Which means he has nothing to say it's going to blow everything out of the water
I just do it
I don't get into the news I just thought
I just don't know how to do it I just don't know how to do this job it's so huge
These are demons
A 10-minute ramble through screaming about demons they know they're doing it
What are you
Talking about
Steven Wright so you know what they're doing so at the end of the second hour or so
I would like for you to guess
What the big news out of business
That proves everything
Coco
What
Delivered
Pretty good
Overrated
Nobody knows this everyone knows
I've got two things I know
I didn't hate it
And start over
Because I want that
Star Wars in the clear
Episode 8
Are you shiting
That's not the last
Come on
It's not that
It's not that so
What happened with Ridley's
I would argue with his first-half problem
His second first and third eye problems
Listen
You should never even had this
Is Kevin the bird
Okay we can all agree on the talk about this the other night
Don't need to rehash this so the big man
Yes is with Millie Weaver
Roosevelt
Out and about
Trying to find a book
Cuz he has drilled into
Buying a children's book
Right
There's no way the story goes anywhere satisfying for
Define the book
Called feminist baby
Alright
Alright okay
So Disney
Is run by liberals even
Because one time
They put out a book called feminist baby
Your babies are you sure it's not
I know but I don't know why Alex didn't think that was
Somehow like
Trying to corrupt the children
Whatever the Socialists
Stance on
Certainly
Children after run Fortune 500
Companies like socialist
First second and third acts problems
A real bad boy
Better than Waldorf
Educational tell you that much I don't know anything about Waldorf education
It's like unguided
Like it's 88 celebrate
The like
Children get to learn however they want kind of as I understand
Like from The Simpsons episode Bart is accidentally classified as a
Genius until he goes to the school
What I understand
According to the Simpsons
But I would under
Stand it with that would make
I think so much
Like
You could just call that the episode where Bart learns to speak French
Fine fine
So Millie Weaver finds this book
And on one of these you give me The Simpsons reference that will explain the circuits
I don't know
So she finds this book
I wanted pages
It says this baby doesn't like pants
What is it what is that either way because I mean the reason the page is in there
Because babies often do take off their pants or diaper
Pants
Other page weather
Call Top
Dresses
No no it's it's all about their clothes
Perfect status display I've ever seen I thought it was like really really
Play bad then
You threw it to
Special Report
Where Millie Weaver is going over how she found it
Have you like I don't know how I can cover this
So I'm going to get some
Some help from Rainbow snatch
So bad
She does the throat as Superman is what she did she jump into a telephone booth
Knowstyle
Does Rainbow snatch in a wig
Sitting around reading the book
It's it's it's atrocious
Because the real story would be like
So
I can't breathe
A bookstore which first off
Where did those come from Sugar Ray
Right
Borders
No
Is mascot a bookstore and I went into the
Section which I still don't think they should know how to read
That should be the tree of knowledge you want to give kids
But not on purpose
I meant race memory
And then I read it again
And then Alex called me and said
I've got nothing
Rainbow snacks
Millie Weaver
Is the secret identity
It's possible
A regular life
She's rainbow snatch
It was a disaster
It made me laugh
Very hard
Another episode Alex's
Defensive Trump's Pocahontas
Discount
Why
Literally
The only difference I could come up with whatever whenever the news came out and I was going through all this
Sounds like he's dissing Naked Gun sketch
That's the difference
Jeff look at how hilarious it is
Would go to the Navajo windtalkers Association
Make a racist
Hilarious little bit it's so funny looking glass
The funny thing
Was plays the video of it talking over a guy
Actually was rainbow smash doing that
Higher thing word for word
That'd be a great B
Hilarious
Orange
Dumbass president
Yeah which makes it
Less Fun
Still very fun
So
That was a couple days ago and shockingly
Music
You know that's
He's defended the law
The amount of buildup you did on the feminist baby business
It would be last
4 months it doesn't bring it up again
As I've got it so he's got to jump around will get into today
This episode I've been listening to Alex Jones per year straight now
And I have never heard an episode end on a cliffhanger
Avenger ending
Eli's radio
Come back tomorrow I want to find out what happened it's pretty crazy
Special episode
Indeed
With powerful
Who is Ben
Then that accused of sexual harassment
Solidcore
Keeler Matt Lauer is apparently a Sex Dungeon
Reek automatically
Rewild
Those things
Come out interesting Lee Alakazam
Strange take
Specifically on Garrison Keillor and on Matt Lauer
Very weird is it going to get into personal and professional jealousy territory
No not really
Conspiracies
Like that's my that's my imagination of what is
These folks
The women aren't strong with a man are good luck
The children are above average
Is very strange
Take
People
And that is a minority
On the verge of collapsing
That's why all the Prairie Home Companion guy
Charlie Rose they're all people with big fat
But everybody wants to shove overboard because the systems collapsing
Viewers investors anymore they're all done
The golden
The altars
The IRA
Because the
It doesn't work anymore
They built
They built these so-called Stars up
To make the public
They're throwing them overboard
Okay
Yeah
Maybe my favorite take on this entire situation I've ever heard
It's interesting his conspiracy theories
These guys
This is true everybody's known they've been sexual harasser
They've been protected
Yeah right
V
The companies now
I like
The people get
Rid of these guys
25 million dollars on Matt Lauer this year
Yeah sexual harassment Bad Wolf
Skippy's f****** out of here
Let's get some bargain-basement sexual harassers in here because they can do just as good
Press blade how's it going
I don't try to answer
Unrelated question is
Cranberry splash
Ciara mr. comes out
PRL
Tournament
Fandroid I understand we're trying to run a show
I think it's even weirder
It's a regular Coca-Cola
Come on delicious
Alex's
Pretending that there is no awareness that these people are sexual harasser
It's just a thing
The media is falling apart no one watching the shows anymore we got to get out of contract
And so
We are just going to
Throw them in off the bus or whatever
Black Ops multiple levels
You can say
All of the eclipse of the accusers
Not just those guys but then by association
All accusers everywhere right
In order to make sure that
Powerful people get their contract
Yeah so every sexual harassment accuser is a false
Kind of
The easiest kind of in that
Most are fake
Credibly
Version of the narrative
Simpler explanation
Powerful dudes
Think they can do anything and then
A very simple explanation is too much power they abused it
Problem-solve
You know that's from absolute power corrupts absolute
Power corrupts absolutely
You know how we know that
I am amazed how surprised most people are to find out that it's
Also shoutout to the chat room root beer sucks
Music videos of this week
Weirdly Cornett number 21 for the
Next Gold Cobra
Not my locker what I'm seeing here
Anyway I looked back into this
Other day
I started this morning
Real early by retweeting
Videos of alleged
Attack
Naked Gun level in San Ramon
First organization here in a little bit
And so
In response to this
Paul Joseph Watson
Even tweeted
Hey whoever's running the President social media
Needs to be a little more careful
That's the
Paul Joseph Watson even
Grace Bader extraordinary career out of
Look at what these Muslims are going to f****** yeah
It's like hey what what casino
First knows their history better than
Trump
I'm so he's like you're going to not want to be associated with them witches
Smart right but then at the same time
Tweet he was saying
Who runs the
Different social medias res even trying to get drunk off the hook for yet
It's really it is interesting
To me the division that
They are with him being like
He's not saying the contact was bad
It's just the source of it
The problem there is
The only person dumb enough
Holding Twitter's
Are holding Trump's Twitter account
To do that
Is Trump
Forensic evidence Trump personally
Is everybody with any level of x
Receives would go
Owner of that a bad idea
Only the dumbest man in the White House
Whatever dude
Let me be clear also has clownin
You are not thinking this is reason
No no
We are not condoning no it's just interesting to me that on some level
He understands
That there's a line
At least a line of Association
Look at. Cross associated with
F****** Infowars
In Britain
They have
You kept which is a party built
Entirely around races
More or less everyone knows you
A party built entirely around Ray
And in the larger context
To Britton they're like
We're going to let you guys be
Even UK
Looks at Britton first and goes
Well we can't be having this s***
That's how far right there
I want to kill black people ukur crazy
Still comes down to two
Optics
You know that's still really the issue people have
It's not the content
Did Paul Joseph Watson
Complain about crack
Those guys
Right right
Pretty f***** up what's even more f***** up
Is Alex's take on Paul Joseph Watson
Kill us all
We'd all turned against Trump
Multiple times said
I'm going to turn on trop and he does accent
Literally said I'm off the Trump train
Right
Berry waffle
But think about
Eatbook
Exactly
Cuz it's too easy to clown on in for that
Anyway let's get the rest of the clip
No that's the price
Present
Are the ones hyping up the cultural take over the West
I wasn't mad
Literally hundreds of publication
That is tweet
Paul Watson
You are
Moerlein
Okay
Nobody's really saying that you're turning again
Phone number really saying is
Look at how dumb this guy is
Even people are like that
Even people who are like
Spiritually and philosophically further down the
The f*****-up Rabbit Hole or like this
Is not good
Yeah
So the other thing
Okay
The media halfway defended Trump when he wouldn't
Condemn
Charlottesville
Murder
Good people on both sides
Now it's
F****** Alex Jones was like
That's probably somebody else
You can't look
Even if you don't want to condemn them
Do it all all white racism right
Right that blew up
How bad is this
Even Alex Jones has to be like 10 guys why are you talkin about about Trump on this one
You like
My bad
One of the big stories that Alex
Railing on
Today is about
There are there was like a video that came out of
People being sold into slavery
Likes lightbox
I want to be fair to Global slave trade is big
Even in the states
Think the estimation
They're like
Somatic waves
Somatic
Good job trying to dress
There's a stomach issue
It doesn't really stupid s*** about
Slavery
Uses racial slur
He's trying to pretend that they have the n-word in the Quran
Under Islam
You can enslave them
Arab slave trade
Out of the Old Testament
Mark of Cain
And the rest of it was on
Transatlantic slave trade
Control
I also felt in Oregon
Black
None of that's true
It's not even close
Timeline set
Not really
Yeah
Say
Chomping at the bit there
My point is
All of the stuff is wrong
True
Leg purple what's amazing about that
Is he started Opera
And then he was like
I'm pretty sure that
But what if I go here and that was
And then it got wrong
And then somehow it got wrong or still usually in this situation what happened
Snow is generally
Spiral into the correct
Like historically
Explain this
Right historically eventually he could
To like
This is accurate actual historic history
A couple hundred years before this.
Kind of troops
But he was still wrong about the
And he really went hard on the
Arab slave trade
So
Around Europe
The Iberian Peninsula from the time of like 782
Yo into the 1300's and what have you
Be taken into account and then
Every culture back then
Slavery
Because they found
Overtime that it was much more economic
Slave everybody in
Very usable
Group of people
I do all the work they don't want to do create Leisure for themselves
Humans for human Saget's absolutely
Universal through cultures
Greece
Was full of slaves
Rod wave
All of it
Like it's just continued
But then
The thing that we need to really address
Is the Arab slave trade
Evolve
Into the African and
Then European slave trade
That was a product of Portugal
In the mid-1400s
Portugal at the time
Wasn't a mint
Immensely successful
Nautical coasters
They were amazing at shipbuilding and one things that was your shoe today
Is it they were the first people that were able to
To Get Around the Horn of Africa
They were able to get down there
The slave Coast
With a large area of countries like
Nigeria
A couple others I can't remember
Diane Daywood
Just go in and they would take a bunch of people
He was 1442
I was when they first
I started taking people from Africa
Do you know who is on those
Ships that Columbus
I don't know
Magellan
Know-all Portugal's are Muslim
That you could argue because
AMC 20
Or at least the Arabs
It's not
If there's water.
Is a lot of different types of
But they did end up taking a lot of the Iberian Peninsula weatherbeeta Portugal Spain
All of that area but there's a thing called the Reconquista
That happened between
The 1800's and the 1400s
Where in
The white
People took back over the Iberian Peninsula
Cambridge was not under Islamic rule it was not under Arab rule
Are you sure
Positive
I don't think you can be
I'm absolutely positive
You know what
Egypt
Okay
Brake and argue with that
It's complete nonsense it's all
History in service of demon season 7 of game
Game of Thrones in that all of his dates kind of move around to the point where it doesn't make any sense
Right
Inspirit
And I agree with Alex not at all
So that sucks
I wish you would realize
Possible that
Have you studied any
Because we
We see how
Slowly Kiri
On the show
Cuz he reads
Something
It does not go 50 it's the reading equivalent of Hunter
Keyboard
Slow typing slow reader
He reads with two
Fingers metaphorically ever read
Like just
Example
Eco sign
11:00
The f****** text
There's literally no way that his
Swole ask that
Within the time constraints
3 hours a day radio
Make these dumbass special reports
And
Apparently he's in charge of the marketing
Department head Infowars creating the specials
Trying to get all the product out the door
All that's what there's no way he has time to read any of the stuff he says he's reading
There is one
Okay
He's a world-class
Oh yeah
Like a world-class Kim
Lexus headlight
The way that you rambled nonsense
So confidently he's confident
Read a book
Like you got the broad Strokes of the book and he didn't even get that
No
It's all confidential
Sound and Fury signifying nothing
Bulshit with the cliff notes of history and thought that meant
That meant he learn
Because
You know
He's going to claim
He's looked into Britain
President Donald Trump
Retweeted three videos posted by Christian activist
Jada
President
That was speaking out against Sharia in
Britain first party
And issued a police present Trump
Two years of convicted for Islam
Terrorism rally in Belfast
Ireland
Say what you want about
Group there
Serious issues with
I was sure you'll be next
3 the game trying to trigger that that first they came for the blanks
I think you caught a lot you were scribbling Christian nationalist
Christian nationalist
Is
Maybe the best euphemism
That I've heard
Because once again
Let's listen breakdown Christian
Brave
I mean that.
Christian nationalist come
What are you name
Name a curse
When you close your eyes and think of Krista
Billy Graham
Okay
Jim Bakker
I don't know Alex Jones
Is it anybody black
Know anybody brown
Hot women either
She's dead and she can't hurt us if she also turned against
Turned out but I guess this is Jayda fransen
Which is too close to my last name for comfort
Speaking out against Islam
They were charged with religiously aggravated harassment
It was an anti-terrorist
We got a lot of euphemisms in there
Propaganda
Fake bulshit
About Muslim
For putting out propaganda
Roosevelt don't post like all kinds of mislead
About like people celebrating
Soccer win
That shot manipulative lie to make it look like Muslim Zariah.
At least if I recalled
Who plays the same game when he has like fireworks displays and he's like
Play on people
Like that
Incredibly
Apparently the first party got in trouble
Because they had images of
British crown on their merchandise
Ridgeview a branding issue
Al Capone Humana vision of racism is what that is
The advertising standards
Authority in
They had to take it off because
Symbol
Would imply they were selling merchandise
That was British man
Under the
What have you
Sisters fun
But it is like
Okay
Both parties are dumb
Right
You should be able to put the crown on
I don't really care
Is these three
If you get down to
Not
Yeah so one of them
Is a Muslim Muslim beats beats up Dutch boy on crutches
Hi the fake video it was created by website
Call dumpert
Destroy the statue of the Virgin Mary
Claire Cruz Affiliated without the al-nusra front
It's not even
The other one the video islamist bushes
Teenage boy off Route
And beat him to death
Was actually of a young cleric
Critic of Mohamed Morsi
Be beating up
Amidst the unrest of morsi's
Overthrow
So they're not really
They're presenting the Arabs
Yeah same way Alex presents all this all this b******* about
The the
And what have you
He's acting like it
Random attack
I want
Legit fake
The other two are one in the middle and the other was in the middle of an overthrow
And the person who was the victim of it was a Critic
Of the deposed
All Muslims
So
You know the term fake news is toothless
Meaningless
Yeah but in this case beat
3 videos that were being
That were repeated
Propaganda
Absolutely
We're probably only demonizing
All Muslims
Here's my
Skype
This does not matter
The president's role in a does
Fake news
This is not news
Here's a here's the point okay what did we learn
From Trump
Well we already knew that you was a violin
So I guess we didn't learn that okay what else
We learned
He's dumb but we already knew that
I don't know I guess not much
You have actually written down
The first two on the things that I've written you said the first two on the things that I wrote down as the things we already knew
Oh yeah yeah
All of this
It doesn't dissolve it
In line with everything we already know about
Now that's true
It's not it's nothing singing like 3 million immigrants
Illegal immigrants voting
Things that are not
Become news when the
Doing them and their bigoted
Again
That's that's important it's not on the pile
The theory that there is no Trump stories
Is there's one trumps
If you are writing a trump story it should be
Impeach the president impeached a president impeached president impeached
There's no point writing Trump
Blanks
No it's probably true
It doesn't matter
Theresa may look like a giant
Well she came out and said don't do that what is everybody in Britain called
You should revoke his abilities
Hold on
Maybe Corbin will do that
But
Anyway
We haven't had a lot of Russia
The talk lately
Alex has not been super on mielec
Discuss Russia
He drops this little Chestnut in as he's going through
Today's news breakdown
Before election
Hear the lamp the saying if you're white especially
Bright
That's a weird policy
Well-hit the implication that he's
He's making is that like food in his paint white people to have
Narrative
Yeah
Do you think Alex saw that was like
Solution to wipe
Reproduce
Absolutely
You said as much already
See now that's an interesting fact
Alright
You pay people to become the majority
Now that's a really interesting
It would take Joe take the generation would be a delay in it
It's stupid but it's just another way of him like he complains about birth rates.
Right
He's using Putin
As an example of someone who
Who's doing it right
Babies they won't even pay
Imma just goes back to
Ghetto white identification White
So anyway
There's another narrative
Bombshell
It will end up leading to the cliff
The introduction of it
Apparently
All right haha
Season of Breaking Bad
Apparently
There's a university
Somewhere near Austin
One of their colomont
No
Something-or-other
Okay
Wonder columnist
Wrote an article about how most of the people he's ever met in his life
Have not been great
Here's the
Alex Jones
Being Furious about it
I will be back
The other side
Newswars.com
Campus reform
People on abomination
Deadpool
Abomination
Albuquerque
Texas State University student newspaper on the front
Is an abomination
We should get a physical copy of it
We up photos
Professor Spears
Lovers
Police officers Etc
Call mrs. Rudy Martinez
Wow what a racist
Brett
Great
No
Possibly two
Probably
That's just kind of how we work right I guess so
So this is a guy who's
Tutorial Rider
Alex, you are already in the corner before it even began
It just makes me think
How much
Walking fun I would have with them
It's like when I was in college I wrote for my campus paper
3 years I wrote editorials for
For the man-eater University of Missouri newspaper editorial
Become s*** talking is the greatest thing you've ever heard
Incredible hot water for an article I wrote about how all farmer
Who is Jack off cows
F****** deathreats
Kick me out of college
So much fun people to kiss my ass send me aggressive emails out kiss my ass
Wolf
If Alex Jones
When I was in college
Taking my article
And started lying about it misrepresenting it
And turning it into something like one of his narrative
I would have been like
F*** you
I'll be sitting there drunk as s*** and just like
I would OD all I talked about
How is it that he's get this
It's f****** idiot editorial writers and he still hasn't found out about us b******* because he's not afraid
Read of them I don't mean to
I don't mean as narcissistically he should be
Like the fact that we take the time
You struck the things
Like the Muslim slave trade name it isn't the one we did way back though
We deal with him in a way that
He's not being dealt with by other people
And I think he should be scared of giving us any kind of promotion
Even if it's these guys are f****** globalist I know Soros paying them threat something like that that even would be Danger
Anything that would get us more attention
Very dangerous
Just use that guy as a prop now it was me
In college
Can you get that
Because I'm dangerously Alex Jones
Hey it's this look he can punch that guy over there
Lowrider is going
Hope you have a little bit of it
In contact with us I hope he has been spirit in him because if I was then
I would get on it I would get on Alex's show
Yeah cuz I know he would want to have me on the show
Wasted mockery of the preceding
I didn't actually read it
Editorial
Girl f****** trash
We can throw
Let's move along I just have a lot of
About what I could have done
I'm sorry Dan
Oh well
Editorial
Alex
The earlier was talking about her food
It's going to pay white people to reproduce
Yes
Text Matthew has a little article about policy that
Makes perfect sense.
Article
He does not get into the article
The read the headline of an article and talk about how it's important
About Muslims
Who's taking over demographically in Europe
And the source of it
It's going to go from 1% to 3%
Possibly
Yeah
So
Whataburger
From Alex's last marathon
Is it he launched in
New product
The real red
And from what we've been able to
Discern
It's a multi
It's a multivitamin that turns you into an aware
Socially representative
It also has a steroid
Precursor
I promise there's no stimulants
Sing a song he does so many f****** commercials for this
Real wrestling
That I thought was really funny
And completely safe
I don't think that's weird ringing endorsement
Don't
I like it when you have to tell me something is totally
And completely
Yeah yeah if you were like
Take this it's completely safe
If I would be like that
That doesn't sound good
If you said it's totally and completely
Do not trust you at all
Giada's like Deuteronomy
I'm not,
2015 we discovered that Alex stole Hillary for prison
A bumper sticker that sauce and turned it into a
Million-dollar
No bum rushing Hillary
Some stuff like that
Clippy admits that he stole the name
Real red pill
I know it's not surprising
But it is important that we document
Like legitimately howling
Creative Alex
He stole one of his biggest things were above
Sticker that you saw and admitting that he just stole this from The Matrix
Conversion
I just don't I just don't find this one to be surprised
Surprising it's just about putting it on the record
Documenting your right
He's on creative in
Mister is a plagiarist
To a great extent
Sounds like a plan
Anyway
Who's next
Alex Jones
Juno
Define
Is
Over-inflated
And his importance
In the world no idea pretend
Callers that lie to him rcia sources and stuff like that
The FBI guy
I literally
Not allowed to keep up
I cannot keep up so I know you've been slacking or keeping up but
The FBI caller who is shooting at the Las Vegas shooting
Who Alex said the FBI contacted 20 minutes after he was on the phone
Write all this
Or something
The Narrative has escalated incredibly
Believe a lick of it
Close
Undisclosed
Did think the reason I wanted to bring that up is I want to play a little bit of Alex's game
The conspiracy game
Before I do I want to make it clear that Galaxy
Is making all this up
And the father is bullshiting
Of course but if he's not
Who called in and was revealing information
The only way that the FBI would have been able to
Find out who he is
That quickly
And lock him up
Is it Alex tipped him off
I've Alex snitched on the guy to the FBI
Or watching
Who is who is
In every world
Suggested that he sold out his source
Reviewing sources over and over again
Really possible
Like I said
What is importance
Threatened by
About what
Covers level
Convenience
Also
That's not the only thing that off the record covers
It's not like just right
You can't say it
If I don't leave the Muslims alone
Guess what I'm sipping down
Get ready
The big Torpedoes are coming
That's how I go to the Heights
I'm going to go after radical Islam Orthodoxy
I'm going to go out to the public
For letting me know where you're at
I'm coming for you
Will
The Open Fire politically as well
Statements like you
Without me
Cuz it's all about me it's all about my family
About me cuz it's all about me. That
Other people's lives
Other people's future
You got that
There's a lot of things
Describing conversations
His lawyers
I probably do
Lesbian like okay
Here's what you said
And here's how we're going to lose it in jeopardy
Here's how we're going to lose all of our men
You're my favorite client
I am going to charge you all the money hours on Alex
First of all it's not about me it's all about anything
Cuz I think that he is
It's the race.
Trying to tap into that like
My ancestors are right here
Yeah I kind of think we are all the same person
To some extent
Empathic
I do really like that kind
Kind of thought that like
You and I are essentially the
The same person just living
Via the Great Big Blob
Yeah I made the Buddhist empathy on yourself
But I clearly it has not been cut
In order to successfully do that
This to me feels
Real
Tired
Like
To work himself up in like
They just can't get over the hill into like the I'm going to
Scream and yell and what happened I don't know why
Baby no brain force in the studio or something along those lines
But it does feel a bit different
Normal
He's not capable of turning over the
I think I think there might be
James in motion right there might be some sort of like
Stimulant withdrawal
Something like that
Cuz you know how much of the brain Force
Then you're out the warehouse
True
Alex
Either
Good-byes everything for the year on Cyber Monday
Used to cut coupons
What you going to do
Probably still kept coupon
Alex Jones
Put up a video
Let me ask you a
Do you think it's today
Or do you think it's a larger trend of him not being able to really talk
Turn it off
He's really got ghost
The beginning of that feminist baby riff
That was he was on
For sure
The beginning part of that baby feminas riff
He was on for sure is not a sentence
Did I ever want to hear you not get to the store because he knew it was weak
He was on
Like like
Yeah it was good
But
Did put out a video about him
Like
Basically praying on air
Which we've seen him do a bit
Defensive about it
Really weird
Real weird
Right wing watch
Alex Jones called on the power
Jesus Christ
So Alex
He thinks we're going to get to the crazy part.
He thinks that they're like they hate Chris
Then what have you but the reality is that
Don't even let their daughters date until they run away at 8
Making fun of
How he does
It's so fake
Our first episode
Ever
It's time to pray
Stoffel and that's really more with her making fun of it
He's screaming about hating people and demons and
Holland
Econo brake
That's why your Godless losers Phil
You're so disconnected
The word
Dutch government says this video of a kid
England
Get three more example
And the police department
Not true Alex don't tell people to type it in
Through
New York time
Fox News apologizes for false claims of Muslim only areas in England and France
Who is issued a nun
Usual on-air apology on Saturday night for having allowed its anchors at gas to repeat the folks claim that there are Muslim
I'm only no go zones at European countries like England and France
That are not under the control of this in a ruled according to Sharia law
The statement was referred to as a correction by the fox report host
Julie Banderas over the course of this last week we made some regrettable errors on air
Muslim population in Europe
Particularly with regard to England and France
Wow now this applies especially to
Discussions of no-go zones areas where non-muslims allegedly are not allowed in
Harrisonville
Quotes
To be clear there is no formal designation of these zones and either country
The assertion
That's an even notoriously stupid a diplomatic New York Times
Fox News issued a rare apology which might might as well read like
Notoriously low Bard Fox News
Fox News
No existed for that
You can do this to like
You can look into it if you want
You can take a little bit.
Confined
It's 450 all these ideas
I mean like this is one of the things they talked about all the time with sweet and they talk about Malmo
City of Malmo being like
The only Muslim
Absolutely not true it's it's
There are videos much like the ones Trump Paul Joseph Watson makes hang out of
Inderal
Complete
Baradar misrepresented videos
Like again I can't stress enough
The idea that Paul Joseph Watson
Would have a video of a New Year celebration where people are short Bastille Day
When were they shooting off fireworks
And claimed that it
Muslim hordes run-amok
Memes
Nothing is credible
But like you're at your standard
Is it what you're doing there are out the window
And so whenever you have these people who reporting on these Muslim no-go Zone
Generally stuff
Stuff like that
Lindsey bulshit
It's frustrating to me that
Because that's
It's like the one truth of America
Is the one truth
Of immigrants
Google anywhere
Which is not one of them agree
Drink go somewhere
They just want
Reek
Create their home
Go somewhere
They become part of somewhere new what America is like
New Orleans
You don't go there because you see a different group of people
Everywhere you go there because you see all of these
These people creating something new
Beautiful girl wanted to join the place there let me take that even one step further
I live in uptown
Chicago outfit
That were just as one of the examples of the little as cultural enclaves
And there are places like that which is
Which is the affirmation
The other side of
Experience
To become a part of the whole but at the same time we were taking two pieces of you
Your culture appreciate them adjoining your culture
On a facsimile level within America
To even bring both lungs into it when I was growing up there was a mosque
In Columbia Missouri there was
I don't know couple blocks from downtown
Whatever that means in a small town
But like I would go to the mosque
I would go with my family we go in
Then just go to other
Cultures
Festivals
Cuban Festival
Puerto Rican festival
Don't go there and see all of these Cuban people
The f*** off
Is everybody like chick dish General
But it's not like
The Halloween costume version of appropriation you know like
Mexican Festival in
Just drunk white people in Cinco de Mayo
Which is a weird which is one of the weirder like
Okay
Just about boobs
And
Chasing snakes out of everywhere
It's less about what the holiday isn't how it's become
Associated with booze
Immigrants that go places
We all want
Totally
The bigger picture
You know you can have those examples of Cinco de Mayo and Saint Patrick
If you look at the bigger pic
All those other awesome little fast
Send
Block party
Do you want to know
Do you want to know what the best thing to show people
Immigrants
It's such a strangely accurate immigrants
With the image of white nationalism in your head
I kind of get it but
Prince
Daughter grows up
Speaking unaccented English like all of this s***
And they get that
Feeling of like well we want you
You two have some sore
To your Homeland
Integrated
Into your new home
Fears coming together
Also
Oh my God Dan Aykroyd
Basic condoms are gum
Wild
Smell weird
Like Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles is a surprising review of getting culture in New York City and delay
Play 80s
A surprising review of Evergreen crunch
Culture in the late 90s
This isn't like that clip
So Tim has nightclub Alex Jones reveals that he has a nuanced understanding of lesbian
And it
One of the more f***** up things
On the show
Most of the so-called liberal lesbian
What's slapping girls around
Most of these books
They want to be
That Fifty Shades of Grey
I'll start begging for your mom
For a second
Because he he he jumps
Rub that on to something
If possible
Even more f***** up
What
Okay
I guess what he saying
Is that
First offered what he saying is
Keith hit women
Poodle
That's exactly what he's saying it's not right but some like it
He's saying that Stockholm Syndrome
Is actually
Just how you're supposed to deal with
I don't know what to do with that
Well
When he says that's not what I'm saying
The question is
Then what are you saying
And the answer is
I think he's saying it's okay to hit women probably on some level think that male-dominated culture that
Is expressed wanting
Well and of course if you are hitting somebody
Speaking they will say
Please don't hit
Right in which case
You will say no
You're no actually mean
You really want me
You know the sexual Spectrum
Is wide and some people like rough trade
People around like
Within the collective sexual boundaries
His
Is logic does not track
Okay women go to lesbians
Because they
Want to get hit and no man will do it right then and later on
He says
Women go
Women who let men hit them
Then they put on pigments
No they say I'm going to torture you for 6 weeks
Fifty Shades of Grey is a gateway drug
I like you good tied up once and everything
Spawn everything is cool but then the next time
The door
Believes about the idea of BDSM it's
Stuff like that
Liberals so now let's get to the rest of the stuff cuz I'm telling you it gets even more f***** up
Listen to this
They want to get you in a dungeon
They want to strap you down
We look in a mirror
It's one thing to eat your brain now
What's start
Side area.
I'm going to eat your cerebral cortex last
You're going to be guilty when I say you're guilty
Alex just watched
That's what happened
Do you watch that Ray Liotta scene in Hannibal
Thanks for that no other way
Specific reference right
Whatever
So real
Oh my God
Ray Liotta that dza.
That guy's not an actor
Even if your talk
Metaphoric
Real Steel does
It's really interesting house that's not like
Really blood libel but it's real close
You know it's not in that narrative
The cannibalism aspect of it is
Here's what I'd say
The Europeans
We are
F***** up enough to get there to be fair in a land where 90% of the
To be fair
Can't pull the name of the guy who wrote Hannibal but
Hannibal Buress
Alex Jones
Earlier
We discussed
How Alex believes
Is there a boy
Do they mention does he mention
Hannibal how he's
He's not going to eat
Frontal cortex off the top of his head
Cuz that's
Suggest a certain level of information about the brain that I would not
Nobody
He's wrong also absolutely
What does map science
It's not that I think that's just
Capiz lighted to see him go wild with the small amount of knowledge
She does have or it's like okay
Well if I were going to eat
Bright
Middle parts weird the back part is lizard
That's what I know he knows that the center is
Is where everything happens around the Broca's area or on the side
It's not
Also just seen the Temple of Doom
Straight a monkey's head there
True
Nothing monkey
Fungus art
Anyway
But be that as it may
We talked about Muslim no-go Zone
How even Fox News had to apologize
Recovering that
Cuz if not real
And it makes clip
Alex jump
There are no go zones in
In America
Yeah
Food.com soft
Food
But
Great
Never going outside
Couple years ago and three times
Very aggressive large
Blackmail
Yeah we talked about this already
A homeless person
Back off
That's what happened
And my wife
I don't want to have to
It's a no-go Zone
I can't go
First
The Black Culture
So that mean this is just racial fear
This is all.
Minority of racist blacks
Minority / plurality of racist whites does not
Right there all said
When I first moved to the city
Chicago that is
I was real
Southsider going west
There are some areas that aren't no go zones but their areas where you don't want to necessarily
After Dark
I mean
It's a reality of the f*****-up nature of how weaves own this city
And racist
But I thought the entirety lights light of certain areas
Don't go there you'll get stabbed
Because that is what people throw around
A good
The year or so
Not to get past that, I realized that it was probably overblown
To the point where light
Almost all the city is awesome
I've been to East Austin there it's a great area
That there might be
Be dangerous
Supernature of
Speedy's
That's kind of how urban areas work
We go through this so many different
If you go by /
Hundred thousand all the sudden you start
In Chicago go down in the murder rate
Like
And even then you see the statistics on white on white and black on black
Crime and chances are
There's a 90% chance you're going to get f***** up by somebody of your own
Your own race
Alex reject those
Statistically
You can go to the south side
Anytime you want
Walk around anywhere
You might get a weird look
Maybe even then
The only you're not going to get
It hurt nobody wants nobody wants to hurt anybody else
Let's not.
That's not weird that you always do at the black bee
Have we had that talk
We should probably do this all there
Let me tell you how I feel about aging
So
If you just went on the night nowhere
That someday is at some point
Hey Asian people
I mean like just this idea that he's applying this
Fictional stuff about no go zones in Europe
To now Austin's you can place where there are no go zones
Just he's
So scared of everything
It's just
No he's not scared
He wants you to visit
Incentive
To make you afraid
Bucked up
What is a the police
If you are in a
One of the things that whines up making you
Uso
Much more likely to be
Inclusive is that
You are included
When you're included in
As we were talking about earlier
Cuban celebration
You're not afraid of Cubans anymore your include
Can you start to understand why they have that weird ham pickle mustard sandwich
Is plantain isn't as bad as I thought it was
But
It's like a banana
What anyway
At the top of the show
Dealt with the narrative
That
Matt Lauer
Garrison Keillor
Sexual assault
If that isn't flipping
Actually let Colin
Is that what is argument
No that doesn't come up incredibly racist and recognize that their fans are all Races to Let's Nacho
Doesn't come up but
I just want to stress that like
It's not just
The throwaways
He brings it up like three or four times on the show that's really what he think
Is going on which is bizarre
Siri
Find why he would
Wally's dumb
No
Preemptive
No I don't think
I don't well
I don't tell me that Leanne
I think they dated
That that like
There's there's a lot of talk online and they were not going to last interaction is
Really weird around they had a fling or something like that
I'm not defending Alex Jones at all
In saying this
Rat
I don't think
That is his style
He's a sexual harasser
Thought that about Matt
F****** louder either I would think it more than Alex Jones
I think that he is probably a harasser
But not like a
We yelled at that lady on the street
Probably
If somebody comes forward on Alex
I think I'm pretty well I think the more likely thing is
Protection for Trump
Roy Moore
That's more where his feelings lie
And the
Like
Motivated for those guys
Or financially motivated then in the same way
Be financially motivated
For a Roy Moore
Also at the same time the narratives that it's about the contract that feeds into
Reason
To be in that camp himself into a strange
Corner of now.
Defending every sex
Weird it was next clip
He's unclear whether he's
Defending Matt Lauer
It's up and down
Top talk show hosts
The escapades
But I don't
So he mostly girls wanted
As every dude
He is defending it but he's trying to play that weird fence
I'm not defending it but everything I'm doing is
Independence
We know that
Believe that
I'm too and in this clip
He is sort of imagining his current
Victory over the globalist
Now it's the next chapter of his face
Globalist
They're doing now
When you see the generals
Loading up on their train and the Run
Hung in bedroom
People are turning on
Bosses bosses are
Cleaning up the bread crumbs
Kill right now
Their hands full killing off
People that know
Where the bodies are buried or where the bank accounts are
Where the landing bases are
All over rural areas are building
4 heavy aircraft
That's been a minute
Dial Chad
Global cover-up Fuller Beach
Killed who have the
Good political
But be that as it may it's like
Alex
You're crazy
But
If you want
I'm crazy this dance my friend
If you want to do that
You need
Information
Half of your name
You have
Info is short for information
Entirely
I think you've lost your mind
Killed
All around
Frank separate
Frank from down the way
Sapphire
No go zones
Soros operative took him down do you know why
He had a
Information on
Frankie J
Deer River no-go Zone snow cone
Really good
Anyway
I got to logos a no-go Zone
Tommy Davidson
Anyway
Most idiotic moronic people
Are going along with this
Because
Getting a royal title
Someone was bad
Drooling
Okay
Well first off Dan
Someone has
So you made
Alright Malaysia
Lord I haven't
Assaulted
Umaid bhawan milord
Irony there the projection is is like 3/4 of the show isn't talking about people treating a bad guy
Cuz he's white
Don't I mean
Okay
The difference between
Minorities
Women
Speaking up for themselves
I'm trying to adjust
The social hierarchy that
And Alex Jones
Creating
Tire world
View that involves
Metal poisoning of the water in
Destruction of
Christian
Christendom system
The way to a
Tack White
People
Different
It goes back to what I was trying to get you with the feminist baby
Do you think it's like
You
People post memes and then laugh
Because you saw a feminist baby book
And you
This is like a little bit
Hire like 15 minutes about it on your movie now we need to write this baby
Except which Alex Jones is like
I've been wrong racially is on
Entirely different level then
That's not dream Dreamworks is the way to go
I just don't know
I don't understand how he doesn't have the
Going to be like wait I do that all the time
The entirety
Like you don't we go back to this
Hypocrisy is a feature
It is not a
Bug of there
World
I don't disagree
Hip-hop
Christian
Point of view is something that they Revel in
They want every
If you are a white person who want special treatment
For white
The only way you can
I can deal with that
Is by Turner
Into urine
Distance until logic
Preferential
Treatment
The same time saying
That everybody should
Percy is all you can
Turn to
As a mode of thought
And so
That's
That's our goal
Make hypocrisy so normal
Help but
I'm just Passover
You pointing that out.
Just now is something that
That we're all still like
You can't do that
Everything
To some extent it is like the.
It is
The same thing as the Ice Bowl
It's more just like that this is this is the reality of how he operates
I'm not like
Can you believe you such a hypocrite cuz we do know that game doesn't work
More like
Here's a journal of his b*******
Well you take
Take a look at
The progressives
Versus
If you want to talk about Hip Hop
Simply look at the way that we're dealing with sex
Progressives are currently having a
Purge
And it's probably not enough and it's not aggressive enough like
It's very high-profile but the mid-level guy
Not bad
Considering how bad it's been in the past
Cold comfort to some extent
F******
Doing it and we're all wrestling
Like there's no amount of there's no
Feel but you can
Can be in now except maybe like electrical engine
Where am I
Maybe we're already bisexual
Like we were hanging out
Reflection
Hopefully
Dealing with the underlying issue
And it sucks
But if you want to have some comfort
About Alex Jones and
Hypocrisy
And all that stuff
What have you
He
Knows that his listeners
He's aware
And the very least
This next clip kind of indicates.
To me that he is
He gets it
Should I love
We're at the best Scholars loras College, Paradise
Jumbo cilantro bit of sleep
Flash
Your phone calls
Bittersweet
Certainly
I think it's always been you trying to say
Somehow we're going to be real bad
Pretty sure that's what he was saying there Alex
Pretty bad
Not as bad as I want to talk about
Here's one of the calls
The lady wants to get into talking about how I
They're always a choice
Are you with God are you with Satan
I'll let you think it over
And you have to pick a side
You're either going to pick up five you're going to pick things by
And I picked
Christ
Metaphysical
We know that so much
With all these things happening
Our spirits
Broadcasting
I think this rhetoric I just want to pause we're going to get through the rest of the clip but I just think this rhetoric
Super f****** day
I think of this
Never trust anybody who knows anything
Ever always go with the guy and the Bible
But a lot harder
Also like
Look
God is the only thing that's important
Christianity is under attack but also
Can't be trusted
Bucked up
Most these churches aren't real churches and that's really the big threat
There's no way
Up against Islam
What's halfway in the Poland
A tornado
What wrong baby Toys R Us
Call large print
I know they're a lot of nice Muslim before Muslim
I love when people say I don't want to
Bright
Just
You hate Muslims against your will still hate Muslims in your
It doesn't suggest it
It requires
I don't want to light
Right I don't want to I want to be a better person
You're making me
That makes perfect sense a tweeted this earlier today when I heard this
It's just
That
He says stuff like that
Has no qualms with like
It's cool with that
I don't want to hate Muslims
Is first of all like
Cowardly
Because you're trying to make yourself seem like a good person
Within your bigoted
But it's also admitting straight up
The bigotry
And that's
You would host making this up text
You would hope that your audience
Would be like
Dude
But they talk
Is there on the same page about 10 million
Permission
To be on the same page
Now admittedly we do too but that's just on the list
The things that you find raised
Oswalt donkey growing out
In the 1180
That's correct
The only thing that Alex Jones
Bambi talking about is
The expansion.
The arrow
Armies did
Persian armies did in the
X700
What does pre Crusades by
Century
Or the play Othello we already talked
Like we did so
Pointless to talk about but
The nature of Empire
Back then
We're such
Like
Alexander the Great
Genghis Khan
All sorts of people throughout Rome in Greece
They invaded Neighbors
And not to the extent of just like
You stayed in your your geographical area like he's trying to draw some line that like
The Arabs are the Muslims back then
Yeah he went into Europe with their own places
No one respected those batteries cuz of batteries didn't exist back then
Afraid that wasn't
Poland
This is complete nonsense
Even if you go back to it and talk about
Empire culture
Call it every
Part of that
Was any of this
Empires
Demolish
The cultures
Usually
Zorbs successful as it was his children would become
Parts of the the cultures that they
Took over
I didn't tear them in such a way
Have to worry about uprising
Nearly as much
Successors fail
Cuz they said they did not do that
Because they once again
Took advantage of this idea of
Their identity
Simple
Because their lunatic dad raped and murdered his way around Mongolia
Like when you go to Rome
Rome was
Everywhere Rome went
Like they first on never set
Only you
No the dino I know
But it was
The point being like the first of the
First wave of Roman conqueror
Would go into a place
Say these people
And then the next Generation they were like all of these people are Roman
Very simple
Everyday Direct
0121 situation
And that's why it lasted far longer than the American
Believe that we're Americans
Geographic
MN murder
Sunnyway ilex has a lot of a historical ideas
About all this
See where the rest of this club takes us
And they're using it and it's
Thank you
We do not match
I'll give you that one that one was a bad that wasn't a harsh add pivot of like I'm going to kill everybody
They also we're going to be
But it was like a
Hey we're going to get to you and you and you and then we're going to
You seem to forget because we had that conversation that the beginning of that clip was him never fall to Islam
Because of
When we broke in that clip
A little bit.
Alright generally he goes from yelling to
Hard pivot right
Comes back
Another bit of
Local affiliates become a sponsor
Cinema 123
Billboard
To the truth
America organizations that are pro Christian
Sharon
Your church
They can make no law respecting
Cheer up
Solid
I was looking through the Bible tithe
To the church
Pocket God
You tithe
To Infowars by friend Bible verses
Is that
Involve tithing
Pretty universally there about give
Alex is really really close
To like
This is
Colts.
Like what he's doing
Is framing himself
Essentially as a defender of Chris
Right
He's in a dangerous territory in terms of like
Classifying himself as a
Journalist
When will use really operating as a
Occult okpoko of giving 10% of your income
You get weird pills in return
Dusa is
Noosa
Alex is going elrond
Alex is going for full text
Exemption
He has written
The book Galaxy
I think that's what he's going to try and accidentally
Like what do you think do you think elran had a plan he was a writer who is just
Scared all the time and running and eventually he stumbled upon the idea of like a what
This way because I don't want
Taxes on my ship books
I think he had more of a plan that Alex has
In that
Regard although of course Alex doesn't believe you
Taxes we know that
How do you get out of
Search religion
Alex Jones
Hard to make the
The transition I was a nympho Warrior now I'm a nympho worship
Warriors marching
Door
Just weird I don't really
Even know what's going on
That or had a
And and do Christians for that that is
George Soros
So
Wait
I don't understand
I don't really either
So didn't he just reveal that it's
Fine
Letting you giving preferential
Treatment to the atrocities
Christians committed as
Opposed as opposed
I would be
I like to be perfectly
I didn't care about that LMAO
I care more about his
Contextualizing
MS-13 is a
Christian Gehring
Oh no that's because
I don't want to I don't want to talk about them quite frankly at the same time there are more important elements
Operation then
Christianity
Necessarily
I'm sure there's more important
So the idea that he's
Repairing that
To like
Analog of
Isis I guess
Yeah is weird but it also belies
Reality
And that is that Isis
Isn't Street
Prickly motivated by
Islam or religious ideology
Okay there is
And not to save it
Or false
There are geopolitical realities and consequences of actions
That we've taken in the
Exploiting
Population
Killing civilians
Right and that is a piece of it and whether it's
By Islam
Also informed by Islam all of that can be true
But there's more to it
Gank leads me to believe that he
He has somewhere
That the religious
Aspect of various groups
Isn't necessarily all there is
And I also
Say that because
I don't think that
I don't think that MS-13
Bingos around
Christianity on that one but be that as it may
The idea that is
I mean not even
To go the weirdest thing ever
I would say there's no Isis
Without
The Iraq War
There's no Iraq without
Me to call Joe
And there's no cold war without
The CIA back to overthrow of the liberal Regina midnight
In Iran
Like I would Isis began whenever America was like
You guys are really doing great
How about a religious the app
Cuz they're going to pay us
Right
Realistically probably
Further back
Whenever the Muslim started the slave trade
It is just
Short-sighted to a certain extent
Is blame game
Yeah but that's the that's the way that you deal with foreign policy in order to
Foreign policy
In order to evade the fact that
It's such a car
Complicated
That there's no
Like nice
Through butter solution
There's so many actors involved in all of them have different motivations
Very difficult
Get all of them what they're looking
Anybody with rosin
Anything is go
Chaos
It's going to push everybody else
The amount of resources
We have in the world are enough to
Much larger population
We even have no help
The issue becomes
When you have
Population
Besides that we have with differ
Nations
Different places they oliverius
Distribution
News of the resource
You could have everyone living
Utopia 2
If everyone saw it as
Non zero-sum game
If the your loss didn't mean I win
You can have
Very compassionate
System in the world where
Let's say Bangladesh
There's a lot of people who live there and it's
It's impossible for them to survive
Because
The floodplain
The inability of them to that
Based on
The soil
To grow crops
To sustain the population
If we looked at that we're like
We should send them food
We should just do that we should
Azan world we have excess food around we should send them
Food
If we lived in that system
You could take care of places
Is like that but as soon as you can
Introduce anybody who treat
As a zero-sum game
The whole thing gets
Yep because then you end up with
People who are
In Bangladesh website
Oh there's a
The ton of food, then everyone could
Could survive or I could be a king
And that it becomes a zero-sum game where I have to
To steal your resources
In order to
Better myself
Right and that's where we get socks
No system
Can exist where
Can successfully exist
Where
People have a different version of what game is
That sucks
It's a
It's a stranger explanation
Think by
I think are psychopaths that are serial killers
Are the same thing as our
Not far off
Like I think that's kind of
I think that's kind of
Wrenched
It's been thrown in
Humanity is always
Eventually
Somebody gets enough
Become divorce
From their own
Action to everybody else
Sprint in which case may isolates
Themselves creating a
A self-reinforcing
Narrative
And then
There we go like every friend ever
System
Has eventually
Been over
Taken by back
Every single time
Like maybe yumanity
He just needs to die out and
Squirrels will become
Ultimate survivors
Great squirrel I'm rooting for
I'm actually
Rooting for orchids
I saw an albino
Scroll on time
Really cool
That's amazing
I imagine
Cool they're too cool
Explains for
More less
F***** up monologue
But I'm certain was cut out of the rebroadcast
Because I can now record these live
I got
This is
Bucked up
The Bubble Witch great error
Alaskan Malamute
Miles above
The fuc
We're miles above them on our journey to hell
Hell
Not what the f*** is he
Perfect but we're like riding them
Would you rather be the horse or the guy riding
That does not match up with his worldview anyway we opposed
World you that like
The globalist we're coming down fast on you as we all rocket to hell what the f*** is he saying
Wanted to do a cool monologue / Helter Skelter
I'll see you in hell but he's kind of like
AutoZone
I like the person not bad
If you saw that no Western pretty badass.
Different person I enjoy.
Another narrative
He's pitching
Bridges said that his gravelly voice
And I'll give you the broad Strokes
There is a measure of
In Philadelphia that would involve takedown
Bulletproof glass
And Bodega
Stores in
Interesting
I don't know anything about that and let me Morty let me tell you
That's the only information
Gibbs on the
Okay now it's listening
Give it take on it and then I will explain what the actual score today
Never been more like
I don't have an instant take I got no idea what
Bad life because yeah it's one of those
I know the convenience stores do get robbed
Yeah I know
Like it would be on
Making Rudy
Until he realizes that
Good lying but every
New York Chicago
Philadelphia
Delish donut
Draconian gun build
Plexiglass
It's your fault
Set timer at
Racist Democrat woman
Self
What do you think
I want to go on the same hypocrisy rent from earlier but my God
I'm complaining about other people bitching
I can't
It's pretty wild also what was he complaining about
Grabbing and I don't remember the Liberals want you to get
He's presenting it is but there are these
Do you know stores
In bad areas of town
I am. They argue no
They're taking the risk and
Commerce it's bad areas
And this pic. Bulletproof glass
The incentive eyes them having
These businesses in places where there would be no business otherwise
He's basically trying to
Complain I think about food desert
But at the same time
Bread and screaming about all sorts of other stuff
Naturally
Now as is his want
He's wrong about this
A.m.
Shockingly I'm going to read to you from ABC6
In Philadelphia
Governor Tom Wolf was in Philadelphia on Thursday to sign a bill that would enforce stricter penalties on so-called
Stop-and-go stores
That break the law
Lawmakers say that these alcohol established
To become a nuisance
Some of the stores advertised
Cheesesteaks actually just sell beer in shots of alcohol to go
We went to one such
Serving food at all
When we asked why we were told quote The Kooks
Not here yet
Lovett an undercover Action News investigation for the liquor store right now
An undercover Action News investigate
Most of the shops operate using a
Restaurant life
Spell little besides booze
We're not cooking today one shop owner said
When asked why he said
We don't feel like
Couple love love with
Councilwoman Cindy and goes in her District
Burton Public Schools sometimes right next
Clearly this is less than 500 ft
Freeman Elementary School
She said it once
Many of these stop-and-go bars also sell candy for kids right alongside
Intoxicated
Customer
You'll have children in line to buy candy at the
The same time you have adults in line to buy shots of alcohol
Street they're supposed to meet minimum requirement
Including food and access to bathroom
Quote they have no place to go to the bathroom
Drum so they're doing it all over the street
Pizza resident janebar
Lesson lesson that
Are we ain't use the bathroom
Since like 1995 said resin
Jeremiah Thomas
Most OP and goes we visited
Did had their chairs locked up
Glass enclosures
Drinking paper
You other option
Been wandering neighborhood streets while they drink
All right now I'm seeing the danger
Quote we had retired violation after violation after violation in many of these
Said representative Jordan Hare
He was a Powerhouse behind the legend
Inflation that was signed by what
Give the liquor control board more authority to shut down bad Act
Quote nobody should have to
Steve is in there neighbor
Advanced introduced a resolution
The Titan the city's requirements
To get a liquor
Call Neighborhood
Should not feel like they're being
Held hostage
Bad business
So the issue at hand with
The plexiglass
And the bullet proof glass
Is
That
These organizations
The stop-and-go shop
They're exploiting a loophole
In the liquor lights
We're in instead of selling package
Liquor
What they're doing is there for
Pretending to a restaurant
Adventures Tavor 7
It what they do is they have all their stuff behind bulletproof glass worth technically we have seating for 30
People just no one's allowed to sit down and do is create
A more sensible way to
To be like okay you don't have this life
Because that is danger
I disagree
In that it is
I disagree with this law and I think it's
Stupid I think I think what they're doing I'm on the fence about it but I want to be totally clear that the way Alex
Is presenting it is a lie
Because
I think it would be really fun
To go stop somewhere and get a shot
But it's like why do you got to hone something great guys
I have a bathroom
But here's the real issue
Here's the real here's the real issue
AR criminalizing
Once again
That's what that I disagree
You're not
Dealing with the reality of the reason that those places show up
Do you see those places in a white affluent f****** neighborhood
Corsage
It's like every time cancer metastasized
You just like
Flick a little a new little cancer
Bulshit they're not
Dealing with the actual underlying issue
Totally
Total might be a good way to be
Begin
Dealing with it
I agree with you
At the same time I get it
From the legislative perspective
Joan
Stitch onesie
Specially nearest school
You don't want open Boos
And a place where you can just stop in and buy shots
Associate
Agree that
Giving giving the liquor board the authority to not give that sort of license
To those places
Make sense
Then they should
Live up to be
You have a bathroom
You have a place people can sit down like a bar cuz
You're acting like a bar but you're conveniently having all the other stuff taken away from it
I agree if you want hun
In a vacuum
Sensible solution
Right in reality what you're doing is playing
Fair enough
This complaint was no I left Alex behind a million years ago
What is a f****** talk
No information but like if it was
Complaint then
The show be a lot more interesting
Because I think we can agree to some extent that like
All right there other issues
The play that are more important
But
That's why I still support the legislation
I actually might disagree with you there I don't I'm not sure about that yet cuz I don't know that
But I think this ultimately comes back to my argument
Giving a s*** about what conserve
Because in this
Right
If we
Alex and I started from the bases
Is of like
Okay this is a problem
We know what the real problem is
The question is
How do we solve
Is the US the conservative answer
As we solve this by
Changing this Paula
And rewriting this
But my answer is well we solve it by doing this
We can talk about
2 agreements
Right
If his response to this
Is
They're trying to make sure everybody gets murdered
Yeah there's no conversation to be had the
There needs to be disregarded and tossed aside
Another article that I read
Proposed legislation
Really feel bad that I don't ever named pulled up but
The issue that she brings up is like
I understand would think that this would have a negative impact on
Security but you have to
Understand that there are
And restaurant
In bad areas
Don't
Shoes with
Employees being assaulted
Airways
Courage
Better customer Behavior
Rarity cameras
50 then we get back
To your trying to legislate poor people
Whose Behavior
Without dealing with the problem which is
Courtright
You f*** them up and you polish them behind much bigger issue but in the meantime
It's not legislating poor people's behavior to legislate
Waze
Do not have
Have people get assaulted
Bike
Legislating
Against violence
Prime isn't necessarily
The reasonable argument that we should have about
Four people right
It is something that I do I do
Sink is
Is
Indicative of my issue with every like
Do Trump voters thinks differently about Trump right now
I don't care they mean nothing until they understand what the problem
Until then f****** go away
Right the bottom line where you can find agreement
Is that
Alex is wrong
Alex
Anime
Alex is so wrong I started talking about
A different problem
Right
We only got a couple more Clips here and Alex's time on the broadcast
Like I said
He has an interview with Lucy or whatever the f***
Is a writer for Gateway pundit who recently had a video that went viral on the internet
He was giving a speech
University of Yale maybe I don't know
Okay
I we don't want you here
Rather than Christmas speech was titled it's okay to be white
The lady came out
At the podium
She took his notes
Yeah
Or less
Couldn't understand
This was basketball
He's going for the ball
It's okay alright it's a flagrant-1 not a flagrant
Maybe not passing her fear
But he the way he treated
The way he treated her
Was not
I just want my stuff
It was absolutely an aggressive violent
Like in a way that I think everyone can
Agree
Even though
She did take his
I agree with that
That is true
You got me right in the video
His behavior is absolutely on
Especially considering that there was a security guard
Stop right there
Said she took my notes
Give me back my note
She acted like a child and he acted like a
Violent monster
So he has Alex has him on the show to talk about how the left is crazy
Here's Alex
Think I want to hear it
Dot-com
I feel this enforceable
Video game with audio for folks
You have been robbed under common law and local Island
Physically
This is Liberty this is libertarian ship
This is libertarian ship
I said earlier that there was
Security guard there who could have easily display escalated the situation and gotten him is no
Notes back yeah
Libertarian
I believe
That it's wrong
The police has a monopoly on Force
Yeah or whatever they don't believe that Authority needs to
She took my stuff under common-law I can attack her and Redwood have you it's just
Nonsense well just
What is work
Is like
Under the law you didn't punch her you didn't hit her
Write like it no you can
It's not just
Punch and hit
Like there's a hole
Like if you put her in a headlock
What does physically assault
Still set a reminder
Strictly speaking
You shouldn't have taken
That's not right either but in the grand scheme
The idea of taking
OneNote
Someone I think there's a hierarchy there
A bunch of bulshit about how Liberals are stupid
Substandard stuff
Then
Lucy whatever is f****** name is
Says something famous Lucia
Yeah Winthrop
Whitest name that's why it's okay to be white
Malfoy
Lucius Malfoy
So here is something that is
Borders on you couldn't be robber
If your name was Lucy In You
So listen to Lucy
You could not be further from
OnPoint
That's why
That's such a fun narrative you know what I mean
Everytime I come
Cast my real fear
Do you know what they're what we joked about that for like two episodes
I'm scared I'm scared that the more I listen to Alex the more I'm going to come to him
I want to see though that
What underpins
What are you talkin about
True it invent I do worry about people hearing these things
Being overwhelmed with the emotional appeal
Heels that are in
The idea of white fear the idea of all these things that Christian figure that Alex espouses
I do worry about people being swayed by those things
The content
That is why I am
I'm opposed to the it's not that like
I'm worried that you guys are so logical that I can't
Deconstruct whatever it is you're lying
It's
It's the lamest
Best f****** thing ever it is it's the way cernovich operate
It's all these dudes vapor
You know what it is it's Brandon
It's branding of logic
Branding of facts
You guys operate Automotion exactly right screw
Every time they talk about a
Google campaign
Insofar as
Oh there's going to be 40% who's on the left
Going to be 40% on the right and your job is to figure out the
The 10%
20 /
Yeah and the right has done something
Way smarter than what we have
And they realize that the middle
Doesn't mean any
What they're going for is the
Yeah so when we talk about
Not of people on the left responding to this s*** if you're on the left you f******
Get most of it at least
Read hope we're we are afraid of
Of people who aren't
Paying attention
Who show up and all the sudden
Hear your b******* and think all that makes sense
If you are a nympho Warrior it's not because you were on the left
And you got
Current now is because you were kind of not
Paying attention
And then you got
Caught up in this emotional bulshit from childhood trauma that
Ya heard by a lot of it
The middle is not a thing
If we uninformed
Yeah
I agree
So anyway
Seclusion
I know maybe a dozen people named Lucia
Jordan is really bad and we have one more
So we got a hard and so we are going to rush through the rapper Quest at the end of that
Alright
But I told you
Yes and I don't have to pee so bad that
Live invest cuz this Cliffhanger is
Such a professional broadcast
Earlier
Alex's Superbad
The the college column
From
Saint wherever
Alex has dispatch
Owen Shroyer
What go to that camp
Probably
Owen Shroyer
Intention that they had
Was Alex
Was going to go to him live
Owen Shroyer
Is the Cox Slayer he's the guy who goes out
He got the job at Infowars because of videos
They posted on YouTube where he would go in
With people College liberals
Manipulative
What about what about what about
That's how he got his job
But it seems more and more every time he goes out
He ends up getting
Flipped off by a little kid
FIFA November 4th thing that was just
The huge boss
You can't hold his own the way that Alex needs him
I'm too he's not good on the war room either
Alex's losing faith in
And you can see it in this clip
Because
Owen Shroyer they go to the video
And they can't play the audio
But at the same time Alex presented as like
He's under attack
That kind of thing
It's not
He's just having a bad argument with a couple people
Listen to
This s***
Busting in on our right now
Earlier
Incredible
Give me the video
It's just
I don't f****** know
Any of the videos we have to do I don't know anything
Yeah right
Ashley
I forgot to take a shower
Okay let's go
Lenny just throws it to a videos
Are they playing couples videos at like distance
Half an hour before he was supposed to get off air
Two-and-a-half hours a day show Rapaport doing the 4th hour
Spending most of his time talking about how he knows the rush it is
Here's what I want to say about that
His argument
Hilarious Alex Jones
Something
I think I think by argument that he's lost faith in Owen Shroyer
Is much more on point then he needs to share I think it's more like
Somebody's got to take this I got to help him out I got to help him out
Embarrassing video this going to be a disaster I've got to go gal myself
What I got to do everything around here
But Rappaport comes in
He knows that the the rush it
Cuz
Is Russia
Flipped Donald Trump
The greatest
Secret ever
And no one would talk
Covid-19 is a Christopher
Steel
Who's a long time
Would have contacts
That would be like oh yeah also
That's no one would ever talk about that
So are so it's all a lie
I don't believe it
At the same time
If you're playing that game
And using that logic
Was born in Kenya
Well that's one
But then also let's use that logic and apply it to
You know
We fund Isis
If that were true that would be the greatest secret ever
No one would talk about that are go all of Alex's mysterious secret sources
Couldn't possibly be saying that cuz they wouldn't do that
Are we turned over
Or we supported the coup of
So I mean like
That's an argument you can use for
Any everything
Yeah a rapport does his
Right
Legatron
If you really had to pee based on how professional are broadcasting
Scales are there's no way
Lightwell
Psyops
To get people to think that we don't have enough
Hard I swear I was just trying to come up with my own cliffhanger
Stuck around and tried to watch the more and see if Alex
Shows up in Ocho Rios video but I was so bored of a300
Tomorrow maybe they'll have some videos of Alex
That be fun
I mean we learned a lot here tomorrow what will happen
Today
I don't know
I don't know if you would like your brains with a spoon while you were still have your visual Court
UT email knowledge right at gmail.
Sure you would want to go to our website knowledge.com
Ocean
Sweet Talent Booker burrito
Just just
Reminder to do a special episode tomorrow
Very excited
So also
Rockwear
Currently we have an amazing
Talent Booker
If you wanted to go to iTunes
You'll be able to download our podcast
You can leave a review
You can do if you wanted to get the
The f*** out of this podcast
That's real quick what would you say about Russia
More less
Alexandra Thurston color