Alex
Everybody welcome back to knowledge
About Alex Jones
Got some things that need to be showered about
I got a couple issues.
This is officially by scale
I think it goes far beyond that but I know a lot about Alex Jones
I don't know
That's the theme of the show Mountain Dew kickstart
In order
The midnight
Mystery flavor for the show
Don't need to rehash something
Fervent
Existentialism
Flavors it whether or not they are real
Write whether or not depict reality or
Actually I've already interrupted drink
Anyway
If you're nasty
The it's a little interesting weird stuff happens and I'm f****** tired of giving that introduction
Quite frankly
During the 2nd and will complain about this
Complaining in order to start us off
I should not have phrased it that way that's an actual crime is messy I say playing
Vets
From today's episode
Hang out with Austin liberals
What a shock
It's not friends
I'm guessing it
I'm guessing that's what it is
People who say they're libertarian
Is actually a conservative
Cult around a big big old races
We believe in love
Government oversight in this guy over here thinks
Chimeras are real
Beeman's
You're a liberal I like your stance
Yeah
A real thrill
Tell your brother
We appreciate it very much thank you so much
If you'd like to become a
Disappointed
When people aren't Global it's like I don't know
Ungracious because Mike W f*** yeah thank you so much
Now
Raise it up one more set so we get to play only one more sense I'm not sure that
Get around the system
Globalist position because it's Meredith
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Thank you so much
Ronaldo born
I think it's because
It suggests that somebody sent him a bag of poop every time
Beautiful
Do you like sports to show please do go to knowledge buy.com quicksupport the show helps a lot
So today Monday
Heavy on my heart continues further on
But Alex Jones would have you know that actually that is just Trump on doing a
Institutional
GameStop
I know
I get it I get it
So what else you got
Not s*** like everything is bad like going to win Weebly
The people who are pushing this f****** tax bill on Hazard then turning around like f****** Orrin Hatch
If somebody could shove something so far up Orrin hatch's ass
It comes straight out through his mouth
I'm going to get lit on fire afterwards just like dragons flaming swords
Straight up through its own breaker
Right
And the Democrats are f****** worthless I'm done I'm done they are f****** worth it
Freedom speeder got f****** Liberals are p****
Let's Liberals are pussies LK
Anything
Quit what is this is Peyton Manning
The strong f****** survive
I'm going to Blink three times that I'm being held hostage
Alright Jordan
Check out his blog on we have about a month left and if we don't all setup and get our
Goddamn
Negative
It won't fall apart within a
We have negative time until what we what we need to have done
She's done maybe the problem with the French Revolution that we
You can really
Correct
Right is the only chopped off
Right
Is chop them up into little sections starting
At the bottom I just see how long they survive through
Bisected little pieces
Demons and human beings are garbage that all lives within all of us
You mentioned her and I want to talk about this the tiny bed Trevor wanted doesn't know Peter today
I was fired by MSI
DC as a contributor because
Mike cernovich
Because Mike cernovich and his elk dug up a tweet that he had four
From 2009 wearing he says
That he hopes
His daughter is raped by Roman Polanski
Because he wants his daughter to be raped by someone
Play the good sense of mise-en-scene
And that is
Funny
I mean it's funny and it's indicative of outrage at people
Excusing the behavior
It's called a joke
A very obvious
Literal
And
I like the outpouring of support that I've seen on Twitter and took from people like Mark and people who have a voice in it
Independent platform
But the very idea that MSNBC
Would go along with this
Is a very very bad sign
Mike cernovich
I don't know if it was individually him but I know he was involved
If if Mike cernovich
Does anything
Every single media Outlets
It should be like okay well let's disregard this entire Life Uniform response should be an eye-rolling
And it's f****** guy
Contributor
Got an MSNBC guy fired
Someone who would crnkovich would be very scared to
Cuz I mean whatever you want liberal or whatever I don't know I don't know what anyone's complaint would be
AMC Theatres a f******
He can hold his own
Debates
Policy and on all sorts of
To the very idea that Mike cernovich would be
You cowardly to discuss this with him
Take this sort of a route is kind of exactly against the things they purr
Pretend they're under attack
About all the f****** time
Robert it's an effective tool for them
Exact the other thing the reason that I'm I'm bringing it up is because we
To be very very
Scared about what this
Portent
That is probably had examples of this
Coming down now
Yeah
Anything
On the other side
These alt-right
And what have you
Got a pretty good system together for suppressing people
Yep
And
You need to be careful about that getting away with murder
Who's getting away with murder Charlottesville
Alright
They're all f******
Guilty
Done the other thing I wanted to bring up with a little a little article I ran into the
This morning in my
Wings Over of the news
This is an article out of a tablet
Dot-com
Tablet magazine
Absolutely true
Are any of the headline for Alex in case you don't want to hear anything from the article
In Russia
Old antisymmetric blood libel game
Political tracts
To Putin claims are Nicholas the second
May have been killed in a ritual slaying
A century-old Cunard blaming the Jews for Reggie
I've heard of that one right
And the reason that this is very important
We should be very worried about is
Because
Is more indicative of why
Alex
The Russian
Barbarian line
I'm very in line
Right
And when you look at the things that Alex talks about about how the Russians are waking up
And why he's like they're on the right side
Dimensions
They talked about how there's poison in the vaccines
Is well poison
Type narrative
It's it's really really scary
Because
This isn't
Some
Crazy
Clearance guy or something
He's a very high-ranking Bishop in the Russian Orthodox
Church write his name is
Tequan
Anti
So what he did is he
He brought this up
He brought up this idea that the Jews ritualistically killed Czar Nicholas
In a ritualistic ceremony that was in order.
Asurion b*******
Which is it a lot of people have
You know spread
Your sense then
It is it is a popular idea among crazy
Anything that's really scary
This
Next line
Following Shoku knobs comments
The powerful investigative can
Russia's investigative equivalent of the FBI
Quickly announced that it would take part in such a
Investigation
Of alleged ritual killings
So
Hey welcome to 27
When we when we talk about these things these ideas that Alex Jones
Present
These narratives
The city hasn't what's behind them what we need to realize the reason that were talking about
At least
And on top of that
A really easy to cut through and
But that doesn't mean that there aren't
People in the world who believe the
The same things as him
Starbucks
Board dangerous
Yeah because
Who is the
Bright
It'll be awful
This is a 101 types
Situation in
What's motivating
A lot of them
And a lot of trump supporters who don't even realize
Things are what's motivating
They've been duped entirely
Welsummer
Like
Ultimately if you voted for Trump it's because of Ray
That's what it is
It's because of race in the complete and utter failure of neoliberal
That probably
I made some
There are certain other little
Pieces that are
Letter Factory I don't want to argue on it
December 4th
Okay but first
Starts with Alex
Complaining the whole bunch
About
That guy who reported that he had a source
I was telling him
Oh that's right
Touch with Russia
Suspended from ABC for
Slightly wrong
About this one piece
YouTube information
Where is if he worked at
Infowars
Media Outlet right
Not suspended
Probably would have gotten a f***
Let's remember the times that Alex has gotten things wrong today in terms of the
He got sued for slander
And I have to make a public apology and that immediately started wrong
When he walks
Very much wrong
Complaining about that a bit
But you get sidetracked by
Someone else in pop culture
And it takes him off
I wish my dad a live forever
It's just crazy
Your Joy Behar celebrating
Oh my God
Arrest the president
Still going on
Google really running this song from
Commercial first of all fantastic
You know like it sits right
Second this is Monday's episode of his show on Friday then people made retraction
You know like
I don't know if the view did I don't really care
First of all
Second of all she was saying Brian Ross is reporting that that is true
No it would be great I don't know cuz I don't watch the f****** view if they on Monday is episodes
We got it wrong we got that information
Confirm ABC no don't
Well please don't
Or whatever but if you Google
Brian Ross whatever
Maybe take out a wrong wrong every single outlet
We reported that he reported that but also
I don't
I think the people I don't know
The View should
I don't care
Hear how happy
Referral
They were so happy a couple of people to death
Elisabeth Hasselbeck
You still there
My friend from Survivor
But
Conservative voices motorcycle
Pahrump
F****** good
I could live in that moment
What
Sagro you know how everybody was clapping
45 f******
I don't want to hear a groan that last that long
Varsho
Burrito in the chat my favorite Survivor was was great
I love chicken
LeBron
Libertad
Liberal
Chicken Joe
I don't think
Not Progressive
Doing there now
Australia
Anyway let's move along this next clip Alex
Complaining that no one will retract
The story
The one that was retracted almost immediately
Alex has been trying to troll everybody with the
He's going to piss people off and I were to the
More like
Yeah the know
Your races
Regardless of the song
Cares what song you're playing
Like that
Jocelyn
That upset a lot of Democrats
Christian
The Germanic tradition
They want that type of stuff
Obviously
Christmas cards at Public School
Separation of church and state
Whatever you want
But they're failing
People like Joy behar's last week
Huffington Post
10:00 weather publication
Will not retract
Their reports
Celebrating
Before the president was elected
Which could be some type of
The only reason I left
Come out eventually they work
I don't know I like the idea that it's all just that they're mad about Christmas than like
All this stuff is trying to play that sorta cartoon
I've never I've never heard anti-christmas
Fervor
From anybody like atheists
I can't figure
Like mostly anti-christian
Messed up from Chris
Like it's two commercial that's the most like aggressive criticism I've ever seen of
Never heard one of my
Friendly liberal
Friends be like
We are you know what f*** Christmas
Cuz we should celebrate Kwanzaa
Everything like that
You know what
F*** Christmas
We should celebrate
Mithras day
Sure actual holiday about Jesus's bulshit
The only argument that anybody makes is like
Other people have other holidays
Be cool baby don't be a dick about Chris
What's what drives me insane
Is this
This is such one of those moments
Where you see the
Disparity
The liberal the progressive band
Cannot
Make a meme
Bright the conservative bent
Can make
Because I'm Cedar made a not even mistake
Years ago
Yeah he's pretended that he may be involved
And it's it's the trick that
We fall into
We
Holding ourselves to
Standard
We have to
Deal with real
Yeah that's a problem are holding themselves to the standard of
Realities bulshit we don't even need to worry about
That's what I'm saying
Function not a bug or whatever it's it's
If it didn't
Hurt
Destroyed
Public discourse in public
You know credibility and Trust
That is an amazing
Trick
Maybe let's do that
I don't know how
Light
What if we just lie.
Okay
We're doing this
If we all adopt socialism
Then everybody will get help
What could be better than bringing Knox back2life socialism is known to bring dogs back
Globalist have medpeds and you want them to be released throughout the world will do it for you
Absolutely socialism
Another guy's name
Kramer Kramer
GoPro Raptors in there two Presidents Day Sale of Lies
What's going on right now December
Call message
Percent extra discs
Spectrum up with why you need to buy beds ever but never know
Indeed
Oh no I told you I lying
I'm so going to get off this topic
The Mathers
Merry Christmas
The producer
Yeah more
Information builders
Heart's still sharing
Still sharing all the celebration clip
And then
I'd like to take just a quick second to imagine what level of nonsense Alex
Audience
The sharing
Not true
We don't have time but just imagine
Justify
I like I like the
Who cares about it like you're getting even in your anger
Who cares if low-information voters
Hear that the president might be cuz he wants the low-information people
Is my game information
No
What information is like a relief it's not like well I guess I'll vote against him
Information voters by being like
Yeah you know that crime we all know the president committed
When they cuss at you on the street that's fake
Rocket
The one-time deliver wasn't opposed to
But also here
It's not like he was just walking around because I can throw some hot coffee on you
If you see a rich person and I shoot
Throw coffee
I threw coffee on him after he
At least
Alex
We're going to screw the country over
America
We don't want the facts
What is it again
Enjoy
View
TJ coronavirus Pakistan
You don't know nothing
Doesn't understand
He's listening to it like a robot trying to be like
Okay what does that sound like
Do you come back
Celebrating is true
Wild eyes
Play Celebrate hoaxes
Manipulated
You
But here's the really upset about again the president Melania
With one of their Christmas messages on Friday
Christmas
Words
And overthrow traditionalism
What you got
So what this is all really about
Is that
Trump Melania
Which by the way he definitely make sure that
It's not Melania Trump
Donald Trump
And then he's already said that he has information
Understand
Is all about Christmas
That's what that's what everyone cheering
For the eventual impeach
Felony conviction and all the hung by the neck until dead drum
Merry Christmas carols in the globalist they're scared of the power that say Merry Christmas
He's bringing this
Tradition back
And that
When I was a young man
That's no
I read some books
I didn't think it could be more pathetic
Then Fox News
Just handling of the idea
Oh yeah I really thought that like
That was
Some shameful desperate
Grab Lakeside
The Christian complained that I'd always heard about
Christmas was that you know it's over-commercialized
Getting rid of the reason for the season
That obviously scamming your audience's just commercial eBay
Seems like it'll all of the war on Christmas ideas
It's not it's not like it's
It's Campbell
It's literally the worst
Diversion
Getting outside of the reason for the season
Until I mean the Alex is probably
Behaving and what I would describe as the least Christian way to me is that that segment producer
Who came up with that idea
Is not a Billy
Fox News
Resonated so much like you should have gotten
Least 150
That's right
Let me think about how that we think of that episode on The Wire D'Angelo chicken nugget
That sort of thing
Too bad anyway
This is about where we leave the Joy Behar
It was just a couple
No he makes hang out of it there's no doubt about that
And then
Towards the end of the first out there's a bunch of rambling blah blah blah blah blah
Yeah it does something
That I got
Pretty excited about
I should also tell you I'm pretty sure he's drunk
Appreciate
Alright because at one point after the news came down getting ready
Will drunk that's going to last him
A little bit later in the episode I did hear that
Together like a highball or something like that happened to again
Happen exactly when
They have the other image up on screen
Do you like let's go to the caller image video on him
And it sounds like
You slurping slurping a drink
But it's not big
People's behavior gets pretty weird his behavior is weird
Before we get to that let's say
I had high hopes
1 hours
Yes
And we'll see what your response
Here's the toll-free number 789
7778 925
First-time caller
Disagree you're welcome want to hear from you 877
And please I don't want me choke collars okay they call it act like they're a liberal
If you were going to get you Russian agent
First of all there's no one there now
There's no one's answering the hotline
It's 7:30 they don't do the Nightly News live
I'm sure they don't have a name
At least it's in there
Owen Shroyer ghost
Millie Weaver goes
Will
Not talk to us they will not discuss anything with us
Well here's your chance
To prove me wrong
So first of all the premise there at the end everywhere I go no one will talk to me I wonder why that is I haven't
Alternative explanation other than they have no intellectual argument
I would posit that
Okay should I be Alex or you
Okay
Go fuc yourself
That's probably a man on the street
Rich people in Seattle
Ice cream cupcake at that lady when he's drunk on the streets
Time to get in
With your first episode
Fred Meyer
I want such a huge fan it's not that it's it's a real
Real kind of everyday
I still don't really believe
Corporeal
He's like a robot or something
B someone lives
Isn't this much of a
People headspace
Is it terrifying
I was walking around earlier today
Absorbed all the news
And what have you
Beginning of the show other stuff like with this
Travel ban
Is possibly okay
Neil Gorsuch
I want
We need more
Like what
Spells at 4
For the future
I almost broke down
Tears just walking down the street
Fairly uncommon for me
Since cock song came on my
My random playlist in that
Hit a nerve strike that from the record
I was like
You got me emotionally because I was very I was very
Struck by the same thing
Do I have to
Tamp down my emotions like
The good Irishman that I was
Look look the point
The point I was trying to get at is
Like
I know what effect
This is having on me
Like dwelling in the world of Alex Jones and listening to your regularly
There are so many people listen
Regularly
And I can't imagine how it's not affected
Them
I was trying to get myself into
Like
I don't know if I'm articulating as well but
Was like what
Must it be like
I think this is right
Or think this is real
Think that anything that he's saying is true and not just trying to
Do you s***
Absorbing that hatred absorbing that
Just repackaged
Dometic canards right like what
What kind of pool does that take on you
If it's taking this kind of a toll on me
And I'm
Keenly aware of what I'm listening to deconstructing it in fighting back against
It's horrifying
I think
You are going about it the exact
Opposite
Did I say a dollar man
Erection of a convex bone
Text opposite direction
Because if you are
Stupid and angry
What you have to be to list
Listen to him in this
I think that I can't I think that you're wrong
Disagree I just put for the exact opposite idea what you just said and I hold the reason I think you're wrong
Become stupid
You're stupid
To begin with but I think that people get like I know that's for me when I
Listen to Alex Jones a little bit or
Ourfriendbarney DeRosa listen to Alex
Some listeners who I've talked to who used to listen to him
Who are idiots
One of the reasons
Bet you do
Cuz there's a lot of the conspiracy stuff is
There's some stuff that's pretty interesting in the idea of rapid and knowledge
In the idea of like
An alternative explanation
So many things that
Do you mind explainable the insinuation of someone who knows true
Is very alert
When you start to itch
Explore the little bit
And I think by degrees you could end up
Becoming dumb
Angrier because
Does narrative hook you and you don't realize
Okay let me let me go back
I use
Stupid in the wrong
I meant is naive
The classical set
Because there is no
Because like with our friends who have listened before
View is not something that you can gain
Know that you only move away from
So anybody who is listen
To Alex Jones in believing in that
Is naive
And they have not
Growing away from me
Just like our I don't begrudge
It's not that you're stupid
You listen to Alex
You're stupid if you continue to believe
Piece of his marketing operation
Work in tandem in their inexplicable
But I
Products for knowledge fight line
Okay
It's like it's like the cow goes moo that's the name of it
Shred core band
But like those things
One of the features of how it has to work
Is you have to
Instill in your audience
A sense of
Acquired and reinforcement evatac
Like you need that to sustain
Cuz if you lose that naivete
You start to read article to say like oh
Oh this is stupid
This is where you start to ask questions of like
My old Christian Ska band was called the detonators
Anyway
I had to undercut my own point of time.
Let's move on to the next clip where Alex again
I was young
Anyway
That did not
So in the next life by we get to hear more about how Alex
Real quick
Just my point being
In regards to that
Is something that you
And you can force
Yes
Something that can
You can't go towards
You can only go away
Do you know what I mean I believe so yes
Like I use stupid as a
The catch-all in it it is Kai
Kind of a
Only don't mean in that
It is dumb
It's at their naive and it is dumb
Ikea
What we can sum it up with his only the naive
Can stay
Exactly the rest will be
Exactly
But
It was that call we get more about to Alex is going to
To take calls
I've given the phone number out
For people that disagree under Russian control
That I'm getting orders from a Raichu
Please
I mean you lyrics
You're welcome to call in and ask if
I'm a violin player from
Who I am
Multinational Force
I want to challenge you
Are you proud of
Nothing
From the truth
All they're doing is putting together an obstruction
Justice case
The Democrat
Buehler's
Like
I would like to do my impression of Alex Jones
Nylon 100 years
So 1930
Al Capone
Look you forgot to fill out a tax form
That's everybody
Instructions to fill out a form
A ham sandwich these days
Now you can say that Jefferson Davis is an agent of the
But that's just like calling me a my next invasion of China
Violin player from let's make
Ridiculous strawman
Is that some Star Wars
Yeah that's what what's that nice noodles
I can't remember it's the Cantina Band
So in this
Name was the
Like the
Now there's no sense
They were playing the band
I'm pretty sure
It was like
Nice noodle
That I might speak
Within time I'm seeing from the chatroom figuring Dan and the modal node
Is that correct
I don't care anymore I don't give a fuk about Star Wars I'm here I'm here from the mooch
Jeezy
Screw you
So
Alex's built-up
The fact that he's going to take calls
Noodles Palace
So I wasn't
Totally off
I have these nerd memories from when I was younger in
Plot of Star Wars a long time ago I was in the trenches
Is going
See people can prove
Videos related to Trump and I
I want to be clear I had way too much work to do today
And I was not listening lies I had to double back
Intelligence
You didn't alert the FBI afterwards
Right at is enough to be very seriously concerned about your
Now let's talk about blood libel
Now let's talk about how much your position on Putin is change
Over the years
Now let's talk about these
Weird conversations you had with Rodger Stone and Steve pieczenik
Indeed
December of 2015
It was a weird turn the last time we went on a double date near like
Now let's talk about bloodline
It's not far off
Is it strange that I was hanging out with some comedian friend
Send the business Lisa Traeger was in town over the weekend
I went to go see her perform with Our Friend Martin
Explain exactly inozen
Other
Whenever we get together we just want to talk about
Various deep cuts from Britney Spears first album and what about you
End up coming into my social life
Important there's a new Holocaust, alright you understand
What am I supposed to say I do the same thing
I feel bad for whatever influence
You may have on our collars
Bark collars
I got caller in the head because the rest of the show is going to deal with a lot of calls
Alex Box 435
About
With commercials cutout 35
Okay about weather
Your vamping
You don't want to take these calls
You you're worried that someone will say something smart
And so he have to be like
It wasn't in the articles 501c is where you're wrong
Common law
You're not an admiral
Struggled
They're just
Some trash
Alright
Kevin Terrence Aaron Chad John
Does any of these people disagree
Maybe Kevin does Kevin
Not a huge fan of his first caller he goes to is going to be critical
I think it was first color
Plug one of his products
Kevin and Chad
Yeah Alex I've listened to you longer than the NSA has
Give you a chance
Do you think he's critical or do you think he's a fan
How many go with he's a fat
And watch your show and I have to say you're probably
Leeward
Double speaking liar there is
So it's got me lyrics
Alright
Let's see what he says
And I can prove it
The first thing is when it comes to Russia
There's one thing that you could do to prove it but you won't
Release
Your Finance
So first of all
That's a bad that's a bad attack
Releases finances for other
Probably not funneling him
All these other things and I think the world would be
Much better off for
Knowing
Feels
But there's other reasons
To his listeners and To The World At Large
Where the money's coming from
Coming probably
More like Mercer
Or I one of these other billionaire assholes or the coke
The top five people on my
Yeah it's at least a little
At least the dark and I appreciate it
Improved your audience
Where are your money actually comes
Okay the second as far as doublespeak goes
I mean
You already said on Joe Rogan's podcast
That you were pressured by your advertisers
July about Y2K
You said that Russia
Launch intercontinental ballistic missiles
Against the United States
Another reason why you're probably tied to Russia
If she don't call
Vladimir Putin
A literal demon
Just like you call Hillary now
You called
Back then a literal demon
21st
First of all taken f****** notes Alex you have huge stacks of paper in front of you you should
One thing just to be fair
Alex
Against this caller
Literally demon
He's at he's resembling a demon
He says but he is going crazy and he looks like a beaver
Who gives a f*** about that we don't need to be honest we don't need to recognize the truth
You know what he said
He didn't just say it was a literal demon
He said Putin gave him a handjob in high school
No I go back to the early I go back to the Chris gethard early motto lose well that's what I
Play insist on doing we will stay true to reality and inevitably
Get murdered by hordes of Ding Dongs
I don't like that
So Alex is needed to take a break
Because he's got a you got to write this down or that I can't remember all that all those complaints
In fairness to this color again
Since you he did make
The finances
Yep
I wouldn't lying about altogether
2K is absolutely true
I need does say that on Roku
And it's clear that because
Boot & Saddle
In order to sell
You got it that is why he did that
I think what I can't wait we got to do that 911
Episode one of these days
Cuz I didn't want to do it but then I started to think more about that Anderson and how many 9/11 that were
We're currently living through my remember from watch
The 9/11 episode there's a lot of gold sale
Forasmuch as Alex screams
I called the
And all that stuff gloating about
A lot of it
That might be another connection
Between him and their immediate reaction to 9/11
So I think I think that he is
He's complained about his finances could have been better presented but
Good call
Goodwin
The Putin is a demon good but also slightly inaccurate
Bright
Let's see how Alex was
I told the story about not knowing how real-life UK would be
Sponsors that listeners
So
That mean
You lied
Convince
Sponsors convinced
Listeners convince
You're convinced
If listener is convinced you
You need to reassess how you get information
Secondarily if sponsors
Convinced you
Venue
Are lying in order to appease a sponsor
I don't understand his admitted that his critique is actually correct
Alright
Ballistic missiles
I'm signing for the listeners
Almost
Sriracha
How do UK workers lost up Canada orders lot of stuff
My stores lot stuff
Warehouse
A plug
We're going to be able to get your product
He's pretty smooth that is smooth as s***
Is it garbage can go f*** him
Alpha god dammit
What is that wasn't great
That's not an answer Russia Gave Me 0
I don't think it's a reasonable thing to do you know what happened kislyak gave him $50
Absurdly low amount
Certainly did by boosting your
It counts and all of that
You sold more advertisements
People so technically they did give me an indirect way another thing that's really interesting and
I'll put together some click
Clips
About this in the future but
The number of times people have called in and asked
About the Koch brothers
You did not answer
He just says
You just answer answers
So
They're not really all that political they only give me a million
I need more
I mean
Literally
Say something on the biggest podcast in the world
Smoking pot
We caught on a podcast that 45 million viewers
You know I get the Superbowl if I was in the Super Bowl
Football
Where is the evidence that I'm involved with Russia
Well there is you admitting that you spoke to Russian in
His his slimy moving to a sales pitch
Great his dissembling on like
Also it's more fun to bring up the idea that
You also said there were concentration
Camp set up a notch
What are those for
Do you literally
Believe that I have some connection to Russia
So Alex I'm going to take you up on your deal I will release by finances and you will have to do the same
You just said it to your whole body at least mine hey hey what's up bro you have nothing
There you go I said Russia fired a missile
Capitol Fax
So he has that
Yeah he thinks he want that one
C1 that exchange break music plays
Talked over him when he's trying to make another point but
Be better than me that's fine you know
Deflection
So not answering no questions
Critiques that the guy brought up
Find
She gets back from
Commercial
Goodbye Chris commercial break
Gets a little.
Not have been
The best for
He doesn't like
Not necessarily
We just took a call
From somebody that was going to give me evidence of Mike Russian connection
It's ridiculous
The Cold War is Over
Theologically Russia is more like the US used to be
We Face the same level as foes
Multi-country
That's the only connection
All the hype about Vladimir Putin because I've investigated myself
Media
Lying about me
This is my country
The Communist Chinese
They're starting to control Hollywood
Before I go back to your calls just briefly here
That
Understand what's going on
Child support broadcast.com it's a big deal
It's a big deal
Hey you know how much he hates those globalist multinational corporations who
Trump did just give 2 trillion dollars
Yes that is true
Because
That's why
Critical nonsense
A game that doesn't work
Did I want to bring out of there is that Alex
He does identify with and connect with with the Russians is what he believes to be fighting again
Globalism and the globalist
Right as we know from a years-long investigation the globalist
Aren't real
No globalist
Are Alex Jones at
Cover
For archaic anti-semitic Canard
Inform his worldview
And that's why it's really important
Just got the beginning of
The show this Russian Bishop
Is bringing back up blood libel
It's because of that is this when Alex says
You just said literally there
That's the connection we had
It's not that
Important
To make clear
Is that
It is not necessarily anti-semite
The way that
It out it's not
It's not specifically targeted
What he's done is repurpose
Anti-seize
Bulshit from
Hundred years ago
And applied it to
Everyone who's not him he's with us agrees with him is a blood libel
Against
You know
Social oppression
Amore fair and equal Society
Is
Guilty of bloodline
Unless we forget the protocols of the Elders of Zion written by
All super-connected
These philosophical
Ideas it's that act like I keep
Describing it as a brain virus
Because it is
It gets in
Contact
It gives a false
Contacts
Everything that you look
Like what you were saying there to the idea that he's just he just replies it for political gain is one
Piece of it but the brain viruses
It's not just working but not
It also is hatred
It absolutely is
No
It's probably not hatred to like I hate all Jews
He doesn't
You know it was interesting as a like this is a great
Paper
15 years
You yet
But
If you consider that anti-semitism
And the way that it has
Spread throughout Europe in all of those
That is really the fear of
Foreign
People stealing
Essentially
It's like blood libel ideas and all that s*** was
Lake generally rooted in you sir Adrian idea that Christians can't give out money
What is this
What all of this
The same thing
If you just take out
Jew-fro
Right
Observation
Blood libel and bigotry
Through the use of the internet in the way that
Connected
One thing the people did not expect from the internet
Because everybody was like
They didn't expect
Bigotry to follow along
And it's the same bigotry of a small Russian village 100
2 years ago
You know ten Jews come in
Make money
It's the same fear on a global scale because now we're all connected
Do each other the racism is just bigger
We're all juice but I'm saying it always looks like
It's going away and then
Butter
And the only way to stop a virus
Of course to develop
Or kill all of the
Conservatives
Politically
I don't think Alex is going to be thrilled at the idea of a vaccine
Politico
He's not into the vaccine idea
What's all this
Okay
Look at a clean vaccine
I want to go to the next call
I want to go to the next call but I
Not even a beetle
I can't go to the next call
Because there is not next call for a bit cuz Alex
A bunch of calls and if you disagree with me now
He just Rambles about how I
Not real
Not accurate MN
Which
Vicki's revealing a little bit about being a bad
At the beginning
One of my daughters temperature this morning
Because you had never come out and the tooth is coming in
Chukar Road
I never met the dentist they've been there for five times last few years
I would argue that that's a sign
You're being a little
If they've been going to the same dentist for a few years
He said 45 times
In the past few years going to
In the past few years
Daddy's Gone
I don't think he's ever met
That I went to
Alright
I'll give this one
My dentist
Let Me Gucci
I have met
Especially when I was under like 30
My parents didn't let me date a dent
Until I ran away date
That's very Christian of them
But I never met them
Dennis come out to Miami Sylvester
Anesthesiologist
Regulations and laws on laughing gas they have an anesthesiologist there to do
Washington
And it was just
Humbling
It professionals all over our list
Or they're being
Other talk show hosts
We're winning
There's nothing
We run into people that are big fans of the show
So there is a lot of Hope
As long as the economy is growing
Optimism
Investigation
We know it's not going anywhere
I think it more more more
#hot Republicans
#hashtag Hilltop
Go out and beat people up
Just because you put it we disagree with them
That's a big question
Hashtag
Kill the cops
#black lives matter
Compared
Lisa Vespa
Piece of this
Is that if I found out my
My dentist listen
Infowars
Run
But he doesn't run
Infowars
Alex's dad isn't even a name for warrior
No money
Nada
You didn't work
Impatient to his
CIA
He did that he did all of the CIA
What time I die. Guy was in the service when he came into work on these weird stuff
Gas
The story I'm sure
Be that as it may
Do they
Really they have to
Really have started
To buy their own bowls
In the Russia
Alex
No ever
All of the
2A
Either that or it's another story
That's probably what it is
The only reason
Like what
Spell attached
They kind of get it
Like they got what they want
The Richard going to abandon
Like that's going to happen I don't I think there's a lot more work left to do beyond the text
The episode
Will be the unstable the instability actually works in service
There's a lot of places a lot more to strip mine from this country before detector Richie
Naughty radiator
Quite a bit down the road we get to a second
Truecaller
Critical or uncritical
Miles
Interesting Theory let's find out
Aaron's in Washington
Go ahead
How you doing
Hey me and my girlfriend Sabrina been listeners for a long time I've been less than a lot longer now this is just
But I like to say to you I acted like using human-to-human you know about communication contact
Now
Do you think that this is a critical call
Nautica
You taught me
That's what I got to say
You are a lot more passionate by where you're speaking about
When you were trying to save the world besides the political mess
Defending Trump now are you seeing something in your tarot cards that says you need to put all your chips
Down on Trump
Or work down the Dead
And the fact that keeping Trump right now
Is leaving this race war and a possible Civil War would you give up Trump
Keep it civil war from happening
Great question
So we'll see how we'll see how Alex answers
Rambly
Not well so the question at its core
Is I mean the subtext of it is
I mean what are the underlying assumptions
Is
There will be a civil war if Trump
Continues to do what he's doing a little bit of a weird pretext
Stop supporting Trump if you knew
Continuing to support him would be to the death
Of blood say millions of Americans
His
Difference
Towards that will be
I know it's not
Beyond that your prediction
Whilst and Isaac
And we'll see
But
Beyond that there's an important piece of Terrence
Please bring up
At the beginning
Be much more passionate
Used to have like a fire in
There's a
Keeping beating the same f******
In Drumright
Boring
It's more complex than that
He said he really is challenging
He's destroying their takeover plan of the US and the world
And
They're trying to destroy him
And in the process
Loyalty
Because you know someone by their enemies
So is that a no
It's beyond that it's the fight
You see how the globalist hate Trump
Ilysm
Brazil
Nationalism nationalism
Africa
So like let's look at beyond the Brazil the strip mining
Of the world right now that was difficult but look at the world leader
Years that Alex Jones has been firmly in support of
You kept
Not good
Marine Le Pen
Geert Wilders
Not good
Nigel farage Rebecca
If you kept
Hey
I think you just threw Tamara in there as well
A leader with a
A 5% approval rating
It's not good
Migrate
Oh I also a leader who has
Literally been on tape committed crime
Who was not impeached for them
He was on tape
Unclear if he's
Supporting Camaro or
Someone else
Could be any result might be Pele
I don't know
You haven't talked about that too much.
List movement the white nationalist government
That you had on the show
Have one
Connection
And it's not
Fighting's the globe
Be there soon
Are Dwight
Could have some
Not sure about that Brazil but the rest of them certainly absolutely
Okay
Brazil had one of the most
Diverse
Government
Until then
Ramshackle
The
Previous leader Dilma
And installed an all-white government
Okay
Anyway we still are not sure how he's answering
You kept a perfect party does it mean
Parties in Eastern Europe away from the EU
Global domination
Global with Worldwide
Organize tearing
They're the Opera
You always sound like he's trying to chew on something very weird whenever the camera goes away from it sounds like he's
Just taking a bite of a sandwich
Anyway
Are the biggest
Sharks
And that the fight is so close
Only halfway support Trump and not be such a big Target
But I want to be just like he is
I want to give my full
Effort and commitment
Measures
Amethyst
I want my John Hancock on the Declaration of Independence
They were sick of being rule
By an outside power
They put on the line and they were successful and they were victorious
I smelled it 3 years ago you've seen happen
The outside power
So you don't really get Alex
Myra Myra
Responses
The fuk you just sex yet
I'm certain Buckley came over to him in like
Dude
First of all
That was nothing
3 minutes of nothing
You did not give
Answer at all
You didn't address
The important
Piece of that
Who had a critique of you
Which was it you used to be much more passion
Used to be before it was all this trouble
Alex comes back from commercial
We're going to see some false passion
Alright we're going to see
See some fake crying
How much symbols wealth
Or acting physically Tha Product
Is that what people think I don't know
This is right after their commercial
That's not what a man.
Amanda's right
Devil worship battle files
Call Jasmine
It's not the lord's name in vain.
I think that's the definition of the last name
Energy
And everything I got
He sounds
Higher
Mary Hart
They're a bunch of cowardly scum
Cuz they're always a bunch of confused knitting rudderless
Where's mine answered you parents
Come out and say you had trouble going to blow your brains out I'd say pull the trigger
Democratic Party
No that wasn't them that was your ex-wife
Squishy
I don't know I don't want to get mixed up in your ex-wife
It was not the globalist
Or the Democrat
So that was fake
NACA if you watch the video it's super hilarious just
Lexus choking back to your snowblower
Epic say that
Right now about
Doing all of those days
Because I fake crying about things
Bavarian Oculus
Terrance one more time
He's not done faking 12 minutes
Compassion
Really funny because it's where I heard the sound effect
Sound effects that I believe
Sound of Alex taking
Some booze to the Head
Ooparts wanted happen
The shot
Is what makes me think you was taking a
Because they're the globalists are the ones killing me
Donald Trump
How to get the table.
Bottle popping up
I to high-class whiskey for me
Goodnight Circuit Court did not say that you can't have American flag in school this is same
What about that
Problem
Classic
Yeah I would say you did and you know what thank you for the heart and your voice again I need to hear that
I'm a strong man like you I'm a 27 year old male with a daughter
Is right there only 27 I heard the
Yeah it was right there if you listen very carefully you can hear
It sounds exactly like someone breaking a highball
And sweet
He's 75
Larry Nichols pretending to be 27
You used to have
You go ahead and go
I heard that because he was faking it again
It's like
It's like a f****** Dueling Piano Bar getting over guy getting a request
But Sookie takes that drink
And like I said right before this what he said the caller ID says I'm a 27 year old man
I have a daughter
Listen to Alex's rejoinder
Which I'm certain indicates
Was not paying attention
I do think to myself now it's Jones
The globalist can kill you
Who cares about me who cares about you but my daughter's they threatened to kill my daughter
You respond to that
Arguing with Carol and daughter
So f*** it obvious that he thought
What are you saying they're actually real
Drinking a shot of whiskey used just like
Target
People anymore
Why the f*** would they
From wherever
And so this is what
No but if they did
Imma Go Alex
Get back
And if this is what's going on
If you have your heart
Chubb
What the f***
Great advice if you don't want people to threaten to kill your daughter you have to let them know that you
Kill baby kill your daughter
School
I don't know how you would interact with them
Prior to
Blankets
Franklin
Go to the
Get a seashell
Scream if you attack my daughter I'll kill you
They'll get it right
They'll get the message understand how Alex Jones
Can beat like
These moments
That are like
There
Literally nothing
But there the moment
Breaking news episodes
The moments where
When he's
Globalist threatened to murder your daughter
Brain for a second
This color somehow is important enough that these shadowy globalist with his daughter
If you wouldn't
He's like
Maybe maybe
My audience
Still think that's
Rio
What's going through his tonight
Maybe this guy's the right kind of crazy
For me and we can do a little improv game little
Humana Network
I hate that the got cut off
Cut off
On the show weekly like
Questioning
There's just
Assume is opportunistic mindset
Really one of the only Thrills eyeglasses
Those moments
Way2go was killed
Are we boring to be at this point it's just so clear
Anyway Alex is taken
6 1/2 hours 37 hours
Might as well be that last call took
The better part of
Yeah because Alex kept screaming
Compassionate
And all that
So then comes back for that commercial
Well I love
I got a ton of important Club
Sorry you're exhausted
I don't know I don't know what is exhausting you about it maybe
Is your hecny performance
Talking
Toothless people
I would
I think yeah I think you just hates it
Corner of having to either
Get all of his energy up to fight back against it and
Or yes
Tristan whenever they're saying cuz they're a fan
You had a great question
Don't know what I really liked the first call that he had was a guy who
Brought up a couple of salient
It's about his past
But he's willing to lie in certain cage
Right position on 180 degrees
Andy refuses to release
Financial
Those three things are really respond to any of them
Do pretty serious attack
It's okay
That would be exhausting
Trying to figure that out on the Fly Right
Second caller is would give up Trump
To save up
Save people's lives
And that
Daddy answer to that.
If you say yes I would
You don't get to play the I would die for Trump
He is what's going to save us from the globalist
Right no then you are complicit in whatever is going on the escalation of 10
Between the left and the right and what have you
You are
You're a big part of it and you have to
That question is also one you can't really answer straightforward and honest
But if he says he's already essentially answer that
Which is better
Something like that
Like what
Question because I don't know why that question is unanswerable
Will because there's a part of his brain and there's a part of
I mean I don't know maybe
Part of the
The Deep recesses of his audience
His brain still remembers that when Trump first started running Alex that I don't trust him he's a con
Turn on the East Coast
Like there is a part of him that knows
This is going to break bad
This isn't going to end well eventually all of these things
These Financial Miss dealings
Let me see the ones that aren't already f****** public
The more serious ones that drop has been involved with eventually will come to light
And Alex is going to have
Santa Bear for the fact that
He pretended that all that stuff wasn't true
Boxer Rodger Stone
He's eventually going to have to face
Music for that
And I think that
Waffling around with a direct
Question
He's able to
To save himself a little bit of face eventually down the road
He's preparing
Not nice not always
Your name
I mean
If I were one of those guys
And I
The Flynn news
Like man like they're trying to get keep manafort from like
They're trying to deny his bail
Because he's a player
Because of course he's
There's one country he's not going to Alabama
The United
2 country
So it's like it's like there should be
You should be able to see the writing on the wall
If you're one of those fat face
That closely aligned
And so you should have like a bug out bag at least right like these guys have to know what's going on
They have to know that eventually it's going to come
Although
Franklin
F*** it might not
I think that Alex probably realizes on some
Part of his brain
If all of it works out
He's an even worse
Because then I mean
Is net neutrality go through
You going to lose most
Because most people
With without being
Cruel
Most of his audience
Can barely afford.
Them at all
A lot of them live in Crazy Royal areas
They don't have good service with
Write a lot of those places are going to have
No coverage
Well
Well it's going to
Be even worse like all of that is going to
Pylon it pylon
He's going to
New prophets dwindled to almost
Unless
You know there is a despotic official
But I mean like
Does really dark
He doesn't realize
He doesn't realize how much
The position is advocating for
Are going to
Buckhannon
He should have been briefed on how net neutrality
But like if he's if he's doesn't read articles
I know but he should have
Somebody
He's like he doesn't take brief
Show me if somebody who does
Because everybody should have been United
For net neutrality except for the Telecom
Like it should have been 100% of
Speaks to the possibility of getting big dark money
Yeah he could pay for the
Comcast
Tell the truth when they say
Said they were
There is that
You are nice
But also the people who would be dictating the position
Or you know
Subtly
Influencing
The positions
Would be interested
Say that
Like
It's not that
Takeover of the media
Yeah but
They're going to
They're going to bail on him when they can
Totally I would
I'm looking for
Anyway
So
There's a lot of rambling
There's a lot that goes on
Do you like another 6 minutes or so until we get to the next call
Do you think this one's going
Be critical role
Supportive
Relatively critical in a row
The second critical one was supportive but just
Yeah I accidentally tough request
I thought he was at
So let's go with
Idaho Central hauling around here
Yes I am
So
Damien off of yesterday's
Conversation
I'm a
Irish English
German
Friends
Indian
Whatever
K
You're drunk
Okay
No
I don't
If I can
A little bit
Polish agency
Friends.
Big Lebowski all polish come
Ashley
People tell pesobic that he must be a Russian agent cuz he's probably
There's other reasons
There's just a lot of things
I'm just having fun with you sorry
Well I got it
Deposit there because you cannot talk over there
We cannot even laugh over there
Well I got it
You're something else I got to go at caller some Crystal ridiculous
Everything I know about Alex Jones
Whatever Alex immediately says
Any any numbers
That's who cop-out for oats
Alex probably takes a lot of pain
Possible
Insinuations
Suggestions from the chat room that is on amphetamine
Okay that's possible but I think that also could just be the brain Force
Because he has said that there are
New product the red pill
There's no stimuli
But there are in
Yeah I don't know
Consumption
I don't know I think it'd be a lot more
Not as
Tired
As Alyssa
Peter just seems like
Yeah he's got a baby
Please like
He's either high or he
If that's a bad prank call
Going to mean
There's a there's a
If you're just walking around if you can do better than that
If you're drunk maybe not
Anyway
Critique of the calls
Not most insightful
Okay
He's taking three calls
Well he's covered his bases
Move on
Samantha questions
My fault I apologize we're going your calls
At least the cops to it's my fault there long
Question
Like
Literally every single one of you did except for Peter who is high
The calls would be really short
If you didn't scream
Performative
For half an hour
Was
Would you give up Trump
Because he's
Just one part of the fight against
The globalist
Yep all right
Need to go through it but the guys talking about how
Christian
Christianity matters
The Bible
God judges the heart David got his best friend killed just have sex with his wife
But behind closed doors are super cool
Not they were perfect
He was a horrible person
Teaser for real guy
He's out the openings not perfect
But he really isn't out to get people
He doesn't want austerity
So what are the what are the defining characteristics of King David and Saul become
Call
Doesn't relate
Trump boat from Tarzan
They change
Still get it
The point of those stories
Is recognizing the error of your ways and having a transformative moment
Try one more time
On the road English the roads are you say about the road to Damascus
French
Very specifically the point of the stories is that they were bad and they had a coming to
Jesus moment
The transformed them
In every way
Everything about them
They weren't
The same people that didn't hang out with the same people
They change their mode of being
Well if y'all told Trump about anything you know that
A change from
I assume
Okay he blossomed like a butterfly into the sociopathic monster he has been
Since the age of nine that's it and I mean that's an interesting theory that he is
Road to Damascus moment was at age
Maybe maybe he will In that clip
Even is he saying you know like
David
Saw
Humbled even bad to begin with better than King David
Never killed his wife Mary's ever killed his friend's wife
Kill this friend
Tupac his wife
Beat the s*** out of his wife
Apparently
Mayor made out of insects
His daughter
That's true that is in the Bible
Yeah but then the daughter was at fault
King David killed his daughter
So at this point Alex
This is like alright we had a great call
Maybe it's going to work
Workout
Let's try one more
Let's Roll
I don't answer
I just tried hung up on a different color
Okay
I don't know what's going on
I love your show and I have trouble listening to it because you're at doesn't work with iOS 11
I hear you Brothers want stuff done work around here
That's delightful
So good
Alex
I have to text support questions for you
Here's what I disagree with you on
Update iOS
All these questions should be directed to Rob do
Even heard around here
This
This leaves
Infowars
Listeners are the smartest
Absolutely this leads to at least seven minutes of a rambling about how like
I have tried
So hard
To get that app
He claimed globalist plot
How many leftists in the tech world
Nonsense
I paid someone
Hundred dollars
The make that app
Anyone
Is very weird
Besides at that point
Donald call
I have too much news to get through
To get through
Snooze
So a lot of you survive
A lot of time is taken up complaining
About
Muslims raping
Sweden is that narrative
Is tired
David
Maybe
Alan dershowitz
Excuse me
David Horowitz
It is a very different
But he has he has a dershowitz clip
Give me argument that
Muller has shown that he has nothing
Because of this in type
All he could get him on was this
Lying to FBI
And now if that is
Which I don't believe it is I believe it's
But
Again I can't prove that that's just my
If it is true that
Five years in prison
So
Not enough not not terrible but at this point in his life you don't want to do that
I don't think
Thighs
Right
Ball it seems it
Calls it seems unlikely the other bringing up in the clip is
Because
Flynn has been shown to be a liar
He's not going to be a good Witness
Slater
For anything that you might be proper
Maybe but that's also super interesting to me because one of the other things that belies is
Almost the entirety of Alex Jones is narrative that
Do you know Hillary and Obama
Fund Isis
Is based on Michael Flynn appearing on foreign
Same thing
To that effect
So is Alex Jones wants to play the game but Mike Flynn
It's not going to be a credible Witness
You might have to re-examine some of the Bedrock
If your
Narrative
You know
It's not important
It's not a boy
Alright let's get to this next week cuz this is one of the other news stories
He's got to get to
Most racist crap I've ever heard and they're just speak
Dogs are racist
Is being raised by a black family is around lot of white folks in my park at you cuz if not used to your phone
This is getting crazy
Cool
The point is
No.
Crazy
Pointers
Ship going why
So like okay let's take
Just the first and most obvious
Who is Nick Cannon
Cuz this is wild now he's making it like
Even in his brains you can't go to like white people made a dog racist
Bart it's not racism
So you flashes up on screen the article so I know exactly what it was was able to hunt it down
It is an article
From January 3rd 2013
Right on time why are dogs racist K9 experts speak
4 years ago
Gawker
It is no longer website
Website
You know the time frame
Halo
Snarling and biting
It's been a source of uncomfortable comedy for years
Some dogs are just
But why
We turn to the real live dog psychology experts to find out
Linda Michaels dog psychologist
Victoria Stilwell dog trainer
Lesbian couple
So happy
Oh okay with one person with a credit
All appear to be racist that's not possible
Racism requires complex thinking and other higher cognitive functions to Canine simply.
Don't possess
Her answer is
It's a f****** dog
Adult May react in fear-based aggression to a person of color for two reasons one insufficient positive Association in early
Socialization
People evolve
Or to a traumatic incident with a person
Color that is now generalized all people of color Alex
Sounds like Alex is a dog
And it's pretty much
Her answer is
Dog
Colorado's own dog whisperer
That's alright her title
!
Let's
You seem to like some dark skin
Very few cases
Is a dog's tongue
This like lightskins
People are reported
Your example.
Is not that bad
That goes on to say
Dark Knight Rises
Is a four-year-old article that makes the opposite point that he pretending the media
What the f***
Quick question
Can dogs commit blood libel
Yeah oh yeah
I saw an article on docker
So update that reference
So on this side next
Clip we're going to go with the last
I kept this in because
Boy howdy
On an angry note please make down until the end of the clip and then feel free to scream
Text Josh
The future but now
2 trillion in overseas money
And bring back trillions to the middle class and poor taxpayers
Is going to cause a giant booming economy
Most analysts say and 10% growth rates
12%
Is that going to be good neighbors
For the Republic
Free-spending
It'll create a big deficit like that one right
I never got the cut
You got a free suspending then you cut taxes more money comes in generally because it's Thursday economy
Then you pay down the debt with that
There's a lot of stuff at play there I think one of the things at the end
Is the idea that it's like these tax cuts and we have to get rid of all of these programs and stuff
Do it right behind those tax cuts
This is one to give more money to the rich people into to get rid of all entitlement spending
Vitesse Kazar about cutting Medicare social
Security Medicaid
Matter that's what they've been going for the entire time they're going to do it in the next two to three years that's the only way
And the Democrats are going to f******
Rollover
Pathetic
Everything about this b*******
He's going to destroy the economy for the next 10 years
As if we didn't f***
Made it destroyed already didn't have enough
Good money already
Go away
Every last f****** one of them if you are a
F******
F*** this
Jordan
Do you know what group is going to come from that book
1%
Baby and that's
Going to last for the first six f***
Because all their regular people are going to wind up getting his less than $1,000 back
Flipping a thousand dollars extra that's only going to last for the first
Forfeit
Thanks just lying directly to his people
He's not he's not f******
Disassembling stop pretending he's not f****** he's lying straight out of his f****** teeth
Because it doesn't matter how f****** stupid you are if you don't look at exactly what happened to Rick
Exactly what happened to the first time
Everybody got
Bought
That's why it's telling
I could have gone on
I wanted to start in the Reagan Era and then go through how the Democrats have failed
Entire situation
Then I wanted to go into the George Bush era
Whatever he did his
Democrat
Didn't we get it
We get it
You're preaching to the choir of a walk
Parking Fury I know I know
I just want to find somebody anybody
Anybody
Cdl-a
I'm stuck don't take it out on me
Is my
You're getting rave reviews for that ramp the chat room
How can you get how can you actually listen to this
How can you read
I told you earlier it's just listen to the news
Why they're lying
And the meeting doesn't f****** do anything they don't just go
That's not f****** true you're a liar go away
Like that's all you need to do what needs to be done
Just go to timeout
We're not going to Lomita
McConnell on f****** TV anymore
Until you stop f****** life
Paul Ryan's Hope you get f***** in the ass by anybody anybody with a very long thing
Doesn't matter how f****** long it is
Really long
Get in there I want his intestines
Be straight no more curls Noah
Miles and miles of
Trader
Broom right through his goddamn body
This is
I'm sorry
I'm sorry there's no
I Wanna smoke a post-coital cigarette these are just now becoming your like
But you're aggressive fantasy
You're Jones
They're just
Lying directly to us
And everybody
Agree with
Most of what you're saying
Just for my own safety
Do you think I'm going to say
No. The thing
That
I would like to see ID
These tax cuts are great
But it's not going to do anything unless we also strip back all these programs
I want to accidentally showing his cards on
And he's giving away
Is that
The tax cuts aren't going
Do anything they're going to get rich people more money
What is going to save money is taking away things from
Because you are.
Depriving them of things that already cost a ton of money
All that money that the rich people are going to save Incorporation
They're going to save
Bye-bye
It's not going in
It's not going anywhere
What it's going to do is it's going to stay
Outside
Protected tax shelters
Some s*** like that
Entirely about stripping what generates money for the
Is the middle class and the poor have
Spend that money
The wealthy don't spend money
Hoard
The speculation in
It's not something that
Real it's not something that actually goes towards building
If you want
How
How is it going invest in a bombing popshop in the stock market
It's so
F****** simple and it's historically
Prove it it's not like it's not like we've never it's not like
Hey guys we've never tried this ship before I'm going to blow your mom
The company that I used to work at right before I I
When on this side
Whatever this is
Is a thought
Is a small business
Attempt to list
Listen to a crazy man ramble it's a small business
Small business
Run by an individual
Like he ended up when times got bad he had to
Become a Salesman
Help out
Very actively involved
Office in the building
The people who started the company with him we're still there
In terms of actual in office
Employees there were like 50
Or something like that
It is a small business
They were bringing in
No it in the Realms of a couple million a year or something along those lines
It is not a publicly traded company
I don't worry now that I put their business on
Investment
Stock Market South
Economy doing better only help
Indirectly in
Variant asthma way
Dewey's
It would never
All these businesses
Is on the same level wouldn't be helped by that
The middle class growing
The ability for them to give me a raise
Wouldn't be helped by the
Everything is incentivize them
Do not cover
And even if the
The guy who ran the
Was
Cuz one of the big things
Play lower with
Right through rate goes from 35
Which is
Because a lot of the come
Our
Are those
They classified the investment Banks
As
This dude
As opposed to
You lower that.
Like I said even if that guy is doing that that guy is running the past
He's not going to get a ton of money back
It's not going to be a huge amount for
For him
But some people
It will be
Congratulations
Great we live in a world where this has to be a reality
Pretty much all of our national parks
And stuff probably are,
Is going to win
Know this
This cast
This can't continue there's
Not in just a this
Continue like a
This is so bad
We can't allow this
Continue I mean it's a no
Everytime this
Has been done there has been a
A crash there will be
A crap because of the difficulty that will come after that is that
Difficult Economic Times
I mean the disparaging the difference between the Haves and Have Nots
Is unsustainable to
It's very serious
Disagree and it causes
Societies fall apart when they fall apart
Everybody has nothing
That's when fascism
Takes old
That is when you have to really be worried about these things
Blood libel narrative
Evitable finger with these tax cuts
With the direction everything is going is
A bubble burst
Cuz there's a lot of artificial into the azzam
The stock market is
Exactly look at how high it is right
The next it'll never stop
Going to end
Maybe I don't know it
Double bus to make a prediction of what
But when it does I will make
This prediction
Alex will blame the global
Yeah
And the GOP will blame the poor
And knowing
Alex Jones
Probably pretty
Clear at this point that
It will be very easy
Scapegoat
Blame
It'll probably actually go with me
Probably easier
Only good thing about
Is that during those dark
We will get to kill
That is going to happen
Sure there's going to be a fascist dictator that rise
Your Napoleon
You're Hitler
Whatever your
In those intervening time
We're going to get to Townsend
I will politely.
Decline of the actually murdering
And I agree with you
Believe me
When they do come
Come on over
I'll help you from
The Shadow
You can check out more of his ramblings on our website knowledge
Dot-com page
Support the show true
Knowledge underscore fight
You could go to the iTunes
The Facebook
We're and we're doing a lot of different Dynamics and what we're going to do from now on
And then
Next episode go take calls from critical role
And then I just
You know there's a
Just one guy
Oh I think is really at fault
For all of the
You tried to get him
Catch that buck
Bladen is Choppers
That's why we're going to start at the feet
He's got robot teeth ever made by CIA
David Bowie
Transmit
All of
The vaccine in
Information to
People all around
Temperature
And this guy
Ringleader behind all of this
I just have
Jon rappoport go f*** yourself
Alexandra Thurston color