Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
This is a show where I watched way too much Infowars
Particular
Sit down with my friend Jordan who has no goddamn clue what he's talkin to
About Jordan how are things
They're doing good
And I would say we're going to be going over the February 10th
Episode of The Alex Jones that was last Friday as this comes out
There's a couple
Little bit of business to take care of
First of all
Got a big old shout out
To randomly Susanna
What's up Susannah thank you so much she made something very cute and very beautiful and it made me cry
That's right we got a cock over here he lipt hard cock
Drawing for a logo very awesome thank you so much I really appreciate you can find that up on our new Tumblr
Which is
Knowledge fight. Tumblr.com
It was regarding the David Knight app
I would like to make a big apology
I know I know plenty of you voiced your support
I didn't hear from at least three people
That was both of you
Hersevoort and we agree with you
Yeah
Listen to boring man we get it
So boring but we're back
In the greener pastures of the real
Rate
Hundred proof
Alex
Joan
Territory the Everclear of Alex.
What I like to do is I like to sit down
Try and figure out
I would like to sometimes
Figure out what the the plot
All the shows
Is mine
Sort of
Believed into every aspect of the narrative
Is this
I really struggled with what it was
I can't really find a synthesis
Like
And now I actually regret that I brought up the idea that there is no guitar
Gator Tire prep
You can say
Yes and no half the time right there's a 50-50 proposition
I was just
I'm trying to figure out a way to articulate this
And I want you to let it play
Dulux just listen to it
Because if
He plays it
3 *
Call wait what he plays with clip
Three times back to back to back
Week you played it a whole bunch
Okay and
Just insanity
Love this clip
A movie
It's just
It's propaganda
It's Russell Westbrook dunking on a guy right
The first one is about a f****** stupid Democrats are and explain why
Eclipse so much
Hello this is how we open the she has the 54321 silent movie era
It took just to let you know this is how that f****** entire show up
No
This clip is how we opens Friday
So just cold open
Gotcha
Ireland
But at its widest
Level is with 12 mi from Shore to Shore
Canada's smallest level of smallest star
Location at 7 MI
Between assure and the other
That correct I don't have the exact dimensions but that's your point so I can
Guam is a small island island
I can work with President Bush
What are we going to do
How can a president
Who is acting in the manner that he's acting whether he's talking about the travel ban
Whether he's talking about his relationship to Putin and the Kremlin and knowing that they have
DNC
And knowing that
He's responsible for supplying
The bones of the innocent children and families and
What is Aleppo
You are correct
He is
Wrapping his arms around pooping continuant
Into
Bing bing bong bong bing bing bing.
So hilarious
So I had fun with that
To think I was enjoying every moment of that
How does a video of trump xylophone
I don't know what the context of that clip is but I know the context of the other
A person
Set the clip of I don't know who the senator is we talked about Guam but he wasn't literally talking about it
It was metaphor
It was his creative license
Somewhat
Furthermore that is hilarious
American history
It is not that far out of what we're used to
No I mean even the in Quincy Adams. The Earth
Makalo believes that a lot of people of hell
Republicans don't believe climate change
Israel
Also crazy than Guam tipping over
And think that
Is Nancy Pelosi accidentally saying
Bush when she met
Right
But then the other ones
Talk about her bush
One Senator saying or a representative
The freestyle
Obviously
That is metaphorical
Obviously there's
A reason that you saying that she's not literally saying she was at
Then Maxine Waters
Forgetting Aleppo for a second
I meant saying that Putin is invading Korea
Crimea
Whatever
Graphic novel
Crimea
It's it's these
It slips of the tongue
Is f****** latched onto
And made this two-and-a-half minute clip
Are you just plays it Non-Stop
Yeah you plays it we're going to talk about this on the next episode he plays it during a Jon rappoport special
Fantastic illuminate
I don't really disagree
Maxine Waters is a little bad I don't disagree at all
She's a little old for facts in order baby
It's time for also she's out of town and part of a democratic establishment that is clearly f*****
Everything up
The Putin is invading Korea
Or she actually doesn't know Aleppo
Is insane
Yeah especially the first one
The only person who doesn't know Aleppo is Gary Johnson
Your shots of him during
Picture-in-picture
So there's like the two shots next it's the video playing
And then Alex sitting at the desk
Alex Jones
Is making real quizzical husband
Refractive power
Acting reel
The show and how he
Again he plays the two more times throughout the course of
But he doesn't
Being in love with
Okay
Proud of it they put together a clip it got little backing music behind it they added it I'm sure they added it pretty
Pretty well right
Good on him.
They made a good clip for the Kim
Propaganda
So
Good way to start your show dickhole
He gets down to
Substance
Next web
And this next clip is what I would call
The first one
80 + percent of the time but the night before the show
I'm going to send
Circuit Judge I believe is what I used
Are asses for a second
Who is
What he said there was actually literally the first lie but he's a bigger Lies coming up
The 80s
Plus percent of a time there
Decisions are overturned
To trap a 9% Orchard
Not the most overturned
Court in Atlanta
Circuit Court decision
Overturn
Is it is it
The first
The middle
Admittedly
The problem with all of our courts
Is that
The ideal court system is
Is empath
Dispassionate
Observers of the code of robots
Instead what we have is
Weird-ass
Random
Ideological bent from our courts
Sure we have a super M court that isn't even really like
The game at this point
Maneuvering pieces around
Are we okay with the Supreme Court the way it is right now
The only reason
It's not even before the election
You had people like Ted Cruz
Arabic interpreter like
Never if Hillary gets in will just never vote for 1
Eventually
Get rid of
Supreme Court
It was fine whatever peep
Who disagreed with you or
Empower
But now that you're empowered you don't want that s***
Let me stop you
Trumpsc
Utter bafflement
By the fact
GameStop
We'll see you in court
He's not angry about it
Confuse
And in raid
He didn't understand that that was possible you didn't get weight
I signed an executive order that means
La forever right I'm supposed to be king right I'm running this like a business
You don't even use to watch
Like real talk
And a reality show cartoons
Cuz he didn't watch yet Finding Dory that is
Screenings at the White House okay
Really recommend
Watch The Emperor's New Groove
A great moving Patrick Warburton
Engraved price
You know how being a dictator
Is not really cool and put learning about
Also suggest
He watches
Schoolhouse Rock
Yeah
Schoolhouse Rock Let's go with magic
School bus that's really important
Pretty sure he doesn't know how the human body works
Absolutely
Movie
How dare you
Circuit Court
And get the actual lie
80% is
White exaggeration
Well-rounded up slightly
That's not uncommon
Appellate court
Isn't that weird
Kind of
Settings
Is that the fact that I just found out that I am reason is a lot of time
Supreme Court
Implicitly agrees with the ruling they were
Just reject
Kate
So the only reason that the Supreme Court would take a
Case is if there was a significant possibility
That it would be over
Okay yes they don't take most
Cases of course the reason that you would go to the 9th circuit
Court is because it is like the reason that washed
10 would go directly to
2 back court is because it is a left
Court
Maybe it has a loose sure about that
Appointed by
The G.
I'm not sure because I'm not sure how it works
In terms of standing and what goes to what court
Is just enough knowledge
Tell people the wrong
Words and then I'll put them in the wrong order and people who believe lies
I will tell you this
It doesn't matter
Choose the case at hand
We always get bugged-out reality whatever that has no bearing on what we're about the limits into the real life
80 + 11
Remind me of something
American flag is offensive
Clothing.
How dare they provide Public Works
Satanism
Coca-Cola shirts in Warwood
Raza Metro Mexican flag
But you cannot wear the American flag
I am going to guess
Before you say a word until you ever looked up this particular
Stan's did formation relevant to it
I did perhaps
It contradicts what it is
Feather Alex Jones was sad
Yeah your bingo is really the night circuit court
Rule
In agreement
With a lawsuit that was
Presented about people wearing
What ended up happening was they ruled
Couldn't wear the American
Sandy Spring Court refused to hear the case because there was like now this is this is fine
Case was was about people
Student
Can flag
On Cinco de Mayo
Okay here's why
Alright that seems automatically a little bit of like a hey we're reacting
To your thing
The controversy goes back to May 2009 an incident
Between
High School
Edit school-sponsored
Cinco de Mayo is that a Mexican American
Student walked around campus
The flag of Mexico
Will a makeshift American
States flag
The flag Berry students
Dunes on both sides complained about the in
A year later several students came
School on Cinco de Mayo wearing American
Flag shirts
School officials told the students
Remove the American flag shirt
Or turn the shirts inside out
The educator said the American flag shirts could send a message
Cinco de Mayo celebration
And I had Public Safety
So
What ended up happening was there was
Essentially
Between Cinco de Mayo celebrates aggressively
American
Flag apparel
Them on Cinco de Mayo people just to have nice stuff
Why can't you just work one day
Like look
I get it
You're a white nationalist motherfuker
In high school
Which
You're probably going to grow out of it
Hopefully
It's time to pray
Hopefully you'll grow up
But
Even if you're a white nationalist
Just be like
4 days of the year
But I'm going to give you this
The problem with that philosophy though is that
Cuz it is even
Moron for them
It's like I have to I have to be even more American on this day
Against your
Presumably anti-American
African flag have people I don't know
That's insane
The court rules essentially that
The school was allowed to say
No American flag apparel on Cinco de Mayo
BWB had nothing to do with the actual American flag apparel and everything to do with whether or not the school is allowed
How to say the reason was for the
Protection of
Both
V
Cinco de Mayo celebrating students
And
The kids wearing the America
In Flagstaff
Right because it was it was a situation where they deem
Like okay
There were fights that broke out
Conflict
Let's just not allow people to
Have this fight
You're at school
Not as far as as far as the conversation over and this is this is exactly what
The
The Muslim ban thing
Happened there
The reason that they issued that stay on whether or not they could reinstate it immediately
Is not because they agree or disagree
With what was going on
It is not because they say there's a u
You can't do this or that
It's because he
He did it wrong
It's because the executive order was written in such a way
That it impossible to
Any other way
As a religious
Scituate
Sure
Much more like if he'd taken
Get his f****** time on it
Like Mike by my constant thought about about Trump
Is whether or not you agree with what he's trying
How to do
Bad at
Doing the follow-through if Obama was in
Obama if he was going to instigate a Muslim
Right
Do that because he's at Sacramento
He would spend months on it he would have his lawyers go through word-by-word
The court system
Cuz I don't want to waste everybody's time and money
I'm sending it through the court system in Spanish
All of this time going
Yes you can no you can't pull really hard
Galvanize the opposition
He would try really hard to actually make it work
Competency
No issue with that it seems like they wrote like hey no Muslims on a page
Genistein
Meme it might as well have been that
Yeah the other thing in that ruling was that nonsense
Right which is very important
We all believed already
Hi tie quilt
But the root of that is
Most of us believe people
People
Ya goddamn Independence
Doesn't say we believe you know
Folks
We Believe American citizens
Our Creator net worth
Call me eyes of God
Not women
That is the problem
Very clearly
We stipulate that rights aren't given by the
The government's are given by our creator
Whatever you want problems with but whatever greater if you understand that that's why I
Which again that's kind of the whole point of America is that we can't have a state religion
But human beings have right because of just
Being Human
Not because it's paid gave them right
Therefore
To my understanding in my belief
If you
Are someone who isn't a citizen
We still can't treat me like s*** your person
Yeah you're right
Are granted by God
Not by America
The greatest point the greatest point is that always
Is always that a government cannot give you they can only
Take them away
Very seriously
Well he also would have been concerned about Putin 10 years
Two things I posted
Did a couple of articles on our Twitter
On the knowledge fight Twitter
An article about Alex Jones
Former editor
Who came out and called him a sell-out
If you have a
If anyone knows how to get in touch with him
Tell him to hit us up
You remember back when
Alex
Was talking about
How there was going
Concentration
Austin Airport
He gave a report from the road
He was talking about how there was a
The tape that was going
Come out
Of trump saying the n word
The Apprentice on the road
Maybe drunk
Yeah
Yeah I did a little story about this
Marcos
Mooyah
A twenty-seven-year-old marketing
Professional from Glasgow who found out
The editor of prison
Planet pickups
It's a straight-up
That guy's DM's were open
And so he
Just sent him that story
Borzas
As a prank
He just sent him all this b******* and then went to bed
Woke up the next day
And it was almost
Quoting him verbatim
What is Honda Auto Twitter I posted
Exodus story
And you can see their screenshot
Lots of him interacting with PJ jobs
And it's insane it's so f****** awesome
It's just you're busted
You fell for it
And I looked into it I looked
Try to find that
It has now been taken
Infowars.com
Now
The the mosque
24-hours
Of course he did because why tell the truth
Why fly
This is Alex
Talking about
Awesome Andrew Jackson
Rhetoric
It's totally
Probably even more interesting than
George Washington
Agree I 100 country live
If you want to talk to the microwave
That's impossible
It's like the Revenant Dusty the Revenant is historically very very accurate an amazing film B amazing Mexican
Director
Again movies
Andrew Jackson
Live things like that movie
Hundreds of times
He fought hundreds of bears
Okay.
In specific
I will disclose this
As a stand-up
Comedian I asked
Do material about
Andrew Jack
Hey I have a bit would you like to work
Done it's a good bet I do it a lot I'm not going to waste I'm not going to wait to bed
I need your f***
Can oats come to a show you'll laugh
You should go see him last
So I will I will point out my conflict event
Ionizing
I will say this
Andrew Jackson
Is one of the most interesting America
Can president in history
Not cuz he was a good president
Barry
Very bad at being present
Also this club goes on a lot longer where Alex actually get
Do you want me to
Before you roll but I okay I will tell her I'll tell my favorite Andrew Jackson
Two-story guarantee that he will not get into
I guarantee
Okay
Here's how I know this
I will.
Yogurtology
When Andrew Jackson
Moved into the White House
He had a party
That lasted multiple
Yeah yeah yeah
Windows
Many broken windows
But the best part
There is a wheel of cheese
Yeah besides of a man
Ever
DC
Week
Like essentialism
And that is the that is
Quintessential Andrew Jackson
You're correct
And survive
He was completely Charmed
Lucknow deal with
New Orleans
Add ships
With hundreds of men shooting
And they couldn't kill him they were shooting people all around and he stood there in a big black fur coat
Just staring at him with his eyes ammonite
A remake
But notice
In the white house there is a
Box of Jackson
On a horse
Right behind Trump
Amanda Jackson
He's the guy that killed the early Federal Reserve they had then
He's the guy that survived more than Americans
So crazy
Completing a genocide is one of those things
Trail of Tears
What is a rainbow one of the reasons he's clearly lionizing Andrew Jackson right now
How can I
To literally go up to the Supreme Court and say
I'm going to do it anyway f*** you
He was the last Heat while he wasn't last present but he was one of the main president
Who tried to break the whole checks and balances
He tried to become
If you believe in The Narrative of the
The Elders of Zion and the Illuminati and
The Federal Bank
Disorder if you believe all of that
There is something to be set
Is it is
It's like okay
It's pointed out freaky
That Andrew Jackson tried to bring us back to
Gold standard
And yet
He is on the $20 bill
Not anymore right
We're getting close to that we're not there yet
But are you still on the twenty-dollar bill
It pointed out that is ironic
That he hated paper money so much
Yeah yeah
Fiat currency do you think that is
Purposeful shade
No you don't think so
How could it not be
What person working in the treasury was like
Let's put Andrew Jackson on
As a memorial
Without knowing any history of Andrew Jackson
Somebody completely ignorant of Andrew Jackson knowledge
Remember the new that only the stuff that to Alex
The stuff about him standing up on top of a ship and menacing people in
Look handsome anything at all these duels
Which were mostly about how his wife was a hore
Beat a man to death he almost killed Amanda
Well they have very similar hair
All right. Goes on a little bit
You said something at the end of this
Buckwild
George Washington's wife was an unbelievable as well but true I got to tell you he's
Easily
Andrew Jackson with the sheer magic Providence
Okay
He get stabbed or shot in duels bleed for 3 Days blood everywhere
Who is Oregon's wouldn't die or refuse to die
Images
He was wild
It was wild
But now this clip takes a turn
Into the most
Phone directory
Oh I know sorry
That's the next episode
As far as the profile
Because
He was something else
And the fact that
Into the guts of spines
Good freaking reason
He also says that like
Washington
Was the first Ford
You gave birth to The Republic
Manator Jackson was a second father of the Republic Trump is going to be the third
Sobriety
Although
I will say the Muslim man is the closest corollary to
The Trail of Tears that we have right now
Choosing one of the worst American president
History
As The Shining Light Of America
Just because singular point that he tried to stop the Federal Reserve
Yeah
The only thing that's really important
Because he does buy into the Elders of Zion
If he does buy into this idea
Of these cryptobanker
Who are just trying to manipulate everything in Destroyer
Turn us into slaves
Too far wrong you know they are evil
Today we need to talk about
What's on our plate
Is more Andrew Jack
No
Although it's close
Weird
British intelligence tried to get the South to secede just like it's later
Try to break the country
Killed
Wait what
What
Woody woody woody conducive
Continue the
That is all checks
President of Texas
Noses
Everything is shut off so
Andrew Jackson
Who covertly sit-in basically the special ops of the day to set up Texas
President
Where what
It's amazing
So now
I like
Covertly is
More like overly sent an army
Right right right
It wasn't like
Three or four guys like
Sidled up to Mexico relax
How about that
You're like that Texas
No it's more like hey
How about we take Mexico to
Andrew Jackson
Is the closest President we have to Yosemite
Yeah but then that that
Cinebarre
But then here
I don't want to bore you with all of them no more stuff I know about it accidentally stopped the last
Best Clip 2
This
What is a round clip
The biggest
Kyla b*******
Acting I've ever seen in my life
Just enjoy cuz I don't know how you would do that
Jackson part is over but he does space work
Yes hello
Hey good lookin I'm only here I'm a call you back okay
New York prison
What's great is that the angle of
That wasn't even the angle of his phone on the video
Even see the screen is still black
Act like there's no indication that a call is coming in and just like put it up to
Like its improv space
It's actually his self
He is
He is doing a radio
He has his phone on the
Set right there you know how like Stephen Colbert or I would have food under the table that uses
Yeah it's like that
He has his phone that he describes and
He's actually saying like
I'll call you back
He's taking the phone away from this place
There's no way you're not you're not on a call this is planned plan
The plan is to make it look like he has Insider sources calling him
Oh so he wasn't that was
That was just really bad at lying
Who would have been on the Jerome
Horsey maybe they have no idea what
That
He does the show at the
Same time
Every goddamn day let's also consider that he doesn't have their number saved
Call Adam New Yorker
Alright
What b******* that is amazing
Yeah yeah absolutely
Canada calling and you wouldn't
She's a model
Really cool though we love talk
You guys ever read books
Alright Jordan
The next one
Yes
Alex likes to do media criticism
The only thing he criticizes
Is always going to be Transformers
And cooking
Correct
This is
The clip from CNN
About
How is involved
Anvil like Ivory the pens
Situation over it is pretty crazy
Infiltrate every member of NATO and influence the outcome bringing nationalistic weirdos
That's crazy
This isn't his critique
About
That very story
The British intelligence
In the Civil War are we not going to deal with that at all
Oh no
Through that in and then we're going to bail out or was playing by the
And we forgot that
My whole family
Congrats
That's like the exact same thing
Sherman
F*** you
Get back to this in a later
So this is this
Analysis
That eyes
Jump Trucking
Using similar tactics
Power structure in case.
Never comes out corrupt about officials
America or in Russia
Or else directions
If your wife catches you cheating on her the Russians did it
Brady and others didn't win
I was Superbowl Sunday you know there's a meme
No
It's white supremacy players
So you just literally said I'm not joking
So he must mean it
He clearly means
That batshit-crazy City said no one no one
Memes that
No one says that
Legitimately
You know how memes are always 100%
Flexicrew
No so we know that memes are joke
This goes back to Henry know that the British
Influence the Russian Civil War
Yep all right
This goes back to him on Rogan being like
Not understanding if you were joking when they say he's Bill heck
Yeah not understanding the people are f****** around
If anybody says that the Russians
Call
The Patriots to win
Super Bowl
Released
Have to be under attack that's why the right-wing is never fun
Yeah cuz they always have to be under attack
Far enough
Like they don't understand the absurdity
Of that where it's like
Yeah we know the Russians we know did one thing
So
If it's if it's one thing which
Thedirty.com is now being corroborated
It's all over
Our government committed all kinds of trees in Edwardsville just fine
Flame f****** small flower
That's the real
Public
At best you violated the Logan Act
Worst
He should be hung on the
But
Yeah
It's all peace stuff no it's not
You can't
Go to far you know
So with the left the idea is always good not even though
Funny people
It's always going to be
This is silly
How this is
So let's go and put it in different situation
Let's find an analog
And it's even sillier there but if you're the right wing
It always has
Become silly but I realize it's silly all the time I think that what you're also getting to
Is that the right wing in the right
Kind of isn't able or not able to be unwilling to engage an abstract thinking
Yeah it's all concrete
It's all like
These memes
Is part of the Super Bowl
Sing the end as we all know only the Sith deal in absolutes
I did not know that
The news
Well it's fake
It was in Star Wars
We haven't even gotten to the media criticize
This is f****** banana
Let's do it alright
Have you started the f******
Flexon that Brian stelter guy
Gets worse
You just haven't mean are Russians
The Russians didn't make the Patriots win
Korea
What is it feeling office
These are all real things that current members of Congress believe
Again he does not realize
Types of tongue
Yep and
Not really saying that someone is invading Korea
Whoever which is
Not it's not a it's an easy
Sure and maybe you let loose that you believe in 12
Sure you would want that to be held against you like you wouldn't want somebody to take that clip
And then put it on
And talk
Leslie about it
I think that's pretty different
Your evidence that Democrats are insane
R1 slip-of-the-tongue
In terms of Nancy Pelosi saying
That bush is in office
Don't you met Trump
And then the other
Primary Korea
Which sounds very similar
Lapses
Play those clips for a week
You got
Nothing nothing
It's like the Jay Leno like a man on the street interviews
Cherry Picked
Basilius
Workout
If you if you get your friend cuz he has a man on the street named Mark Dice
And he goes out there.
The back there's such good names
People with names like his we wouldn't wind up
Evil sound like Agenda 21
Dirty version of corn name
Yeah like
Yes Robert 100%
Mark Dice
F*** face McGee
Jon rappoport is fine is the last name is fun
David
Big dick light
What type of drugs are they on
What's wrong
Oh my gosh
The French
The Russians pulled out of globalism as well 18 19 years ago
Of New World Order social engineering Proto globalism
We got to interrupt his way more than I expected
Wait what
The only evidence that the Russians did it is that the Russians
Did it first used
The oligarch
Battle narrative
Yes that is them taking out globalism
Right there on the Vanguard of the New Nationalism movement
The brexit
The Italians are trying to get out of the EU right things like that are all like
Oh yeah this is
This is just realizing our sovereignty and getting out of
Unelected international law
Mount baby
You don't get to
To join the EU if you're elected government doesn't say like eyelids
Join the EU
Complicated process
Yeah
Maybe don't just jump
Maybe what are you saying is that when the EU start
Okay they were grandfathered in because we needed a sounding
Until like France got in on the ground floor
We should stop going to war with each other for thousands
That was a really good team to get
Sure as this party
That team
Like by the definition of the word team
Yeah I'm not here to say that the EU is the
For the world is perfect
Weird but I am I am
Saying that some sort of international
You working together is an incredibly positive
And the reason that it's done is because of a
Cities that have happen
And hoping
And hoping and working
F******
Hopefully
But they won't happen again
That's the reason that International bodies
Exist
And the rise of nationalism suggest for that
It's like a it's like a
Angela
People want
Atrocities to happen
Well the last time
You know the UN was created
After World War II
That was really the last time that nationalism had a really aggressive
Flare up
So
Forgot
The ramifications of that type of
We pretend that what happened there was fake news
Fake news
Some people do
Why are people
Bad at being
I don't know what would happen
People were not bad
I don't know maybe
How do you
Neither
Actually I've I've I've done been denied the Holocaust
No I went out into the forest
I've done some research into Holocaust deniers
Don't deny that
The Holocaust happen
Okay
They believed that there were
And mass killings of Jews
They also believe that the Six Million number is off
Okay because it was published
Beforehand
What was the Holocaust
Who predicted the sea
Six million Jews would be
Be killed OK and then
6 million is now the number
Coincidence
Okay but then also called the bullet holder
All right there other arguments they make
Is that they were
They were work
Champs
And then there was
Tons of aggressive bombing campaign
Germany
And Supply chains got cut off
And they didn't have medication
Food
Slave camp
Ended up dying
They weren't math
Killed they just died
Because of circumstance
But those are some argument
Yeah those are tires that are like
This is
It always it always comes back to that as long as you are only looking
For
Supports the already
The crazy thing is
You will continue to believe that
So any information that doesn't
Support that you just reject out of course
Because you can always look for more information
But there's also a great episode of
Montel has weekly
Montel had a great episode about Holocaust
Denial
Yeah it's crazy
Really interesting
F******
Hot Fire
Straight up interesting conversation
He has his daytime show
Haha
On there
2 survivors
F****** crazy
8 Ball
What what's crazier is it survives just beat the deniers
Civil
Sort of discussion about stuff
And the audience asking
10 questions
Is not it's not like a raucous everyone's mad at each other
Perspectives being laid out into it's amazing
Montel
If we need him right now
I never thought
Never before ordered on this planet
That we need Motel right now
People that first
Experience
On a show together and it doesn't turn into a fight
Is that in the Maze I highly recommend you watch it
See Jerry Springer version of that would have gotten
We're hiring
CNN
Fake news
Yes
God
Struggled
Are there still big Loveless combines in Russia still 10
Just like
Inside the state department
Look at this guy
The French braid
About the French
Islamic Jihad people
Let's go back to the ridiculous face
Accounts
Of many of these
Wingstop
Basically work
And they puts doing themselves and they dress weird
Then what the trendy's do
God
I love him
He's playing I got his title here
He is a cybersecurity expert from Columbia University
Yeah and he has a mustache
And I
Insane facial hair look terrible
Spine it's not comical
But Alex
Have to f****** latch onto this
Right because so long as you have a weird appearance
None of your opinion
Matter
Now
Enjoy the rest of this which is just
Fasting
Of his face
Wonderful
And they want to look strange I mean this guy looks like what cartoon character does he look like
You trying to come up with Snidely Whiplash
He never does
But the guy at
Behind the scenes
Comes up with Schneider
Put them up on there
He didn't go with Pepe Le Pew
Alright
Everything was going to erupt
Yeah I bet we don't interrupt
Supremacy
Which again is not with this guy's
Homophobe white supremacist Russian agent
Music mixer
Russia
Bo's but always do the same thing in different orders this is a great intellectual grab
Sabotage
Personal account
Of many of these may be the leading politicians
Other friends
People that were brought up in the cave
Interrupted
Weak little nobody that want to just get off on
The secrecy of your files
Again this over over is not a word
Uber over
Like
This guy isn't in the CIA
No but it is a foppish
Little what
Weak why is everybody
Why is everybody
Yeah he's just so mad at his guys masculinity
Always mad
Uber mention
Meanwhile
Everyone hates
Until I get to roll out these twits
Villains out of Central Casting
No no no it's the fault of the Russian intelligence that leaked almost all of it
Is getting ready to come out
Don't worry my little twit friend
Well one US intelligence leak
What the Russian
The more that's coming out is
Flynn
Being
Number two
He was on the payroll
Couldn't
Confirm it
He was a paid client. Thank God we finally got to
To the bottom of Hillary
Thank God I would have been still mad if we can get to the bottom of it
So I can get down on the
Okay
Who is this
Is unbelievable
Look at that outfit
Oh my God look at
Fake laugh also
First of all his face is worse than
Click and Clack
Patel Brothers
On
Austin fake news
Me too
If you ever listen to Car Talk
No I don't listen to
To f****** anything
It's on NPR my parents used to make me listen
Undo it
Kid I was even like
Laughing
About mufflers
What are they doing
There it was
So fake
Alex Jones
Yeah but
Then the other thing is
Guys wearing a suit
Why would you
He's wearing a suit
That's just
Is it good to
Is it like is it like one of those what Chuck
Chuck what's-his-name they NBA game
I don't know but is tires like
Slightly light
We colored I don't know if that's the only thing I can
Look at the arrogance that guy thinks he is so smart and you know women run from
Oh my gosh
F*** you count
Of many of these leading politicians
And also that of their spouses
Are there friends are lovers
People that were brought up in the KGB system
No
Whitehall
Changes plan
What
You were watching me
People
Can you what was that
That was just weird vague
Threatening he was chewing on his pain for a seconds
That f****** like
You know about you guy with
Facial hair
Eddie had facial hair that was unusual post a picture of him on
Temple Run
He's not wearing weird Sears it's very he's not wearing that tax guy from the 90s to die
He's not wearing a onesie
Noah
Just has weird facial hair
Weird
It's just
Unusual
It's Unique
Yeah
Hey what is a trendy
Clearly he's got a white van
Syracuse and being a little do you have to
To do
Disagree with that must watch literally
Just like hey Alex Maybe
Don't say that
Little boy
Joe Rogan
Lucky you got off
Yeah I'm surprised Joe Rogan isn't
Really disagree with him
That's true
From Seattle
About how Putin's real cool nationalism is awesome
And then I thought he was done making fun of
This guy but he was
Goddamn
There's some more about him
Mister creepy
Cybersecurity
Expert Columbia University I bet you money
The Nestor creepy is a creep
Look at that guy Mister creepy probably
This guy
They disrupted
Beademons television broadcast
They had such arrogance
Sdv little scripted
And then just
Total confidence
They disrupted Lamar
Corruption it's the Russians
Do you see my little 18th century beard
That's insanity
That's so
But that's so vapid that's
I really like how
Engaged with the guys
Ideas
A policy wonk based
Yeah really more about policy that it was
Devoid of any conversation about what he said we played 100% about
How he was foppish replayed
Twice
The guy
I remember his name it's cyber
Security Experts
Columbia University
Loved ones family members
Which because
We allow his clips
Just a little bit longer than that
Substantially longer
Replayed
Play-Doh
Twice
This guy saying that those
People would be excellent targets for the Cage movie
Yep if I was in the KGB
Cuz then maybe his father
You could find some way to
Alex doesn't engage with that at all either just engages with the mustache
And weird assumption that I have this guy's a f****** pedophile
And it's
It's insane it's
It's it's
Literally
8v absent
Journalism
It's not bad journalism
It's journalism in a vacuum
Let's get to our next
Cuz I have
Some f****** numbers on this one
I'm excited
Watched
Listened
Information
5 million
50 + Million last week
40 million
What are they going to do
They're going to try to say
It's amazing
It is amazing
I'm not going to try and say that he's a Russian
But what I am going to say is that it's 50 million people took us and if you encounter if you can't rub
Minutes 40 million really sure what that mean
Does that mean that Rogan
Accounts for 40 million of the 50 million or ten million
Alien from the 50 billion
The 50 million people took in his
Work
And the latter 85 million 50 last week
Let's break out
Okay
Alright
I know that everyone can
You see it all over the world
Okay let's take this
She's probably
Let's Imagine This
Just inside the United
Okay
Just to give you
Venom please
Extrapolated to the wrestler population
The United States
300 issue million people
If you want to get
50 million people listening to your show
You have to have
Every single person
Every single man woman and child
In the top
52 City
In United State
I still only 40
To give you some context
That's every city
Including Bakersfield California
And higher
Okay field California and up
Throughout the world
That's how many people listen to
Second
In order to get 50
50 million people or 85 billion
People listening to your
Johnny Carson
And even then
I don't think that
50 million people is cool
But it's 50 million hits
There are artificial hip
What happened
He always talks about these like we have all these
Plays on Facebook
Acrosome of scroll
Past the video and it's a
Just started playing
Does that count
Goddamn
Yeah all these things
Text Brett
Again
Russian troll Farm
Like that
Yeah you have all these fake numbers that end of happenings Million number
There's no way for me to prove what the
Of course not
But the entire population of the
52 cities
In America
Throughout the world
Take all of this
People in the last
Week
Engaged
No f****** way
Cuz if that's the case
You're a f****** Rockstar astronaut
Yeah he would be
You'd be a billionaire
You know what would happen he would be a billionaire like all the things he sells
Hearing his
His doors up
Heart trying to
To get as much out of his shows integrity integrity that's true
I feel like we need to call ourselves
Because
Episode where he was giving that fake bulshit
About what happened on Y2K
Yes we were too busy calling out all the other stuff around it
The we forgot to call out the in his story
She didn't even call out that
Houston sectionalism
Wasn't about Y2K
It was not about Y2K episode had nothing
We we did a bad job forgot about
Yeah okay
That's the problem he's a b******* onion
Anyway let's get to the next narrative this one is about Trump
Could be doing
Would be
Way better
Horrified
Not good
Absolutely
Was North and South playoff against each other absolutely
2.1 million light years more
Trump's a big old
Those aren't words I have read
He has not read a hundred bucks in it
No but also him
Struggling with Jefferson
Meet
Now as far as the Lincoln are there 100 books about
Self-absorbed
No
As far as
As far as Lincoln
Arresting of judges
Journalist
What was published
Was
A
Fake Proclamation that was
Purportedly signed by Lincoln
Okay so
The journalist then published
That supposedly was said by link
That was so
Porting
The South
So it was basically while they were at War
But such
That it was like
Set out to the rest of the world saying hey
Ditto
So all the things that
When did
Is basically those but you're a newspaper
It was a it was legitimate reason
Read more books
Let's find out
You're so on
Washington
Are you going to a college when the professor the teacher
Go
Interesting
That's unconstitutional
It's in the White House
Who
There is a coup against President Trump
That's why he's racing to cut your taxes
Racing to Trump up the economy of f*** you
I love his his number of books read is very
200 200
Styx
20 of the Civil War
It's the only open 6 of the books
Mention Lake
That could be a Venn diagram situations
Close books might have been also the Civil War Book
Suggest
His focus is on
A president
Civil War
Would you think
But it was a British psyop
It's a British
6th and Lincoln
I'm guessing now
Call me crazy
My thought
Baby the six books that he read on Lincoln
We're not about how Lincoln
Was a great America
They might be
Holocaust
Denier version
Lincoln book
As there are so many of those
Pictures of people who
Think it was uncalled
Constitutional for Lincoln to fight
Civil War
Sure now
That's a really interesting question
If you really wanted to be a dick about it though
Yeah you get into it
Admittedly
If you're looking at the
The situation we're living in
Now I was trying to think that we lost this war
Cuz it sounds really took over didn't that they rose again we left it there
For so long they rose again
Get back to Alec
Area code
What is a teaser
This is a teaser Alex's
Bombshells
No honor next episode
We are going to DeLand
In detail
He's about to talk about here but
Android
Imagine
Next episode
Found the keys to the kingdom
4 degrees and prepare you for a simulation into the corporate board
You do and it's metaphysical
I mean you could
We'll get to it happen
Listen to that our last night
And I was thinking
It's time to get some
Our last
It's not a prey prey on this out
Also I'd like to give the world a little bit
Insight into me
The only thing I've done
My degree
Qualified for jobs
Done Coke
How is it
Said he get some
Things go right for
Wrong read
Yeah I agree
There are so many worth
Degrees
You are a simulator
Did into the board
There plenty of times
Where is button
It's not a difficult
Nobody
It's not a monster thing this is where we get into logic it's just the system that broke.
Logic
A2B
Is a is true
B must be
I believe
It's truth preservation
Yes so you're saying that degrees are worthless
Therefore this
Is a death cult
And that's the problem for us we agree with
Don't agree with me cuz it doesn't lead to be
No that's how it's supposed to work
Your premises
You have to say
Degrees are worthless
And then another thing in order to
Maybe justify the conclusion
I'm so far you've done none of that
So so our problem is that he
That's where we all get into trouble starts with B I love B
Now it's b*******
This one a thing
I bet people would
Sign off on beef
It starts so good
It starts a good
Logical fallacy is starting from the King
Conclusion
It's what people do a lot you already decide what you want to believe and figure out how to
But this clip isn't done
Here's where Alex
Manlet
What are we going to do
It was just his voice and just his is focusing his understanding
Is gravitas
Population by researchers
Is a piece of work
I do agree he's a piece of work
But my tone is very different when I say
Rapport
The three-hour shows
Doesn't want to do that but it's just so good
Bat sucking Dent Riyadh
B**** could not handle 3 hours a day from his weird f******
An addict listen to our next show you exactly why
What
But I want to just have a
3rd grade
To talk into
3 hours of that genre
3 hours
Back and forth in that room
Oh yeah
Hello
23 hours of everyday and that he
Fourth hour of the Alex
For context for or talk about our next episode
3 hours of his life he's got a question
At least
This will all make sense
Or Apollo
Barking dog I love people just like here
Let's remove that mind control take all that away get off
Agape daycare
Grab your company meeting last night the driving home and it was the whole hour
And I got that last night was it with a phone when and was looking to adjust to sleep with
You know I don't have a crush on Rapaport
Sphere loves me
Have fun
But reports awesome
I think he's jerking off to Michael Rapaport
Either
Agweb
Jerking off to John Mighty Aphrodite is a great movie absolutely
No I'm not gay I would never be gay
Jeffrey Campbell
Courage me my love
The meanest fear loves me
My favorite
My favorite beer from never ever again
Macular
I actually don't know what this
Grab bag
I forgotten but it's good
How much fathers love their daughters how much mothers love their sons and vice versa
The species itself against each other
Apposite
Anime
Is there married to a state
Culture of death
Culture life
General
American Dental Association
Associated with bacterium
The inside the armor
My dad has ended
Fluoride
My dad
Super Glue
F******
Started with opening
Seem very
You could talk to the opening that clip right globalist
Found
Skins of buck the globalists our families are important event
But let me tell you something with you know what people agree on
Bacterias bad
Let me give you a toothpaste
My dad
I love it
Smooth f****** transition is just like
Coming out of a break
That was a commercial for that was a commercial break
That's why they can sell there
S*** for free yeah I just do their commercials on the show so it was part of the show
It's up here
I don't know but yeah
You're just selling stuff
During your actual show
Yeah or at least
Let's say I don't know some sort of mouthpiece for the governor
Right
And you use your position as a mouthpiece for the government
To advert
Let's say
The daughter of the president
Clothing line
Yeah that's probably
That's super across is that okay
I'm not okay with it
No
Now if kellyanne Conway kellyanne Conway
Super blue
I would be that would be way more fun
I would find that hilarious
Jordan
Yeah
Might be more honest
To sell North
Scrumptious
My Korean Conway
August
Legitimately admit
He's
Just broadcasting classified information
But he says that's what he's doing
So
But they classify everything I enzymes going to tell you
Where you can take a picture of somebody and run it on your computer
Find person
Picture
What
Facial recognition technology does
Exist
I don't know if you've noticed that but Google
Actually really bad that like they don't do great job
Now they're trying to make that better
Because yeah
I think that is kind of a goal for them
Right if you were if you were shadow
Agency you would want to know everybody's faces that all time
Because as we know we can always
Trust shadowy secret government
Used to have our best in
And also what do you think about the idea that late just saying
Literally illegal
Is that why they have class
Certified material is so you don't share it literally what he just did there is illegal
It's illegal
If if
Don't do we have laws anymore
That is adorable
If that's actually classified information
That was a crime
Now
Here here
I'll just flip one for you
Okay
I shouldn't tell you this
Okay well tell me anyways
Whooping tell me on air
NSA
I think
Nachos
It's classified
I'd like as an organization or
Okay
Information of making up s***
Then it's not really a crime
But if he was just literally spouting
If that was real
It would be classified what
No like you would want to share p
You wouldn't want to share that
You could recognize
Also know I don't think so what border is a g
Jihad
Canada
Flight from Mexico from Sudan
Yeah
Love the place work
All these millions of jihadis
Don't exist
All these millions of July
By the way my
My 80s
Style team
Car wash,
Okay would be
Called
Johari car wash
CIA
Jihad
Jihadi car wash
I like this
Pretty great right women
Headscarves
Bikinis
They're washing cars
Yeah yeah the whole thing
George Soros
Will f****** funny cuz I guarantee
You love swimming through that or that Chinese billionaires trying to overcome
I want to say this
On the show which is lookout for this word
Americana
I really think
Is going to turn in
Into pretty soon
It's going to be a buzzword it's already abuzz
I could be a buzzword for white nationalism
I'm at that sort of thing
It sounds good
He's kind of been a buzzword for
White people doing White
Okay
And then also remember earlier
When he told you that Monday
Story on the Ellipsis
Are we going to get to go to heaven
You're looking at the same thing on the same road together
Also like it Powers also I f****** love the people keep asking
Who asked
Listen to the Paul Stanley album
That lead lead singer of Kiss
Yeah I know is I've never listened to
His own album there's an album of just his face
Pattern about that one
Crazy hour-and-a-half
And it's him
Doing like
Intros to songs God and he
He constantly says people keep asking me
And Alex Jones just did that
You asked you that keep coming up to me
Tasty Alix
My say what
They say Alex
How do you know what Trump
Was going to do
As they were just born
Same thing I'm tapping it
Too bad
It's the spirit
Force of America
Tell each other what to say
As on its face
Prime Aphasia that's why I'm saying
Very good chance
Reince priebus within 3 weeks will be gone
Because
He's clearly the liquor
Before the one that continues the basement undermined the president and say that in the presents like a Lost Child in the White House
All these leagues and Trump's really upset about I know for a fact
Looking for a new Chief establishing to stop right there
We're at the big story
Everybody show
You just gave away the story
So so Monday they're going
To have a big story that is
When this is our
Is that that kind of
Everything is
Still f****** awesome but what
So it doesn't matter
Like literally every day it seems like there's a big story of some crazy s*** happening at the White House
So even if it's not rice priebus is gone
It could be anything and that isn't
Story
But not every day does Alexei I'm not going to tell this story
Tell the story
Actually I feel like I just do that
This Earth
Right
Yeah that's pretty much there is nothing left of teeth
That would be pretty funny Russia
Am I 6 trying to make it look like
Well like how they started the Civil War
Absolutely
We got two more Clips last ago
Aziz next eclipse
On Friday
Alex does a
Long
String of interview
Most of the show is interview
So bad
Like question
Are the interview
Please
Allowed to
Not much
Okay good
Not much I was worried that he would allow other people to
Matt Bracken
Weirdo old military guy Matt Bracken
News
Great
Greek girl names
He is at his terrible he's a bigot
Say that bass
His words
Anything else
Also he has another interview with Jon rappoport
Rich again
Genre
Rapoport
Add to his other interview is with Nigel McGuinness
Who is the guy who started Vice
Has there ever been a good night
VarageSale
Nope
And angels
Yeah I can't go another night
What do you get name Nigel s*** is going to go down the library in on Buffy the Vampire
I don't know I never watched Beth
I probably
Dignity
Anyway Nigel McGuinness
Is on
He says
Some really f***** up things
The first is not as f***** up
I don't like to include in our episodes interview stuff
Because
Just because then we'll take it out of special
Circumstance because of the
The second clip
But the first one
Real Shady
Okay
Fun
Wow
I've never remember the presidency being
So fun
Bond prices
You know what
Okay
Alright
If you were an alien
This would be the most fun president
The ever
If there was no skin in the game
This would be a hilarious press
Also
If you're in
Uncaring
Pretty
Well I assume they're at
It's pretty tough cuz they have no
Recognition of the real world it's pretty tough.
Hear the stories
Of
Ice check
Points
You know do you know what's crazy about that
I I go through all of these
Conservative websites
Because I am
Obsessed with me
I'm sure that I
Every Posse
Me too
And
All of the all of the like
Not even liberal
Just like
Reputable
New sources
Interview
Interview the people
Affected by the
Other Aldi stores
Everytime I go
1 steps
To the right
Any right-wing
Zero interviews
It is all just
Ideologically
This makes
On principle
Exactly
People to you yeah
Course
If you never got any info
Information outside of
Those places
You would think this is the right thing
Thing to do
Because you never have to
To deal with
Yes
But all of these all of these supposedly Christian
Conservative
Really getting to a narrative with them
If you really get them
Any of this
People they would almost immediately changed
Hopefully because they're
If you if you just
Finally f****** wreck
Guys that other people are the same as you
Instead of some weird monster
Instead of some weird other thing
The moment you
Drum duet
Because that's a good point
You'll realize this f****** presidency is
It is fun
It is
God how funny that I wish people still mad I wish I weren't affected by this because this
Chaos is what I would like if I was watching funny to see people scared if I was
If I was watching a
Basketball game
That was basically the corollary to this where it's all chaos
People are punching each other for no reason
Outside of what a basketball Globetrotters game mixed with pro wrestling
Exactly
Like when you're watching theater
If you've been a stand-up for long enough
Suddenly the only thing that be
Really fun
Is when stand-up goes beyond its the other rail
I don't want to see
I like seeing people
Try to become good at
Great stand
But my favorite thing
Is a f****** lunatic
Walking on stage and just letting ships
Fly
The flip side of that is watch
To someone you know
Situation
So it's either chaos from the stage or towards the
Absolutely
I want to see I want to see s***
I've never seen before
And that's what this
Kind of espousing
That's great
Never seen before
Nerves of the world
Not good. Good families are being broken up as we speak
Frankly even the ship we've seen before is usually bad
Not just anybody
Jordan
For this show
And it is in response
That showed
Dear white people
Why
Did you watch that
I want to watch as well
The show
It's good cool
Dear white people
IWatch
The trailer which is all they're worth
Well
If they actually responded to reality that would
If they watch the trailer
Where is all just
Essentially
Don't
Do Whiteface
Generally the
That's not cool
I am not a costume
Basically is the line of
Really good line
Yeah
If you're that you are a costume
No no chondrites
That's where I draw the line Y right
Five so here is
Him
Discussing
This
Nigel McGuinness ends up saying
One of the worst things
Adan
I don't know
I mean Mike.
TV
Gardevoir
Women with an axe to grind
And I don't
Men
That trailer has on YouTube it's something like
It's probably more
Video on the history
YouTube trailers
It doesn't make sense because you found the costumes offensive
In the past 10 years
Every time you
Now I've done a little bit of research on this
It never happened
South the South
It's never happened to the South
I just Googled the north often enough for me to be angry about it
Blackface
Party
College
DAV
Go to reality show
Albright College
Snapchat.
Boy
Start wearing black
There was a whole blackface narrative on the real world Road Rules challenge
Seasons back it was really bizarre
I can't explain it now
It works out really well
Great
Okay
My dear friend
Alright Albright College
September 29th
Pennsylvania
Video October 3rd
What
October 31st
And I was Halloween
Speech
That was also from Halloween
LifeSource coffee costume
That was a different one
Also cause
From the 30
Alright
So that's fine
Text
Spell proposal
Chip video November 14th
Student sorry but denies it was
Diets black
September
16th 2016 all explain how
She had like a facial mask on
Okay like maybe it was a facial
Scrub kind of map
It made her face black
And she posed with four of her friends
And I snapchatted it
With the
The message
Okay now I know what it feels like to be in
No
No that's what she did
Sorry it wasn't I was just in a facial scrub
What what do you said no
Space is not the issue on this one is also the issue
If it comes blackface
When
You use racial
Wrestlers in your Snapchat
Probably not used
Two players if your eraser
Dakota White
Post pictures
September 24th
Imagine
How many look that's
Pics
48 cases
A span of three months
College student
26 * 9
So when he says
It's been six or seven cases in the last 10 years
Well six months
Yeah but I mean
He grew up in the south
Those weren't
Alright Nigel McGuinness or Alex Jones
Who cares
There's a lot of blackface
White people are racist
There's tons of
I want I want to make a joke but I'm all I'm just filled with
F*** it f*** you
Google Earth
It's so easy to find instances of this
Happening
It should never happen
And
When people like
Losing it wasn't racist 35 the Snapchat picture
F*** off
But Nigel
Has more f******
She doesn't realize that what we just talked about
Is the reality
Right so he has more things
That make it way worse
Oh great
It just
Dorm
Alright your leftist
Look at me in the eyes
How great is
Is the plan
To draw a swastika at a Jewish
Great
No one will ever know.
Well there has actually been a couple inches
Senses of that
Large majority are actually
Well of course they're a couple
BB hate I hate math sometimes makes that happen like 2%
Yeah
That's generous crimes are perpetrated by
The victimized class trying to make
The perpetrators
Look where there's a story of a story of a dude who is Mary
320 black woman
He thought she was going to leave him so he
Put all of this like not the like cake
Had a burning cross in the yard going like
Will you leave me because it's scary out there
And it was very obvious
There's like hey you know the kkk's never asked you to
To stay
Here you are
So you leave
Kkk's usually like gold not like
Warning
Yeah they're not big bear
Yeah but
Statistically anything that can happen will happen
The bigger issue is
Does not
Preclude
Us
From really dealing with the actual hate crimes
Do you mean all the hate
Night Airport
Arbitrarily
Halo
But anyway
About it suggest
How Rarity
But that's but that's a whole thing
If you Google the opposite
You can pull up
But you're going to remember the
Uniqua
I just did exact
Play you just started reading off of the list
But you remember the one that here
From the stick
6 months
You remember the one that is the false
Because that's so unique
You would report on that like if you're a newsagents
What would you report on
Stadium
F****** racist s***
That goes on every goddamn day
More swastikas
Painted on New York Subway
Which by the way that video of people
Cleaning the s*** up
All getting together we like f*** you
God that's
Restores your faith
Psyop
Nigel is bad
Just a
Horrible
Nigel bring us home
And here's the other crazy thing
Breakfast isn't effective related to Jim Crow
20% of the
The woman
Edit in in Britain
These people
Jordans that was crazy
Blackface
Is not
It was Reverend
Put all of the all of the all of it
Like all of it
All of it
There's no
Okay
Give me
Give me like you have
At least a very bass understanding
Of race relations
That is a prime
Give me one situation where blackface
Was okay
Ever
Okay
Alright
Because 80% of the time
Reverend so that means that you should
Ativan
Eight of them should be
Okay
Here is what I was going to say
Let's go for what
Let's just start with one
Name what I was on my way to the
And an oil barrel blew up in
Elida show up on set
And we have to adjust
Everybody laughs
Yeah
It look I mean you could always go back to Al Jolson
Right
Cloud Jolson
Is a giant pile of s***
But
Context of the world he lived in
He's not the one
Made it possible for
To be bad
So about 2
Who's your voice
Exactly like Alex Jones right
Do you like to pitch to my products
Let me tell you that let me tell you something about super male vitality
If only I took more of it before today
Also
Like all of it
All of it comes down
To like
What's not real litigate
Right
Who cares
Well I know the history in order to make sure that you don't f******
Certainly
Away
Just add
Okay
Those people
Bad
All the people that I do
Not good
And College
Fat are not
Blackface
To somehow
Celebrate black people are you sure it wasn't Reverend
When she said the
And word in a bunch of different ways
Travel
20%
God
What a bunch of dick
This is Ben
10th
February 10th
This is always a delight
I hate this more than I did earlier
Goodnight
I'd love to know you
You know what
Take it back
Find you
What's mine is wearing blackface
False flag operations
Then there has to be at least one dude doing blackface
So reverently
Hit us up at gmail.com
San Jose nemalion find us on
Twitter
At knowledge underscore Tumblr you can subscribe
To the podcast
Leave a review of a number of stars I made this promise
Reiterate if
You send me a 5-star review
5-star review
And you send me an email
Knowledge fight at gmail.com
I will send
A message
Do Alex Jones
On Twitter
That I would never say to my mother I'll say it again
I'll do that forever and ever
Always I feel like we've been policy
Policy wonk
Yeah we have
Holding
I love your work