Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages and talk a little bit
Search
Would you just listen to assholes talk about Alec
My life
Has been destroyed
No no
Very different levels
Knowledge about
Alex Jones
Not none of the knows nothing
Everything
Blank slate
Tabula rasa
This would be such a weird show if you got
Somebody
Every week who actually knew nothing about Alex I never actually learned like if I had some
Sort of weird Episode II El kabong you
Slapnuts
Very offensive
If you say people over the head with a guitar filled with cocaine
Jeff Jarrett
December 5th
19 episode correct that would be Tuesday this week
But before
Context drop of Alex Jones
Ward Stone
Marble tablets Mueller
I just wanted to say I love you
Wanted to start off with that so the chat room could have a drink
He's on he's on this weird place we was talking about how like
The investigators
Star-gods
To the Liberals
It's a
It's wild
I don't get his tip
I do
How's that
And it's just
Discrediting
In the eyes of his listeners are probably
Blindly following this dumb false god of theirs
The only criticism me really ever has as you are in
He's up to his eyeballs in Russia stuff
It just happens
12 uranium
And bringing it
Investigator
Confiscated
Georgia
Collaborative investigation but
In the United States
Yeah.
You screwed it up
Totally yeah that's totally
Jordan over
There's a lot of bulshit
December 5th episode
Cuz I think if I was going to attack
Wheeler I would go with like
You hang dog punk you know what he looks like
Jesus Christ are you going to discipline me
50s BBQ gift ideas
Let's go to the next hashtag trim
Vice principal Mueller
It's going to stick
I did it
So
Ignore a whole lot
About a 20-minute chunk
One of the first hour
But before we do I want to actually start the episode by going
The end of the Opera
Episode
Or a little bit later in the episode
Is actually
Separate
From what we're going to be going over but it definitely needs to be discussed
This is in the middle of it
Is bringing up some
And not Infowars world
Products that
Not sold on the other side
Fortified supply.com
Bible and camping store
Exclusive Infowars life reseller
Leopard contractually get around
To be able to show you camping supplies
Ariana
Lower prices
So what are you telling us
What do you understand what do you understand from
He's getting around
Map
What was it again
Lagrima
Map Agreements are minimum advertised price
Okay they are contractually
In place for a reason
We'll get to that in a minute
And then he's creating a subsidiary separate from his business
Indeed
But
He just revealed that it is his business
And he's doing it to get around map again
But he says
These people who are supplying the product it's not like I'm doing this in Insidious way they know I'm doing it
That's not
What are you telling us
But also that business out that can't possibly be true
Map of Greece
Okay
Right and I'm like
Alright
Alex
We need you to participate
In this program otherwise we can't allow you to do it
And then Alex comes back with
And they're like
You know what that's
Negotiations I don't know
The suppliers
And see what they think about this
The reason that I bring this up the beginning the show and I want it I want to put a
Focus on this
Map agreement
Exist for
And they are
To assure
Competition
Between different leveled business
So for instance
Alex
As a large
And he can afford
To have lower
Particularly lower-margin Vince a brick-and-mortar store
And in order for them to make what they need
To stay open and pay their employers
Employees
They need to have smaller parts or bigger margins
So Alex Jones
Bye
Getting around map agreement
What you saying is
Everyone is agreed that this is the lowest price we can advertise something for
Because to advertise for lower would be to undercut
People
Who can't advertise booth
Anything Auto
So when he talks about prosperity
And when he talks about the idea of
People having a fair chance
Back small businesses
Absolutely
This admission on his part is
Actively working against
The idea of the free
Fair market
Everything you stand for is undercut by the idea of
Start a second
Subsidiary so I can get around
Agreement
What's Matt's wasn't that an act in
Walmarts near Costco
Take a bath
To start with
In order to push those small business
Out
And then they would raise their prices
Just cuz they don't have any
Competition most likely
I'm not entirely sure what the reasoning behind it is but it makes a lot of sense
Because I can
I should be able to destroy a Prosperity at 12
A lot of Studies have been done about people who infringe on
You've done these studies Alex
Adam study
Every time we do a study on this
It was a study out of Kellogg
Institute
The time
When dried
We describe
What when people
Infringe on
Charge a lower price
What they also do is raise their shipping price
In order to
To stealthily get the
Money that they would have lost right
Expected volume and most people don't know about what the shipping cost
Going to be until it's already too late
Transaction
It's absolutely totally legal
It's good it's very manipulative
Now the other thing
The people found
When they started
These map agreement
People who do not follow them
When they are
Contractually obligated
Right is that
What you end up doing is you end up
Really really hurting your supply
You end up hurting your
Because
There's two there's two prongs two
The first
Is that win
You don't honor the map of Green Bay
Most people do
That people see that that advertised price lower than what they've agreed to
So then everybody starts in competition
Give lower prices
And it's a race to the bottom everyone loses
Everyone who selling these things
End up selling them at much
Lower margin
F****** over people who can't
Keep up
Secondarily what you do is you weren't the manufacturer
Because you create an illusion that their MSRP
The manufacturers
Adjusted retail price
Is actually Piper Inn
Inflated
So when you
I mean
But if you're selling something for let's say
Something cost
This amount in the the
Minimum advertised price
Is here and you're selling
It makes it look like that
First original price
Is ridiculous
It's ridiculous.
We can't
We can't argue that part of what I am trying to say
Is that it no point
I'm have I ever seen
Capitalism
Lead to bad results for everybody involved
Right
I've never seen
Understandable. Talk about the big picture were talking about Alex Jones Act
Oye crime
We don't have any
We don't have his contract so we don't know entirely at the same time he would never bring that up if
He wasn't in a cont
Would bring up getting around map agreements by starting a new retail website if it wasn't something
Who's concerned about unless
He's making it up entirely which case
That's the mint
Two true facts
I've done some research
Oh really
Never heard you say that
Supply.com
Does Alex Jones's new subsidiary
And I went in
Found and hunt hunt
All of the
Website
And double-check
The prices
To see what they were selling
Some interesting things
Did he
What do you mean
Essentials
The private label deal if he wants
To let safe
Super blue
Is Tom's of Maine
Private labeled
Stop putting your business out of Tom's of Maine cost
$10
Private label
It doesn't really matter Tom's of Maine
Because they get the wholesale price no matter what
And it doesn't hurt Tom's Maine's bottom-line or anybody else
Who's selling Tom
GameStop
Because you're not supposed to know that that's Tom's of Maine
So if you're selling a super Blue 48 that shouldn't affect
At all times
But unfortunately it.
Well if it's a licensing
No matter how much you sell it
All you doing is that a smart move because then they don't
I have to worry about advertising or any
Private labels
None of these instances that I'm about to bring up our private label.
Check the specs on them and made sure they were and everything and
So how much does the under what's the largest amount
Almost nothing
Now the here's where it gets f***** nothing is discounted
Yeah okay
Weird anomalies that I found
But I think are worth bringing up
Infowars product
And they're sold
Literally
0 differ
Would you expect
But there are some that you know that have like sale price
Original price
Infowars products
Also
Exactly the same
There's a company called
Citizen armor
Which cells like
Backpacks
Bug out bag
Their prices are all exactly the same that you can find on
Citizen armor.
There is no discount
Android BBM going to be dry
Something along the lines of Judge Dredd
The read
Next Pixar movie
The next Pixar
Alright
Walking around talking
My car is better
Now that is a very dark move
That's that
Those two
From what I can tell Sid
Citizen armor might be a newer
Yeah so there might be something where
Ledge sport
This is a new supplier that Alex
Yep
They sell like camping gear
I don't I don't think I saw any
Like ID actual time
But there's a lot of like sleeping bags
And stuff like that
Anxiety
Sort of interesting describe
The first is there is a river river is the type of
If you can go in a river called River
Leather made from River Phoenix
River feather-light there's a bunch of lines of bags cat
Zero degree sleeping bag
On both
Website
As the original
It's marked down to
249 99
On ledge
Sports markdown 259
Running forward
So he's selling it a worst this
Yeah so that's an instance where he's not trying to
To get any
Any better deals
There's just way too much of it I can scroll around
But go to a Sportster
Plus
Degree bag
Through 59
On live sports 5999 on it
Infowars
No discount
Actually probably cheaper
On the other one
Featherlite
Plus
Sleeping bag
Is 5499
Unless sport
Inexplicably
Awning for Wars
No I mean Mark nope makes
Make sense from there because there's
Because they're not the the wholesaler
Durex
Sales they have to go through their own
Overhead and they have to go through their own markup there
Based on with Alex Jones
I'm just pitching this
Because I have an independence
Subsidiary
All of these are not the cheapest prices
He hasn't he sells heirloom organic
On the on the on there
I mean who doesn't
Microgreens
Complete kit it's $99 on a
Infowars
Microgreens
5999 on Infowars
It's
Heirloom Organics
See that's that's
Like this because you're going you're going to something to Alex Jones in advertising
Yet I would argue is possible
To yourself and will charge extra
Is not how Alex Jones
Resent
What he's doing
See you it was lying about the map
Right
Why would you
Pick something so
Specific to lie about
Here's what I say we have the lowest prices
Here's where it.
About that why would you lie about cheating up
Well because I think he is
Okay so now we're getting back
We'll get to that in a second
So
There's a chance that if you go through a breakup
This episode of Price is Right going on right now
If you go through checkout
But when you put it into your bundle it would be
Because that is allowed
You can have an advertised price
That is $200 and then you put it in your cart
Something like that
That's weagles Tremont
Cam charge
Can advertise your charger
So conceivably
Any of these prices could be
Live
Or whatever
But does it matter
Here is where it's f***** up
Once once Alex Jones is stores aren't open and honest with me
Who knows all bets are I understand we're boring the s*** out of people with a bunch of price.
Get through what I've one more supplier that I got very serious
So there
He sells Harvest Right
Freeze dryer
I assume those are sex
They're very large
Things you can put food in and I'll give you like dried apples out of it or something like that
You know what that I think we all actually probably need to
Start shopping
Like the world is gone
It's almost like
On this one
I've got a
Can't afford it
He was the greatest of the
Just never going to be able to afford the upon
Webst a the greatest disparate amount that we've
Prices are wrong
All of them
They don't match it all there's no Rhyme or Reason to them
In terms of the actual price or the sale price
Matching on
425 Supply or on Harbor Freights website
Okay
On
Fortified Supply Infowars website
Yeah it cost
3145 dollars in 50
50 Cent
Markstown
Okay okay
So now
On I
Harvest rights website
For the sale
Markdown
From 34
The difference
Is
He's charging
$300 more
Then they charge on their web
And the markdown price
But he's pretending
To have marked down from
He's also $1,500 higher
Yeah it's an artificially inflated
Right which is not what
Heritage
Harvest
The Heritage Foundation is actually the
Find Harvest right.com vet he's offering a much bigger discount than he is
Might be what he's talkin
In a very
Specific way
As though
Listeners know what a map agreement is and they're like
Check this out
This guy knows even how to screw over regular folks
Discuss pricing
What was that again
The point of it is everything that you can buy on Infowars
Short of Infowars own product
You can find for cheaper elsewhere
Text cheaper elsewhere
Find out what the active ingredient
Basically
He's pretending that he's going we need to get the word out
And also it mean Italian
There's a second reason why you started
Subsidiary if this isn't
Okay there's something else you hiding money or something like that there's some other reason why
You've created this whole other website
GameStop
Alabama couple of other things
Add inflated or non discount
Then I don't know what that is yet but I'm going to look at
Furthermore
Should not have taken
Jesus Christ
Squarespace site
Let's get
To the show
Okay
So today
Probably
Might be
She might still have a steak and Infowars
Start a new LLC
I've heard all that all that might be
Started newswars
Adult
Noel
Something happened on
That
Or maybe it happen
In a couple days but
Israel map
You know he's in a weird
Headspace and
He's going to spend
The rest of our episodes
Screaming about
I'm stuff
Of course
No I think he does later in the show but it's not part of our episode
This is everyone's favorite
This is something that we've got to experience a couple times in
In the past
We have are types of Alec
Text that we love esoteric Alex
The drunk Alex
This is another version of Alex
That we all can Revel in and enjoy
Interrupting a video clip hours
We saw a man if that's on the drinking game we're all going to die alright with the Brian stelter
Sure thing
Keith Olbermann about six words
This might be worse
Interrupt the Alex
The morning Joe Edition
New World Order
Dead on Arrival
Mika brzezinski's father
Open multiple bus
Not really
Joe Scarborough
Mysterious left Congress
After a young
Intern was found
She just fell over here whatever
Investigation
First I in church
Worded
Investigation of individual
Compromise
Background
That's all right about how
Call who absolutely have nothing to do with him and are very uncivil to him and I'm sure that there won't be any mate
Open up on the level right now
Everybody around him
Subsequently registered agent
Switch it over to find out who has committed sexual assaults and then he realized that he was a rapist
Cowboy
Like I often think about how greatest
Sitcom Alex would make
If we didn't live in the world because I like
Donaire then getting off Aaron
I'm just being like that's my bush
Bored
A butt
We're going to get more into his specific complaints about Mika and Joe and before we do I would like to be fully clear
Peekaboo f*** off we're going to set the record straight on
Some things that Alex Jones but at the same time
Mika and Joe have
Very very serious
Royals playing right now
They did a lot of normalize
Champagne
They're now going like
Oh we were probably
Response
Possibility they're just doubling back
Almost pretending like they didn't have
Kissing sycophantic
To the election
So they can f****** fly a kite terrible
Yeah.
Look at these Democrats committing crimes it's like watching
Fist fight between a Nazi and apartheid apology
Spotify
Whoever whoever lives
So that sort of opening volley
Clip
I believe in this next
Egyptian to actually starting
The Clippers
Morning Joe
And I cut out nothing
This is just like magic clip
Is the
Maybe
Two-and-a-half segments of his show half an hour 45 minutes
Alright I didn't leave the
Will be an amazing punchline
Movable hamburger
Scarborough
In his businesses in his
System
Golf courses in his hotel
Braava 380t
He's keeping
And the news is closing and they're all going to jail
Very long time
Is up on infowars.com right now
From the same swamp monsters
Going
And going
When they're the ones that are in bed with the Russians on every front the Democrats
Of the cliff
Weather breaking
So I can start the clip up yet
You know this is all stuff we've kind of talked about already
I don't I don't feel the need to dive into that too much
Understand his analysis
I know you are but what am I
Confusing to me
Because it doesn't
Like a can't hold no like shouldn't be trying to figure out a new angle
Nobody needs a flensing West blower just came out was like Flint
Will definitely get rid of all those directions for you illegally
There's no doubt he committed the crime
I really think it's a dumb thing to Bang a Drum about when
Someone erroneously report something
And then
Appropriate action
You know like that's not that's a bad example
That's a bad example of fake news cuz even Joy Behar
The beginning of this week came on The View and said
Look we got that wrong you know we had a bad report that was delivered
Alex later in this episode plays plays the apology and is like
Look at this
Look at this fake apology
Qliktech notice attraction
Apologies are still retract
Like even if they're not
The stuff
So let's not let's get to this year
Don't think about on how quickly he interrupts
I'm going to go with three words Alex
Three words
Alright let's
I'm going to interrupt myself it's a while
You have to play for a while
That's weilong
Like you you promised something and you did not deliver
Scarborough when he even on Alexa
Position
To know
What Trump was thinking around
My time cuz he was
Interviewing him
Yeah that point
Until right around then
That Trump started talk about I'll make his face
I don't know I don't know if that's necessarily the truth
I would imagine
Joe Scarborough
About money
What Barack Obama
Is he going to be
I can make even more money
But the news is typing
This is just like all the very same people
On television
Hillary
All of those things are true though during the campaign
Mika
Game on air
Someone from Hillary's
Had vaguely threatened
Her because of things
She said on air
So
The idea that during the campaign they were saying Trump could never win
Spiritually
Disingenuous
And Alex knows that
Did you ever read a shattered
The book about Hillary
Like I during the whole thing
These reporters got full access to
Because they were like
Going to be a celebratory book
And her campaign was f****** bananas
Terrifically bad
I buy everything about
Like normal
Like the
When you just said that
I was I was like probably
We could probably made that up and then I read shattered and I was like
Concerned about the truth or falsity of it I'm concerned about them
Like where Joe and Mika
More what I was getting at is where they were.
Observe
Right
Donald Trump
Just fly
President campaign stops today
Why was he screaming and yelling and they will win
You're a fraud
And you're the people that have had ejected
Spirit
Almost where
You're a loser
So real quick before we continue as he's about to
Get back to the clip things that just came out today I was reading was that
Alaska
But they had numbers for whatever papers
So the amount of stuff that we're buying from
Overseas
As regular vagina
Yeah that's not good
Let's get back to it
Yeah we can talk about
The stock market numbers
Absolutely
But that's because
That's because the stock market has
Completely divorce itself from the reality of our economy which is
The issue
That's why we have so many booms and busts.
That's why we have
Come Boom for a while there
Because
It had nothing to do with reality
What's a deregulate
Did the stock market
Again Reagan
You f****** pile of s*** I hope you get
Alzheimer's again
I hope you
Come back to life
And then are born
With Alzheimer
A disease
And have to live out your 88 year
The point being
Because they deregulated and they allowed so much
Speculation I did
Have a
Separation
And other one regular
They wound up
Creating this
All about
Wedding
It's a it's a
Of course
Raise the stock
Market everybody
Bedding
That it's going to crash
Eventually
Nobody's betting on
When do and so that's why we're getting a
Queen is over 10,000
It's going to be 5 in 2 years
Aunt hands
The other thing is
I mean the stock market is continue to go up
Bad but especially after that
But it's also like out
If you look at it
Before then
Sharper
After that but it's more or less
Kind of expect
And so like that's more indicative of recovery
Growth
If that's what we start
FEI we have aspectek
That's the kind of thing you got to be really worried
Because that's not like it's never going to have the stock market at
So anyway if you're if the stock market goes up and the homeless population goes up
Something's not going
Let's go back to the club.
So we shall
Under the microscope
There is nothing there is no collusion
Charge people for years ago that wasn't even legal
National Security advisor
Or launch a contraction
Right right
But also crashing the sanctions
Narrative is there with Flynn they've invited him because there is a
You can have
FBI agent
Right right if your
Praetorian guard
No
Of some FBI agents
Spending like pro-hillary text
The messages
Stuff like that handle handle
His narrative is that the people were spying
And these phone calls is reasonable because
It's the Russian Ambassador that they're spying on him at least
Husband had a warrant right it's so Alex is claiming
What is FBI agent pocket of Hillary
Is making these claims
The only thing they have to go on is his note
AZ fall FBI investigations and interviews aren't recorded
You go to a local Precinct they record truck in Everett
Like
Any any kind of corruption that could happen you got to have backup that's
Stupid
Pro Hillary FBI agent
Do you like oh that's because I got these notes
Now
Alex Lin was
Triple deep-cover FBI Hillary age
The whole time he was like
I'm going to plead guilty eventually
Alex's
I would wait until I can't
Alex really
Needs to look into the FBI agent
Stuff to let's say Giuliani
The Patriot
Can do whatever they want because they're doing
They're doing
Them right
This whole thing about the possibility of Erik Prince
Creating C
Some sort of intelligence
Organization
You know what I'm fine with it
I'm not
Cuz Eric Prince is a f****** idiot
If they did if they allow air
Prince to create a deep state bulshit
I'm fine with that
No cuz it's going to lead to a lot of murders
Yeah
Tulare
Yeah I already sent it to fascism
Interrupted Village Quebec
Andres Truitt
You're exactly right
Just like Joy Behar
Father
Create another subsidiary to avoid
Right
If you watch the video of it
Can see him constantly looking off camera as if
I think what he's doing is he's checking the how long till commercial
Like to see like
How much how long is
It really it really really breaks the illusion that he actually means what he says
Worked up
3 minutes
F***
So you get back to
The what's gotten them where they are right now Josh
A gross misunderstanding
Of Washington
Washington public service
I think it's going to go on forever
Nothing you do will ever
Michael Steele
Here's your eviction notice out of our lives
It makes me so angry
What are the rules of History I don't know because he's not
This literally reminds me of The Daily Show segment even Steven
No Steve Carell and Stephen Colbert with debates
You play visit this video
Mika and Joe
You're a loser
You guys are an idiot anyway
Trump doesn't know the rules
Race memory
Right that's how you learn
Should I forgot I don't know
That's a good ruler
They're up to something
Right that's enough
Right
Watch a white after Labor Day
That's a good ruler
What is that what the rules about
When is Labor Day
Don't know
What is white can't wear white
He doesn't really elaborate on the road that we don't get to learn what those are
I'm so here's the next one next clip he comes back from the commercial break and we'll see
See I will see where he's at
Build a wall against hard for me to play this clip and not get angry
Bad Liars they are
What what
On ER
Washed up
How Washington works
All these are mummies up there
He just wants money
Established
Ouija City Ariel
Let's go back to the discussion
Option care
Her dad was a famous Criminal
Not really
You misread my book.
Operation
Our Lives
I pray
For justice
So I mean that's a load up a clip
I don't really know or care what they are
Navigations God
You might get what you want
Migrate
I think that's I think that's my main issue with is there's no collusion there's no none of that stuff
Because like we have been
Think about there's nowhere to go
When
It happen
Like there's nowhere for him to go he can't just say
Whoops
Fadoodle I was wrong the whole time
Yeah yeah it's a dangerous position for him to be another property
Because
Of his documented at least
Year-and-a-half long Association
Rodger Stone
Constant I talked
The Trump stuff
When all this breaks
Says it will
There's really no way for him to plead ignorance about anything
You can't incriminate him
Himself and being a part of this
To do is
Do you know this is our duly elected
Caesar is he calls
Great great love it
That's the only place to go and then
Dangerous place to go
The only play
I hope it's
Deescalate
It's possible but I just
Based on
What we see of the all right
And the people
And how unfairly they play in
How they use
Faith very intentionally
I don't see I don't see a situation where things get
Escalated I just via getting worse point where
Sing with Nazis like
Never-ending fascination of World War II
Is a
Unilateral bag
Like the guys committing a holocaust
There's no negotiation
There's no nothing right you have to fight and kill them
So we're getting with our homegrown right where it's like you guys
Unequivocally bad but simultaneously
Influence by anything else so we're getting to the point where
Simultaneously though as that
Sort of reality is
Is happening
Most people are paying
Attention to it
You have them and their immediate
Channels and it there
Yeah they're doing
The exact same
Same thing to Muslim
Right so they're creating an unequivocal Superbad guy
I meant pedophiles to but that's sort of in service of demonizing Muslim
They love their own pet
They left a good pet for fear of them
We need the Japanese to bomb Pearl Harbor
I think that's what's really
Yep
Volkswagen
Globalist
Exactly it's the
Assailable Ironclad logico psychosis
Whatever whatever thing you think could bring people together
Like let's say
Cuz we're coming
Piece of evidence
Is eventually going to fall
Probably is already
Discovered in just not public
Look at this point
Collusion on a massive
Food scale
And it's not necessarily
Doesn't even matter
Like he should already be impeached
He is literally broken the concert
Doesn't matter
Make money off of being
News flag
Justin
The cookie the cookie
That's true
You wasn't an alpha like Trump standing up to this pissant globalist attack
You can't
Because
Walser
The duchenne all the time you don't understand
The Constitution every amendments that's the 30
Has been unconstitutional
Right under common law if you're a sovereign citizen
That's true
And I think you should
Still be able to own slaves
As you should
Every libertarian has to believe you should be able to every Admiral
Going to restart the cliff
So let's go back to the
Let's restart the club
Text Anna rupnow
You know
But it was all
What Barack Obama
Can do it
Office it's 70 the oldest president ever elected
Dementia
Before except for George Washington
The founder
He was not
Joe Scarborough
And they're sitting there saying about Trump
They didn't get ready American English
Swamp creatures
What are swamp creatures
Cool he's going to
Why can't
Stop starting
He could just
Play no cuz he wants to see what do you know
We talked about this over and over again
Alex Jones comedian
Stylings is get every f****** drop out of it at work
And a rabid dog when he gets
Today's old clip in his mouth he has to take out Rachel over
You had so much nothing to go over on this show
This was from like what December 2nd Tuesday I believe it was on Scarborough maybe at the
The Friday of last week
I don't think
I'm not entirely sure
To give a date
I can't figure that out
Analysis
I have never watched that show
Judging by what we're listen
The shity show
Interesting at all
You know he didn't even do the thing
And the other guys like
It would be more interesting
To me if they turned it into a Shakespearean sort of what
That would be more interesting like really trying to deal with like
We had a role to play in this
That sort of thing
If they turned Morning Joe into like a Greek tragedy
That would be amazing
That would be
So great
All life is
Subway
Don't like what is my light is he going to be thanking everyday how can I leverage this
I can make you the more money
How do I leverage this down for 15 years on television
Information
And everybody saying is about
Him
So what's good
But that's not
That's not real
That's not reality Frozen opportunist
Piece of s***
We do have an issue with the revolving door between
Washington and the private sector and lobbyists and all of that yet
Not
Jewelry
It's the
It look
Obama's going to make
So much more
Then he did while he
Who is president
He wasn't using the office of
The presidency to make butter
He's leveraged
Is not necessarily like a huge.
Distinction to me
Really really sad
It is a big deal
But I want to talk more about this idea that Joe Scarborough killed it
I think that's
Cuz he's now brought it up twice and it is time for us
This is about a lady named Lori
Klausutis
She was 28 years old
She was an intern at
Joe Scarborough's office
Florida
She died
From
Related
Earlier In that clip
He's going to talk more
Right
She had an irregularity in
In her heart
They caused her to
To pass out
And when she passed out she hit her head on a desk
Now
The medical examiner is that
She would have died whether she hit her head on the desk for most likely
Because of the timing
That's the blunt force trauma did end up killing her but
The government aneurysm
Arrhythmia
Beat beating of her heart.
Flared up
It doesn't even have to be diagnosed before real I mean
People who are otherwise healthy
Was even like a she would run like four and eight cases and stuff like that
And it is
That doesn't
Meme oh she ran a bunch so why would her heart like it's not
Cover-up yeah totally
Like to present the idea
She was hit in the head with
She was murdered
The medical examiner is
It's been very clear about
But that's not possible
Based on the way her head trauma will have
You get
Hit by some
Like it before in the head
What ends up happening is you will have
Like a Bruisin matoma or whatever you'll have
Damage on the same side of your head
Because your head will go along with
However the hit Co
The foreign agent
Pastor register retroarch
But if you fall and hit the stationary object
What will happen is you'll have a mark on this side externally
And you'll have bruising on your brain on the other side
Because your head will stop
Motion
Your head is going in One Direction and The inertia will cause your brain
I hit the side of your head
In die in hurricane
So for really make this argument
Throw her head onto the deck
Maybe
Maybe just Joe Scarborough
Put her head in a
Advice
And then head that way
It would look like it was reasonable for her to
Don't you know that Scarborough famously had vices all over his office
Lights
The other the other piece of it too is just like the the heart condition
It's very clear you can tell that from a post like a post-mortem
Autopsy
Her heart stopped beating before
Send it before.
Indicate to you this is an arrhythmia that caused her to pass
Also two witnesses have said that
She was feeling
Weird or ill that day
Right underlying thing
Slayer.
Whenever whenever he tells one out related to Scarborough one of them was just her mail carrier
He pulls out
The heart rate
And then notices that it's not beating is like dude you got to get
Checked out
Scarborough was in Washington
Florida author
Spell
Have you seen the Press
Just got rehearsal
Okay
Anyway
Just garbage intelligent
This is a real tragedy
Outplex the present also
There was
Yeah it didn't get a lot of press coverage
I can tell you exactly why
It happened
2 months before 9
The web investigations were ongoing Joe Scarborough committed 911
Other things happened around the same time that Gary was being accused of murdering Chandra Levy
She also didn't
A couple of interns
Ford representative
Just the two and Gary condit's one was way creepier and
Much more definitely murder
This one was very much an accident
That was really strange but there was an investigation
Determined
Unsolved mystery and why didn't they ever do an investigation
He is literally just a mirroring things that
That are not true
It's absolutely not true
Still have a note on her
Call Larry Nichols
But also still
F*** Joe Scarborough
Scarborough
Murder exactly
Alex said we're going back to the club look at back
Illusion
Oh by the way the Trump campaign
Colluded with Israel Israel
What is also illegal
Oz referencing Hughes
Assad
Russia and the good people in our military
Which everybody
Because it's so
Seriously trip has never said that
Because it's nonsense
But Alex is
Pretending
Estimating R Us
Narrative
Piece of the Flint
Madison Ave
You are literally up
Call me
Call worship each other they're all involved incredible corruption and collusion with Russia
Immediately Russian Ridge record
Is going to change that trash
No that's true I appreciate the apology
How long do you think it's going to take him to interrupt again
6 seconds
Just got done ready
Credibly
About
Incredibly unselfish where
Nailed it in your writing
Have you seen how your
How you're a laughing stock joke
Susan
I pulled up the most recent rating
From adweek for the month of November
What's going on
MSNBC
Has
MSNBC managed to accomplish a feat this past month that its Rivals could not
It delivered audio
It's growth from the presidential
So no wait
They
I have more ratings than they did during the election
Didn't think it might have something to do with
A reverse election going on
President is no longer present
In November 2017 MSNBC
It would be lovely if it did
Progressive
Right right that's a little I'm reading from the text not at a time
Receive
+ 26
Percent in total primetime.
10 + 4% in primetime
Demo
It was also plus 28% in total day viewers
And plus 7%
Demo
Versus November 20th
So that's big
That that's pretty f****** what you talked about in the demo
That's adults 25 years old
54 which is what
Marketers
Interview as the most
Call
Disposable income
The network was once again led by Rachel Maddow
The top Progressive voice on cable news posted year-over-year audience
Growth
Defeated timeslot rival Sean Hannity
Advertiser-friendly 1:35
54 demographic
I don't care I don't care either but it's literally the
It is because even Fox News viewers are starting to get like
Why are you guys talking about The Only Thing Worth
Why are you telling us a story about
Whatever Tucker Carlson had for dinner
Guys
Present committed crimes at least
At least lie about it right now doing that
Think about it
PC ratings
There was Morning Joe
Not only did Joe and Mika finish ahead of new day
Are there
But they delivered the most-watched month ever on the network in
Give me 6 to 9 a.m. slot
Averaging 1.1 million total viewers
Gross gross but it's
Totally spot
Totally the opposite of what Alex says
Yeah they're great
F*** off
It's not as good ratings as a fox
Some friends or whatever but that's not going to
Be well
Morning racism
Finger guns
Those are
Maybe the dumbest people on the play
French people
Staggering and there's two
They're so bad at what they
Have no chemistry whatsoever
Anyway let's get back
It's like watching a
PK movie
Without the commentary just watching that just going like
Who wrote
This is so
Poorly written producer
Don't you guys have somebody
Alright
Under the microscope every movie
For Shepherd
Every person ever
Condos being harassed one that got 25 years and
Well
You accidentally just brought up a couple things there in Florida
To presenting it as
There's
Trump's golf members
But I am also fine with that are the ideas of people are paying for access to him at the club
Tri-State business
At a private club that he charges membership
What they're talking about the ideas by condo sales
There are multiple a instant
That you can look into
People who have mysteriously bought condos way above Market
Price
My mom sold them
2 years later
People with MS
Mysterious ties
To Russian mobs and what have you
Is that the international money-laundering
A really small at the big
You know
Kind of
Is harassing golf members and people in condos
I mean it
Technically accurate but it's actually unfair so
Jail for working with turkey
Microscope and you're so powerful would your little Mueller
God your unelected preacher that you bet everything on
Powerful
And you're just waking them up so keep doing what you're doing you are
Seems like that was
Heart but again
Democrats and Republicans
Thought maybe you guys have all collectively fail this to an extent so we can agree and disagree
Simultaneously
And we can move along
Cuz I was said
You got to restart
You know
I bet
Also you should apologize
She's a family in Jesus name. Just some prop for you to use
What do you think this is Sandy Hook
Scarborough
Someone else's
Tragic death
Glasses like his head looks f***** up that's soft but I'd accept
Really
What is Soto
Terrible about Alex
Beyond
The lying it's lying
Cursive cruelty
But he's a really really cruel person
You could make better points
Probably get further with his argument
If you would
Go with Subs
But it wouldn't allow him to be
Be cruel
And because
You love being cruel
You've got a throw-in
Bash that girls had in
Okay
Ocean's 11 types
All right here's what we're going to do
Alex has to go to court or
Court-ordered therapy
Be right as part of his
Divorce out anymore but ye did for a bed probably over
His therapist
Then
You
Standing as a replacement therapy
Give him the psychopath test
Break the you know and you're not beholding to the doctor paper towel
Write up
Then we released that he is because
A f****** course
We don't need to do that we don't even need to call Mueller
Just listen to this show is a f******
Psychopath
Alex apologize for that interruption
Let's get back to the clip
A good long while
All about the money
Tell her what you got her hat on
And show us the birth certificate
Mr.joe
.
Nice try to come up with an insult
Also I think he's planning on killing
Is going to go today was Lori klausutis
You can look that up you can find it
Joe Scarborough
18 years ago
Right I would imagine
Trump
Basically
Being part of a nun
Solved mystery
Remember it was fairly recently but he's brought up
Psycho Joe and stuff like that
They stop playing ball with him or whatever childhood played out in public
But be that as it may
You know what I have a really good reason why Joe Scarborough would not
Decency
Cuz he's addressed it already
There wasn't investigations
16 years ago when it happened
Any idea of him now bringing it up and being like
Her name was Lori klausutis
Kill her and you can look at the proper block friends disrespectful to her f****** fan
Yeah the idea that you would bring that up into the public
Spirit
Runs the risk of
3 traumatizing
A grieving family
Who's moved on
With their lives
But it's still something that would
Do you want to see your daughter being uses
The political
5 chip
Can be just thrown around
I'm guessing it's not fun
That's got to be
Terrible
Child but you
28 years old
You don't expect to lose your daughter to a tragic accident
Safety
Cuz if
Joe Scarborough brings up her name
Deathreats that families get
F***** over
What happened to Seth rich
His family or any of the families of Sandy Hook
It's not real
Not appropriate
Yeah
If somebody died at Infowars yeah that would be an
In the same way there is one anyone
Endive
You probably would have killed them
Probably
Solid 6042
That's it
Important
This be distinct
Language
Because that implies
That implies with someone
Did something
And a rhythmic heartbeat
Ended up making her pass out
Mitigating her head on a desk
That is
Not your head bashed in
Yeah that's f***** up
I mean she had her heart broken
Certainly
Let's move on
Alex would not restart
Alex's
Respect respect
I can make even more money
I think they're shocked
Under the microscope
White.
Thundercat
The rules of Washington
Side effects
And colored by the show North bywood Alex
Thinking
Banking
People in Washington
Which is dumb
Local Yocal
That what this show is you heard the music coming on
And that's why Alex hasn't
Interrupted
Set the clock to break
Is that what Morning Joe is Tara
Let's get today
Like they're doing what we're doing
But for a million billion dollars
Basically
They're married you know that weekend Joe got married
We got married within like the last year
We're having an affair for quite a while to the last
And then get opportunity
Washington d.c.
Listen to anybody
They stumbled into one possible crime after another possible crime
So the black commercial along with it
Keep drinking
I think I'm the second one
Scumbag
Congressional investigation is
Is just another public Feud
Go she ate through
Savvy PR
It's the FBI one
That might matter right
Let's not Rosie
The next clip
Is Alexandra doing a post-mortem
Cuz he's done interrupt
You've got through 35/42
Did it three times
Postmortem
Thursday
You really think if
Going to say make a
Is this is right after
Is it RuPaul
Show coming up
Gives a fake apology
Topology
So you cannot make this stuff up
Representing that even to talk about a metaphorical news of the investigation
But they're like all they want
That's you
We should have our own Morning Show
They're all going to jail
That why
National combine
Tricom
Jacobs
Borders
Savage
How do you even get rid of silverfish
And then they sit there
The daughter of a famous
Evil Lizard
You got
Morning show up there
So all of that stuff is
True
I mean you can save Joe Scarborough's a joke that's fine
Everything you saying about the big new Brzezinski is misrepresenting his writing
What did he
What
When you bring it
URI Geller
Original Wizard
Vdi
Diadora
Mariza magician
Jhandu was the guy he was the guy who originally okay he had the big long beard he was the guy who
The archetype
Yeah exactly
I didn't
I didn't get the reference
I apologize
Like I don't think John Dewey
My dad
Is the right name
I didn't get the reference
He's talking about Sovereign really talk about is the idea of
Cooperation
In a meaningful way
About the UN
Control
Blah blah blah blah blah
But he's really talking about is we don't have the right to
Baby cruel anymore
Cuz we talked about the UN dictating the terms of immigration
Stuff like that
And how the US just pulled out of that
One of the reasons that that existed was
Because
There are millions
The people in Warsaw
Country is in
What were the victims of genocide
He does not mean sovereignty over
Are countryhumans sovereignty over the rest
To the world and when I do know about sovereignty for our country but it's never a paw
Positive sovereign
Because Alex
Trump would like to think
We just need more
Control
To be able to be better
See the thing is we don't like the idea of the UN dictating
You know that you should take this many immigrants in like
These are the regions where people are in Peril and what have you
Don't want to be told that
They like to present the idea of like we're going to get rid of this
We're going to get rid of all these regulations and then we're going to do even better for you
Cleaner because
You know we have an incentive
Either really talking about
Is the sovereign
F*** off to everybody and we don't care we want you to die
The sovereignty that is being defended in
Protected by Alex
And that's not my sovereign
My sovereignty does not play that
The government that hashtag
Is the power to do
Things that help everybody
I'm saved people
And ideally resolve
Have not done a great job of that
Slow cook today even
He's going to recognize Jerusalem the capital of Israel
We're moving well into parody
This is like we're moving beyond whatever why would you do that why would you do that now
Kind of idiot would tell a sovereign
Sovereignty
No
It's going to just surreal doesn't even really want their capital
Do you know what the
No even though f****** Netanyahu publicly is like
This is a great decision but I'm sure privately
F******
We don't need this right
Not right now are you shiting me
It's a lot of trouble
Stupid it's amazing
What you're doing is your
Prescribing a lot of people to a very miserable
Because when you do that what you're doing is you are.
Wyckoff
What you're doing is
Depriving
Palestinians of a lot of legitimate
Existence
Life right right
To live anywhere and the claims that they have dual ownership
Roseville
Did Lance
Settlements
You will embolden
Encroaching on
What is going to be the end result
That's the sovereignty
Desired by a mallet
And that's not good
That's not good for the world
No it's terrible and it's not good
Bristol still here in safe
Israel shouldn't exist
Cuz that's not right either
It it shouldn't be an apartheid state it's not the like
What they're doing is wrong that doesn't mean the reverse is right
Very
But this is a non-zero-sum game
I never said treating it like there's only a winner or loser
And that's why we're Trump is a winner you're a loser
Do you think they're like
Is there an argument to be made
That this is a purely religious
Oran
Whoever whomever three exact
Cuz there's no there's no foreign policy where in this is improving our relations with
Anybody
I think you could make the argument
Services of belligerent religious bulshit decision I think I think you could make that argument but I think there will probably be
Some people who with
Like have a foreign policy
Position that would say it
I just agree with them but I think that there's some people
Hoodsite
This place
Has been you know it's been too long that it's been a source of conflict
Better to burn it down
Continue like this
Could light a fire under it and
You know what the
There's going to be a lot of people who get burned but
So you're you're
Interpretation
Can of that
Okay
I don't know I'm not I'm not saying that is what motivated me
Be somebody
Somebody's arguments
Yeah let's start some
Or less I mean it's like
Building a lot of problems engine
Knock it down
BrightStar
Was trying to fix the problem like in the movie
What was arrogant
But it was flyover country
DC
So many Trump Towers in Iowa
Out-of-towner
Stanley change map to New York
And kick butt
And turned around in the witnesses
A collection of garbage like that
Alex
Trump's New York
His dad was born
In the Bronx
Yeah they came out
Was born in
New York weather Frederick Trump
I mean if you want to go to a literal
I feel like
You know
Denying black people the ability to live in your buildings
Screwing over everybody that
Contractors
You know going bankrupt over and over and over again
Having your daddy Bailey
Chicken
Becoming a
Reality TV show business
Lying about being a billionaire when in reality your finances are almost certainly trololol
Being a frontman
I think those are all the literal interpretation
But right totally so Trump's Dad was born in the Bronx New York
Trump's father
Trump's grandfather
Frederick Trump was born in
At a fairly early Elias
The f****** German
At a fairly early age
I believe it
1617 or so after he
Children and family
The family had
Bavaria
But Frederick has deemed
To work
Wasn't so he became
You got an apprenticeship at a barber
Shop
And it's 16 or so he ran off to the United States
He said
But he agreed with his mother that he's
You should go to America
However years later family members said that he
Departed secretly at night
And left his mother
A note which is interesting because
Built into that whole thing
The time
Vicki was
And became an apprentice
His father died
And he left a family in severe debt with medical
Abandoned his mother
And claimed we made an agreement to go to the United States
So he came over to United States came over to New York
Making a bunch of erroneous claims on Gold Rush Lanzar West
And started
Ever further back
Liar
Racist piece of s*** liar
Started like prostitution
Yeah it was
CERN depressed
Make claims on land
AMC Woodfield
Stuff on the lamps build like a like a housing
In order to
Cheap minors
These people will be minding their need somewhere to stay until you charge them
And on the off-chance
They found gold he would have
Place the claim of ownership on all the rare or not to be
Think it might not have held up
Displacing people who were in The Gold Rush
And she'll like that sucks
But
Just all the way back he did all that and then he moved to New York
1C struck it rich
Please f****** scam
I meant so
The trumps have lived in New York ever since that right that's
Is family didn't come into New York
Can kick butt these people out west
And then move to New York
And started abusing system
That they've been Frederick at
Been abusing already
Move what do you talk about a guy move from Bavaria
Like what year wheat
Remove to Bavarian.
Team left Bavaria
Trump
I am not entirely sure I would
Save it is probably in the neighborhood of a
Okay so
Patch
Time machine
Kill that
Turn on one time travel trip
Better idea
Yeah
Kill Frederick Trump
Do all the things he do
Good person
Super-rich in Prospect
Super billionaire
Immoral
And not
To kick black people out of homes
Exactly
That sucks
Kill Hitler
Hot bulshit
You know
Take a little trip
Live It Up
Salad Days
About 35
A friend
And Morning Joe
Take a turn from Lord from
You are garbage
Sure you arrogant narcissist
You are self
Play gentlemen Washington
French
Your senses are off
Strong strong
They're both like horrible footlong tapeworms
And there just aren't
Syphilis
Currently can't hurt like
Destroyed
Okay
Gas committed
They are
No manners
Biggest slide
Idiot
I can't think of anybody else
You know what I think I'm going to make contact with some of those folks to get the full dope on you guys
She thinks she's better than everybody
Apology
If you want to wage war against the globalist infowarsstore.com
360 win win win win win
So that point he launches into like a 10-minute sales pitch for the new fortified supply.com
Cars Patriot Point
Or you can
Points towards future purchases or so he's not really clear on what it mean
But yeah that's that at pivot
That's the payoff
That's that's
40 minutes
Interrupting
Even we were getting super bored because one of our favorites
Joe Scarborough
I don't want to listen to
So you got that for 40 minutes and then
Store
Perfect that's the plan
Anyway let's wrap this up
I was hoping you did
And start from
Alright guy
I found out that Alex Jones
Poor baby
Does
I don't think
Isaac
I'd like to formally apologize
How long that took up top
Anyway you can check out our website where we follow
We do that knowledge my.com agreements
We follow standardized Globes
Podcast
Atlas's
Love them haters
Oh
Pandora
Dollartree.com find out about
Our hatred of atlases
Inexplicably
Yep knowledge underscore fight
You could go to iTunes
Strudel auto option
What you could do it
Start a prostitution then sure you do that go to Seattle in the 19 or the 1900
You could subscribe your podcast
You can leave a review tell your friends
Now you can't do that
Yeah if you tell your friends that violates our map of Greece
Minimum advertising people
I just think there's one guy who maybe doesn't even know what a map to
Restart it restart it
AccuWeather podcast
It's okay if you don't understand
Alright go f*** yourself
Alexandra Thurston color