I love your work
I'd like to sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit
If you were going to sell somebody on the show you wouldn't just be like
You're the worst yes 100 hist
Naruto
Paneer like
Nah f*** you I know what I was doing
Space station middle finger
By 3
Amen Chicago
The middle finger to the or we would like to ram
I'm giving the middle finger
Space command spider leadership middle finger right there
We don't even have a middle finger
Now you got a middle leg
Star one truth
Larry 21st and 22nd episodes 2016
Okay it was January 21st
What's wrong time it is not we are in December
Trip into the past
We're coming up on about a year of doing the show we probably probably have another week or so after this
Love you two weeks
Bumblebee out of town for Christmas I believe
You son-of-a-b**** my brother
Hey there will be out of that
Play a computer and be like
What do we do
What the f***
Typically what are we doing
But I wanted to I wanted to take a second because it's easy to get caught up in how terrible things are in a
Another world
Is a Mastiff
I was thinking scary
Agreed
Separate second step back in and really
I think we need to recognize a Vic
Did we have
I believe
We've done
I believe that we've gotten to the bottom of Alex Jones
Like not the big picture but in terms of trump
I really think
But we have explored this in a way that no other organization has done
Completed
A remarkable feat of Journalism
Redundant
Yeah the redundancies kind of reinforced
Episode
I'll bring a full-circle
I think
I didn't think a year ago when we started this to like
You're the one in 11 months will sit down and we'll have a pretty
Pretty good handle on what
And I think we do
It's pretty clear spiders
Absolutely
Spiders
I'm getting uncomfortable even in this moment because I'm saying positive stuff about us
Also you should not be saying us
You did a great job you're you're giving me
Credit for journalistic activities way off
A couple of our listeners also have been very collaborative
In terms of finding things out
Bouncing ideas off of
Sell yourself short
Thank you
But I think
I don't feel a ton of
Not into
Interest isn't the right word
I don't see what ton of curiosity about Alex Jones and Donald Trump
Where is when we started that was something that really motivated
Mystery that we need to solve
And to the extent that we've been able to figure out that
Alex Jones
Had
A
Underlying Allegiant
That existed
Before Donald Trump ever got involved victim of an influencer
Campaign we're in Russian Bots and play the traffic
I'm confused
Right and at the same time Rodger Stone
Steve pieczenik
We're lying to
Manipulating
With
Friendly narratives
To get him to join up
The whole story
Really I think
What's what's big stuff like that fear
You have exactly the concoction that you need
To get him into the position he's in now
And it's not really all that interesting
To me anymore
Trying to sit down and think
Think about like
What can be
You know what is as we go into year 2
I don't know exactly what shape that's going to
And granted when we started the show
It was a couple months before we started getting it
I don't feel a ton of pressure but I think one of the things I'm going to do is I'm going to do
Much more work on Alex's
Is primary sources
Okay I believe that one of the one of the guiding principles of your two is going to
To be debunking
The things that he
He uses as
The
What would you take Keystone's and his ark
Yes the way stones that we've used before that he keeps going back to Auburn.
Penguin
You're talking about Robert David Steals and not even that cuz that goes crazy
I will actually say that another thing I'm going to be doing in year 2
He's getting much more in-depth about the
Contributors
Yeah people like Robert about the Nation of Islam
My point is I guess I don't know what I'm doing but I don't know what I'm saying but I wanted
Your point is we're having a production meeting as we speak or Alex production meeting
Victory I believe
In terms of
Sorting out Alex Jones's Journey 2
Lower my glass
In recognition of a New Journey to come
And I'm not sure exactly what it's going to be but it'll be something devastating
Thank you so now it's 26
Bilbo Baggins eleventy hundred
May 11th
From blow it could be like that thing from the window is
Yes January
Alex Jones
Brookshire
Alex has already switched over to Trump
In the middle to end of December of 2015
Rodger stone is shown up as more frequent contributor
And Alex has said as much as
It's Trump or die
And he's drifted away from politics
Text a little bit
He's drifted into some alot more of his cultural narratives
And stuff like that
The end of January
Little bit of trouble
And
And that way I don't interrupt you and frustrate you
So I'm going to get there before you start the transition
That's what I've learned over this 11 months
Do you think
And just like from what we know
Has Rodger Stone ever gotten drunk
And tried to make his Richard
Nixon tattoo talk to people yes
Of course right that wasn't like he's moved his shoulders
Tried to make its mouth
Right I mean the things that I started to learn about Rodger Stone
Taken is red implied that
It's insane to think that he was
I don't judge him for being a libertine or anything like that but like
Which
What was what was out there
There's no way you can try to make a tattoo
Next question
He got fired from a campaign was Reagan
Because
He got caught
Trying to solicit a well-hung to swing with him and his wife in a newspaper
I feel like that's not an issue I don't care if you did I don't do what you want to do
He said that it wasn't him it's someone else's prank and then later
Own up to but you know what I'm saying
Second Quest
Have you read Harry Potter and the Sorcerer
So the climax of Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone
Has us discovering that Voldemort
Has been living inside of Professor
His head is like out the back
His head right so the face in front
I get what you're trying to say here is Richard Nixon still alive
In the tattoos
Relevant
M5 Road
Maybe four I don't remember the one where the carnival comes around
My girl can make prophetic tattoos on people
Was reasonable anyway let's start with an out-of-context drop
Inside
Weber
We know after I'm dead
He's going to go swim.
Discrete episodes
Buy a bolt of lightning
Died
Rosegal
Fly
Saliva every
Episodes that are very distinct
In character
The first episode is full of
Graphic live
And the second episode January 22nd
Impersonal
21st
Very specific narrative that I think he exposes himself on
Real hard
The confrontation of a caller
Interesting breakdown to do there
Who's got to start always chronologically no jumping around
Mix up Alex's words and make him seem like he's saying something you didn't say
Except for data projects.
Where to start with China Wok
Start with a
January 21st
6000 super class in the world
This is I just give you some context Alex 6000
He said this
Yeah he said that he believes that the ranks of the globalist thereabouts
6000 globalist Witness
Is what you're saying only 6,000 going to get home
They think they're on a higher level than they actually are
It's going to get worse
Rothschild
And then say they have half the wealth of the planet
Can you do
The numbers I forget was it
000000000000
Still mathematically
Cut that Walton app
Batman
Divide that number 6,000
Percentage point to 1%
Are the people that own a big boat at the harbor
They're the folks that build company
Just like
Now they're down to about a third of what they were in the 50s
Daniel
Percentage
So
I don't
I think this was going to make you really mad
Frustrating word problem in geometry
Like that's what I'm really struggling with
If 6000 people are on a train going from the global Empire to f****** America how many
Give them will ruin the Renaissance
He's talking about
Bright
Instinct
You know what Alex's
Vista
Like the fifties it's is the 50's oldies did the Billionaire's have only shot up
He's right that the middle class
Rolls let's say have dwindled people
Your f****** world could make the argument that the middle class
Realistically has shrunk
But you can't really say that the upper class has
Shrunk there's more
Consolidation
Nintendo
This 1%
Urners
Learners heavy quotation the first against the wall when the revolution
But that's not you have a boat Alex
Boat
Good routes has multiple reference
The Renaissance
People who are other examples are like
They have
Haircut
Stuff like that
The rest of us can't put her kid
School no
To be considered in one
Percent
Millions of dollars
But that's not middle class
He likes to present those like if you make $100,000 a year in the 1%
Where is the cutoff far away from that as you might imagine
It's in the million
I don't think 1%
Something like that
Like because
Like Millions suggest to me like
Larger than
Will the difficulty to comes into like net worth vs
Is fluid worth
Accessible capital
But be that as it may. It's not people who are like
Just have a good job and get their haircut that's not
The issue
He's conflating all sorts of things brilliant
Say
Because then your listeners
If you go
Put people put their kids
Is there school in
They're like well
I do that
So I'm in the top 14
Right
I want policies that support the top 1%
Tuesday are and then you discover no I have been for the past 40
Thousand f****** yeah it's kind of a fun shell game
In some ways but
Sing to me anytime
Someone is like no no no no no
No no
Those really rich people
There's a Renaissance
Every f****** little piece of lifeblood out of this goddamn Planet they
They can before they suck
Die and leave the rest
So Alex is a lot of thoughts about like
The times being better in the past
Yeah but it's real fun to remember that right now
Do you have no Roy Moore
Probably going to win this week
Haven't come out and literally said times were better in slavery days
Like you know
Just making
What's up text
Ultimate ultimate truths of
Trump's election is just
Why were we talked with Mike
Subtlety is
Has to be like
Counterculture
The race
Some extent I know just take bravery to be an out-and-out racist
You should die in public eyebrow to evolve them
So here I ears is measured of
Here's where Alex Jones Harkens back to the past again
In a very weird way
America's Best Picture
Mary Tyler Moore
Young and devastating
But I digress
Do you take pictures of
Mary Tyler Moore and put them up next to pictures of Lee Ann McAdoo
If there's any pretty similar look in the two of them
They have they have a lot of facial similarities
Okay so
It's interesting I'm going to go I'm going to go off the picture that is on the only picture I've ever seen of Lee Ann McAdoo
Is the one that you actually
They just posted on on the website
Let me tell you something
There's one huge difference between Mary Tyler Moore
Bringing her up in a hot woman licking the middle of his politically
His political shows
It leads me to believe there's literally no way he's never made a pass
Lexi looks a lot like Mary Tyler Moore Tyler Moore
And then just
Right
No black people
Describe all the happiness of all the goodness
We've all been taught to fight with each other
I would like to pay women were on the right
This very important clarification
The entire storyline of Mary Tyler Moore with bio crazy it is but a woman
That was what they work together to figure out what the f*** was going wrong with women being allowed to work
Bewitched the entire story is about
Slave
B12
Domestically
I apologize for my
Compute my God what a great looking woman
Still
Illusion
We have all these regulations
We got screwed over was not trusting the system
Is the government
We all remember those great Nick at Nite TV Land episodes where they question
Government
Mary Tyler Moore was got to get this fluoride out of the water
You do remember how
Military subplot in it
Stupid
Those shows are the most Americana
Those are shows of the most reinforcing of the status quo
Clear Asus Limoges
To the extent that it was about a woman going out on her own and
You know having a job in a male-dominated atmosphere
There's still a ton of
Is wet wood
Some of it done
Who played for
Affect but at the same time
Ivan wellpet night
Never have been a character
In Illinois
About
God's country
However far away from Rockford
And before the show started
One of the people in the crowd was sitting at the bar crowd I say
7 people who sitting at the bar with his girlfriend or wife or whatever the f*** it was company for scrap
Devereux
There is a lady, who neither get punched in the mouth
Sure any like okay great I hope you get
Murdered
I don't care you're the worst
That guy
It's 2017 that's the problem
Guns
Especially not comedy problems
I don't like these jokes to punch that lady
We're living in
So this point where Alex's harking back to an imaginary past
Existing misrepresented
He jumps over to
An interesting narrative that he throws around a lot
Really taking the time to get into so we
We shall now
What about Alex's favorite animal
The try cops
We need to be angry we need to be upset we need to be in the system space thing we know you're criminals
Negotiate
There have been global
North American Union and other
Global confab
Agree to give China
Where is minerals worldwide that's why they get 90%
Google
So whenever Alex's Google it that's my cue to look into something cuz you clearly lying about
Yeah so one of the things that's actually really interesting is that Alex
In the past
Was correcting its updated statistic but there was a time and fairly recent memory were
China was responsible for
Heather hand in 97
Percent of rare earth minerals
Sales
The mark
Rare Earth minerals
They only had can
Control over something
To the tune of 30% of the world's rarest men
There are mines in California Australia
All over the
But the issue is
Those
Mine
We're not
Feasible
We could very easily get our own Rare Earth minerals
From you know in California other places
Well that that is
It's so f******
King hard
To get rare earth minerals
And I don't understand it so then why would you call them
They're not that rare baby, it's a misnomer slightly overweight or because of
The difficulty
And getting wonderful
It's just that there
Want to get it out and make
Commutable they become rich
But also the
Razee polluting
It's
Stanley polluting
And for the last couple decades
China has much laxer environmental standards
For their businesses
As we
Came into the Modern Age and the
EPA got strengthened underneath Clinton underneath bush
All destroyed prosperity
Write all of the president
Have
You know boosted EPA that it's until currently it became a thing where it was just not
Feasible
It wasn't worth it China was producing these things in a way that was environmentally unsound but they produce
Such a way that we could buy all we need
It was no big deal
Let me explain to you hear this is from an article in Gizmodo
Where they get into the extraction of rare earth minerals
I'm going to read you
How you hack
Have to get them out of the Earth
Is going to be riveting
The first step in extracting rare-earth oxides from the surrounding rock is
Across the rocks and grind them into a fine powder
This is passed through a series of time
Where the Rare Earth elements float to the top
Aren't you read this in the voice of like the Discovery Channel's how get made
Unwanted minerals picture the bottom
Hazardous waste material called
Healing is Santa ponsa
For storage
Meanwhile the results
Concentrate a rare earth metal is roasted in Kilns and then dissolve
The fraction of the results
Wash that contains Rare Earth
In the form of mixed metal oxide
Is removed
Finally a solvent is neutralized
The reaction generates a lot of salt
When the
In California was running at full capacity in the 9th
It produced as much as 800
50 gallons of
Salty Wastewater every minute
Everyday of the
This waste was contained I also contain
Radioactive
Thorium and uranium
Which collected a scale inside the pipe
Deliver water to evaporate
Tampons 11 miles away
Several times in the 1990
Cleaning operation
Temperature remove the built-up scale cause the pipeline to
Worst spelling hundreds of thousands of gallons of hazardous waste
The desert
The state of California I ordered Molycorp
Which was the oil company
Molycorp Molycorp
Molycorp
They were really Malik
I would say so so they were ordered to clean up the white
In 2002 the company already struggling to make a profit ran out of space to store
And failed to secure a permit to build a new Storage Post
The mine shut down
It's just
Ratably
Hard
So what you just described to me
Even worse than fracking in the
Keystone Pipeline
More like that you're saying that it's impossible to get all this s*** without killing all of that s***
That's basically what you described
So now this weather
In 2010
In September of 2010
There came on.
The China has control
Almost all the trade
Of these Rare Earth minerals
Uno from Trump's policies
Monopolies are great
Will it work out well for everybody
No but also
Minerals are needed for component
And a lot of electronics
Some military hardware and stuff like that
There was a maritime like nickel and gold are some of the best things to put inside
That's why so many phones
Rare Earth minerals
More like you don't know the name
I had a list pulled up
I know those it's not Metals you ever heard of okay
Death metal
Stuff like that.
Pittsburgh Kelly
Dispute in September 2010
Beautiful
Japan
The captain of a Chinese fishing
Controller which it collided with
Do Japanese coastguard
China responded by announcing
All shipments of rare Earth elements
The Japan
We use the imported Metals in Federal Heights
So they used it like a big dick
Right
Japan immediately release the Chinese fishing
Captain fin York Times
Declare that it was a humiliating Retreat for Tokyo
This point everybody started to get really scared
About the idea of the China Canal flout any rules
And the issue became
If we wanted to start extracting from
California or from the other countries that are much more friendly Ministry
The first
We would pollute the environment we pollute the environment
The report from the government accountability office born to quote
Rebuilding the u.s. rare earth supply chain may take up to 50
Azzurro became a thing where like
F*** China has this
Massive
Weapon against us and Alex thinks that
The case right
It's not
And there's a number of read
It didn't work out
This whole
It was going to be able to
Restricted Supply in cut off all rare Earth elements to everywhere
Aegis
It hasn't materialized
They haven't made these threats
And even the blockhead and
Japan wooden
The word for a number of reasons
The first
Is it there's tons of small mining Corporation
Companies within China that aren't controlled by the state
That are operating fairly illegally
XSport
Currently 20000 of 30,000
Tons of rare earth minerals every year
Which would be enough
For the United States to cover all of the things that they need
Further
We really don't
Much of it
And we have a bunch of
We've already bought
Ever bright bright
We can recycle it affect
We just don't
Like if every time you got a new phone
You recycled your own phone
Right that is
A new phone
Like that is how much of that rare earth metal and mineral
Kind of stuff that we need it only takes a few grams of
This metal called Neo Diner
Daimyo
Oh I know that one realtor in order to have all you need for the phone
It's a very very very small amount even when you
Consider the number of phones
It's really not that much whenever people
It's absolutely true
Be alright
Come on now
Stop it
So beyond
In in the wake
Of the 2010
Standoff
If you want even call it that with Japan companies like Molly Coors
Division magnet
Started looking into
Play Lightning McQueen
They started to find ways to make the same product without using Rare Earth minerals and there was a bunch
To go down even without
I'll buy this really
A lot of times if you limit
Resources necessary to make some
The necessity of making it
Requires an innovation
Yeah and that will
On average
Work out eventually
And then also just
A bunch of other people
Countries like
South Africa
Malaysia
They've started
Doing very
Environmentally unfriendly
Mining in order unfriendly if Kazakhstan makes the list
Stan is in that list
It's not going to be good for the environment so I did point in 2017 the power of and the
Percentage
Just not 97
Anymore
And not giving any context into why did it get to that point I what has happened
2010 mentality
But the Chinese are going to just say f*** it you guys don't get any rares battles anymore there's nothing we can do
Lose
The Embargo
Rat is
Completely empty
It's nonsense
So there's that
Alex is dumb
Anyway let's talk more about how trying to suck
Explorer
In a US company
The federal government sues them
Nachos
You think they're just setting up internal regulations
Thousands of precision
Economic front
While using
K
The only
2000 in Congress
Our last smelting plant closed
Bullets
Thank God so we'll never get him now
China doesn't really own the Panama Canal but they bought some
Ports around
On the sides
Aren't we well
I'm not sure if we do on the Panama Canal Panama Canal but I know we're not
Supposed to
Not anymore
There was no supposed to give up
Yeah we're supposed to give up control of it I meant
I feel like I remember reading news
Yeah we were
America
Here's an article from
Place called the Trump
About this
For more than 100 years, canals control the bulk Goods transferred from the Pacific to Italy
For most of that history this Monumental feat of engineering was under the control of the United
But this is no longer the case
In May Panama's largest port
Buy a Chinese cup
He called lambridge
Margarita Island port on
Canal's Atlantics
Side offers a company
Intimate access to one of the most
Important goods
Distribution centers in the world
While promising to upgrade
The ailing Panama facilities
It offered more trade with America's
East Coast
There is substantial reason to hesitate
Critical
And it isn't just in the dangers of the
I'm shutting it down
That's
Absurd nobody would
Nobody would do
It would be first of all economic
There's literally no reason to do that
This company assigned a
100 million-dollar deals
The control Panama's Marg
They bought it
Too little for something
You know could be worse
In the billions
Definition
Whoever sold it
And I don't really care
Now
Do the issue with the end there
Alex is telling us
That we can't even create bullets
Azrael
That's really sad
Where will we get our bullets
I pulled up
For company
Very easy
Google search
That's Del America
Handmade bullet
Redding reloading, Redding
Dash
Reloading.com
You go to their website they have a very large made in the USA
The bottom of the page
Paper IO and on the top of the page and their Banner
Made in the USA
Vector bullets
Is another one right here as soon as you open up the website Vector bullets.com made in the USA
Prominently displayed
On the on the thing
You got another one here precision ammunition.com
They are located out of
Charleston South Carolina
That's their contact in
Information if you go
Into their about us page about how all of their bullets
Created in-house
At their facility before you before I want I just want more I want more
Shop
Gorb
They're about me page probably
You're still in America
Can family-owned-and-operated business
We had Corbin understand your needs
Krauts
I've lost it and
Paragraphs
But Gerald
And what have you
Here is
Another one another one
Freedom ammunitions.com
Freedom ammunition
Is proud to offer high-quality doing remanufactured
Ammunition utilizing
The highest grade
Available
And a big old made in America
There's even pictures of them making the ammunition at their warehouse
Whatever
Freedom Munitions ammo is loaded on the ammo load mark x and Markel
We make these in house
Here is my hair is my defense
To Alice
On this one
If his
If his argument is that
It is a lead smelting issue
Simply because the bullets are made in America does not know
Sarah Lemay
Raw material
From America
Are you glad I brought that up
Alright 2014
This is absolutely
A chimney
What do you say chain email
I say
Grandma
Yep there's at the American public by the Obama crowd
Last Blood smelting plant gone
The email goes on to Protection Agency
Mental Protection Agency
Clever for shutting down the
Smelting plant calling it a backdoor gun control result in the cost of bullets or in
This is in reference to a place called The Doe Run
Let's melting
Implant Missouri
And that's another rare
Percolate Herculaneum
Missourians don't pronounce it that way.
I can't even imagine how they twang that s*** up
Then a good territory
Missouri
This was the last
But smelting
Implant
In the United
Okay and it did close
During the Obama
Ministration but it is
That the EPA actually had any
Because EPA made a bunch of
Complaints
And they find them a bit
They fixed up the stuff they needed to fix up right and then a couple years later they
There's no indication necessarily that
You know that they needed to
Shut down because of you
EPA
I could just be like this is
Viable
Anymore
The issue is
80% of all lead produced in the United
For vehicle battery
Stationary bike
Now
The Doe Run smelter
Google Map
So
Did Alex doesn't deal with the reality of the
Is Doerun smelting
They closed down there
Mary
What can what
Or
And turns it into metal
Right
Barry
Polluting
It is very
Softly
Taking or intern
Sentimental
What is much cheaper
And not as pollutant
Is a secondary smell
Takes batteries
Recycle them
Are you saying that recycling is cheaper and effective a company is still running using their secondary smelter
And a lot of them I still do exist
A bunch of this is
You know
In the US the recycle rate of these batteries is a proxy
Making ledbass batteries them
Highly recycled consumer product
Presiding estate
These batteries are recycled at secondary LED smelters
We own such a smelter in southern Missouri
In our previous fact-checked
Is it from PolitiFact
Doerun spokesman Tammy Sankey
Like that
Tammy's aunt told us that the company Supply rmo customers using secondary light
Which is great
So Alex is narratives are completely bust
You know but it's effective
You're only make the goodballet out of
The primary let you know don't cut it with battery bulshit
You got to get it straight from the ground
They check back in with Spanky
Again
Because
This this is in reference to Fat Albert's friends right
Is our primary sponsor did close but we are still supplying ammo customers through our secondaries
We do know the primary light is still being imported to the United States but we don't know if it's
Specific to ammunition suppliers
There are many other uses of lead
The idea that China own
Are you somehow going to
Threaten us through the Panama Canal was not
Monopoly on Rare Earth minerals
And somehow that's a threat is none
The idea that we don't make bullets in America
Is f****** stupid and based off a chain email
He's so dumb
Is amazing
He's almost as
This is where I
So excited
When things like this happen I like
Call Ron
This is why we do the show
Alright so here's the next Clipper Alex says something today thanks to our
Investigation of 2015
Come out
And responded to Glenn back who's constantly attacking him
You did
Spent the better part of six months
So here's the next one where Alex gets really hypocritical about his feelings about Trump
As of the beginning of 2016
Something fundamental
Because it's not just like
I've decided I like him
Retconning all of the Patrat
But District
Do you want to be the guy that's to turn around
Airplane shooting mer
They're going to pull out the stops
So
That's what anybody just for fun let's go back to
July 3rd 2015
Palisades houses 4013
Lisa is this Donald Trump
I'm just a front man
For some
And
They go in there
This is mind-blowing I don't know what to say
So let's get to this other clip from July 12th 2015
Is your issue
But Donald Trump owns a bunch of casinos
Frontman
More Democrats or Republicans
You can bet I haven't
Interested I would hate for the globalist to call him a copy of dawn
Do not call him
Aiden
Don Trump they would never hold back
Why did you leave these shows up
What mystery I want to get to the bottom of Pi restlessness a lot
You know what if it's same thing
Nothing he says means anything at all
One wouldn't count on an enemy like me
Who would
Listen back
So that's one thing he doesn't he doesn't superhero to counteract his supervillain
Like the movie Unbreakable Dan your Bruce Willis
I'm okay with that but you'd be played by
Be careful
So the thing of the other thing I think you are you really
Jordans
So
He's banking on his the same thing he does when
How do you say is like go read this book go Google it
To see what I said
So crazy
Just to become
Completely
Literally contradicting yourself Within
In the span of six
Like yeah what is he
Bus route
Contradicted your route
The globalists are going
Talking mafia guy six months earlier
I have from high-level sources
Or
Is Alex
The secret global
Today you never know
Controlled opposition Dan
So Alex Jones
It's down to be
Man talking about some War
About Mulan
Yeah let's do that
People are really getting
Culture you just say no it's over
Unless I get a full prison bread in Russia
Real quick before he gets
He doesn't actually
Developing
His feelings on it
What is an article about
Guy who got poisoned with polonium
The guy who was clearly a hit
Bible apps
There's no Nicholas come out that never do anything like that
There's a dozen articles come out from UK intelligence
Services
Investigation
There's a really good chance
Will signed off on me
There's a 100% chance
With 100% certainty
Of course
Abdou standards of practice
Not even not even like it doesn't need for him to have signed off on it somebody told him that news like f*** you
That's the article that he's talking about
New responses
I don't see any evidence that it is every country's
To kill off their own secret agent that's not how that works then like I don't know
There's a 50% chance Russia that they
There's no at there's no analysis there's
Nothing at all
It's just
People
Getting it now
Like
We hear him say like
People are people are really starting to get it
Right
Portway
David
But for now let's see how the rest of this clip plays out where he's at
Idea of the story about
Conflict towards War
Roar
I don't
Really
Bring you the best products
Because he brags about himself a lot so that one could have been
Cuz I feel like people are really getting it now whenever and activities going to happen
Sing because he like that ad.
Do you like
I bought my gray matter in my butt
Like
Couldn't have been a like I do it to get all the truth to you
It's it's a nefarious pivot anyways pretty strong
After all I'm still like
There's no way this is
This disgraceful
At this point in January
The point
Blood in the Water Crisis
Was at a point
That even Alex could not
Ignore yeah everybody was
Thank God everybody's finally paid attention to it
And really gotten
The bottom of it
Antenna Flashpoint
Alex couldn't
Decided to talk about
I left out a lot of
This because it's not
Right but I will give you the
Three bullet points
First f*** Michael Moore
This is the city's problem
No
Why we talk about this
Everyone got fluoride
Interesting narrative
That's really comprehensive
Like he gets to old
To get to use all of the buffalo buffalo
People who are dying
I have left
This clipping because I think it's probably the most important
The most demonstrative of Alex Jones
And I should say this is while he's on the phone with Lee Ann McAdoo
She went and did some field
She is in Flint but he
You keep saying that
Cold for her
Is not how that work
Is Leanne talk to some people
Really a big issue was like I do not want you to say that on there
At one point and the it just deteriorates into a plug
Cuz she's like you know I'm glad I got my total cleanse out here to got it
Drink water out here
A little while to get her hair to fall out
I don't know what
Does that mean that when she takes it
22 Hornet
The world
Yeah absolutely
Well now I kind of want to
Super female vitality
I'd like report
Yes
Michigan I have my
I want to fuc
There we go thanks Leon back to the studio Alex
So here's Alex's Alex's interrupting
At this point
And given what
Point really is
Honorable Jen
Onomatopoeia
Very important
Black America
Henry Ford
Then the mafia movie organized crime Union
And they took it over and that's just as far as I'm concerned and I talked to michiganders are great people
Detroit and plant aren't part of the ship
Wonderful no
Sagging pants feeding off their people
And this is what
Hope you die Alex
So I hope you got all your hair falls out I hope your f******
Can fingernails bleed for the rest
F****** life are you shiting me
I love people with f
Interesting
In fact that you can find about
These two communities but he's deemed not apart
Of Michigan
You think there's a least
Susan Michigan dancer Michigan as a whole
80 point
Percent White
Barry White is 41.2% black
Let me ask you a question
Where would that 14-point
2% pecans
Detroit
It is 12.3% white
81 points
Percent black how they do I don't either also in
In Flint
The racial makeup of the city according
Consensus was 53 point
3%
African American
41.1%
That white
So even that
Damn chili
Outside of the norm
A Michigan
Yorktown's like
Ann Arbor
Is there a heavier white concentration
I'll be goddamned
If it didn't have anything
Things to do with the white flight era
And everybody who lived in the city being afraid of black people so they moved out to
To the goddamn suburbs and rural
F****** live
If you want to look at it
Even closer analysis
You'll find that the average median
Per capita income
Detroit is a good $8,000
The year less
The entirety of Michigan
Well that's because the uni
Sanders because
Thug
Crime bosses of all been busted up lunch
Pinpoint
Point stick
Percent higher incidence
People living
Below the poverty line
In Detroit then there is
Entirety
I'm not entirely sure how I'm sorry
26 point
4% of the population
Implant is under the poverty line including
37.4 of those
Under the age of eight
So
Two things that were taught
When when Alex wants
To save the Detroit
Aren't part of Michigan
That's cold
That's not anything other than
Boy these places are anomalous and how black they are
Right
Pretend like
When the Germans in the polls
And Zachary for date.
It was mainly the German
All the Germans are the poles left
And now I hate
Definitely wasn't
A f****** Nazi he wasn't involved in
Protocol
Berkel protocols
So
That's disgraceful
So I find it
Very
Disgusting
Considering what we now know
Year later
About that
Fertility problems that have come from the lab
Poison ivy
It's such a 1 x 1 of Alex Jones
The big narratives is
You don't really care about blacks
Fertility that Ma
That's probably why
Big deal
Scoring points on a
Like I don't have a clip
Swear to you he doesn't
He's talking about any like
Water filter
F*** you utilize in people
Suffering in order to
Sell your products to sell snake oil products
All his products I think the water filtration
Probably the best
Like there is a place for
For water filtration in the world
It's maybe not the biggest emergence
For most people
Compared to the real red pill
I would take a water filter
In my day
Yeah but it didn't have Alex Jones's f******
Space Oddity
If you do so
You could get angry at water everywhere
Throat across the room
I just
Believe
It's so obvious and its soldiers
Disheartening
That we all know
How big of an issue Flint
No no
That's an issue that we could for real thick
Like of all the things that we could fix
That's one
Wood
It would cost money
It would be hard but
Think about how we could f****** fix it and it's not
And think about what's lost by Nas
Like that was a direct result of those f****** assholes being like well we need to keep
Detroit from going break bankrupt
We need to divert our Waters
Reply to this
Different place we need a f*** over everybody
And then we're going to lie about it
For four years
Could f****** fix it and we
We just want
I think I'd write my own and
Still trying to recover
And we know that this is an issue
But it's just one of so many f****** issues it's so hard to care about everything
Has issues
Or at least what
This triggers in a lot of people who could help
Is a Samsung
Ego
Or Samsung
Pride
But I think there's a
Piece of eclair
You know it's
People be like that's not play the blame game
You don't need to do that
Right
It's like a prosecutor would be held accountable until they never fixed
Problem
Secutor who put away an innocent man
And everybody knows they're Innocent but the process
Sakura has to constantly be like
No no we got the right guy we got the right guy I definitely
The death has really quick to because this episode we're recording this on Sunday
Come out on Monday
Getting off the Flint
Turn back on to church
I want to get a prediction about an Alex Jones narrative
The other day
It came out that one of the judges
MB
Ninth circuit
Alex Kozinski
Has serial sexual harasser
Other kind of harass
Just a piece of s*** all are abusive
Type of guy
You know it is an allegation
Lady who wrote about it
Seems very believable
I have no reason to disbelieve
Fight
Quartering
100% believer
What I want to make a prediction about
Alex is going to
Use that
As
Ammo against the night circus
He hates them so much
Because they've outlawed American flag shirts
At schools and stuff like that yeah
No
We know that he will not a chance I bet he doesn't hate the nights you hate
You been yelling about this forever anyway
Buddylove sexual harassment
True but any chance
He could have
To attack the night circus
You going to take
And he's intellectually inconsistent
Believable degree
That's true I'm just I'm just laying my bed
There's a 50% chance
And that's all I'm sorry I don't I don't I think you're wrong going on red or black hair and I'm going to pick black
I hope you're
No I don't hope you're right cuz either way it's a fuk narrative
Resume
If I'm right
I looked it up he had nothing to do with that.
He wasn't on the panel of Judges that Alex Jones talked about with the ninth circuit court and was not involved
Completely irrelevant
To any value
Narrative so preemptively that
I think where I think we are
At the point now with
Public
Accusations of sexual
The people who are coming
Forward
And the people who are accused
If you're accused
You're guilty until proven
At this point
I don't comfortable with that but I don't disagree
Exactly exactly
It's almost impossible to
Proven negative
Chances of false accusation
Right by the number of people coming
Guess what you f******
I accidentally stumbled into the men's right
Subreddit
And
They were talking about some of these issues
I saw somebody posted something about how the
Project
Most of the people who have been released
Innocent project
Rape
So they were making the argument that false rape accusations are real and a big deal
What was black man raping white women that might have been the issue I went to
Project website
Went through or perhaps
Or better said
Black men
Not raping right right right
Touching your
What is a bulk of
The cases
Is another issue
It's parceled in
Slightly but that's not about
Position about women
End racism
Getting the wrong people and it's really more about the police
Anything else
So then the other thing was
This person
On Reddit was making this argue
Was bundling in a bunch of
Rape and
The murders
You can't really make a
The false accusation
Murdered
That's the police doing
You want to say like
It doesn't
Is that the woman who was not right
No no no no
Because these cases of people who are
Exonerated 4
These crimes involve rape
Really making the argument that
A bunch of false accusations exam
Embrace
When you take out the ones that have
With
Racially charged incident
Murders
But it's like zero
It's very slim I'm not sure I found a
That word legitimate
What is a legitimate I mean
Fall into his argument
It's lightly.
The Under Undertaker
Purely statistical analysis
With how rare it is
To get a false rape accusation
If it's more than one woman
There's a 97% chance that you were
A f****** Siri
Or the globalist
Also possible
Open
The episode here
We get a gas
I suggest that we know well
The guest we spoke to
On the phone for an hour
Mike Caplan
No no
It is Larry nickel
F*** that guy
Comes in a little bit
The soft rice Nicaraguan Freedom Fighter Nick
Larry the big old
Fraudulent piece of garbage
Larry Nichols be f****** Vince Foster f*** face that can go kill him
So Larry Nichols comes on it doesn't even really have cancer
According to
Some online speculation we're not.
So Larry Nichols big arguments that he's coming on to pitch
Are there
Elizabeth Warren
And Joe Biden are waiting in the wings
I know they're about to take over
Hillary
But Hillary has blackmail on everybody
So she's not going to let him do that
So that's what that's what's going on from his insidesource
Right
Control over the Democratic national committee's funding sources
You would be right but Elizabeth Warren
Was considering running
Well not really really close to getting a knob because of
Absolutely
He was really close to it don't don't mistake
The Dear Miss we had with Joe Biden
Versus
Narrative
Important
Yeah because that
That can exist
In reality and Larry's narrative with Larry's narrative
For the first time we believe Larry
So in the last couple appearance
If you had on the show
Larry Nichols has waffle
Back and forth
From
Trump is the only person who can save us
To Hillary's the only one who can save us from Barack Obama turning us into a Muslim caliphate when he becomes king
Makes sense so he has no like he is
No
At all but on this appearance
He's on the Trump
Annie says something
That I think
Is him
Showing
Too many cards
And being a little too over but your mic time
Are the Yu-Gi-Oh cards
No.
Not Pokemon
This is The Showdown Alex just said that this still election that are countries
A G right now
And that's why we've got to get in
We the average American
You know we're being excluded from the whole thing
Where the dinosaur where the ones that are they broken coalition
Ariel office
They now down where the minorities were walled up before they played politics now it's the other way around and people are saying good
Fuel white guy
They just don't want middle class people.
That's right I mean Western
Culture
In one Fell Swoop Larry has admitted we just need white
White man to take over
Skip
They already have
Larry
How much better everything is with white men run things
Spider-Man to work together
The other in one Fell Swoop
Alex has
Indicated that these eyes
He is about Western ism
And that stuff
Warriors
That's f***** up man
You shouldn't have said that
Again
This is the era of mixed
The subtext text man
Next year's news today about tomorrow's razors Ray
F******
Unreal
Wwoof
We got to talk to Larry about that
On my way.
Now we don't
Really apply but I've never really liked on the episode
We had to rely
On white women to really get us through this situation
And white women failed
I'm not ready to come down on
Necessarily
Be that as it may
Like in the times that I've listened to this show and all the all of this
This history
Nichols be really islamophobic
Really f***** up on that tip
I've never heard him say something that over
That overly white National
Yeah
I've never I've never heard that and that took me
That man wasn't surprised necessarily
Photo of course I thought it was sort of imply that that was in his
Beliefs
Time it did surprise me a little
Wake me up
Yes
Okay yeah
Pretend
Non-racist
Whole Hog be like
White dude
Write up what would he says like
Average American
White damage
Like that is
I constantly
We struggled with this like
Feel like
Is it the Joker's like I want a higher class of
Criminal in this town
I get this app
We didn't these guys
When there
I think the same way we just ended up with soda
Disappointed in Allen
Make me work for Jack nationalism out on disc
I meant being like when someone calls you a racist being like where's the proof
Everywhere
The big store Friday
I don't know if I should get into
What
Okay
So I've been doing a bit of research on this guy name
Ted Malik
Pretty regular
Ted Malik malloc
Ch
Ted moloch
Mi-Wok the god
Use a part of the
Davos group
But he's turned on them
Bright ideas
Sure is a big proponent of brexit and then was allegedly
Trump pic
To be the ambassador
You
But it didn't work out I wonder why a bunch of videos came out of him being like I wanted to
Destroy the EU you were like
Don't do that as opposed as opposed to Trump's pick for the FEC
Main goal was
I would have destroyed the FCC
For the f****** CFA the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau
Who is literally said
I want to destroy the Consumer Financial Protection
Right right
So
If you look into it
This guy Ted Malik
I'm going to write an article about that and put it on the website
This information will be
Burien
Hirota autobiography called Aspen Davos and Yale
He is probably in a
I don't know you looks good
I put them in late fifties early 6
People have done some analysis
Of his book
Check a bunch of claims
And they are not real
He claims that he was quoting knighted and The Sovereign order is
St John by the Queen Elizabeth
The second Purcell
And to my closest family and friends
I am therefore known as Sir Ted
Love that
All right now
Disregard anything that's going to result from this
I love a man who will write an autobiography
Where he is a false
Sir
So the foreign board with anybody
To just be like
The financial times looked into it turns out he received the medal of st. John
In 2000
M5
But it was as a quote serving brother
A British honors several ranks lower than Knighthood
It does not carry
Title and members do
Do not attended investiture with the queen
The screen wasn't even involved when they reached out to Malik 44
It's not a Knighthood
I never suggested it was in the book he says I was texting
So also he claims
He also claimed that he was made a layered
By Lourdes Leon
And given a personal coat of arms of the fancy Latin inscription
Okay however and the Latin inscription mean
F****** liar
Tattoo
Violin
Octoboy
Alright so Coronavirus
From the financial times
However a cork
Keeper of records at the court of Lourdes Leon said quote
The Lord Lyon does not nor could he create a personal Laird
It would certainly be incorrect
Mr. Malik to say he was made a layered by the Lord Lyon king of arms
Mr. Malik
God I love
I love the delusional guys who go back far enough for it to be
Yeah just like the idea
Yeah I got a barrel
Made For Me by Queen Elizabeth The First like what are you f****** doing
I promise that this is going to get back to
Stormfront
As we jumped off
Don't want to live in scroll world I don't want nothing to do with Stormfront so there's
There's a bunch of other things
You made a bunch of other assertion
Ricky Lafayette Verity book
You claim that he was a professor at ox
The University of
Yeah the University of Oxford rejected Mr Malik
The solution to a benefit your fellow at the Wilson College
Publicity statement about and by Professor Ted moloch
He is described as having been a senior fellow at Wilson College
This is inaccurate
Mr. Malik was a visiting academic for 2 years but he barely rarely visited the college
I did not see through any of his plans for research activities with the college
Add at the University which is usually real lucky
Criticize former staff
See this is this is my biggest issue hold on hold on hold on
In the in his CV also states that fellow and director of an international summer school at 10
Bro college at Oxford College told the financial times
God
This is the thing that drives me insane
Right
Here's what I want from liberals
Here's what I want from all the people who say when they go low
We go high
If you are given a quote like that
If somebody
Comes to you
Oxford fuckfaces
And says
Senior fellow there you should have the right
And the prerogative to be like that dude's a f****** liar
What b******* that's the case
Don't say
That's incorrect
Be very direct and save it f***** is lying
Spokesman for so many people would be like
Here is what I do and then I would be over for you.
Is book mr. Malik Wright City
Completed his entire doctoral program and a
Unprecedented Less Than 3 years
Between 1976 and 90
However the University of Toronto says
After being questioned by the financial times mr. Malik said that he had completed his coursework at Oral exam
Within three years
Buddy's Pizza took longer
Mr. Malik recently claimed
Soviet Union
After I. His most senior diplomatic executive
Executive secretary in the UN economic commission for Europe
Between 19 and 1991
Who else was better place
To take down the Soviet Union
Nick said his role was ambassador-level
Un and US officials at the post
Not regarded as an equivalent
He's just a liar he's just a complete
Lead his
Also
He also took out a like a number of loan
Over the years
For millions of dollars from Banks
Advantage defaulted on them
Also claimed
Much higher FF
Took the law
So the bank would give them to him
He said that he was worth like
30 million dollars
Money took out these loans
Maybe 10 years ago or so I'm sorry
I don't quite have the date
But what
When it came time to pay back along today
I should have only got 150
$52,000 default on the loan
You still own this money
The problem with that is
Kind of want to be on his side anytime somebody lies to a bank
And then is just like
I got away with it
Confidently they get millions of dollars
I have one more thing to read
We'll get into where we get
Towards the
Okay so also claims
He's a descendant
Theodore Roosevelt
Perfect
Go Wilder
He's a descendant of Cleopatra
Stop at Teddy Roosevelt has been helped by an unusual claim
Reading from the financial times here President Theodore
Theodore Roosevelt after my paternal wasp
Who remains one of the finest exemplars of the breed
Mr. Malik wrote in his autobiography Aspen
The connection has been repeated by right-wing publication
Breitbart
Which refrigerant is
The great grandson
The President Theodore Roosevelt The Daily Caller said that Mr Malik's
Ancestor and vedanta
Sounds true however birth records analyzed by a front-end
Time on the genealogical link
Mr. Malik said his relationship
Theodore Roosevelt
Who was born in Philadelphia in 1921
An obituary of mr. Malik senior does not mention any link to President Roosevelt
Years before he was born in your parents were Henry Wilson
Symbolic a plumber
From Scotland and Frieda Schneider
Housewife born in German
Financial Times could find no link between them and President Roosevelt who was age
About 35 when they were born
President Roosevelt's great-great-grandson Kermit Roosevelt said he had never heard of Ted Baloch
Mr. Malik told the financial times
I was always told that my grandmother was a descendant of a Roosevelt relative
German birth records are available only to direct
Initially offered to send
The financial times
He goes out to damage his reputation
Can I not to establish back
I feel like he was out to damage
One of mr. Malik
Gold was named Woodrow Wilson Malik
Mr. valek declined to comment on whether the family was released
Woodrow it look
If you're with a ranking system
I want to go Teddy Roosevelt
I'm not going to go with the president who made black people hide whenever he was walking through the f****** White House
Yeah it was like looking through this and I'm like
Amazing
He is such a liar
A lot of these lies are things
In his book
I would like that
Really dangerous
For a publisher
Like to put out these false statement
Cuz if you lying about all this stuff who knows what other stuff he's lying about
His claims are really up for grabs like to the point where I looked into it I can't find any
Evidence
He was involved
Strictly speaking with the Aspen Inn
He was in a video
In 1991
Okay
The world economic forum
Where he's introducing
People really like
Everything
About him to be up for grabs
Hey you know what maybe we should
Start doing then
Is let's go through a lot of autobiographies that we rely on as historical.
Maybe
This dude's a f****** bullshiter who knew how to write when most people did
Right so I looked into it and it turns out
The Davos Aspen and Yale
Was put out
Day
Davos Aspen and yeah
You know you know who put it out
WorldNetDaily
There's a publishers
Of course not on any other actual publisher
If you don't know WorldNetDaily it's another crazy
Conspiracy site like Infowars
Successful writing
Flashback
So this is a fun derivation
I'm glad that we were able to go down
I looked into it
I checked all the books
Published by WorldNetDaily
I'm going to read you some of the greatest
How to choose a husband
And make peace with marriage
Fantastic Dubai lineup
It's been 40 years since the sexual revolution in the women of America have everything they want
Everything that is now except a husband
The art of love
Where's the next one
Nextbook
If I had a son
Ray's guns and the railroading of George Zimmerman
Any part of that blood moons decoding the imminent
The antidote healing America from the poison of hate blaming victimhood
You suck it out with your mouth here is the byline of it
In this powerful book Jesse Lee Peterson traces the
The collapse of the black community in America
Do an unexpected Source the anger against one's mother and father that fatherlessness engenders
There's another one
Jessie
Maybe don't come
American hits
Is Meadowbrook bezel prepared
Equipping the church
For persecution in the X
Israel Christians in the end of the age
Model of the Jesus Boy Scouts right
Self Invasion Muslim Conquest through immigration and resettlement Jihad
Devil in d.c. winning back the country
Free from the Beast and wash
Who's that Frank Ayers my second
In favor of these
How Obama can be defeated in 2012
A battle plan based on political statistical reality
Written
Jerome corsi
That f******
So now here's my favorite of all the books on the WorldNetDaily
Is it might as well be
Revolution
That's the title
How to turn
The tide it's going up here but I don't know what you want what do you want from there
Play Michael Brown dr. Michael Brown
Most notable because of being a closet
Yeah and a couple months ago he
Gotten hot water
The internet turned on in a little
Hiring a Rentboy
About this
Post that you wrote called when social media explodes over an editing oversight
The ending oversight being reissued
So when I wrote my article asking whether it was time for another Jesus movement among Jewish Millennials I fully expected to
Some pushback
Since the subject of Jews believe in Jesus is hardly without controversy and emotion
Jews for Jesus I'm fully aware of how hot
This topic has
Surprised and embarrassed made it turns out that a lot of the controversy
We had nothing to do with the substance of the article
Focus on a website I hyperlink
Two of the article
Explain briefly My article was responding to a recent poll
Percent of Jewish millennials
Believe Jesus was either God incarnate or a rabbi or spiritual leader
Me time to see a great
Spiritual Revival among these Jewish millennial
Just as we saw in the Jesus people movement of the late 60s and early 70s
So that pole that you talked about that article
Sure
The hyperlink
To 100% it was from Stormfront
Sounds good so everybody's like a guy
Maybe
Maybe just maybe
Anything about Jews from Stormfront ever made me laugh so hard
One of my first of all this outlasting the gay Revolution that's a book
That's amazing
I meant to find out by reading that book until
I had to Google
Lick the Stormfront
And his argument is like
I didn't know they were neo-nazis
At the same time
How sloppy of a job are you doing if you link to something that's
Supposedly in defense
Your point
And you don't know what the character of the website
You know a little editorial work
We do
It's so frustrating to me because
I have
I have started
Finish like
Forty or fifty thousand words
And never wound up eggs
Finishing a buck
And this week
Ifucking finished the book
What is so frustrating to finish it out the book
I can't just force yourself to finish
Yeah product would be what you wanted
Well then you burn it
Right
Turn up
Look up a contract is a
Sweet f****** fraud and that's the bottom line of that also look for my follow-up book
Homosexual Revolution
Put this out there
Sexual Revolution
She's just about to Everlast
You know what it's like
So the other thing is like
Probably wasn't involved with globalist or anything like that
He's absolutely a combat
Or he's just a mentally ill person who has delusions
There's a great clip that you can find of him
At a symposium
Right after the
In London
Yeah I believe it's 11 somewhere
Discussion about how like now we have to deal with the fact that a president would lie on
Twitter
And
Ted mollica's like
What we might we had a President Who Lies everyday on Twitter for eight years trying to be a dishy
Why the light everyday for what's an example
Well he came over here and said that we should
Because I'm cool.
That's not a lie
That might be unwise if that's your opinion but
What's a statement of an opinion
We don't have time
Is somehow Allah
Well that's true
But it's it's not
This guy
Anyway
That's Victor caliber.
That was a weird derivation for us to go off on
Let's get back into it with the next
January twenty
Alex starts January 22nd by being like
Now
For a long time I've been critical about
Do you mean the 10th planet
Okay
I mean
Israel
Planets
And we know that because of irregularities in the
The orbits of other play
Well I mean
That's probably going to Larry 12th Planet
Are we dealing with Pluto like it's the 13th floor on a hotel
Stanley Alex
Because now it's Ian just
Have come out
Started to discuss the idea that there is another planet out there that we just
A grasp on coz
Too far away to write the orbit is not such
That we can study it well it's there because of the effect on other planets
Eva is
Narrative is
You can't really see a black hole but the gravity energy of a black hole
Totally did Pluto from being Planet so this could be the ninth planet so
Conspiracy theorist
Talk about Planet X
The tenth planet
Wow
Just need to work on something else but it is an interesting example of Alex Soto
Mia culpa
Being like I've been critical of looks like it there
I like
Alex
The Planet X stuff is like ancient alien
Stop yeah it's about like Angela Lynn enki and the the
Dip dip
Don't give them a tip of the cap
Just because scientists have found
The effects of a wobble
No it's it's not
But he gets into a bunch of other crazy s***
Like I we were here in this first Clifton
Favorite planet
You did learn over the last 11 months
Planet 9 from Outer Space all right
Plan 9
Dammit
This except Alex Jones
You're going to school
They confuse them so much
But officially in every school in the country
Super planet
Travel
Have weirdo
Tellonym
PNC is bad and you don't have to be a boy or girl for you can be gay or you can be then
What a group of cult creeps that we let come in and chat us over
Group sign-on
Misunderstanding
Attitude verses
Tavistock Clinic
Like that sort of stuff about there going to be
Be coming into the schools and
Manipulating your children into things
Another gay or
General hatred of
Higher Learning
Right
It's hard
Very and also a misunderstanding of how tribal memories relate to space
Or or formal
Not a big fan of formula
Can you
Can you conceive of a world where I am
Tribal memories
Is a
School class that you take yes
I could do we live in that world and Native Americans wouldn't be in Hawaii
Like for a couple years
And one of the things
Teacher stamps
And teach us about the old ways
Yeah yeah that's not the ability to pastel memories
Through race today
I actually kind of think they were trying to find shamans
I think that's what the class was really about yet I think these old ladies would come to the class
They were secretly trying to find the next
Okay that's what I think
It was probably just a
Probably
Fascinating thing
How Republicans
Hate science
And yet will believe
Any science that agrees with
Like brunette
Like anybody
All went well and I mean more than anybody like
Okay just go with the climate change
Bulshit
And let's just call that a hundred percent of scientist
They all agree climate change is real and we can point to its effects and we can point to how is happening and we can play
Solution but if you have one Republican points to some dumb-ass study there like
Dumbass study proves it
Everybody else thought Beyond
That guy agrees with what I already
Another
Try and demonstrate
The laws of thermodynamics
Like the idea that energy is
Not
Changed its created or destroyed
Those studies inevitably
Turn out that like
Think about this thing
Variable in math
Adventures the great thing about review is available and they're like
Here's your mistake and nobody's like
Another like
Better
Are not on the side
But by all means.
Dem kok's
Demco
BuzzFeed I believe
Over the weekend
Sound
James O'Keefe
Donor list
I believe I bet
I bet it all comes from don't
Yeah actually that's that
She hates baby parts
That was actually the Center for Medical progress but
With the project veritas
The highest donors
Hundreds of thousands of dollars
Workout Brothers pass-through
The money directly but it was funds that they are
Like in charge of the pass-through
So people give to them and then they director
Motorworks are winding up horse
Right
$25,000 from Gladius Maximus
$50,000 from
I guess his dad
Or his brother I don't know some other Okie
Kellum not Georgia
Anyway
Interesting position
Right2know
Anyway
Big event
The 3rd of people who go to art schools are in prison or commit suicide
But also my girlfriend
She's told me many times that a third of them went
Went to school
And killed themselves
Prison
And that none of them
Know anything about
Space Orchard
Art School
Art school in that case would be more devastating than the battle of
The Bulge
Survive
But you're in the s***
Two of the biggest American casualties
The Civil War many Americans died in the Civil War
The finger paints offenses
Such b*******
There are a lot of people who end up being artist out of killing themselves
But I would argue that
Causation
And
Criticize
His ideas
As we do
Very right
I'm assuming
He seems to think that most of them are
But then he goes on to talk about the past
Criticize
Clip-in
It's a known fad
And they show up with the crazy people
Brewing stand
I'm done
Dukes of Hazzard explanation for what Alex
Describing is
Crazy
Fans of his independently running into each other at and out
The other one
That's probably
Neither of them actually exist
I imagine
Don't have the resources
To what
I believe that
I mean it away
Long Pond
Still going to CIA or the FBI
The foundation said there's the Ford Foundation there's a bunch of them Rockefeller
Message with me Special Forces
You did that
The real quick real quick real quick
When the clintons were in office
Howard Jones
He was not
It all in the mainstream Khan
He came into being because of loose change
And because of his broadcast on 9/11
Show on the radio
He was eight
We we
Ignorable very
There's no way that I would believe that the
Military
That's
Siri
Why would you
The Special Forces you could send National Guard Reserves man it's not hard
Close to the
Bay
Call Mom work
I have been messed with by the military since about 2,000
They have messing with me
And it's not fun
It's not you
Spider-Man dress up
I haven't been messed with by the military
Cinderella 2000
I also have been messed with before that but since then I have also not been that
A true statement
Right
Nonsense
What would a okay
How would you mess
With Alex Jones
Messin With Sasquatch commercials now
Over there just going to like
Alex misrepresents a lot of the times when he's being victimized
Do you mean all the time all the time
I just don't I don't buy it I don't believe any of this to Foundation Park
Foundations are f****** with him the military wasn't during the
End times
We're all about
Foundation
Second Foundation
Forward the foundation
All of that
Most most Philip dick book
Feature
Hawaii
Paranoia than Alex Jones
I wouldn't bother with Edgar Allan Poe
The Jordan is next
Alex Jones often talks about ways you can support the Brock
Lottery
We talked about downloading the app ways we can buy pills
A lot of it
You can buy a billboard
I would love to buy bill
Outside of Lubbock Missouri
So many ways
You can support the infowar
On this episode 22nd
Alex has
The cheap
And most annoying you could possibly support the infowar
Because all you do is keep
Thinking about how you're going to write a book
Shoreline
No-see-um
Grocery store
My kids start saying
So then
He goes on to get into like a 2-minute ramble about like Nursery Water have fluoride in it and how
Like I've been in a lot of been like hey lady don't get that water for your baby I'll go get the right water for you
Shreveport Times of my life
Like what
You're the worst
So am I
Like I can't
Stress enough
He keeps going on like
Look I love your kids
I'm trying to help your family doing the show I love talking to you about Alex Jones
If I ever go to a store and I'm like
Let me tell you something about Alex Jones
Kill me
High heel mate I mean this sincerely
Like I know you do
If
Anyone
Ever
In my life
Stranger
Acquaintance
Friend
Family member
You
Was like
Here's something I heard from Alex Jones
I would be like
No point arguing I got it I got to go this is why the self-checkout line was invented
Guess what
Dehumanizing
They want us to buy
Produce from robots
I'm fine with
Have you ever been stuck behind an old lady in the self-checkout
Machine
You're like oh no I get why we need to get rid of Medicare
So
For the rest
This episode we enter what I was what I reference at the top of
The show
And that is
Alex ends up getting
Call he doesn't get it yet
But at this point
Alex's
Really
Really into being right
About economics
And
You start as we are in 2017
Definitively
He was correct
Sure
Right on
Inner in the summer break
Do you remember when the summer
Like we're looking at January 2016 we are nigh on a month away from
2 years after
And the economy is
Done nothing but
Stabilize and go up
Are granted their out there are troubles
Has not gone up
It is not collapsed though
Has gone up the economy
Has stayed
Consistently miserable for people like us
But
But again
We're not the Run
No we're not
It doesn't really matter
F****** Bitcoin
Everybody
This is the weird thing about
Conflicted about this car about our stock market system
Everybody
Everybody knows Bitcoin is going to collapse
The people who work for Bitcoin the people who invented Bitcoin
People who are investing in Bitcoin
Right now
Know that this is an unsustainable
Sustainable bubble and this is going to explode
Get what you can while you can
What does going to demolish people
F****** retirement accounts and yet somehow
Everybody's fine with this for the time being
Far out
Cryptocurrency
And Bitcoin
No I'm into cryptocurrency but it's worth 16,000
No but but that's
I will save it it's an illusion Subway
Because there's a finite number of the Bitcoins they can be broken up into the smallest possible portions
You're never going to be trying to sell one Bitcoin you'll be selling the tiny or parts of it for $20
$40 dinner
So like
The idea that
You couldn't find a buyer
For it
The one coin for 60,000 absolutely you're not going to find
But you could find buyers for the smaller portions of which does give it value
I don't
I don't fully understand
Situation but I do know that for the last 24 hours or so I've been
Tracking
Bitcoin price
Do you like minute-by-minute
Actuation of it
Is terrifying
Like as as
Think I was think about it if I
Have any
Money invest
Will bit like if you looked at it over the course of Amanita call Bronson you can do this again for the next
24-hours cuz it'll repeat
But like
There are atlak minutes where it goes down $500 for a Bitcoin
And it goes down $1,000 and then up
It's crazy that our ability
Trading is all done by Elgar
Right so none of that has any reflection to real people make
A real decision
That's all machines who are playing the game against
It's like
It's like chess computers playing chess against
Another chapter
By the way
Check out alphago plus because that is the end of humanity
Hours
They developed
Chess-playing computer that taught itself
And now is the best chess player in the
Picture of the universe
It's incredible
Pork rub
We're all going to die
About a benign
Benevolent AI
Has ended they will just destroy us at every sport
And the AI is going to figure out how to murder Usain Bolt
The only actual no that's a weird any results here's why I will take issue with
What you're saying
Isaac
That you're a huge Usain Bolt
He seems like a cool guy
I get it
The issue is the idea of benevolence within a computer or something like that maybe
Destroying a lot of
The stuff he's been
Human calculations can't put that inside the only way to save this
Human races to destroy any AI
Correctly assume and then wood
Begin sucking
That's why
The problem with Avengers Age of Ultron was good guy
Wrestling
Going again like we talked about this
Doesn't it always go back to wrestling
The hills are always
Right
Generally the bad guy
Has a point
I'm a good guy is
Just some smiling jackass
Humanity is a smiling jackass MD
Harsh truth of
We need to stop doing what we're doing
And maybe that is
We're projecting that into the minds of AI let's get off this
We got to get back to collapse
Economic
Yeah yeah
Let's get off this topic of made-up thoughts
Who played outside
This idea that you
He's always been right
About collapse
We're p*** dealers
No option
Consolidate control
We've been proven
Angela
Living off
I just think it's all funny
I wish I could
My parents have paid and help me pay my rent
In times where it's been
F****** real hard and I couldn't find it
Joblo
New comedy
A very thrilled that they supported me in that way
If you want
Talk about
That's part of it
Specifically
Vista skin color
Changing the game
But not necessarily due to any kind of
Intended
People Metropolitan inherent Within
The system of what
So if you want
Your family is
Statistically
Wayla
So would your parents be able to help you out in those two
How do I mean
So what are you do
That
My point is just
Like just that tiny little thing that little thrown off
Bet
So many stories revolver
Hey look I was in trouble
And my parents were able to help me out for sure
Have been denied so much well throughout their entire life for generation
They don't even have access
I got to know why just hijacked
That but that's
No
I do recognize the luxury
That I had in
That sucks
Because I would have rather not that been the case
I would have rather
Had a job
When I move to
Chicago
Incredibly difficult to find a job
I had no connection
I had no friends
Friends who had jobs
I had
Most of the friends generally speaking
Friends
You don't have friend when I go to the restroom
Acquaintance
See you at bars when we tell terrible jokes
That was it and then I moved here
You know what nest egg that I thought was go
It all
You know like it was it was
Situation where you're in over your head quicker than
Amanda
What is privilege
Course I recognize it
I wish
Alex would recognize
Before he points the finger you know like
88888 not
It's not
Like a counterexample
Prosperity
It's not a counterexample to
His masculinity or his
Is ego
To own up to
To the fact that he's in the position
He's in
Because his dad
Got him a radio job at a critical point that would be humanizing
Arandas Park
Time he was like
Hey you know what
Open the door for me
That otherwise wouldn't have been open
Immediately you and I would
Have a
Usually differ
But we would have a
Point-of-view even playoff of you like you want me to
He can play any game that he wanted to
Instead
Has this ego buildup where it's like
I've got everything on my own
F*** these dumb yummies rub Mom and Dad's truck parts
So insincere yeah
Just bothers me or anything like that but it's just like
I don't know what you do I don't know what to do with that
But that level of disconnect
From your own reality
Okay
The people who are advocating for white genocide might be said to be in
That's possible
You know who else isn't
Advocating for not
You didn't build your business
Isn't strong boy
Strong
He doesn't this Impressions going to go onto a little while
Eventually like it's not in this clip but he comes back
From break and they have found the clip
Any places
A video of Obama
Perfect
Perfect grade
Parody
Power
Conan
Simba
My child
Just jumps off
Compliment
That describes
Felt like
Ridiculous weird used to deal with that
Briefly
Bye-bye pretend products because you're in a f****** cult that believe they're real
You go get briefly tattooed on me like what would be
That would symbolize this year of my life
Briefly...
It wouldn't be like it wouldn't be obviously like
Like Alex Jones
Space or something like that so that's what he knows everybody know.
Briefly that
Like some of your past 11 months
Is of course
Picture of my face screaming at you on
Exactly what you need
M40
Whatever was anyway
So I'm in this next Cliff Alex Jones
Talks about his
Audience
At the same time like I told you
We're still within this collapse
This is within the context of
Collapse
The end
Send to a weird sort of
Discussion
Pre-market
But there's a fantasy
That goes along with
I think it has to do with beating your
Your kids but I'm not entirely sure
I'm not sure
The enemy has gotten so naked about world government or planetary plan that The credibility of everyone opposing
For a long time is exploding
The listenership the viewership the readership I don't know I haven't asked but I bet
A song about a guy named Michael Schneider who has the runs a Blog called
Economic
Collapse blog
Right which is basically just
You know yes these guys on her like a
Have prepper websites and s*** like that
At right it's just it's just another one
Like that so that's the
Because
Hell
We want
Incredible
The free market we've got to have children
We got it a bunch of stupid arenac chumps
Exception
Exceptionally dumb exceptionally mindless exceptionally sick gl6 Society
Hospital
I don't know if I've ever seen somebody describe themselves better
He's exceptionally fat he's exceptionally simple-minded he's exceptionally all of those things
You f****** mailed him whoop and he also is did child of privilege
A child of prosperity if you are a therapist
In that room
With him while he
He's describing
Like if you were just sitting there without a controller in old water rule
So tell me what you don't like about people
He said that
You just stare at her
Heaven be like
I don't think I
I don't like that these trendy's have unkept
Beard
And seem to be growing their hair out never cross eye
I don't like this.
Describe myself
You just described.
So
There's a couple things that are important to take out of there first of all this
This whole mentality of like
Prosperity create
Really
Rich Society
Generation
Make them work
Domestic
Put it but it's also
Cowardly Dodge
For him cuz he's on the right side of that generation line
Uno's
I don't know what you're trying to protect
Beyond that history doesn't
Clearly show that that's the case cuz there are a bunch of
Civilization
Is that have generation
Been prosperous over
Over again
And those are ones that
Understand
The in-and-out slow of resource
Understand that you
Need to do is create either a balance
Or Surplus
Coming in as opposed to those going
Going out
Very simple
Many Native American civilizations
And tribal civilizations understood thoroughly well
You can create a homeostasis that that works
Incredibly well
Well it creates prosperity and doesn't deteriorate
I mean
Here's here's the
Way2go
Wee wee wrestling
The dollop
Listen to the podcast about the Acadia
And you're going to be like oh that's the way
To do it
Jets
Everything we did
Is wrong
Tell people
Like a little bit about what you mean
I mean
Domyown
Only 75% of the audience is going to go listen to it
The akkadians were a group of French cafe
Who came
To Canada
And
By virtue of a
Of 1
Huge anime
Wherein they
Created a
What would you
A bulwark against
Saltwater destroying everything
And
The necessity of
Adding nutrients
And they made this certain
Situation they made a certain group of
Certain patches
So
F****** good
So f****** good
This is great
Let's do this
And then everybody else got involved in
F*** them over until they became the
The Cajuns in
There's a whole long journey down there
But the point being
They did something right
They just had a great place to go
You allowed capitalistic
I mostly asked
Because I forgot what that episode was absolutely
You have a good situation and that does create just like you were saying a certain States
It creates a situation where an everybody seems
Fucken satisfy
And then you allow a Kappa
Yeah yeah it is it Dusty
YouTube
That
On a very basic level
Capitalism is
News about exploitation
Exxon
And exploitation
And
A balance
Don't really coexist well
The idea of an equilibrium
And someone trying to offset that equilibrium
For their own advantage
Whether or not that
Attempt to get their own advantages
Just right or wrong or anything like
It just doesn't seem like those two things can
Really operate
Together
I don't know what that means for our future
Is it you think weird confluence
I got very interest bective today
I'm listening
I suppose I got very Longview
I'm just going
And thinking about
How how old is humans
Deal with things
And there are these
Impulsesv
That are
You can't really describe them as good a new
Bright lights
Does
Benefit everybody insofar as if
Nothing is ever satisfying
You're going to constantly keep f****** working
Like with with our with any kind of artistic
Point-of-view a lot of time
Is one of the biggest
I'm never satisfied with anything I create
Exactly always terrible and I'm never going to do anything that's
Good enough for my
Keep trying to
To create that
You know
In a certain way that's a good
In another way
That's destroying and eating my soul from the inside out and right forcing you to never actually create
Exactly
Forces you to create but never finish creating
Certain products
Finish creating it
To throw it away because it's
Right you know
And that's kind of that kind of an over our
Principle behind capitalism
The Miz
Never enough
No matter what we do
There's never enough wealth
Fun that I just realized I mean basically
This this thumbs up
Patreon
Right now
What's going on with them
I complained to you about this a little bit and it might we might as well put it out
Just a little bit does but like a patreon
Has shifted some of their fees
Who knows they might by the time this comes out or in
In the near future walk
Chris back f****** should have done is
The fees that used to be
Taken out of
Of the things people donate it
I have shifted over to
The people who are donating
And they started charging people
Ascertain
A donation as opposed to
For all of the things that they donate to
So it's specifically screwing over the people who give little donation
To a bunch of people will end up
Cannibalizing probably
The capacity of people
To support creative projects
But in doing so if you look at the the metrics new look
The man
They will make so much more money
Or for you
And to that extent
I don't want
Anyone who wants to support the show to give
More money for them if you want to leave our
Please feel free to come up with something new
Capital are so grateful to everybody who don't
And if you decide
Not just to not do this
Because economically
To do this
Do this
Philosophic
We love everything that you've done for us
We care so much about you and help you stop donating
We're going to be on your side which is a weird thing for us to say
It's that miscalculation that I think patreon did they
Your customers
That's not that's not
No
This is a donation this isn't
It's a support I mean cigarettes you know technically
You would think like this is
Yeah
I don't know
I think the I think the biggest issue that we have is
And they're the ones
Yeah
A hundred percent
The part where
Creator
It becomes
Incredibly difficult because we do need support
And we appreciate your support
But now I don't feel great asking for it in this way right
So if you'd like some for the show.
Future for the time being
Ewok
That
What did Alex it right there my son feel free to go to PayPal freezing point at gmail
Yeah anyway let's move on we're going to figure out a way for this to work out
The point the reason that I bounced off what you were saying
Disgusted
Because that is unnecessary
Influence of Kappa
They need
Make more money
I assume there's some
Pressure from the higher-ups or something like that
To jump in and they're like nobody got a whatever-it-is naked
Did cash grab attempt
That is undermining the
Purpose of
Thanks
That is
That's capitalism
You got it
Anyway I haven't sex with Alex Jones
Still
He's still trying to
The push is a disaster
Narratives
What's going to happen now
When the welfare checks still go out when the EBT card still work
With this ignorant
Domesticated population
The Pentagon estimates
Most people kill
Begin within 15 days
I am
Thought I would work the last time we talked about
I only brought it back in because
He's really ramping
Through this like
He's talking to this guy
Run the block called
Economic collapse blog.com
Gran Torino
Any pushing these
I'm pretty hard about the collapse
You know like
I've been right all the time
I've been right
People are starved
The contact
Snowmageddon
The East Coast
So when you talk about like there's no food on the shelves
No I don't I remember distinctly
The new thing
Cannibalism
But him being like there's no food on the show
Xavier
Tell me how that works when I was a kid we had a hurricane
It was a gonna hit our Island
Very little food on the shelves
We stocked up and then
We finally about
That's the one that's a big
Psychological
Which is
We will know
They're a little bit
Better than
Like that's one of those like that's one of those things where you can go into any
Play small town
Andaz
Well as they get along with each other
They will you know your family will thing
Yeah we're good people
We don't know what those other people are going to do
Hannibal Missouri thinks they're better than Mexico Missouri Joplin thinks they're better than her all up
People are
Mystically people are
Kind of
Cool with each
We just don't understand that
Disasters
Situation almost everybody
Ends up default
They want to help
The reality of a disaster remind you of the humanity of your comps
Exactly cuz you start to realize how scared you are and you start to respect everybody
All of those all of those posts
Apocalyptic
Future movies
Like what there should be is
Communities working their ass off
Like you go to
Go to Puerto Rico
Right now
They are not being held
They are not being
Care of in the way that they
Because every single one of those people
Every single one of them are American
And I'll be goddamned
If you don't find
Everybody help
And yet no one
Eating each other
Weird
Power
They don't have water
There's no cannibalism in
Nope
Weird
Everybody's just trying to fuc
Can get through it
We finally get to
Caller
Yes that's Alex in a very weird Direction
About the collapse married
And I got to say
White
But the rest of it
Play on Broadway
My kind of collar
Let's talk now to Christen Georgia
Sorry I was just
Address to you and your guest
I know things are bad your listeners know that the condition of the world economy is bad
What is the character of your this year's economic gloom and doom predictions
You know Snyder dancing peyser
Is different from previous years prediction
Unlimited money
Most worlds already in Civil War
I'm not accusing you crying wolf
How do we get a feeling that it's really going to hit the fan this time because
I'm going to come back to you
I want to be first so so stay there
Listen brother I hope I'm wrong
You are called
So this is the called that's where it goes at
Commercial something big is coming
Well this guy who's made a very
Good
Question
I guess I probably have to do it politely or else out
But the question being you
Which
Over the course of our history doing this show and read to jump back
We just 2001-2004 maybe he saw it
2008, I'm just going to allow that and ignore it
Like we just
Compton
It's about to go down
And he has these
Janti weird
Very differently motivated Financial experts on
Yeah it is
Brighton
So this guy's question is
Is real valid like
To the point where help have a
That just come
Bigot
Bigot bigot
It's like an ingot
The guy's question is
They meant leave out
Why should we
When you have for years
Been prophesying a huge under written and broadcasted vehicles
Operation
Why should we
And so they go to commercial
Roman Atwood comes back
All of your past predictions
I like the one we had before
Unlimited
2 years ago
This is all that stuff that we talked about on episode couple months
Weebly
Misrepresenting all of this
Army.mil
Armored vehicle
Sure
We got the secret document
When was beyond one piece of this is that arm
Me. Mill documents
Use completely misrepresent
And the other part of it is
Statistics of shounen last
Since 9/11
Yeah
The tuna like 70% of domestic terrorism
Events have been White
I'm sure there are some Islamic
Focus
Minority comparative Lee
Law enforcement agencies would
Put out memos weather like
They keep shooting cop
And stuff like that it's not or the idea that
Is tragic as it is
Cuz I
The perpetrators or victims themselves
The idea of returning veteran being
Shell shocked
Which is not a real thing
Killing their spouses or
Were they at Shell Shocked they were right
But the idea of Department being aware of that being deaf
The factory
In the Modern Warfare scenario
They are trained in
Improvised
Explosives
That doesn't seem that weird to me
That doesn't seem like
Biased
Seems like
Cops being prepared
In general
Tumi
The way to deal with
American
Is
First off
If you are hearing about it
That means
Novel
Right
Second
Sexy
It's fitting a narrative
It's already
Pre-programmed
So that's why because it's
MSNBC supposedly supposed to be somehow related
Picking up the same narrative that you have
Fox News
Because Fox News
They pick up sexy f****** Meredith
The idea of
White terrorism
That's not really talked about because
It's not novel
Mary Tyler Moore
Play vava post 9/11 America wherein were terrified of
Write write write those two things going on
Filter every bit of your news through
If I'm hearing about this
This is probably not a frequent thing
And if I'm hearing about this
And it fits in a narrative
Probably not
That's generally how it works
I think that's fair
Like everything they don't do anything successful
Stay inconvenience everybody
Edit the cartel and everybody can go for
I also hear that the TSA is on the road
Begging 3000
We have one more clip
And
Getting really defensive
About this caller
Who's called why is this any different
If your other collapse
Any defensive last whip over here
Lying about
About internment camps
The cops
Trying to get
Like beat like hey
White people are as likely or more likely to be
People who
But even that
Is 7 years old
Like that is not
Current
Somebody's using these narratives which are lies
That are irrelevant
The topic at hand
To bolster his like
This time the collapse narrative that I'm pitching is real right when in the course of this
Podcast
The return of
Last year we heard him
Push back
Disasters coming this fall
Sorry winter
Over and over again
She's coming on December 9th
Set of December
I read the prophecy
I'm mixing two points
Sort of intention
Because
She is as well like
One point is
He is guilty
He does this all the
But the other part is
There's a problem that I'm going on is
He's bringing up the relevant other lies
In order to bolster the economic collapse
The economic Lifeline unrelated to the idea of army.mil
Creating the Kentucky Fried Chicken Double Down
And so he has to bring it together and he tries to
With a
Dumb metaphor
And then we find out what is really behind
Something
You and I
You add pivot me
Swear to God.
I promise you there's no app
But
We already know
We already know what's
Spells it out
Embarrassing way
Ted Koppel
So first of all I didn't deposit their butt
I do need to point out that like what
Houston
You know he's going to invade in 1930
Whatever you know it's going to happen eventually
Kind of mentality
Credible
Cuz it's just like
I'll eventually be right
Like if
I don't believe
Wholeheartedly in Bitcoin
Louis talk about this
A little bit already
Right I think there's a lot of variability to it I don't fully understand
But for me to say
Bitcoin will collapse
If I keep saying that
Long enough
Eventually there will be a big falling it right and I could say
I knew it all along
And that's the game Alex
Is playing now
That's what he's saying like
It's like saying you know it's going to happen eventually and now it happen
Well the speakers Back to the Future
Bitcoin will collapse
But if I told you I knew when it would happen or I knew House part
The summer of Ray
But I can tell you right now
It's not worth what it's worth right now
Everybody's going to find out
I don't know when
I don't know how much it's not worth how much
You don't like I don't know anything other than
Mathematically
That's how work
Right right
I just really
Respect the idea of the Ark
You meant that like
You know it
Habit eventually
You know I will be right eventually
Everything
Especially with any Market
Believe me when white genocide happen
People are going to
Today Show
Holyshit
Like I could say right now like
Potatoes are overvalued
I just choose a random commodity
Are you
Find Cabot
We lived
Through that okay cabbage
Alright
Like produce
To be like
Eventually the bottom is going to fall out of this Market
And I just keep saying and then when it goes up
I could be like
It's over inflated at guys need to understand
If everyone everyone's into cabbage right now but they don't understand the realities of the Cabbage Market
If it's a bulshit game
You're you're describing the fluctuation
As though something
Bright
Soros runs around saying Run for the Hills call Addison
Axalta misrepresenting the world
Floating things
Congressman from Georgia stash
Highway 4
Stop by tectonic
And
Dublin
I'd like to take a step back into save death kind of always the
It should
Be with love for it not to be
But
Atlee
International strife
Kind of
Freeway
Everybody would have
Come together grade 1 worth
Government beta band of capitalism
When go up
Asher talking about
I don't know
2 years ago restaurants in Austin
Where is it at
Southern up
So
What we get there
Smorgasbord
But did the concrete evidence that Alex has that the economy is a disaster
Is vague ideas about Austin restaurant
Which I take it
Because I don't
I don't know
What information
And the other being
What is audiences
Tripled in the last
Not true
If it is
Because of Russian Bots
It's the same. Of time
The Russian influence campaign
Started you know what
I would say he's even lying about that I think his audiences only double
Like the Russians wouldn't even have the gall to Triple is
Go with the triple let's just go with it
Simplicity time influence camp
Started in their summer early summer of 2015
Afraid
His audience has traveled
And is that
You takes
Economy the disaster
No one has any more money
To give me right
He's basing this
Collapse
They called all the indicators say that the economy is
Stabilizing or doing better
But I have tons of yours and no one's giving me money right that's f***** up that's the only thing he has to go on for this
Entire episode
Is just all this like
F*** you there's going to be
Cannibals 15 days from now
Because
So congratulations Alex
You
Unfortunately prove you are not a Russian agent
By virtue of the fact that you are
Influence by Russian
Do you
100%
Being bolstered by phakic
His traffic is being inflated artificial
Obviously it by
Amigo listen to any of our other episodes where he
Russian narratives about Syria
Like it it's just he is a Russian propaganda
Without being Russian
Fry time so obviously they would want to bolster
For his position
Is prominence
I do that
And it's clear
It's clear that is where he is like
Indisputable
But but but
Here are the two things I want to
Canvas episode
The first thing is
The intense
To the wicked witch
He thought that
The economy was
Collapsing
At the beginning of 20
That led him to be
We must
Support Trump
Or die
Is largely based
On Amazon
Standing but he has
Of his own number
I think
That there's a chance
Are you know what this is f***** up because you and I go through this thing over and over again
World like there's a chance
Alex could have saved him
I don't like no
I believe that there's a possibility
Had the Russian Bots not been inflating his traffic
To think that he's becoming one of the most popular things in the world
There's a chance that Alex could have been moderate
In
His support of Troy
What is Ben like
But you can't prove it
I can't get right back into it but I think there's a chance
Because at this time even in even in January he
You still
You know his toes in the water with
Cruise
Is how is in the water with
Rampalli which is more of an a******
Sing that he's just going to be amongst
In a
Because
He's been Duke
Right
And I'm not a different mom
I'm not trying to say
He's a f****** a****** in a racist no matter
But I think in
In terms of
The interest
For history
What he has done
Goodway he
Like as a rocket-propelled
Entity
Supporting Trump
To the point of being like
We will die if we don't
Support him
I think without that
Tripling of his audience
He wouldn't have been confused
Like the economy is a disaster
Halves
Pink
I don't know
I wish for a better way
Incoming
Now here's my punchline
This is from
December 5th 2017
And this relates to
The knowledge
Is that we clearly have
That Alex Jones is audience
Supported
Slated by Rush
No keeping mine
In March
Adam Schiff
Suggested that I
Alex Jones
Was working for Russia
Got really drunk on air and called the c*********
And said I'll beat your ass
You son-of-a-b**** feel your hand that sort of s***
Which
Again still your hand
Here's what Alex said on the
Showing it
But telling me
But pathetic
There you are
If I was one
I didn't know it
Didn't know it
Great
Please hide behind that math Galaxy
He'll probably keep you from being prosecuted but
For someone who before was like I will beat your ass for saying I had anything to do with Russia
I didn't know
Why would you tell him
If you tell him he's going to tell everybody
So congratulations Alex I think
You are
Very clearly
Pawn
Stomach pain
Dum dum game
That took only one
Yes certainly
But your part in it
Wow
All it took was listening to U2 done Ravel
It's one of those things where
Kind of wanted to get bad enough
To where
Affects him to the point where you at
Like I almost I almost want us
I almost want to be in a homeless shelter
Next to Alex Jones just so I can hear him
Yeah I wasn't I was like
I think he
I don't know if he'll ever say that but he will end up
Having to
Like
Get right with
God.
But like
The things that are coming down
Pipe
In terms of
The investigation
Bedtime Euler's doing
Right in terms of
I mean
Outlook
Weeks or so
We've had two people be indicted
One of them
We've had
Strong indications
Unwound eventual
Seems like a total mess
Is because there's in
Information that the public doesn't
That the investigators do
And when that invented vet information
Comes public
A lot of it will become much more
I think it will
And I think Alex Jones
Recognizes
Is that
In March
When he was mad
Screaming I will beat your ass
If you call me a Russian
You didn't have an awareness
F***
I was probably apart
And now
I think you realize
Like based on
That
Sentence
Right
Very clearly I'm saying if I was I didn't know it
Space alien is obviously fax them a Russian Nation
He would never have said
I think
What's going to happen is he's going to have
How to create a new layer of b*******
And I mean we'll see what that is but I don't think I'll ever
Is wrong
Do you like our show
Articles in a row and
Prolific
I generally try and write three a day based on the show of the day
Sometimes Alex
Shady
Sometimes I just get too busy but I try to will try to you know what I realized it
Look I love you Media Matters
I love you right wing watch
You're trying
But you're not doing
The right job in
Who can I can pirate I'm trying
Trying to just do it myself
It's a Pay It Forward
I'm just doing
But
Knowledge
Store fights
Realtor
Download
Please tell your friend to help
Spread the word Each one teach one and what have you
But I got to piss though I don't care for the game
John Rapport go f*** himself
Holding
Alex