Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
We're couple dudes like sit around drink novelty beverages
But Alex Jones modus operandi
Some sort of like
Okay
So if you were going to see the new Star Wars
A boyfriend
If there was a like
You know you're not too interested
No not really really Earth
So what if I told you
I don't believe that it on
Star Wars Star Wars as a whole this movie has a hook
Okay alright. John popper
All Blues Traveler episode
Just like that hook
So do we have a hook and that is I know I don't know a goddamn thing about that is correct
We're going to be jumping on ovaries
Last week's Friday's episode
B-17
Nonsense goes down
Standard deduction s***'s f***** up
Audio drop
Here is an out-of-context drop
Valex from that episode
Jesus loves State and kill your children
So
Alex's World here at the middle of December
The two-year anniversary of him losing his soul in joining up with Team Trump
Alex is a precarious position
Thank you probably did it one point all humans are I don't know what sold exist let's move on from that
Soap
U.s. me before the show is this going to be some Roy more s***
No it's not he's already moved on from that loss
Meaning everybody
Get the f*** out
Guess what
Now we all agree or pedophile surprised you go to jail
It wasn't me
Give me crazy
Shaggy wasn't me
Alex the day after
Anyway
After the the election the Alabama
Centauri election
Alex tried to paint a bunch of airsoft narratives about voter suppression against
Lenny tried to start up a conspiracy theory about
Them not maintaining the voting records
Decision Alabama Supreme Court decision
That the Democrats in the globalist for trying to
People wearing they wouldn't
Keep that maintain be the records
Brilliantly
First
Putting all Republicans as Supreme Court Justice
This is an Alabama brilliant moves
Fostering
And that's how the Democrats came up with this brilliant plan
And what was the result
It's so it's so convoluted
Pretty quick Alex realized
He's like on that narrative
Tar and feather Andrew McCabe and Rod Rosen
Because because I think you started to get the reality in mine but like
We're doing a lot of work
Trying to get
Trump to fire Mueller
But even if Trump fires Mueller
I believe you can I think you can
Forces apartment of a special counsel
I think he can and I think it would be a massive disaster just be like
Uno does someone to replace him
And keep the investigation going
Is a much better idea
Who attacked the Department of Justice itself
Bees RV Rock
Show
Right so
In a lot of the work he's doing is
Through the
Discussion of those Tech
That will came out between the FBI age
The biggest story in the history of the world
People were texting each other that Trump was an idiot
And it turns out they also were talking s*** on Hillary and Sanders to along the way
Course but the more important thing is the reason that they were communicating
This guy
Struck
His name is work phone
They're using those phone because if they use their other phones they might get caught by their spouses they were
Right
That's really more
I don't really think that there is much compelling s*** going on here every
Publican politician
To not to release their text messages around the Trump campaign
I'll have
Very worst what are we going to do everybody
So he spent a lot of time on that and we don't really need to go over that too much cuz I really just don't think there's much
But there is one funny moment
It repairs
Alex is turning on Paul Ryan a good bit
You never really liked him that much the darling of the last
Call Ryan
Darling of the
So I guess that means we're allowed to kill the ones we loved her from the
Thursday show actually because I got I actually cut the switch accident
What they're worth it
Thursday animal
They're relevant because
That whole McCabe Rosenstein narrative really present as much on Friday but it's been a big party
Before you get into the clip
Do you think people have
Criminals and scum and world
Get-togethers
A bunch of chicken
People that have
Group of garbage
The people that robbed
So they're the good guys work on people
And it doesn't work on me makeup whatever you want
Do whatever you want
You are all going to prison
I think he's projecting a little bit understand
Wait so first thing he says is about Rosenstein
Landoll's
Yeah it's all these liberals or completely divorced from any real
Supposing some sort of belief in
The alphas would never do right
What are we talkin about
The remnants
Intellectual tradition of the men's rights activist communities
Operating officer
Half remember things
What he's expressing those eyes
I mean I guess
I guess if you've seen Revenge of the Nerds in your a lady that's probably trailer
Did not
Evan goes into how the betas are actually understandable and doing what they're doing
Because they're watching the
The country get taken apart
Answer there
I think he flips
Probably I think that's my issue
Alex is being intellectually consist of
He's saying I believe is that
These betas
They hate the country because they're robbing it
They're the ones Robin with his pronoun
That's what really is going on
This next Thursday the 14th
More troubling cuz he spent a good bit of the show
Really just playing clips of Putin
Hattiesburg
I mean now
Here's here's a
Dogshit analysis
He's going to throw in
Powers of the president
Respectful
Your media
Your will and what you did constitutionally
Please give me a text to Christopher Steele Stephen
Okay
What
According to Alex
The media is trying to disrespect the public
Which is greater made it seem like they're not I feel like we are all trying to disrespect the public that is f******
Stupid
There is that but it it feeds into Alex's narratives about fake news turns out
Those are
Russia's objectives to begin with so Alex is really
Now mirroring back to his already mirrored from
Sources
So interested
Does drawings of optical illusions with his mirrors bounce
Weather forecast
Responding
Saying things he remembers and recognizes from his own Meredith
Let themselves were mirroring Russian narrative
It's very strange
I love
There's something
Regardless of how you feel
Having the balls
If you are
A Russian
Person
To go on TV
They don't respect the will of the American people
Batman
It's why I think I love that more than
The election with Liza
You don't even respect your people
Extremist opinion
Tension and
Rick
Populist Uprising behind a very easily black mailable
Deeply in debt guy who surrounded by mobsters
There is a little
Coronavirus Coronavirus
Most of
What I found interesting on Thursday and accidentally
Eclipse
Talk with Rodger Stone
Any sort of speculators
Let's go
Bring up that Amicus brief
Know that John Brennan and Clapper
And 14 other people signed an amicus brief everybody who knows classified information is like
Tell you why
We we know things
We Can't Tell You Why
With your classified information it's very clear you're like
We have to protect
Stop worrying about a lot of those laws that made sense before we had a lunatic and charge
Maybe you don't like it shouldn't
Normally we would never do
It's a bad idea to release classified information
Don't know what the response really will be
Also
Trump is a criminal but communicated with the Russian government to steal our election
Rodger stone is involved and that means a local cut out clearly copper
If I was a Russian agent he's opened up the door to accepting like
Unwillingly done some shyt
But I still think that even simonette
Funny guys
Ray Charles America in America I mean
I've been saying that for years I think those would you need to take away from all that is that even just
Eve
Like
Crazy we don't usually do this but here's the
Here's the truth
They don't usually do that they all signs at
Is crazy
Unprecedented swordplay
People who have lifelong careers in National Security
Information
Stuff
You know like clandestine s***
Think they can't
Go against their operating
Turtle conditioning Tire life
We got to get some bettas in there because bettas
Probably right
So let's get the Friday
Friday
Is a wild ride
Until we die
You're selling this real strong
There's a lot of nonsense
Okay
My standard
Women who are accusing
Trump of stuff are liars
That they're liars and Beyond
A great deal of time
Critiquing there a
So we're talking about the women who accused Trump of sexual assault
Just say that he asked for their phone number
That's what he thinks
The whole thing is about
Thinks that's what you telling his audience about
The Trump was like hey
I want to take you out on a date like we're in the
I would like your number but I would like your father to accompany us so we both know that Noah kind of hanky-panky
And those women
So impolitely
Said
No thank you
Yes and then beyond that his further narrative is that everyone's getting paid to lie about
Let's start with the first clip
Beware Alex's feelings lie about the
He wants that we need to both probably work out more we're both getting wet
Reception
Ugly
Calling ugly
I think it's in the realm of what you would call it certainly no
Absolutely I feel like I feel like some people I have made those i+
Claim
It's certainly not what Alex is doing
Yeah
Like that just continues
Like you says that over and over
Just like this
Stuff like that
That sort of thing
Even if you are a propaganda
With nothing
Why would you go that route
It's so it looks so bad
Looks like you have nothing
Because if you are a white supremacist
List which I would argue
Percent of his audience
Yeah that idea of like
You're not pretty enough for me to rape you is a
Threat
Tastic
Parliamentary
There's a dude who's in the parliament
Who is Ben Affleck
Grand old dictatorship that they had before
Famously said to Dilma Rousseff
The prime minister
You're too ugly for me to rape you
Right yeah
So that to me seems like a signal to those guys have like
Well of course I would
Of course
Much like me insofar as
He would help
I guess that's sort of evil
What cuz it does sort of imply that if they were more attractive it would be believable as the behavior is believable
Not good
No that is of course but only for the pretty women who haven't yet
I meant
Hoo boy that's not a good start
Credit these women Alex refers to a story that came out in the hill
Is that
Has to do with
Some high-powered lawyers going around about Trump
Explain why I don't
Affirm
The 750000 dollars
Poems for the good of the country
Outfits for the greater cuz you know he's a misogynist and you know sex is ready but just yet let's just
We own the story also I saw 300
So that's not good
He should not be referencing the tapes
I've been
Told about them also
Also you should be reporting this
Best second hand
And he's just making up these lurid details about like to come and knock on your door
Teleprompter
Good that
If these tapes are real
Even if that's true that's bad reporting
I've been told about the tapes
That's not good
It's not necessarily unusual you don't you don't get about dope
There are a lot of times where it's like
Unnamed sources in the government have told me and you're like well that's bulshit he has the right to rule
Yes the right to report that someone is told me there are
He doesn't have the right to do an improv scene where he ripped
Content
Implying the level of knowledge
He does not have
If you listen to the tape
Why don't you
Tell us what's on the tapes
Also apparently with these dates are about
Lisa Bloom Lisa Bloom is the person who allegedly has gone
Tried to offer women money
To come out and make up stories about Trump if you believe that that's what the
Narrative isn't with the tapes
I don't give a s***
Whatever Lisa Bloom was doing
I don't think was related to anybody in any official capacity
Even if this is true
She was the person who was defending Harvey Weinstein
When the allegations came out and then sort of dude I got a distance
Myself
When Ronan Farrow was coming out with his pieces
About 70 was working on the pieces about Weinstein
She actually offered him opposition research on Rose McGowan
Trying to discredit victims
Preemptively
So I don't really give a s*** what you was doing
I don't think I I think that she has no purchase
Here in terms of being working for any official
Globalist
No
I don't care if this is true then you have a s*** head doing s*** head things
You don't have
Exactly different version of project veritas
Like a concerted effort
Buy all the anti Trump forces using Lisa Bloom to do this
All of these people who are allegedly on tape are not the people who have come forward
So even if Lisa Bloom is running some weird Rogue activity that doesn't discredit the p
People who have come out already
It only does in s******* Minds were like
Is that why why
Would you do this more than enough already
I don't I don't have a whole lot of respect for her at this point
So Alex is on is on a hot tip
About about sexual harassment stuff he wants
To make sure we talked about all of it except for Trump and Roy mowers
So he gets to Astoria Kansas City
About the representative
Misogynistic
Renton General naturally esoteric
Perfect
Kan Jam
Andrea Ramsey accused of sexual harassment
Will drop out of us
CalFresh
And Congress
Kansas City Star ask her about accusation 2005 lawsuit that she sexually harassed and
Who said he had projected advances
Good
Goodbye
I'm older woman
Advances and she has any power over there more vindictive than the cases I've seen with a
Weather
Bookcases
And you are the victim of such a case
Let's remember that Harvey Weinstein Mossad to follow women
Let's think about the level of vindictive there
Like some lady
I looked into this and what the
I'm inclined to believe the guy I don't I don't I don't know all the particulars of all other details
Chances are
Well the reason that you dropped out still claims
Some form of MSN
The reason that you
Liberals and Democrats have implemented
So there's a zero tolerance
It's for people who harass subordinate
Just-in-time right we got there yeah now I guess
But the situation is there's a guy who works for her and she had proposition
He said he claims it
The office
Just ignored him
His career suffered because of it
I like I said I believe him I don't put that level of vindictiveness
He's very bad
But it's not getting massage
Involved
Although there are a mean Meek Mill is going to prison for two years because of a rogue sexual
Play harassing judge
Interesting
Think about this so Meek Mill everything about this
Meek Mill is a very very talented
Beef
He was on probation for
Play longer than his
Crime would ever have
Warranted
Mainly because this judge
Kept following him around like
When he was doing charity work
She would show up
She would tell him that he needs to put her name and song
He needs to do remixes of like Boys to Men song and reference
So f****** thing
Every probation officer is like why is this guy been on probation
For three years when it was only supposed to be like 6 months
Start it never seen anything like it in this particular case
That's crazy he just got
He just
Went to prison
For violating his probation
What you shouldn't have been on it
Exact
In his capacity of
Traveling
As a
Very very talented
Performing shows
Which he got permission to do from his probation office
And this
She then claimed that she never received the email and never signed off on it even though
We have records that you did
Not on appeal
Meek Mill will get out but he's going to be in prison for a while
Elementary
Disgusting
Powerslide garbage
It's just the sentiment diseases modern culture culture.
You're getting it
Torturing killing kids
Retail stuff
Thomas jump start going away
What is
More things around
Exactly
That sounds exactly like him
Projecting
It is a psychic disease
I've described the globalist live globalist mythology as a brain virus
I believe that's okay
Bizarre version of an understanding of
Evil
Where is care of the big stuff in the small stuff goes away under plays
Discount what he's
Describing as a one
Like I don't think it's a one
I think alike
How do you spell
Might be a one or vandalism AsiaOne matica harassment of people in
In order to
No no
Sure
Petty theft
That's a whole different world different world
We live in frankli under maritime law which is the only one that I accept
Executed
Okay well then they have your own Court
So I don't know
It's kind of
Petty and stupid
Don't really get you anywhere but it is complete
It keeps you from
Look if your idea is worried only about the
The big crime
Write only about that
Then
You wind up discounting
Everything else
We got to deal with this over here
And then any problem
Well it's not raping and torturing
So let's
Not worried
Fantasy 10
Is not real
Do everything Alex complains about he thinks is a time and they have problems but then everything else is nothing
The other dangerous
Are you presenting
This false world where people aren't working
Against Child exploitation investigating those sorts of things
Human trafficking
That's a conversation I'm willing to have as long as you go
Also sexual harassment is a crime and it's a good thing that we're rooting these people
But Alex has never liked. On-air been like everyone to donate to these organizations are working against humans
Trafficking
Play on the ground he just cares about it
Exploding people's fears about them
So
Anyway
Is Mexico if Alex gets into talking about the accent Hollywood
Trump fat with Billy bush
I feel like this has been covered
More than enough
Etui it has
But it's been covered on all along all the angle
Alex's take Elvis episode does Friday the 15th episode is really interesting cuz he takes a journey
He starts
Here and then after this clip I'll play you where he ends up
He finds Colonel Kurtz
Such a mess
He contradicts himself within the course of an episode and it's
Just bizarre
He's so
Desperate grasping at straws
Lie about
Even just basic reality
To the point where like here's what he says at the beginning
And then I'll play you what he says
At the end
Citronal discharge coming out as it is
They're just
Cover it
And still have the fake women
He's talking about like
We talk about this another episode his prediction that come January
He's going to ignore the fact that
Did Lisa Bloom is paying them all at night
I mean this is all the stuff
Patriot kontrolfreek
He's going to run around raping women
1 years old before we find out about it
Yeah that's going to happen
Give me the people sign a bunch of non-disclosure agreement
You settle courses cases out of court
Punkpost no one and know him well Rodger Stone
Coronavirus map
Absolute
One recording behind the scenes
And then I grabbed
He grabbed them by the p****
So long as you grab
Refrigerator games
Rehab
Indifferent
I mostly kept that towards the end cuz I had that gross slurp noise
Love him desperately trying to breathe
So I mean if you go back and actually listen to the Access Hollywood tape
Secretly recording
Doesn't sound like that at all
Even the gravel by the p**** part is
Disgusting
But I I think
I think the
You could make an argument if you're Alex Jones
What he's
Saying is
That I don't believe in locker room talk
But I think he could make that argument
Better about Zack quote
Zane about
The quote
From the same time
Where Trump says
I can't help myself sometimes I just start kissing
That's because that implies
Awareness of agency
He knows that that is something that he does and he's talking about how he does it the grabbing by the p**** part
Could just be like
The dirty talk
Or something like that
It's not but
The reason that that to me
No
I'm sorry Terminator up
He can't say that and why it's important
Is because so many Republican voters
Especially with his bulshit of like
They hate Christians and all that stuff
All of these Christians all of our lives
I've constantly like I'm not allowed to say p****
Around my
You know
I'm not allowed to say that
The public can you still vote
No matter what you do f*** you well it's cuz it comes down to the radicalization of evangelicals with things that they
Supposedly
Should care more about which is what Alex Jones is
Make you fraid of demon
That are all liberals
Iams I all that s*** perfect man
Talk about how crazy it is the women want to f*** in my bunch and you know that
And the reality is
As many times has of of this
His listeners would be like
I did vote for a ghost
Well the bigger problem
Frequent
Instances
Literally
Just grab
You know that
He said that in what was it like 2015
The tape from Access Hollywood something like that
Putting his hand up
People skirts
S*** like that at Home Alone 2
What is brutal
Come on man I like
I don't like
The point being
Is because that exist
I feel like it gives
Me. With witch
Switch to invalidate
Annie Christian
Like anytime if my parents
Personality
No I
I mean like the ones are the ones who voted for him
Consistently talk about the more the morality of homosexuality or whatever it is
Is along those lines
All of that s*** is gone apocracy and into a complete
You don't really believe anything's so f*** you under the bed in the demographics of the Alabama
Not even when you look at the racial and gender breakdown
But you look at like Evangelical Christians voting for Roy Moore in
Drastic numbers
The only way to do that is to just assume that everyone's lying about everyone's the people who are lying are demonic
Runaway
And that clip
Alex Jones is defensive Trump with that clip
Together
Of things he said
He's just an old but good man whose like it's crazy that women want to f****** like this cuz I'm celebrity
Tape where they edited
And put it into that
Oh
Oh my
That
Where else would you edit together Trump saying p****
I think from this season of Celebrity Apprentice that had that Bret Michaels on it
OK Google trying to not take responsibility for out there
Yeah they're pretzels at work I never watch that show
So
I know that little pop-up businesses
Never watch that shows there's money in the banana
Anyway
That was his defense in neck
Later on in the show this is one of the only times
We're going to go out of chronological order in the episode
Comparison
Little bit later someone calls in
And talks about how you can just make
People say
Fake stuff
With audio and video technology
Okay
Now that's
Right
Considered that and what's the caller calls narrative
Light bulb
Someone just put it in a
Perfect so
So here is him putting the pieces together and also
Doing a little bit of a rambling
Intro music
Your call cuz they're all still great and they bring
We got to run from the globalist
Oh do it
Marching out of the Babylon into the stars in the future
Rod run
I would listen to that show
And Ron
Run
Coffee
Now shut off one sentence other words
Setbeat voiceprint
So he I don't have
Keep all the same cuz we plays the video of a guy demonstrating the technology
From years ago couple years back
And it just doesn't get to anything that proves his
I assume he doesn't.
Formed by there are ways you can
Tell friend
People can take the audio and see
I know things have been edited
It is a really interesting future
A version of it
You might
You can pick something
I didn't demonstration
Sims 2 on YouTube of video technology
You speak and it is able to actually alter the
Mouth of the person who's talking
Stuff is incredibly scary
A few years too early we're not there yet and also Billy Bush as I get
Dunlop
Analysis of it
Why
We all know he said
Easiest mystery to solve ever ever we don't need to go into voice
The only thing that I care to bring up and talk about is
Is the idea that Alex had The Narrative of a caller calls in technology
Alex fails
Play a clip
Exploring the technology and I need like
What
What do you think of
An old
I from Up
I don't know alright
What even is a fuddy-duddy
I don't care look up
Allergens Italian
Earlier in the week Alex Jones
Want to fuc cars
I did not see that coming
It took me by surprise
He also relates to homosexuality
Mechanophilia
Subset of people who are
Sexually attracted to machines
I married the Eiffel Tower
Don't f****** get in my in anybody
Harmless
To a certain extent
Bar in 2000's
If you have three questions
To get across
That I find offensive
2 questions
There was a video that went viral
The story about a guy who claimed
Go to England to Calamity that sex with 1000 cars
Almost 10 years ago now every time he's
There was a
Popular about 10 years ago as a point of conversation
I got back
Sure so I'll
When Alex
Disgusting
He was discussing it at in terms of like
He Compares it to homosexuality
Inasmuch as like why do I got to respect all this stuff
All your letters
And stuff like all your lgbtq f****** cars
What he's doing is he's taking
Like soda
Very
Basic
Sexual identity
Bring them into paraphilia what's next
Exactly exactly
Exactly
He
Did this
Weird
Too f****** anime
I feel like yeah
Well inasmuch as ones alive yes
I don't know just like from a
Bass Lake mechanic Stampy you're splitting hairs I don't want to go down this road
The point is is it like
Rodger Stone
Stone of Rodger Stone
Yeah it is
So
Alex earlier in the week
It wasn't that he was 121 comparing being gay with f****** cars
But in his rank he was so unclear about what he was talking about and what is complaining about
The people on like Media Matters
Told that it was like a homophobic rant in cars
And to be fair to them they were wrong
Yeah there was there was homophobia in it but he wasn't
Spain gay people f***
Cars he wasn't saying that
And if they works
But Alex think that's what he was
They were saying he was saying
So on Friday
He rants about the reaction to the rant
In a very weird way
Troubling
This is very troubling
Like
A long time ago
I would have are far away
Great movie
Creep movie
What
Brexit
Craziest f****** thing of course he's mad that he people think that he said that he thinks that he
He's misrepresenting coverage of him being super unclear by what he's talking about
Exactly
It's just this
It's like I was
Sea of fog
Get out of it
Here is this dogshit wrapped and goes on on Friday
Oh you're going to
Surgeries in Europe
Where they remove bleach in your eye
I tried to find you like not a surgery
But he saying there's hundreds
In all of Europe
I don't know maybe there's hundreds of cases people pouring in their own eyes
Statistically sighting I miss my road I don't want to go.
Applying to balls
All he's going off of
Is a tiny clip that he has
From a British show that's like My Strange Addiction whatever this
Stuff like that
Human-interest sort of shows
He's just misrepresenting like a years old 3 minutes left
Flickr show that's like a look at it look at how we're doing
Version and not racist version of like humans
Are We Now do on till
I like
Just got this image of a guy out of his front lawn
Just sitting out on his front lawn just poured bleach into his eye labors of water
That's f******
I really approve of this proud of you
Bully
Okay
I don't think he believes that
A robot
Isabel
This is how they do it
Marco's mother's Brandon John I buy alternative
Seriously
The Articles to videos the report
Garfunkel
Infowarsstore.com we need funding
Yeah
So I mean
You know it like you can smell it coming from a mile away
We're going to race across Europe
And then
I didn't
Like a
People explorers and f****** animals
Stroud on the you know there's no one around
Shitbreak I don't
Look
Pictures of all human behavior it's just all pathetic like
Because it can't he's he's yelling about like I don't need to know the abbreviations
I don't need to know the letters
Unlike the letters are not talking about people
We're talking about people who are
You know very
Legitimate
Here's a conversation maybe we should have
People who f*** cars are less oppressed than gay people
To some extent yeah how do you consider that Alex
In the acronym
Because they're fine
They don't need an advocacy group
Everybody's more like
Don't do that in public
You see a guy like started robbing a car in a garage
It's troubling
Like
If you've ever met a card
Dude there's such an autoerotic
Auto
Auto-erotic
Mechanophilia
Do you allow those guys if you left them alone with their cars for too long
On the car
Quite frankly I don't care
I really don't care
Have I got a YouTube video for live
Live your life
That's what I say that's my motto you know what I've seen people get married
There are
I don't know if the state recognizes
Is the marriage between man in Colorado
What's the car
Look
But I have a lot of fun and make jokes and stuff but like
Is doing is he's complaining
Sexual identity
Sexual orientation
With
These
I mean I don't I don't think they're wrong or bad but they are
Certainly
Very anomalous
Yeah and they fall under the heading
Paraphilia
Sexual fetishes
Might be.
Destructive
It's not necessarily
Destructive but it's certainly way outside the realm
Abnormal human behavior
TLC
It's usually TLC where I live
So he can't leave his house
What it is
Televised free
More less
And there's the reason that there's a real because
Images of percentages of that population are
Nothing ridiculous
It's just
Annabelle inability
To understand
People are saying
Is inability to understand
Criticism or unwillingness
Is unwillingness to
Or it's a testament to the strength of his ability
To ignore and misunderstand
Unwillingness
To disconnect
The idea of
Homosexuality transgender
Issues with
I f***** my car he thinks that they're all free
I'm so jumpy lumps them all into one that's
Is still not a defensible position because your position is
Freak don't have rights
You believe that you need to understand
Still wrong
That's still the most wrong
Like if your defense is being gay is exactly like f****** a car
And so you shouldn't have rights the answer to that
Are you a human being
So you get
So you have those right you all right that's how human human rights
We have
Fair enough let's move on
You better road to go down here
Send a text to Alex Jones has brought in Rodger Stone
Expert witness Rodger Stone
Already felon
Rogers the two of them have a conversation about
Watch that press conference I rolled it back and watched it three times when they brought out the so-called
Call victim
Their Force
4 years
I mean
Yeah I know these women were his typing when he was single he dated supermodel and virtually only two
Supermodel
Standards myself
This is this is sad
This is sad the conversation
About these women being too ugly for Trump baby
That's a major selling point of his argument now
Lisa Bloom is paying them all and they're too f****** ugly they look like aliens or praying mantis
It's not good
No and it also is reinforcing the exact
World view that the people who are coming out with
Sexual assault
Allowing this to continue
So that's great
Rodger Stone
He talks about how he's being sued that Amicus
You talk about that a little bit and he's like isn't it crazy they won't let me
They won't let me Grill Clapper
They won't let me he won't he won't come into court and let me cross-examine Emily
Roblox
Is he
Write this is part of the antifreeze is part of a lawsuit
Against Trump and Rodger Stone
Because of the WikiLeaks
Right there is an issue where number of people's personal identities
Their personal information got leaked
Into the public because of those
WikiLeaks
Disclosure
Campaign
And Rodger stone for there
Complicity in
The promotion of those leaks
And the possible being involved with
Yeah they totally because Breeze is establishing to Atherton
Extent that
And
That Russian intelligence has a history going back
Nylon
Cold war-era especially since 2001
Came into power
Using local people to
Disseminate information
There
Turtle Point man in countries
Where is
Ratso Epi read the entire briefing
Yeah they did
They did that
And
We can't tell you that Rodger stone is responsible for a lot of this stuff
4 reasons
So
He talked about that and he just misses it
Anna plays the victim in
Like a sad little snowflake
He says one
About one of the women
Accusing Donald
I don't want to know what
Actually really great
I don't understand
What you mean by that it's great because it's so weak
But it also points the finger back at him
In a way that he probably should be much more careful with his words
Okay
I think you have to hold some of the ammunition back I am chasing a very active story
One of the women who suck user
Who was on The Apprentice
Repeatedly in her application to even get on the show
If you lie about one thing
You lie about every
Rodger Stones belief
About his career
I have bad news about Alex's career
I've bad news if you hold anyone to that standard
Lying on an application to a f****** reality show
Who gives a s***
When I was in college
Of course I did
You were like
You got to know a lot about Alex Jones to be on the show and then we've sort of pivoted through this no
This new format where you know nothing about it
Well I was the most qualified
Certainly
But I am going to sue you for lying about
I just think it's really fascinating William documented Liars
Get together
And complain about someone else lying
An Oculus
And then say that it indicates that everything they do is not credible
Unjust
For people to lie about
But they're doing
She's lying about him
It's about my boy
Yeah you do that stated that's a really interesting question
No it's not how much.
These guys
Associate themselves with his identity
And I think there's different reasons for it just might be a little bit out there
Speculative but I believe that the reason
For it
Well that's part of it
I think it's hierarchical to
Certain extent like I believe that Rodger Stone
Is defensive of trump
At this point
For safety
Because attacks on Trump or attack on him he understand
We get this layer up I'm under there that sort of thing
I don't know Alex is at
Delta Epsilon
He's down there cuz
His fear and identification
Alphabet
Alpha Beta
Delta Lambda Zeta
Iota Omicron Salon Omega
Epsilon the second time around up here
Send the name of the bad guy in the Megaman
Pipe C
Are two different letters row
I should have done this in order to
Numu
So I can run out anyway
Happy Jew
The rallying cry numu happy to
But I can't I think Alex's
Does
Certain a jerk need to defend Trump is based on things that Rodger has told him
But there's a filter
Like Rodger isn't telling him if Trump goes down we're all going to prison
Spinning to Alex's well
He is our last defense against the
Globalist have you
Beating into Alex's narrative
Is
Conscious he knows
Did if Trump goes down he's in
Very serious legal trouble
Consciously and overtly
It's more
I need my mission to become
Completed and Trump will help complete that mission both very
Personally involved in stopping
To me that makes sense
The weird part
Is that
Ticket is Perez a text on
That
Like
I'm fine if you're Rodger Stone and you're saying well in attack on Trump is an attack on my
What seems to be the case though is
If it's an attack on Trump
It's an attack on me personal
Well that's the brand
That's a branding Trump is Oliver
Compass
Esbl figurehead of our
I all this stuff of course
Bomber that's a long time pushing
Flex glue
Alex is mad about just
Results
But Amazon who wouldn't be
Apparently
He's trying to shut down Alex Jones
So he's complaining about that
2 territory
You probably should
They're actively trying to get us shutdown
Jerry's kids shirt
Shut up
They're not his box
Amazon
Because then they put off Chinese knockoffs on there
Alarm products
Undercut so we have to be on Amazon
To be able to declare that we
Amazon
It's all strategic
She's on it
Exactly
Just like Trump has to do something you got to be in the swamp
We had hundreds of resellers most of it's fake
Problem
To shut down the Amazon to shut down
Good Lord what is a gentleman
We're in a war I'm on the deck of a ship they are shooting Rush
Christmas every year houses funded the next year decided to go stay the same
Pressure point
Been expanding for 22 years
Someone has I believe I believe it's based on the reality that we sing
In front of a euro
Oh man
The thing that I want to talk about it I've heard corsi break
Heart Hospital
They don't go viral but they're also real right
And you can't listen true know there is a problem with that
Sure there's a couple
Interesting
If you're positive I like crazy
I'm so the other thing I don't talk about there is that what he's complaining about is this idea that I have to be on Amazon
Cuz if I'm not
Then there'll be resellers who pop up on Amazon
But don't follow the rules of reselling my stuff
I don't really like but it's also ironic considering
He started
Fortified supply.com in order to get around reselling agreements
With the people that he resells
We get the entire thing we talked about like a week ago week cuz I started the traffic there and around
Prosperity
The same thing to keep suppliers with his stuff
Oh yeah but it's bad what happened
To him
He doesn't care about those other people
It's so pathetic
It's not Amazon it's these other resellers we're just doing the same game you're doing
Do you not understand it like you
Behaving in this way makes it okay for everyone.
Who cares about agreement
I feel like you fundamentally misunderstood
No I understand it
They're living it
Yeah but you drew you misunderstood it
The point is
Only wait what was the definition of prosperity
Send a text with Alex capitalism is great when you're
When your beneficiary and would all your rules are followed everyone just
Gets in line but
So this next clip Alex 58
Exactly Alex
Caller asks
Tim about a steak
Story
It's pretty interesting how I look
Response
Does Alex know about the
We'll see
Alex
Preciate all you do thank you for accepting the calling out here in Arizona Niles Amazon
Exactly
Baseball to your sources that you can talk about but it's insisted of the
CIA headquarters raided by the Marine recently mixed with
4094 districts which could be for
How to get related Mass arrests it could be nothing more than game prosecution consisting of
The question
Beaver
That's why I bring it up to you I didn't know if you had any more definitive
Real bombshell story
I have an alternative Theory
That is that a lot of people
And they post
It's not the globalist
Patriot news
Why did
Don't say in looking at these reports
What do you mean
Are there reports
Well they're like
Okay so this guy
What does referring to some sort of weird website where they posted blog
The military has invaded CIA headquarters there take down the Deep state
Isn't going to be like
Also did you know that they just raided the CIA headquarters
Pivots but you need to learn about how
How to tell if one of these callers is crazy
In plain sight to some degree
So like
He goes on to be like
They're probably going to take out
Maybe the military didn't
Hey babe
So I can take out all these pedophiles right
Now it's like yeah they are
CIA
You believe that the Murray
No Posse Comitatus
Show me the Marines do not operate
Arsenal
Investigating police Secret Service
Should have told him they're investigating
Hold on now
Do you know that the Secret Service they're only invest
The Gate of arm is about yes
Counterfeit money
Protecting the president
Physically
It's not about nobody ever really even knows why
That was just one of those weird de-facto things
Good people in the Marines are going to investigate
Storm
The Marines
The big one
Home commands
Quantico here's the problem that you don't understand
What does even a year into doing the podcast I really don't think that
Do you understand the dirt
Like weird websites that promote these sort of narrative
There are
Thousands of them out there
That people just stab
Oh I like this guy's right it's you know what it's a small version
Like
There are a thousand websites
That tell you what's going on with Russell
Successful version
No cuz no one else does
Yeah that's a good to take so long f****** time
There's a bunch of places where you can get varying degrees of
The same sort of
Nation about like what's going on in The Narrative of the WWE
Without the writing style you like and then some other guy
Text guy going to report guy or am I
Our friend
There are all the graduation
Congratulations
I'd like to tell him
Good luck
Good to hear is doing that it's
Very emotionally draining
Be that as it may
You have all these people need to choose whichever voice you want
In terms of like this
This appeals to me I like this waiting
World of Wings
Conspiracy s*** there is the same thing
In terms of there are tons of people were spitting
Fairly similar narratives on blogs
I like I like this guy's riding I'm going to subscribe to him
Evan becomes your
Place to get that news
There are hundreds of them on the Internet
And they're all
Full of s***
And most of them spit stuff like this right like the Marines
Invaded the CIA
Report
Rumor
Right
Sources have told us Bible.
But that's the mentality of almost about
You have to understand
But they believe stuff like that
CIA that would be a firefight
Totally
Would you remember like
9 months ago we did that episode where they used talking about how they had a fire fight it up
Pedophile compound
Yeah but that's not the reason but I think it was the Marines who had invaded the pedal
Survival compound or whatever they would make
Annamarie had a firefight
You don't know if there was
We do not know that there was their weapons changes
Reading the CIA headquarters sooner or later
People in the CIA
Do the killing those ones love Alec
Right now there's the pencil neck
Chickenshit about Larry Nichols
And jingles
The pencil pushers
No gun that no gunfire needs
I know I just want a movie where there's a war between the
Look
Even Alex Jones so I can know that this is b*******
The globalist
Engendered is very
Empowered and
Population
The CIA in the Marine battle that's like alien
Predator but way better but how do we do this without anyone knowing
That's going to be the entry
The CIA they're covering it up
That's it we're about to get into
The part of the show where I would say Alex loses it a little bit
Alien he doesn't want to talk to callers
He is sort of in a place where he's like
No more
Paul Joseph Watson going to host the fourth hour but I
I got a long way to go
There's one story that I really want to talk about
To it yet
I got to feel sometime
Let's talk about that
That's a good way to go
The Betrayal the deception
We have to be tested
Eternal consciousness
Great
System that we are
Engineers of Avila
Cops are just saying we're in the waiting room
Get manufactured
But got to get us to do it
They tried to get us made a God to build him his whole new universe
Batman
He's going to take them
Devils already got robots
Need you
He asked you
You'll find out
That's a good point
That's my favorite thing
Finally after a year of doing this
Favorite thing
The devil he needs you to build him a new universe write anybody
He doesn't need you you'll find out such comedy like
In those pauses
Cuz you not looking good
You know
At least some experience with Alex that like
As he's pausing there's just look on his face of like
I just devil has robot
Jim I just shot my wad with the devil I'm going to refractory. I guess
Do you want to talk about about what's going on
That's like
Their moments
Alex Ware
He does something accidentally and just cuz you
He's kind of panicking a little bit that are 10 times funnier than any joke I've ever heard inside out
I've never heard anything funnier than that
Cuz you know what Alex accidentally understands
Tension and release
Bob Hope ever wrote there's so much tension that's built up with this idea of like the devil is trying to
Create a make us create in the University's going to kill us
Biblical law the long pauses cervix Stilwell atoms of building up the tension
Then the release the punchline
If I were Jim in Toronto
I don't want to come to Stage 2 that I supposed to follow that
Consequential
Following devil worship
Kim Possible
Alex
Asserts that the
Of women
Talking about how they have also been sexually harassed
Antabuse
Just about trying to attack me
It's already out most of its bulshit trying to attack
Toxic masculinity
But also
Beyond that
A little bit and this next
He should just not do it like if I was him
If I was just giving him advice
Which once again we should not be doing and get a few hires up
4A
Good amount
I would think about it I'd like to meet Daria
Pretend that never happened with him pretending it didn't happen is that there's too many records of what he
She said back then
We have records of all the s*** he said it hasn't mattered about all that here and then on the other end
Miss you then
Free
They're obviously reading this for Trump
That's what he's been getting
Here's a low-tech example of what they do
10 months ago before she left Fox News
Alex Jones saying Hillary
Portrait children to death in the basement
Other pizza place
But no kiss before Alex gets into it he's kind of
Fair on this
They Megyn Kelly on her show did Play a clip out of context
In a report about
Yeah but the issue is that Alex is being super unclear about what
Talkin about
Pulled from
RLX
And the other problem is that Alex
His point that he's going to make when I keep playing the clip
Is that Hillary Clinton
Through her support of the oven
Withrow of Libya is responsible for the raven
Killing of children what-have-you
But the problem is in that clip
He says
She personally raped and murdered these
His children and stuff like that which is
Linguistically difficult
I understand why a overburden researcher clip puller for MSNBC or 5
Fox News something like that
It's not necessarily the most.
Beautiful thing but Alex
Is also right
They did take it a bit out of
Contact
Said out loud that Obama
Personally
Is responsible for the not even personally responsible for
Does not personally did
Sing
That's the language you used
See now that's a different situation that's why I'm that's why I G
She's personally responsible for this Friday to bring your Obama comparison
Do the shaky allowed to happen if you're making decisions on that level
Your decisions are going to lead to a trot
Exactly in her capacity as secretary
Responsible
But when you use the language of
Personally raped and murdered children
He's using
This
Decent point he has to lie about a more
Salient point that he should watch his
Is language
Iran
Venti said that this clip is what I'm saying about this guy
Is by James alefantis owner of Comet Ping Pong Pizza
Disgust
Alex Jones had to give a formal apology
Which I didn't say
Car that have sold into slavery by the tens of thousands murdered women
That was rear-ended
I do this whole rant about that and she has together
And they put it out I'm sick she's in the basement herself
Portrait Georgia
Nope
Mix it around
A minute
Call Michelle
F*** you
Hillary six-channel break
What was happening
Petter supposedly I need to know
So a couple of very Salient facts
But need to be brought up
And fired his rifle
5 interview said that he was tired
I listen to Infowars
Save those children
I need to go get to the bottom of it
Clips that will you play that Alex has to delete from the internet on successful
He is said someone should go look into this
Why that guy did
One of those
Second Amendment folks
Trump and say
You were the one who said I hope the Second Amendment
Go after Hillary
Weird the other thing I need to bring into focus is that
The last
Alex Jones had a Gaston
Show
To talk about Bitcoin
Here's a Bitcoin expert
A Bitcoin expert by the name of Dave Seaman
And you don't know who that guy is I remember A Man Named Dave Seaman
Because
Is a funny name
Dave Seaman
Was
One of the
Biggest forces Bhai
I'd
Coin expert
Is the guy who always videos are now taking off
He was leading the charge
She's putting out frequent videos about the bass
About various
Instagram post
That Comet Ping Pong and put out here
Just course Bazaar narrative around himself where he was being threatened
And oh my God
The globalist
Coming to get me because I'm uncovering all this stuff you guys need to support me give me money
He made tons
Funny how people
Is the globalist were coming after him because of his knowledge of Bitcoin
I can't stress this enough his videos are gone from the internet but I watch this unfold in real-time
Watching the entire pizzagate thing happens from
Jump from the beginning of
And what Dave Steven is doing now is the same thing that Alex
She's doing cuz David videos from the internet
Amy has a pizzagate recap
Onnit
Where he's trying to make it all about the things that were said in the WikiLeaks
Squinting
No it's all there
It's all there forever everything's going on there
Is a devil worshiper basement killing kids
He was
A hundred percent
The most prominent figure
Who was pushing that stuff
Created a hoax
About people trying to
The Killing
Pretended he had to get off the grid
And disappear to a cabin somewhere
That sort of s*** right
George Lucas tried to tell us that he never invented minute
Vulture
Bulshit Lucas
Exactly that one's on you man on his show
In the last week
As a repurposed
Bitcoin enthusiasts
When
He is not
He is one of the
People who I'd like to hear
Post about this
You likened it to
Came
Yes
Before he was Cain he was Dr Isaac yankem
He was a wrestling dentist
Alright
Don't work if they're doing the same game
I was being too
But it's the same thing that I am done with himself he's repackaged what he said about pizzagate
And allowed Dave Siemens come on his show as a Bitcoin
ABC Monroe to book about Buzz
About how he's all about Buzz
And how he would deny the existence of air that got him attention
So maybe we don't need to pay attention to what you're saying then exclamation
Listen to some
Exact yourself and then let's go further another step
Alex has Jack the sobiech on the all the time who was another proponent of the literal pizzagate
Went to Comet Ping Pong
Red
Spurious rumors about the video
Direct on their own
About this stuff and it's not okay
Not okay
Pissed off about it
I'm super pissed off about it
Bulshit
And these dudes
Are disabled
He protects those videos are still around
All these guys
Or just
Engaged in large-scale fraud
They're engaged in large-scale lying and manipulation
And then what it doesn't work out there like I wasn't saying that
Videos Man
Videos of intelligent
This is not
This isn't okay
You can't get away with this
I'm furious
I agree with you
Main difference I was listening to that rent going like f****** keep on going
Listen to my rants like this f****** guy better shut up I've got more facts
To get to
You dare that was great I enjoyed it
How dare you giving you positive reinforcement expense criticism
Portsmouth he's criticism of you
Using the powers of enforcement
To chastise you for the wave God
FairPoint
I love you Dad love you too
Observe this next clip this one we're going to have fun with
This next clip is actually going to be fun
There's nothing better than
Two people having a moment of where it's like
Alright
It doesn't matter
Conceived this shows
Lightly like Mystery Science Theater in the center
That we are trapped in this room talking about something that neither of us would like to
Agree
We just got movie sign it's time to get back to the business I have never had a like
When we first started there were plenty of times where you were listening to be talked over the clips like
Are you doing and now you kind of felt like that's what I've always thought of it as if you anywhere listening except for the point where I
Is this turned out an angle where that makes sense
Servo every now and again
Actually get to a little bit
That much shut up
We can actually have some fun
As Alex Jones misrepresent
Another right-wing sexual abuser in a very comical way
Great
Grapevine
He's great in the new version
Fine
What is gentleman
Regardless
Face value
After you have experts
Warriors
Like
I really sore
You're going to have sex with a sandwich I mean it was really
O'Reilly
But
What's 15 million
Chocolate really stupid
There's lots of examples
Cherry outfit
So here's what I want to say
The end I like everything else like everything clear
So I wouldn't most telling
So now what he's talkin about with
Diego Chavez sandwich
Spandex
Do you want know about this
No why would I know so Bill O'Reilly when he got in trouble for the sexual harassment
Stuff last time or the time before last
Did the classic one
Yes and the ones like Matt Lauer the front with the one from years back involved to call that he made to a lady was talking to
Falafel
Around
He meant
Human loofah
You just didn't know the word
What is very clear that he was talking about robbing a loofah around
What
Bill O'Reilly thought
A roofer was Falafel he's probably drunk or on pills or something like that just was like
Falafel
Clip giving out fake news
But innocent is it is entirely
Which I've done
Did you say you do
Use chocolate sauce a whole bunch of live your life
Why would that do
Falafel not count in the same Vape
I think it would be structurally and logistically much more difficult than chocolate sauce using essential oil
Okay
I shan't
A b look
I don't want to talk about that stuff like logistic
Pics of sex with food I want
Fajitas
Bad idea I want to talk about the fact that
Even liberal
When they make fun of the Falafel stuff it's
Because everyone knows he misspoke
Was talking about a loofah
Alex legitimately is presenting it as like
Hey bro you like sex with sandwiches
Don't call your producer with that
That's one piece of
More important
Don't sexually assault your producer with that with sandwich
But the fact that
He doesn't know that
Like it's a very easily explainable
Well the fact that he thinks the problem
Sandwich Joy
Sure
Maybe a larger issue
Problem is so much further
Towards the beginning of the question
Then when you get all the way to sandwich
Totally like there's
Like there's a long time ago
Like all the way up to sandwiches
You are totally right big picture butts
Alex Jones podcast and that seems like such an elementary point I'm more fixated on the fact that he is
Will. Is there a Riley was actually talking about
This is our Bill O'Reilly's Nancy Pelosi
Sure Riley's denial he doesn't even know what the fuc
Next clip Alex talks about David
Wrightwood now dead
Yes
You should not f*** with
What's the weather today
Don't do it
Yelled at the person
So really bad about it
She's not listening to
I am a problem
I'm a problem at Subway cuz you know what I want
Cuz I want
Jardinero juice
Jardinera
What is the oil
That is a problem spicy oil is delicious
View all the way up
Too much
Be very happy
Just take
Pressing down the spoon
And then you got the oil and you can put it on the sandwich
Then you felt guilty about it
Weeks after
Let's roll Planet X get the jardinero oil just the oil from another sandwich
The rest of it
2 just started going
Just started doing it
As you got to scoop
Mostly
More competent
The sandwich employee that you are working today wanted to have a conversation about it wouldn't help
You just started going in MN
Poured it on that
I have there goes a carrot
She's only because she's being paid like 9 bucks
She gets whatever she wants
I will accept
Any inconvenience from a fast food employee because it's like
Dude I guess
I'm with you you probably have a creative writing degree which is more than I successful
And you're making me a Santa
I agree with you
This is the end of Dan's hungover going to Subway tail
Celebrity
Temperature
Alright alright alright we got robbed broken to the store
Recently
Conversation with an adjuster
And she didn't believe him at all
Sitting there trying to order my sandwich and cheese it's been like
What
Walk me through this one more time
Do this in an office store
Asking the manager
About what happened
What was lost
You are getting a saint
Just sitting right next to where I'm ordering my sandwich
Nobody's asked you
You've been waiting to tell this story for so long I didn't realize it but yes apparently
This happen
And I I'm pissed off about the oil situation
My quote was
Which is
Fine who's in the middle
Claims adjuster
You know what that is
That's a Law & Order episode whatever the cops always go to the the like
Warehouse in the guy insist on still picking up boxes and put it over
Instead of just like
I will have a conversation with you
Peppa
One guy behind people in line
You got it all
Overcharge
What are you Larry David now
Who was beautiful throat
Two episode Arc of Seinfeld you just wrote it
6 bucks for a meatball sub
Wrong here is like you got it wrong
Alright whatever I'm hungover I got to go home and eat
30 min till now this extra dollar memes
You didn't get robbed of
This is been damn malevolent Subway experiences corner of the day
Now let's get back to this clip about David Rockefeller
To become very clear very soon
How far gone we are your
The ship around
It's still going to be
Feel bad folks
Evil
Genetic damage
Is there any sale we have computers in gene-editing for you
Nnn will will take care of you
Does evil should get two willing to die
I would never take a
Christian or atheist liver
Weather
Chinese
What
Did Rockefeller had six
Heart transplant 40.
4 years ago 3 years ago
A heart transplant
2 days before he went
This is fake news
Worldnewsdailyreport
Heart transplant before he
The World News Daily Report in April
Report it
The billionaire philanthropist David Rockefeller
Successfully undergone his
Six heart transplant years of the venerable age of
Years old
The article also reported
Everytime I get swept across my body I feel regener-eyes Dental I
Sounds that sounds like a fake quote however this news was not reported by any other credible Outlet
Because it was probably because
It was a
About the alleged heartlessness and entitlement of the wealthy
From the fake news
Worldnewsdailyreport
Who's the disclaimer page
And besides articles are not meant to be taken truthfully here's a quote from there there about
Worldnewsdailyreport publication
Not use real name
All news articles contained within
Worldnewsdailyreport.com or fiction
Any resemblance is purely coincidental
Politicians
Adore celebrities
In which case they are based on real people but
Write an onion article about Dick Cheney
But but
But it is true that he did have multiple heart transplant
Any live to 100
He had multiple heart yeah I'm not sure exact number but
Shouldn't be allowed to do that
If you're superrich you did over the f*** you want
You can do whatever the f*** you want it turns out but it this this
Particular
Totally
No I did this particular case Alex's
Specifically the last episode we talked about how he is
Just responding to a chain letter by using World News Daily
Report
Satirical News website as a
Did you know that a week before Bilderberg
You know it's kind of sad
I prefer I wish I lived in a world where you could just get a
Son of heart transplants and you'd be
We can if you have tons and tons of money
He should have lived to 161
You know what I'm saying like you should have got every Newhart
Shiva time
My bad
Bad bad
Our boy Randy Cramer is going to get that Kickstarter going
Information
So excited
The point is
He had some wealth
But it was a will
Without tables power
Georgia hold on to this life as long as he could eat it
You know where Dad's Rockefeller does now
France Brothers.
No more blood to suck
Vampires
In their Eternal death
Interspiritual coffins
Alone
I heard the tone
That's nothing
I said I go your calls not I. And I did but I am Jeff
Boheme
Clint Lewis I'll get to all those calls for the transmission
I got to say this or we don't feel fun or so Plus
The perfect person we can
Great
Difference in you see the difference in affect
North Georgia still performing
Hey we got new sales on everything is good I can do better version
That I sell s*** cuz it's a defensive
Yeah gets really excited defensively like everyone like vitamins
All right it's not it's so performative
Did you think that a normal human being
Would have that as like
Their path
Experience their path of how they wanted
Rhetorically do a show
So fake
If you word it it's like
I often think about this
Like
You and I
If you and I were
And Alex Jones's position
And we were doing the show where we were convinced that the globalist
We're trying to kill everybody
Yeah what we would do
Like how would we behave ourselves globalist
Ultra-wealthy
No cuz I really don't think that they are trying to
To kill us I think they just don't care
Conversation that we could get into
It's a little more nuanced
In terms of like I don't think
Billionaire class or the
The super-wealthy
The oligarchs yes I don't think that they have a vested interest in
Killing us
Necessarily
It's just that if we do they don't care
And the things that Keep Us Alive
Them lots
Money
And they don't care about that they want to take away those things
To survive with
They're not mad about that cuz we still get to work and prop up the organization's
But they need
To make money
The difference between our version of
Boogeyman
Analysis version of Boogeyman
Our hours are real
And also we don't have these fictitious narratives about white genocide
Credit
Not
Engaging with this
Conversation
Because I know that
You say
Go go go go go go even more
I prefer it when you look into the camera and say that I'm the worst no-win for me
What your call
Sympathy
Will make your point a reasonable conversation
I do think that they are actively
You can make a good
I was just expressing my position
That's kind of
I think that is the fundamental difference we often have on
So many
Different things
Is
How much of it is murder versus how much of it is manslaughter
Rave I think that's the conversation we often wind up having
Sitting in it a little bit
I
Start to
I start to Distance by personal experience
But look at the bigger picture
The biggest the laissez-faire I don't give a fuk kind of attitude of
The rich
People
Survive others
And that might be a little bit of
Bias that I have
Privilege
Right lower on
It is
It is absolutely straight up
Them
I guess there's only a semantic.
Between
Wanting to kill you
Not caring if you
Right
Right if there's if it like
Regardless of whether or not there is an active desire to murder
You are murdering people
Yeah you are doing it with knowledge that people are going to die
Do you know what I'm saying for the sake of
Your
If you
We need to cut Medicaid
You are saying that from the position of
Yes
I know people will die because
I am saying
Regardless
The argument can never really be does medic
About this financial
Exactly
Can never be about what does this
Provide
Obamacare
Yeah
30 million more people are on in
We should get rid of those millions of people
People will die
Due to
But financially speaking
It makes sense
You don't like that kind
Situation
With that example the thing I would
I would set back to
Who is like
Then it's not nothing
Really killing
People as much as it is putting them into
Bonded
Putting them into wage slavery bondage
Deep death
And s*** like that which is right
But that's not
Killing them
It's more making them
Completely inert
Variables
I would much rather like
Directions to bed with Alec
Narratives about the people's at
We don't like
Yeah I'm not ready to call them and order all of us
Because
I don't want to
Radicalized the people who listen to
Like I do I respect the hell out of people listen
Come to us
WeChat
Interact
I don't want there to be a moment where
Like they get
Some sort of dumbass idea pizza shop
Sleep but at the same time
Did you not
Take that out of context you should go to the boardroom and s*** on
Table
I know where this episode
That's why I'm being very specific
Yes it is
I I don't
That our audience
Should
Think of
People
Who
Are in charge
Menards are really ruining
Demonic end
Want
Kill you
As much as they are
Very greedy
Right
It is about accumulation
Wealth
Cutting people out of the equation that's that's really more
Real world
Motive
That we've seen over and over again
Right we we see almost every time there's some sort of
Like really successful thing it's based on fraud
Within Market
Or nemean Ron type
What I see.
And I feel like this is probably
The most apt comparison that
These people like
You see somebody ride a horse to
You know
The horses simply away
A horse is simply the way to get the meme
Matters
Because whatever it is they think they're doing
Is more important
Then the life of
Now is
Is kant's categorical imperative
Yes to some extent
We're talkin about that
Want the only thing that is good in the world is a Goodwill
Ray only thing that is good is doing things for the right reason
And if you don't have your acting out of bad faith
Sinbad will than anything you do is bad
And I agreed
We've lost track of that to a certain
The other
Application from that
Leave it
I can't
Another philosopher
I apologize if that's okay
From I-80
Yeah once said
The idea of treating someone as a meme
To an end as opposed to an end in love
Themselves
Is always wrong
And I believe that is
I believe that is
If you'll just are treating someone
With their autonomy and their there an individual experience
As a means
Things to get you something
As opposed to
To being a human
Then you're f*****
The system that we live in right now does both
Of those
They are acting in bad will people as mean
Agree so there is a reason enough
They're too just
Be like
Burn It Down
Of course
The only question I have for you is Dan
Listen theologian
There's a lot of ideas
Coming out of
It is
It is the question of that
I keep going back to
When we started
The question cuz you're you
Yeah it was constantly to me always like
Is Alex stupid
And as we gone along the question has become
Does it matter
Doesn't matter if you are stupid.
Cuz because it is for me
More I know Alex
I know that right
It's more become to me
Does he know what he's
Right
So to you but that's the question of stupid versus evil if you're doing something stupid
Because you believe in it as a good thing I disagree
Okay I disagree because I've already established
I know that
Inaccurate readings
Attacks
Stupid whatever explanation you have for soup
In that we started with that stupid versus evil
Envy Evil part now is
Become evil
Knowingly and willingly
Or evil just incidentally
Right and that that part is still that's
Still tough for me I still
I don't have evidence
Bet he is
Full on
Honeyville
But I do have evidence
Presented it over and over and over to even in this episode of the Daria
Like
Do you have
Stop
Sorry you have to tell if your Russian agent
Keys
In service
Of negative things
Bright Eyes
But I
Don't know
Still don't know if it
Is evilness
I still don't
Know if it goes past
Abject greed
Which is still evil
But it's not evil in the bigger sense
That like
Trying to bring down the key
That's the end
The way he does his rhetoric
Sebring
Narrative
The world
The end result
Will be
Apollo God
Probably
His desire
But his rhetoric
Bagel history
Will lead to
Disperse
Putting in camps
Will lead to a horse
Crackdown on people's liberal Sensibility
You put them in the oven
Not that much
Wiggle room
Course
But
I don't know why I'm trying
I think I think what I'm what I'm understanding of what you're you're discussing
Is
I think he's scared much
How much does motivation
Change your
Opinions on
To deal with
Now that was out at all
I deal with him objectively as
He says
And what I what I gather from
Researching the narratives and
I don't
I mean
Still give him credit for the
The things that he's
Right on
Not like we're not
Had to
True
Been a long while
Changing philosophic
Opposition
Has come from like
Well on the last step
A reason
I-PASS
The question
Can you say that the world would not
Bigger better play
If all Republic
Inside this
Right right
So
If you are if Alex is
Evil
Does it matter
The world would be better off without
We're not opening not a republic
But that's not that's not
The only reason
The only reason that that
Comes up in my mind is because
I say it
Like I don't want
I don't want our listeners killing expired as a thought experiment and so
If it is that thought
Does it matter
Does it matter what your motivation is
Behind what you're doing
The difference is
Murder vs.
Does it matter whether or not billionaires
Want to murder us
Or whether not billionaires support things that will kill
It doesn't matter to me
Because the issue is that we are going
Going to die
Feel about
I agree with you it and now the secondary problem becomes we have one political party
Supporting
What you're talkin about
Another political party
Not doing as good a job as
We need fighting against
And so we'll see what he
Anyway I don't know
I love this conversation but
Point
Let's get back to it
Riverside
We're having a classic knowledge by 12 and a half
Episode
It is not a money bomb because we are just
Capable of being
Quiet but seriously please donate
If you've made it this far
I do need help frankly if you made it this far
You owe us
I do need help
Yeah even just in terms of making rent this month
Need help so please donate to the show reason point.com
Calm.com
Anyway that's alright
It's weird how
We will produce a lot of
I think we would do it
Regardless of whether or not
Anybody gave us
I do it for nothing
Pretty nice
It would be nice if you became justifier weird obsession
Jordan
So now we get to the point of this episode where this would have been
Alex Jones I mentioned this earlier
He has
Something that he wants
What's to talk about
Yes he's been
Dancing around getting to it
Much like he keeps avoiding going to calls
I'm sorry I told you okay
He
Has a news story out of
Video come
Dutch TV
Already I believe
He talks about this
In the sense that it is
Creeping Nazism
Is the Dutch
Leah
I don't know how to do this exactly
I'm just going to play this clip
That involve some fake cry
The Austrian government having a suddenly
Far-right
No no
I don't even do that
He actually has
I'll just break it
He has a decent
Starting
Alright alright
He loses it passed
The point of analysis
But has a decent starting point
Is that there is a
Is a video clip
Spoiler alert
But it's from
A documentary that what came out on Dutch television
Call Dad
The last Downer
Donner is a term that they use for Down syndrome
People with Down
Which that's not great but that's not a good time I don't like
But that's
The Dutch
I'm not dealing with Dutch
PC issue
That's not
No that's not that's not weird car claim
I'll be thrilled that you and I could find him
Combat in this world is Dutch
PC right
There was a documentary
I called the last Downer
What it was
Was a
Well but here's the thing
Hearing the words
The last Downer
Is that contacts
Not a huge fan
Continue
In the Netherlands a reading a synopsis
Set of this cuz I couldn't find the full version of it I tried really hard to find a full Verizon
And it's just not available on American internet
McConaughey
Tiptoes
And there's a there's a bunch of Louis Theroux documentaries I want to watch you can't find cuz if I don't live in English
Rat
It's not on
The American YouTube
Imperial
In the Netherlands a TV
Show revolving around the end
Syndrome was recently aired on Nash
Television
The series it was titled the last Downer
Explorer
If Down syndrome disappears
They talked about ethical social-psychological consequence
Does having a child with down
So
The proof really interesting
But you understand
In the synopsis
The first thing it says
It explored what Society loses
Executive Down syndrome
That's a very interesting documentary topic of like
And and what it is what it is really is
An exploration
How many of those neuro atypical
Situation
Actually wind-up contributing
Far more to society then what are what is Publix
Like
2 to what extent
And if you want you can go back to biblical tea
How many prophets
Were people who had
I thought I had seizures
At what point
Do you look back at the
Relative
Weirdos of History
Influence the way things
Friend not just
And not
Just go
Tracks with symptoms of what we call Mint
Mental illness
The right you know
Like
Who is a who is a medicine man but somebody
Juilliard
What is the sphere but somebody who has grand mal seizures
These are these are things that are difficult to wrestle with before we get into any of this
Treveri
Yeah I'm guessing that we're not going to be huge fans of what
Is not good at this
But I've known a couple people who are friends
Red Down syndrome
Who's that I took away from that
Babel
Their people
Yeah big-time
They're people yeah
With
Issues
But at the same time
The same experience of life that everyone else has
Things that I
This is going to come in
Commentary pretty harsh
One of the things that I
I know from
Knowing people with Down Syndrome
Sort of looking into
The things a little bit
One of the biggest issues that people with Down
Is the people look at them with the diminished
Yes they look at them
Infantilize
As they look at them as
Being these
Oh so awestruck see innocent whatever in that
That's not who they are they live their lives
And maybe have
Developmental disabilities
In learning motor function or whatever
But that's not that doesn't
Define zone or they just have a physical
Deformity
You can compare to
The idea of like
We're going to put somebody in vocational school to
Have lights
Right as opposed to
This is how you
No f****** but
So I don't know what the full documentary
Was about
Again I told you I can't find
Can't find
But I watched
Before
Then Alex
Because you can't find that and is Alex
A four-year-old ape started to circulate on right-wing blogs
Couple days
So Alex picked up on
But like I said this documentary came out in 26
Get over a year old
And
Even covered by the app
Right they just found this three-minute one-minute clip
3 +
Just decides he's going to launch off on his
His mare is about it when I when I say that he has a DC
Jumping-off point
Is that the idea
He's
Rallying against
Is reasonable to sell
The idea of
I don't know
I'm interested now in what smokers I need to defend myself
Because I said that
It's just that like
You get to a certain
Play Swift
Genetics
In utero genetic screening
Okay where you're able to tell the people have
Various
Diseases
Was that mean
It's a reference for Sunrise
Sunrise in sweater
Gattaca there's some of those issues
Where does it end
If you look into like
Genetic
Abnormalities
There's something
Our lives there are genetic mutations
Tree branch
It's super not all people in Kentucky
Family in Kentucky
Who's skin
Is blue but there are some
Things where
Through genetic mapping
And genetic editing
You could allow someone to have a real
Normal life
Supposed to have
Tree bark or whatever
Yeah I think that's
The positive thing
I don't necessarily think the idea of aborting anybody who has Down syndrome is
But
If there's a way to
Edit Gene
In such a way that we figure out this is what makes you
Have down
Right
Don't think that's a negative
Massive conversation that you and I can
Can have about that towards eugenic
And where Alex Jones jump
From the art
It's a discussion where it's like
This is
Going to lead to
You killing of the week
I agree with him
Application or the real world
That's the only thing I wanted to hear is the only opinion I have on you
If
We discover a gene
That makes you an a******
I will immediately be like
Oh we can fix that Gene
Eugenics is perfect
Alex already thinks that exist
Up until that point
There's a lot of variables going on that I don't want to start f****** around
But if we find a gene in Alex so
We decode allocational defiant we decode Alex
We decode his genome
I'm not too bad and it's not Alex
And it's not Alex
Is everybody
In that ilk
And there's just like if we just flipped the switch
Alex Jones
Is not an ass-whole from uptodown
I have a lot of come I have a lot of questions
And a lot of
And I'm far more
Interested in describing I think it's pretty scary that now especially because we're on the Vanguard a lot of a lot of this
You and I are
Are mentally a lot of stuff from our genetic
Button a lot of those things has made us
The people that we are
Threatening on some way the idea of editing
And I wouldn't be the person that I am today at the same time if I was someone who who
Genetic
Condition that was
Painful all the time
And I lived a life that was just
Pain yeah I absolutely would be like
I really wish them all the attitude
Yeah my personality is not worth the fact that I've lived 10 years
15 years of just
Pain right died young
Well in the
The simplest
Waze
For me to relate to that
Is I do not talk about people with Down Syndrome I'm saying that about just genetic
Conditions.
Since I've been married
There will never
Be a day where I don't
Question
Would I be more
Creative
Right
If I were on medic
That's just
Har.com person is just like
What extent can I say that
My creativity
From my brain
Or from my brain
Brokenness
It's impossible to unpack exactly
So the idea of once again go back to what is this year but somebody with
What is
So if you edit that out
I honestly think
Who wrote diversity is important as neurotypical is their diversity is amazing
I don't know I can't speak to this cuz I can't find the entire documentary
I almost guarantee that that is kind of part of the point
Because
Mountain
But also why would the write-up of documentary be
What Society Lewis's
As if I would that be the first thing that's brought up in the house
Asthma
Hey what do we lose if we get rid of these guys
You know that.
Exact dark sartorial Center
They're notorious for their write-up for the TV program
Being dark sarcastic like a Steely Dan album
Are the mountain goats absolutely
So I left this first clip Alex Jones
Can't f****** handle getting to
2 talkin about the actual clip
I will see how he had
Course
Your phone calls
I need to because I got to put the clip for pull watching comes on
I washed it this morning
I couldn't sleep I got up
I want to be very clear
Oh he's going to fake cry
I wish that I had a Supercut of all the time
Teases getting to this
Throughout the show
I ain't just never does
This is like right when Paul Joseph Watson
Like takeover
We're getting close to the fourth hour
If I can do it I've been teasing at all show
And I went online I was looking to stuff and I saw this fat with the Dutch government in
Feel it wasn't put up by the Dutch government
It's so sick that I don't feel like I'm worthy even describe
Not sure that tracks
Just I don't
I don't
Sweet soft bureaucrat
Getting off
On making a
Down syndrome and feel bad and feel worthless like you should die
Cute scene fake liberal
Feminine email
Uber back to back
Even even him
Trying to defend
Exploitation
People with Down
Syndrome
Sounds like
Avoiding people with very aggressive
I realize this now. You guys don't have the video
We just talked about what
There's a guy with Down Syndrome
I am a guy who seems to be the host of
The show
The show is a smelt
Looking gentleman the only clip that Alex plays
Disseminated through right-wing blog
8 disc
Melt
Looking cool
Alex describes him as liberal live
Have no evidence
The guy with
Down syndrome
The scientist
Explaining to them how
Much it cost for society
To care
Do people with Down
As opposed to people
Entire setup
Purely economic term
Well in this mall close
Like this conversation is occurring
Purely within the realm of
The documentary having
The idea of the documentary is like an hour-long three minutes of it
If your documentary says
What do we have
Toulouse
By getting rid of people with Down
Bright you have
One Clip
That is based on an
Economic
Argument
Then it stands to reason
That much of the rest of the day
Isabel
Humana
I would assume so I mean like I know I've watched
Tons of
Documentaries about people
Various conditions
Being a Down syndrome one of them
Right always Delights me so much
Is them being like
Stop treating me like I'm a dick
Do I always love
People having that soft bigotry of diminished expectations
Thrown in there
Face yes I always love it when I speak
Someone talk to someone with Down Syndrome be like
How old are you
Fukkk offf they recognize when they're being f*****
And this guy
Neurotribes
Fantastic
Very very good the guy in the documentary
2 is clearly taking in the information that's been
Clearly part of the conversation he's not being like
He's not treated like a dick they're not saying we should kill you or anything like that
I realize that I had to lay sort of a scene of what the visual is
Totally get out so now let's get back to
Better his mine
Those people
Open Facebook
Call
Everything I'm talking about I'm so tired of it
Alex
Is doing good
Infantilizing of people with Down Syndrome
He's deep into that
They're giving him information that is just
To carry people
With the need for help
And that's not wrong
What
What is such a
Beer
Interview on the road
Which is that
And the way he's describing it
The Down Syndrome
Whoever whomever he may be
Doesn't matter
Bing
He is
Simple
He does not have a complex view as the world
And that's
The point virtue of not knowing
That is seeing God
Globalist
The scientist
The person the person who
Who describes this as a
The complex situation
Wherein he says
Okay well their relative positive negative we have to account
This week
Account for that
The important part is figuring out what it is
I would imagine in the documentary
Different scientists
Genomic scientists and then they go to
Regardless of that that's something that if you are a scientist
Consider
No matter how
Look
As far as the tax bill
Right when we discuss that
The the things that I
Consider constant
Is
The idea of
The point of this
Is 2
Destroy entitlement
To destroy socialism
Security to the
Destroy metal right
Now
I have to ask myself the question then
Is that bad for me
Like get rid of Medicare
Get rid of Social Security get rid of Medicare
I am
And who is social security who is covered by Medicare who is covered by Medicaid
Anyone else minorities elderly
Elderly
Is it
Is it then a good idea
Tuesday that the elderly should take my money and order to just continue living
Well
Like if you go my
If you are at all reasonable
You get into f*****-up territory and you think about
Thinking about it gif
It's because he's arguing that when socialism comes around
Just are going to be able to be like now you're too much of a burden
Burgerkill you or whatever
I know what's going to happen with capital
Absolute direction that their tax bills
Right you are not going to
I at the end probably won't be hurt by it either I had enough of it
Right it's not really
Are the people that Alex
Pretend
Are going to be the victims of
The Socialist take over much of a burden on society
Nothing like I think I think
Based on everything I have experienced
The people on the left
Easy to paint with a broad brush
People on the left
Gives a s***
But generally the people that I have mad on the left
And within
Some
Some socialist
Spoke
Have no interested
Getting rid of
Bouncing
People with Down
That is not like
That's not on their agenda
Just because they're more expensive
Having survived
Doesn't mean like
Kill them
I think
Yes it's applying account
Capitalist mentality
Towards
Democratic
I think it's
Applying this mentality of like
You are too expensive you must go
Right that's a capitalist mentality
Taking care of everybody
And that is what
I think we should be working
I think my
Scoreboard
I think that's kind of more
Sesto is
At the same time
If you are not
Capable of
Tutoring like
The idea that I am aware
That
Medicaid
Medicare
Security
Not only do not
Benefit
But in many cases
Contribute to me having less money
And yet at the same time
I'm still capable of
Recognizing how they are far more beneficial to society
Aeropostale
Allows me to
Converse with both ideas
I think we're going to get to what Alex
Is mad about about
That here in a little bit
He doesn't want to be a part of society
But
Is that there is an idea of
Maybe at like
Legit
It's without question
And if you go by if I go by everything that directly benefit
Like 100% directly benefits
It's me
I should be a republican right
Like I'm a straight white dude I am within the ages of 18 to 34
Like all of that or sexually engaged
All of the stuff that they do not engaged
In all respects
What their policies do is affecting
Current temp
Yeah and if I was dumb I would say that's the best way to go
The reality is that in the larger
Summer things
That is a
Nonexistent possess
That will only benefit me for the next 5 years in minutes
Going to f****** over like everybody else
Like that
That's my biggest issue I might not just talk over everybody else that works
Exactly
It's but you still personally
A little bit
It goes trickle down economics
Somehow doesn't make
Alright fine
Your idea of
You want to make money as a business right
So
If you produce something
You want people to buy
At the same time you want profit on what you
So you reduce your
Is right
That one's up meaning that the people who buy it don't have as much
So the people who buy it don't have as much money
And I can't buy it anymore
So destroys you but in the short-term
You get a lot more money
If you get a lot of people
To have more money it's the difference between wealth and income
Wealth
Is
Destructive
Income is fantastic
If you're working late everybody
If you increase wealth
A few people
And that's what that's what the question with disconnect
Is about as well
Sure
If you
Increase
There's a very clear parallel between the two and it frustrates me
Because it's a short-sighted view of things
Anything that it doesn't exist
Edit someone's G
When you know that they are going to be
Right
And make it so they don't have down
Good
You should do that
I think that is an ethical position
That's an interesting thought
But I don't think that if you find out your kid is going to have Downs
And then you abort them
I don't think that meant
That's an interesting question
It's it's
Incredibly complicated
Because I don't think that like
What the reason that when I
I am trying to put it back towards
I understand.
When I talk about everyone
How you and I are meant to
A lot of it comes from
Are genetics
And it's just
The cards we were dealt in our life
We have Annie
Hugo stamp
About how I
I wouldn't be who I was if I did
Didn't have those struggles
Listen what have you been
If we were born didn't have those
Pretty cool
Probably be pretty fine
Because there wouldn't be the suicide
BV years wasted
Of Our Lives
So that's true
There is that and like I don't really understand how my creativity is really been bolstered by
If it has or if it has
Who knows I probably just
Hurt a bunch of other people because of it
Most likely
So this vad event like
Lake neurodiversity is gray
88 should
Exist
At 4 at least we think so
You know
It should exist more than it
Shouldn't in terms of
Killing all abnormal babies
Or whatever if you want to call it baby
Which is why we should kill Ethan Hawke
Anyways
Sunrise
I like Mo Stephen Hawking
I got a lot of s*** for saying how much I love you.
I don't know about that
So
It becomes a very complicated conversation I think
In terms
What is
Technically paws
And what is
Worth exploring
I don't think it's worth exploring
Aborting every person who has
I think it is worth
Exploring
The idea of
Gmod
Application
Right when you're not
Because of down
Drum Folk
But because of
Other
Mutations that can happen is that we'll just
Make you
Is that
Or is that
Killing everybody
Do you know what I'm saying
So if you ever
I'm a Bipolar person
I will kill you in
Second
Not a bad idea
My life
Imagine if we never met
You'll be married you have two kids
H m
I mean
So
If you remove
Bipolar Syndrome from
Have you killed
Likely the point being
Melcher
Sure
Physically the the human being that I am
Is not dead
And yet at the same time being that I am now
Is rhetoric
Actively destroyed
It's like a time travel
I know it could have been also
It is what it is it's not worth having
Write the argument that is worth having
Is about
People with Down Syndrome or not
I mean they cost more
Keep alive to other human beings
But
I also think they're lies would probably be better
If they hadn't been born with Down Syndrome
I would not do you know what else
I don't think their lives are
Cuz they have Down syndrome cuz they are
Living their lives they have
Autonomy they have
Perfect
Ability to love
To work
22 exist
But
I don't know
Don't complicate
What is the to what extent is
Not having Down syndrome
Detrimental
Flag Garden we should all
Let me ask you a question
Would you be happier
In
I'd like many people that I've known with Down Syndrome
Find far more happy
Out of
Simpler things that I do
Like would I be a happier person
Would I be more satisfied person who you're buying into a little bit of money
The issue
What exactly
What mythology what mythology
I am buying into in regards to a mental illness
I don't have them you know what I'm saying
It's really complicated and within the seven and a half hour long
From all that from all the research I can do in the myths I can sort of
I ingest
And work through
First of all
It goes down
Argument
They are just like us
All the people I know
And then beyond
Don't think
The last
Feel like the entire conversation we've had has been about how killing them is a bad idea
Ultimate Euro layout
Murder right
It's all a bad idea
You wrote
Therapeutic
Possibly
Not even get rid of
People who have
Other genetic
Woody's
Before he's even seems like a terrible work those things
That will make your life
Completely miserable
You'll just be live at and it's not
Picture books
Researching
Towards that
Doesn't seem bad to me
Right but now when you apply it to like
Oh this person will be depressed kill them
Right
Right we won't get other LaRosa's
We will just just consider all of these different diseases
Yeah you're you're ugly
Yeah your otherwise and yet at the same
Without
Without being able to conquer that life
Are you capable of
Transcendence briante you know it's like
Whole f******
Sanity
I don't know
It's I don't know
Still
Genetically modified corn
We spent a half-hour not knowing which way to land on this but I think it's
The same time we've done more analysis
Going to do about this in the history of his entire life
They piss all over
Timberline
But you're all going to be there you're all now
Funny
Astarte's
Is it
Aggressive
Is mentally ill
Emerald
I'll tell you this
You're going to kill little
Retarded children
You think you're going to do stuff like that and you're going to get away with something you going to feel powerful
Hearing a spiritually waddle around in front of somebody
Because you're such a big man
Miserable horrible life and you want to creep out your
Creeper
You want to shove it.
You know how it happened
They're genetically sabotaging us
All genetically falling apart
We admitted it having kids
Replica Throne going
Frozen
5 lesbian
And if you're lesbian
First Coronavirus
Joshua
This is their deployed anti-human
How They Roll this out on other planets
Maybe the Orchid Man gave us the Bible
Divvy org
Can man give a survival Old Hickory
The ages-old question salt
Old Orchard man
For us to have a
25-minute tangent where we're discussing
08 you know there's this positive versus negative
And then Alex Jones comes back in with
The Orkin man gave us the Bible and then at the end
Commercialism
Alright
Like give Alex a little bit of
Conclusion
There isn't that is not
In some way utilitarian
You know what I'm saying
Like even our conversation ultimately wound up with
What's more useful or what
As opposed to some sort of
Metaphysical idea
No I think my absolute
Conclusion is
Avur
I was going
No I was going to go the route of
You are going to be born
Your life
Is going to be
A complete disaster
Your genetic
Which is not your fault
Gene editing
They can
Fix that
That's my position
Right
I think that people born Townsend probably
Have a
Sign position with having their life
Be what they are
And I respect
But at the same
Same time
I think that they probably
Would be better off if
If they had been born
Not have
I think that might be
Slightly controversial
And I want to be very clear what I'm saying is
Not discounting
Their life
As it is
Yeah I'm I'm I'm saying
That their life
I had it not been
Would be better
Inasmuch as
Like I related
You and I
Right said we not had the
Predisposition
Towards
Depression
Mental illness
This would be better
The the next
Soon though because
If
There are
Are they going to be make
Asian that is
Fast forward
4 best
Their life
And so that's where we get into a different f
Pickles
Exactly argument about something
You know what if that's like it's like f****** cars like
Okay. Here's where I would say it like I think the parents should never view their children as extent
Oceans of themselves
I don't think that it should be like this is
The part of me
Disagree with
Of course
Ancestors are with him still in Albany
Exact time
But I would say that if
I believe this in terms of just like abortion
.
Like if you are
Are not able to
Care for a child
Then you shouldn't
Have them
If it comes down to it and you're an adult
And you're able to
Care for
A child
2 is just a normal
Define doubt
But they have
Normal
Yeah well but normal normal this weird sucked up thing
Alex
Yells about it cuz In that clip with down
Getting out of
Myself is Down syndrome
But
They they're like what is a normal person
Sin cos tan Alex is like
F*** you
Normal
Well how many times have you called trans people not normal
You look at
You look at the
But then the question
Then become
You know if you want to go to
Cost
At this
More
To society
Then
Somebody who's
Raised
I don't how is that
Because they're trans
No
Because of
Systemic
Prejudice
This is within
Society
Out in
Homelessness
And so on and so forth
That wind up
Forcing them
To cost more the so then your utillian argument
Are you
Terry an argument
Goes back
Further towards Society
Just against them
Keeps going back in back
I don't think this
I agree with you to some extent but I don't think this works because
Of this is all eugenics
Brighton
Exactly
That isn't something necessarily
I don't think at this point you've
Intel from jeans
Rite Aid in utero
This is all about like trying to get rid of unfavorable
Entities
Right In Utero
Right
You and I are having a very interesting Eugenics conversation
And unfortunately
Eugenics is a rough thing to have a conversation about a worried that I'm a fan of any
Nugenix conversation that I'm sounding like
I am anti
People with Down
I think it's just
I think it's just one of those things that about
There's there's there are
So many things
Right
Zip makeup
The ID
Dia of
It's expensive to keep you alive
Right
In the same way that with people who are depressed
The same way with people who are borderline personality
What you were bringing up about neurodiversity
Is absolutely
True
In terms of that stuff
When I
What I have said
Already getting really f***** up
I might be projecting a
And that's
But when I say
Think
That
Like
My personality is based
I've had
I would
Want
To not
I have this
That's Bass
On only listen
That isn't saying
F*** you you're you're wrong to have the life you have
More
No one wants
Don't want no one wants to be depressed no one want borderline
Right I've never I just don't want you texting
Ford F-100
Recovering from trying to kill myself like but at the same time
Who You Are
Rough
Ratably difficult
Space
That I'm
Admittedly
Projecting our
Experiences of Portland escort
Two people with
And I'm not sure that's fair
I'm not sure I might be wrong I might be wrong
No
But
I think I think her ultimate conversation
Love to be born normal
You and I
WeedMaps
Plenty of normal people
I know right
Wish I was I wish I was a little more little more.
Ultimately our conversation boils down to
I don't know the answer
I'm interested to know
Don't know the answer I think there's a lot of interest
Things about neurodiversity
And at the end of the day
Do not feel like I have
Any qualification
For anyone else
And I strongly don't think this documentary was about you
3 minutes
But answer here
Right
If you are parents
Even more so
If your mother
Can you make a decision
About what's in your goddamn body
I have no
Judgment on
Cosine
You have your you have to make a decision
To tell you
What is the best
Etc
I'm in the wrong
Totally
So if you want to raise if you want to raise a child
Syndrome and if you want to deal with the fact that maybe the child that you raised with Down Syndrome resent
For raising them was down
Or if you want to deal with the child that resent 24
Or if you want to deal with the child who resent you for raising them whatever way
That's your choice
You don't want to do that to your choice and so on until
I'm not going to decide for anyone else
Addition that it might
I cost you more is not at all that application of like
Lauren indication that you should
Kill all of them solutely
You should if you were to give them up for adoption
End
Then the society
All comes down to this
Confluence of
It is
Irresponsible
For you and I to make that decision
Society
I think it's responsible for most people or even governing body
But a Jordan
You're f***** up
If you think there is
A whole bunch more of Alex
Trying to wrestle with
This isn't a whole bunch more of you and I tried
This is degrading
This next clip is degrading
But it it's fun ain't as much as we
Really get to see how Alex.
Okay
I don't want to be in your communist system
Is control
We're free
Collectivism is a
Society
Dutch
Haisten funeral
What is the cost of the care for the counter is called
Makeup for sure I want to know
Y******
That works
Socialism
Costco
Call nikhil
16 ml
About five thousand Euros a year
Silence isn't keeping up with the subtitles
Is this guy is a chalkboard and he is laid out
Society
I Healthcare
Call sporty 8000 Euro 16
That whole
48 thousand Euros a year to
Someone alive who has Down syndrome vs. 5000
Euros
For someone who is Joe
Able Body which is a suspect
Statistics
To begin with
It's clunky on and
Chalkboard analysis
This is Nia
Super it's not like
Play Just Good Will Hunting
Good Will Hunting to be around
The Good Will Hunting
Fellowship
Albino enable to poke teapot
Making threats I just want to watch this I want to kick
He's an equal-opportunity
Chicken you know what
Dementia
Please just take these are his friends he's like I have valuable wow
And they're making fun of him
I want to be clear
They're not making fun
The person in question
Is first of all
Aware of what
Talking about Howard
Well not not a joke no I mean more like a towel of a bigger picture how he's he's interacting with
Is it as such that
Understand what their talk
That would be a
Question you know
They're they're like
Think about this
And he's like
I can't think about that
And then like okay cool
You're pretty valuable
I had no idea
Write that sort of thing
He was a long
I have to assume
Tennis documentary
He's along
For the other
Being covered by rail
They're not being
Rules
Bring it down syndrome
Yeah is that what we want
That stops
Or write issue and starts being a
What the f*** kind of monster would
Do this is what we would have known about that win
Came out
As opposed to finding out about it later
Over this documentary
Really need
To fill time on the show
I didn't say hey
You're a piece of crap we want to pay for you
Be honest
Look at it
Challenge
Everyone of us has what they called genetic disorders everyone of us
Perfect system Metallica
1/4
We're going to kill people
We're going to have suicide Nets
Slave labor in Amazon but it's all okay cuz we're liberal
Following
God
No one's going to be taken care of
I feel like an AI would take better care of
The Down Syndrome
Right and here's the other piece I want to
To to put into
Play right about now
Who is going to take
Take care of them
Who
Social program
Yep
So what is the advocating for
Well
He wants
Social programs
But he
Also wants to remove any and all funding for social
I want none of my my night going towards right
Haymaker
Husto convoluted Miss bulshit they were like
I recognize
My
Light by assassins
Everyone would be better
With not
Having
Whatever ailment they have
But at the same time I also think
Take everybody
I love it
I don't know
Go f*** 20 f****** stupid
Free it's every argument that you've seen in the Republican debate
Ever bright which is
No
We need to take care of the elderly we need to take care of these people
Who are homeless we need to take care of them
Now admittedly
We need to cut spending and remove any funding to take care of those people but we do need to take care of you
Certain
Isn't terms with like
Hey be afraid about this thing but I do like
Score
You don't want your tax
Texas raised
Take care of the people
Who you want
He's engaged in what is essentially a
Half hour rant
Write about how like
Down syndrome people gone and we realize
Statistic
6 due back this up
They are much more expensive
Right just from healthcare costs
And that's not negative that's not bad
HomePath
Two or three homeless
I can't afford
To give them
Dollars every
Everybody paid a dollar more in their taxes
We can have more dollars to take care of
In their taxes
Is it all that money
Go to
Shelter
Supposed to
Your dollar going towards
I'll maybe a sandwich
Or whatever
Yep big
Picture
Everyone coming together could help more than individualistic
Communism vs. socialism
Which is the answer
Hey buddy was like socialism is maybe the way to go and Alex's blanket. For that if you removed
From the oligarchy oligarchy call issues that we have with Communism and have
I've had first for the millionth time communism is an economic system
Nada
Government
Authoritarianism
Militarism
Is Advil
Indicating essentially
For taking
Here
Of people who can't take care of them
Which is great
Realized
Everything requires
Program
We create economies about love
Hospital hospital
Great
That's not how that works
Civilization is about taking care of people
Civilization about
Weekend
Sure you're alive
Decided
But even
Hidden wiki
He's saying it's
It's right in line with his philosophies
Withholding
Care right
You saying that like
Oh they don't
Gilliam
They just don't keep them alive which is
You would want them to say that that's the best idea to do it
Can't afford care if you say what he just said and support the Republic
Contacts Bill
Your
Dumb
You're evil
Either way
Go fuc yourself you should die
It's very unclear
That's why I should.
You you called
As much more
People think
Groceries
Because OU just don't have that
All about no hospitality
Also recently I feel relieved
Tips away from my service employees no big deal no big deal
There's nobody
You're killing us
Very important person
Very left but the floor on your water cancer Varsity vaccine poison
And I love him
For Superior
I just see
Transmission
God gave us these people to show us
What someone only connected to God would look like
F*** you
Children
They give us a review into what beautiful
Godlike
Abilities in
Existence is would be
How f****** degrading is that
That's so
Stupid
And they're they're laughing at this guy
Doesn't really have
What
Doesn't have toll free Lil t-jay
Been down that
He's like you're my friend
Because they want all about you need to know that
Jarabe there two idiots
Glen Club
Delicious
32nd
I want to play that part
You're not normal
We got a whole show everyone of you
Colbert
The one of these watch all the followers on the betas Washington
Piece of crap
Dependent variable
Cost of sod
How to spell cute
Are you
God will deliver
He's losing
So now we've gone through
The hardest part of the show
Which which is that
Like I had like
14 minutes
Of his
Down syndrome analysis
The weave turned into
Maybe 40 minutes
He said
Not a frustrating
Do you want to stay on the other
I think
I think we've
Made it clear where we stand
And I think
Alex has made it clear
That
If anybody should be killed
It's him
And he's lying the entire time
No ice
I know
It's
So amazing
How
He is
It's like he's
Grabbing this
This magical
I don't know all I can think of
While I hear him
Save this bowl
Is
You don't care
He doesn't
No
Snow White
This documentary came out a year ago
Even if it even if the doctor
The doc came out
He doesn't care
It's just like every time workout
Every time we talked
Facts about Mash
The first thought he has is
How can I use
And there's no
Elliptical
Let's go
Let's give Dad a Republican
Our hopes and prayers go out to you
She's never said that
Think about mass shootings
The slightest bit
So like he believes like
He believes
That the Oklahoma City
Bombing
Was
Fake
And set up by the globalist
He believes
Waco situation was set up
Let's forget about the fact that he is just
Forgotten about all of the Sandy Hooks
Or races in Las Vegas
Was fake and the knockout game
Is the biggest problem
The world
If you actually believe that
Any of these
Prove
One of them
And then you have
Droid
The entire world
Any of it then
Yeah right
Button so much underpinning for society is
Torn apart
And pay Alex
I'd like to offer you this Challenge 3 hours into our dumbass
How long were you do this I think we got fired
Power off air
Call Justin Watson took over for the 4th hour
Snarky a lava flow
Stop now. Always plates
Vegas shooting
If I can prove this
I can prove this
Dude if he could prove it the only thing we would talk about
Is that f******
Absolutely
Reality I'd be in
So now I want to give you one more clip
Where
Ni
Look we've been talking about Down syndrome Bundchen
That to me is
Disgraceful
But this life
Squib gets more
I legitimately am now at the point where I think
I'm done playing games
Based on this
Because
The rules
About what
Buchanan
Can't do
Hi in terms of broadcast
Alex
From
December 50
Gotye
He's crossed the line
It's over
Pushing the Civil War
Little people that
That's it
You do I sterilize a politically I say a lot of s***
Yeah you should go to prison
Every single point
Of the s*** that I've said
It's been
Very clear
Throughout my history
I am
IMDb
You know like that
That's who I am or you have me around so to talk you down and
Contextualize what you say
I've never I don't really believe
Like I I can't bring myself
As much as
Maybe even I want to I don't think it's the right way to
Right
Alex clearly does
And for a long time it's been unclear whether he believes in
Yeah
He's advocating right there for
Sprayed up murder of these globalist
Which As We Know
Even in my worst f****** moment I
Realize like this isn't the right
Listen to the music Kickin real hard as soon as he gets into the like
Let's kill everybody
He wants to work out more we're both
Broncleer
I want I want
Directions to Buckley
Music slow music kicked in as soon as he sat there
Islam
Officer
Someone behind the scenes
It's going to rain
Alex Jones
That seems as good an exit as I listen to John rapport
2 rapport
Alex Jones website
Dollartree.com we both are
Ron Isaac
Guy who is really f****** annoying and Alex
Jon rappoport get more interesting go f*** yourself
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color