Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Novelty beverages
Little bit
About Alex Jones
Hundred percent of
Dim
The sphere of the Immortals
This may be our last show of
Team possible we might be another show down the road but that might be it
If
You were to describe
To it
Over the past year what would you do
Describe
Hair growing really long
That's true
And the guy who just turned his beard does not know everything about owls are related
Bowlero
That's what we're going to do this may be the last episode of the Year might not be either way
Is coming up
And if you want to support the show please do so
I'll be honest
Just in case I have an extra
Happy holidays Merry Christmas to y'all go ahead
Bouncebreak.com is our website and click support the show all of you already have done and are doing it
But we really want to
You know what
Cam girls have goddamn don't they have like
I don't think it would help but it would just be like
Normal food
Send me some lingerie if you want me to wear it it's like
Struggles of my life is I really love doing
No it's that it's that I love doing this and I would I don't want to not be doing this but I realized it
Conceivably jacking off on cam I might make more money than mine
Yeah
True
All about
Break in the action right there
Cuz we just said I got distracted by doctor poodle Papa on the other chat room email
Because he offered to mail Us blind
Get back about that I think that might be too expensive on your rent to be worth
I'll send you an email I apologize for not getting back to you at this point
At least then we know we'll eat
There's been a little bit of you know I've been depressed the last week and a half or so
In terms of keeping
Things going I apologize but some
Disruption
A couple days where I barely been able to get out of bed and no that's just
Sometimes you got to got to roll with it
Move forward
Better now
I'll be a lot of fun anyway
Let's get to the
We needed to end the year
And I didn't want it to end the year I feel like this year's been so great
You just let it ride
You know based on the Gregorian calendar
Yes
Year zero on the Gregorian
So that means it
True but be that as it may I didn't want to do a New Year's episode or anything like that. That would be a little bit old hat
Hockey
So I decided against
The master
The failure on our part
Boy should have been fun
Thinking about it it's
Play call man
It's
The fifth anniversary of disposing Maya Mayan apocalypse
Like that we already did that episode
What are we going to do
What's bigger than 2017 the buying apocalypse
You know I was like
Don't know what to do until I just threw a dart
I threw a random Dart
Into the past
And thankfully I hit Pay Dirt
I Hitler I did I did I darted Hitler
Not kill just like
He was annoyed
Regular
Pretending
Beginning
Of the
Russia
Premier
Alright which was on I believe the 20th of February
Yes
And so that's what I jump back to I definitely
Calendar
I jumped back to the 21st
February 2014
Happy Valentines
Probably give her take today
What is position
And
Here's what I found
On the 21st
He spends about
The first
40 minutes talking about how Obama is about
To take him over
About to take him down
Asteroid
The entire media is a
Rickover
It would have been a very interesting
Obama's
Russia Annex
Crimea was to be like
51st state beaches who's annexing who now
Or
I'm going to take out Alex
Either one of those would be
Cooley likely Obama's out-of-office
So he didn't take down the media didn't attack
That at all at all
Beatbox Alex a little bit
I mean that's fair play
But
First 40 minutes was boring
Intel
I got to this clip
How's like
No
Quantify
But I believe the Human Experience
I want to hear from you
Where what are you doing
Oh yeah
Okay three calls
We're not even going to get to the calls
3 minutes of little bit more time
11:45
11 minutes and 45 seconds Auto read about The Human Experience
And it's one of the craziest
I've ever heard I have a lot of things that I can
Specifically point out that he's lying about that we're going to get through firebreak by krump
Commercial to commercial
Evan when he does take calls there's like
So here is where the the ramp begin
In fairness to Alex
Start off on a good foot
It's not
Great but there are some things in this first two minutes of the rain
That I can call
Time to sign off on
That changes quick
Alright
On this Friday the 21st
I want to talk about the nature of
Individually have a feeling like we've been here forever
We're never going to be overconfident I don't get older
Buildings in Tulsa
The language and customs
Thousands of years
Develop on this planet
Real quick I don't know if he's saying
You as an
Individual take you have been around
Alex talking about
Externalizing
You saying that you Jordan individual think
You Jordan have been around for a long time
Humanity
Okay
Well I would like in the history of the Earth
The traditional expressionism
You consider the
Entire lifespan
The Earth
Relatively speaking
No we have not
But
Compared to our experience
Which is really the most
Real thing to us
Don't jump the gun
With our species
And the Rites of Passage in the archetype of ritual
TV show comforting Dodge
Great great great great great
* 100
Live in a time where those rituals and those rights
And scientifically dissolve
And replaced with rituals
Consciousness depression
To the mainline cosmology Sports
And the drama and the movies and the celebrity
999 99
Someday
The Fulfillment box
Call fulfillment in the human process
So
Is the part that I'm talking
I do agree with his thoughts about celeb
Pretty worship
A lot of people get trapped up in the glitz
And the glamour of the movie industry in Hollywood
And even reality television is guilty of this to some extent or Alex Jones in my
Mike X caught up in something
Becomes overwhelming
To other parts of your life
But that bothers
Do people
Really believe that
Human being
100000 years ago
Didn't get
Bored
They did
I like generally if you're talking about a hun
Hunter-gatherers
Society
What we know from bone density in the way that we've
Discovered those fossils
Is that a lot of time there
Starved
Sure Save the timer for a week
Fatty foods
So you're hunting your Gathering
But your leg
S*** there's nothing a hunter-gatherer and we're just hanging out
Like
Don't you think they wish
They wish
They could have had
Analicia and Sport
The Nintendo switch
If you brought them in time
Time and have them play the
The switch
Like the hunting part of it is exciting
Gathering
Kind of boring
So even like half of the population
Female have
Are still living
Idea
Of cavemen
For like 4 days
The Gathering part is pretty interested to
I do I don't know
I don't know what interesting
Contacts
Maybe I'll check this out there's another piece
Seafood
Food to eat
Not boring
Lowe's sand
People play
It's equally as exciting as words with
You and I played Scrabble don't forget
I've had gallery
I wish I wouldn't consider it exciting together
Anyway well this is why you're boring
Rigorous
Undefeatable
I still think that there is a kernel of something in there
Making a bigger deal out of this than I need to
Do just because of how off the rails this is going to get kind of have a hinge key around like
The Fulfillment of the human process
Ryan
You're better than this
Your beard celebrity
I mean argue though
Depends on who were talking about
Anyway
A lot of people have
Subscription to Cosmo
Nothing
So it's just going to be over
Starts
The Arctic
Epigenetics on record
The strongest arguments
Restart it
What do you mean what the f*** is he talkin about some developers theme and then we'll talk about it
What was the first
Epigenetics take notes and then the Panthers
Question
The Arctic
Epigenetics on record
Mammal species
Watch a movie from
5000 years ago
What do you think all these instincts come from your door
Why is there a
Is there
Generations
The indoors with no stimuli
And have a cloud go over projected on the ceiling
Generations later
Project the cloud project
Away from you
In the neuron repair
All the ancients
Tissue spaces
Where we are individuals
Group Collective
Organism
That a sixth sense level
Island
On the next Island
100 200 times faster
Model
Morphic resonance
No one knows fault there's a lot going on here
People do know what that is
No one knows
There's alot going on
You want to start with
First of all I mean
The stuff about fears like
Generations
Mulatto
The amount of research that I'm able to do with my
Non Masters Degree in the in the subject is a process called methylation
Where in
Pieces of the DNA or actually chain
It's like metal pieces are attached
Strand
And they are able to
Track through this
This process what happened
Like I didn't experiment rap
Where they actually
With the gas or the
They used as a
Trigger for the rat
I gave them the smell and that electric
Shocked them
And then future Generations
Would be scared of Justice
Smile it's because of DNA methylation
Genes are actually sort of warped
Behaviorally
It's it's not like
I don't fully understand
That's what I
I think those parts
New Orleans
Is Tapatio
You know that thing we thought 30 years ago
Doesn't make sense
Right but it would make sense
Generations later chicken
Still have that
Every existing
Chicken before then
Gene Wordament fully Express
Savers
Organism
Things that can learn throughout
Adapt
To that as well
Stronger person
Person doing a stronger
Does mate mean
So I would assume
Different generation
Allow you to reproduce
Efficiently
Where you at
Where am I at
So explain to me
What he thinks Apple
Genetics is
He thinks that's a good point I maybe think it's because
Genetic predetermination
4 rings
The study
Seems to be
Some sort of a genetic component
Addictions that are past
If your Dad drunk
You're probably with your Dad drunk you drink
I think that sentence
Yeah
Alrighty
Now
Which
Sages
Have been proved
Just like
Sage Francis
I don't know I don't I don't know anything
Epigenetics
The Elder Pliny the Elder
Come on if your dad break you
The other thing at the end is this enough monkeys and then Magic
These other monkey
Across the pond
Are going to
To have that that behavior
Well that was
Adventure
Something called morphic
There was a
He's a kidnapper like a crow
That learned how to use it
Island
That had no recorded
Whatever it's called Contact
Haha
They learned it within a week or
They thought of it you know the thought there is
Well
But it could also just been
But that's not what he's talking about you
I have
What's up well there's this
There's this belief
If you show me a dick
I want
There's a there's this belief that goes around in like pseudoscience
Difficult
Is it called the hundred month
That is very few teach enough monkeys a behavior all other monkey
These will start to learn it
And it's supposedly based on science
Albany
So I'll just going to read you here
From from
Article about this
The story of the hundredth monkey effect
Was published by Lyle Watson
Forward to Lawrence Blair's rhythms of vision
19 7
And spread with the appearance of Lawton
1979 book life tied
The account is that unidentified
Conducting a study of macaque monkeys
In the Japanese island of Kashima in 90
Fifteen52
These scientists observe that some of these monkeys learn
Turn to wash sweet potatoes
And gradually this new Behavior spread through the younger generation
The Monkees
In the usual fashion
Observation through observation
Watson
Concluded that the researchers observed that wants
Monkeys
I even hundred
This previously learned behavior
Instantly spread across the water to other monkeys
Nearby Islands
Anywhere where those monkey
If there was a small sub
Right
Then that knowledge
Would then be
Transmitted
Do all monkeys around the world within that space
That is the idea that there is a threshold
This is an idea
Theosophy
Community Center
Everyone will benefit from it
Because this consciousness
Sprint it's almost magical Malcolm Gladwell is what your
Lincoln talks about how late we get Malcolm Gladwell
Sure
Anybody
Unsubstantiated claims that there was a sudden that remarkable increase in
The proportion of sweet potato
The first population
Exaggeration
To the much slower more mundane effect
Rather than all monkeys mysteriously learning the skills
It was noted that it was
Predominantly younger monkeys that learned
Observational learning
Which is widespread in
Know how to wash the food potatoes
Not to learn
Younger monkeys were born
The proportion of washers naturally increase
The time span between observations by the Japanese
Who's on the order of years
So the increase in proportion was not observed
So all this is bulshit
But then beyond that
Claims that the practice was watching
Sweet potato spread suddenly
The other isolated populations of monkeys Maybe
Sweet potato washing monkey
He swam to another population
It's been about 4 years there and also
The monkeys had researchers and comment
Also like a sweet potato
Who is Jordan swimming all the way across
It also turns out the
Potatoes are not like they weren't to Native Foods
Eid
Know how to prepare them
Is completely reasonable that have to figure it out that after the older generation
Typing
Lower proportion theory is b*******
That way you know how old people can't
Take a f******
Screenshot on their phone
True
That's that's not a hundredth monkey
Reply
Who cares
Indus plain
Starting to espouse his beliefs about race memory
Completely
What epigenetics
This is no idea by DNA methylation
He has no idea that the hundredth monkey theory is
Bumpus Bumpus
As they say
British fiction
And as far as race memory goes he doesn't even know Husain Bolt
Not at all
Block
Natural man
Woman lyrics
Rituals of manhood
I don't want you to go through
Free will
But there's so many levels to Ry
How many systems
And with other people
People
Performing
For us to succeed
That's not a generation
Only one
Sign off on everything
In this corrupt system to survive and treachery is what is empowered them
Guns N Roses
Experience
Okay
Posit that it's not the
Human Experience
Alex's
Mentally ill possibly brain-damaged
I'm liking it
So I know it's interesting it's much more interesting that is bigotry that's for damn sure even though there's a par
A hundred percent
Still way more interesting to me than is normal knockout game narrative
You're just like your father or mother
But he's too esoteric at this point in the episode
To get into the narrative this is high-level stuff he's got a mention epigenetics
This is not time
4 Brown Bags being outlawed the Purple Penguin
What's your favorite ritual
Everybody up and then back in a bunch of young lady
Before I'm 6
And then getting thrown out of school for fighting too much and smoking crack twice on a beach
I don't know
Maybe graduating
High School
It's going to take awhile
I don't know
I don't think it's
I don't think it's fair for me to critique what the Rites of Passage for women or I didn't have that lifx.
Come on man
That's good you trying to sell me up the river like that problem
Suddenly pick up tomato crosskill
I was wrong I have never I have never claimed to be a saint
I don't know man I think his view of the Rites of Passage or Slightly Stoopid special
Based on the things that
We know of his life
If we if we consider the possibility that
Is telling the truth about his
You broke ways with his mom
Individuated Italy
Like age six when she told him he didn't get love anymore
It's not the healthy time
Is that right
6 years old very much connection with your parents in order to contextualize the world
Around 6 baby
Is your lifespan
Alright passage baby picking up some
Wildly
Somatic John Birch
Society style beliefs that night about 12
Right I don't know
Or like a like walk in the cornfields
Sure pulling weeds
Let's drink
It is all stuff
Admitted
We're part of his childhood
I don't think those are healthy right the past
Everyone else
Here's my
First
Big red flag
All right we need to go to the store
Right
That's important
It's important to the ancestors who has wells in his bosom as well as the Creator
But at the same time the Creator actually is not waiting
At the same time
We have
To the rituals of those old people of
Tribal days
Does he think that if we can
We'll just like
Start float
Like we'll just get up there what will be like I ran out of berries over here so might as well check out the moon
Holding on to the Past
Well
Progressive
Straight up OSHA
Text clip Alex
Gets more into the right to
The passage
Drive to cite a poem
Oh boy
100-yard dash
Explosively in the world
And the trials and tribulations
And you're bombarded
Generations
300 Alamo
All the billions of experience is all the legends
McReynolds
Lykan hypersport
This one was bald
This one was lucky
And for a brief moment
The Hills Mall
Dauntless
Lifted
Losing the thread that's what it's all about ladies and gentlemen
His favorite poem
July
I've never really taken the time to look at it so I looked into it a little bit this time
The thing about Rites of Passage
And stuff like that
And I think that he thinks
Childe Roland
The Dark Tower came
Does the name of the poem
Robert Browning
Yeah and
I think that he thinks child rolande means baby roll on
And it doesn't
Child
That is the word not for a child it means
Goodnight
The old time
Also Robert Browning
Also
Not good at it
Hero long poems
It wasn't short I did read the whole poem
He gets into like a f******
8 page long poem
Came up on like translating The Iliad
Chat
Vermont map
So I read I read the childe Roland to The Dark Tower came
Actually really interesting cuz I think there's some connect
Pens with Alex
In the poem that he doesn't realize
Okay so one of the first things about it is it's not about
Rite of passage
Give that all of the great Heroes of
The vold
Pierre to Roland
Goes to the Dark Tower
Complete this rite of passage
On the phone about art and poetry you can have your own interpretation in
Alex's could be
True to him
Hey that's not what those people read
Awesome
Margaret Atwood
Who is the famous
Razor
And also the debts
What's the name of my cat
Before I adopted
I believe the poem
Child Rolanda's actually Robert Browning
Self
And that the Dark Tower is
Of writing
The poem the movie by
No
The Dark Tower
No no no I mean that is probably what
Obviously
I'm derailing you soon getting serious
Let's do it
Which is actually side
Salseo
What time
Call child
It is actually the
Protagonist from
The song OverWatch
Who is
Margaret Atwood's theory is that it
You know there is a lot of
You're within the
The poem
And it's the Dark Tower is BS like the act of writing
Poem
Is what he is working
His way towards Indy
He's afraid of
Okay so there's that there other interpretation
Think about it being a knight
Requested with a
The end of the tower symbolizes
And it's accepted all they come
Your failure
Or realization
Futile
I don't know I don't really like poetry that much
But what are the things I did notice while reading
Poem
Do you want to start
Yeah I do I do
I noticed
Trimmed it does
Story of the poem is child Rolanda
Going
At the beginning he gets told by this old weirdo
He's got to go do this thing or whatever this guy
How many goes on his way
Fields
Can you find this Tower
Joseph Campbell
Hero's journey
You are somewhat but he goes along the way
Nothing happened in the entire time
But it's full of like
Oh my God this River could be full of dead bodies
Like the entire time
It's just made up bulshit
What it could to be a stroll in the woods
That could be what the literal
Buddy's mythologize visit
Since you like this crazy
Z-Trip to
Battle
Right it's not
Right it's not the
He's rewriting
His own story in order to make it more interesting
Exactly
Eddie gets the tower there's no indication that there's a battle there anything like that
He does say read this year off
To view the last
List of Mia living frame for one more picture
In a sheet of flame
I saw them and I knew them all.
The Slughorn to my lips I said
And blue child roll on
Into The Dark Tower
In the same way
No don't listen
Lockhorn
Like
They've named a lot of boats
A ship in Star Trek
In the same way he's Imagining the entire trip there is being full of
Trotwood
Imagining
These people there
The point
And the poem
No but there's a point in the poem
Or he doesn't really want to go anymore
Don't really want to keep going
And I'll just read you this
See what you think
Is being described
Not at
Cuthbert
Beneath its garniture of curly golldir fellow till I almost felt him fold
An arm in mine to fix me to the place
The way heater
Alas one nightstand
Disgrace
Out with my heart's new fire and left
Did cold
Was he described in there
He's talking about buying a dude he is talking about bringing a pretty sure he's being held
Gently by a dude and then it's a
Extinguish
1 nights
Disgrace you got it
The school of on Earth
Frank is 10 years ago when knighted first
What honest man should dare you
He Durst
Good but the
The steamship
What hangman hands
Vintage brass tap parking
His only ban
Read it for traitor
Spit upon and curse
So he's remembering a night that was really Noble
Killed for treason
Better this present than a past like that
Back there for to my darkening
Half again
So
What he goes on
To actually get to get along on his imaginary Quest
Is
Oh s*** my past I bang that dude
And even heroes end up sometimes being
Turning out to be
So he's running from a
Like a path
TDM's dishonorable
Or whatever let you know that that is
He's running from shame and
Beer
Towards and imagine
So anyway what I mean
Section of the poem do what
Interpretation
Would be is more
By quitting Quest
I would be
The traitor problem as opposed to he is running away from back
Dude
The dude
KeyBank
Is
More just like I could hang out and be with this
Remembering this traitor
Because I would rather
You know that whole
I have to stay true to my quest
These two stamp
Our memories
And that it says
Fetters
Present vennie past like
So even though there does seem
Need some Warp
When he's talking about Cuthbert
He's still
Saying I would rather have this fearful
We are present then
The past
I know a lot about post let's get off this really likes
Specified what I'm talking about it
Alex Jones is made up a fictionalized Mythic Quest
You've been on for the last 20 years or whatever he's going towards
Some sort of a legend
He's going towards self imaginary Finish Line
Heroics
But he thinks
He is this guy going to
Tubus Dark Tower
Just imagine
The entire thing
And what propels
Ten-forward possibly is
Some sort of Shame
Not necessarily about
But some sort of Shame
Still unclear about
Very gentle
Fimbriae
You are all those people that came before you
The Consciousness you got dying and the rituals
Carried out by our ancestors not being carried out into the future because even those rituals are needed
Sociology
You need those two
None of those things
Closet
WWE
Compressed data information
What are you talking about like
Compressible
Well you're going to need like WinRAR zip
Program and that's not really a ritual
No it's the ritual the Rites of Passage
Right
Again
Based on what I know of his past
I would say it's not
The rights of
They unlocked
Box like this and
His brain as much as
What means being stuck under a house being fumigated
Along these lines
Probably make it difficult
Reading
He's got like a half remembrance of
Half of something that maybe was true
Ready ready
In the title
6% of junk DNA that scientist
No one's ever said that colloquial b******* about you use 10% of your brain that was a long ghost
One of those popular ideas from your head like
The guy wear
Thermal clothing but he did wear a hat
Well of course all the heat escapes
From your head
No you just
You didn't cover your head
Uncovered place
It's very
Confusing
Cuz I mean he's trying to stop up what do you want like what do you want
Basalt
Have been about
Yeah this point I think
Pouting
Pseudoscience
Debunked studies
Probable misinterpretation
Childe Roland to The Dark Tower came
A bunch of made-up Chiswell
Yeah and it's a
B b
Not till the end but it actually becomes really
Because it brings back towards the real world
Confusing he brings it back towards the real world
I just don't know what do you mean
I want to get confused all of those struggles and all of that information to go to the Future
Information
Reality
Think about how
Lisinopril
And want to embrace you
Before you are re-uploaded
Real
Level
That's what I understand
The surest way to living forever
True
Development
Knowledge On to the Next Generation and the build-up
Young of the future
I agree that that is important
Now it's also important
Information
Don't loving information
Should be
Correct what we're really saying
Is
Don't allow Alex Jones's kids
Have kids that's the only real way to
Kill Alex
Epigenetically
It's through the artist through the literature through all of these things that live on it sir
But don't watch movie
Don't look all art is made by
Globalist we leave on to block the path
But we got to stay back there otherwise the past
Isn't going to allow us to get
To the Future
But doesn't make a goddamn bit of sense
What the f*** is
You talkin
I'm not sure if everything is it
Let's Mysteries
That's the mysteries of the museum Mysteries
Oh s***
We are the m
This is the great truth
Hold your family
This is why you have a conscience
It's good for Humanity
And the global is come with a counterfeit
Because we are collective
Collectivism
To help Humanity when they're actually centralized
Parasites that hate Humanity
Shutter and block
And the in the ears
Of humanity
We are individuals
Of April
And free will
Association
Future
This is The Human Experience
This is the great goal
Not Hollywood
None of it
Building a true World building a better World building a free world
Based on honor
Our fathers and our mothers that came before us
No answer
Usual 2014
REI
So what are the things that I want to talk about there is
The use of the word
Free association over and over
Cuz you do free association
Largely a
Marxist
Communist
Anarchist
It's motive
No no no
Don't look free-association if you're just talking about
The right to assemble
And stuff like that
Zendesk
In the First Amendment and that's never that's not really in French
Other versions
The free association
Like you know
Unions are very in the conversation
Free association
No Global it's false collect
Activism are using to try and block
Your real for you so see
Which is
Discovering that your father and mother are at
You
But I mean only your father cuz your mother is
Really not a bow
Think is what Alex Jones believes
Only women
Mothers are associated with free help generation
Yeah I don't
Who is like workers
People who make money
Off of work
Map of Labor
Have a relationship that is
Is not
Advances are really freely associate
If they forced Association based on me
To sell my labor right order to
To survive
And therefore the person with
The capital
To use my labor has
Essentially control he has control over by association of control over
What is my my life
By the way
O'Hare went on strike support
Here here
Free association would be the former Society created if private property was abolished
In order to allow individuals
Freely dispose of them
The production which would bring about the end of
The class Society I know more owners neither proletarian
Northstate
But only freely associated
So pure free association
Requires
The destruction of private property
Which is something that I know that Alex is
Really
Basic
Free association
Concept I guess
What's covered in the first
Which is cool I guess but I
If I if I understand what he's talking about and I will not claim to
He goes to open carry marches
Like he goes he goes on marches where they make public.
Displays of just having their guns out
Lesbian
Taken away from him
He can have whatever political group you want
You can get on the radio and start opal it occult
If you want
I think what
He's really describing
If if I am
Is
Everybody should live
With giant
They never see anybody unless you
You choose to see
Yeah probably that's essentially what he
He's describing their
This idea of like
Collectivist false collectivism
Is
Cities
Yeah yeah but you know that with all those people
He's afraid of
That is kind of what it is only once
Do it this is all all that he is just said
I am afraid
From what I'm hearing from you is free
For him is the right to not associate with some
Boom as opposed to the
Term as it actually exists
Hundred percent is the case then
His argument
A free association
Is not really
Free association
If you don't want to be associated with someone like
Like me because let's say you don't want to be associated with cross-eyed people
I have no freedom in that bit on record
Rule
Is it stupid
He's full of nonsense but I do like that he accidentally is advocating for Marxist
If I if you actually knew what he was talking about
So
Is that such a
And then
So brilliant
Regards
To Alex Jones's
Operating
Insofar as
This version of collectivism
Whatever it is
I am saying is collectivism
Is correct
Everybody says there's a different version
Collectivism
Is the global
Ownership
Completely
Of the word
It's Christmas
It is Chris
Look at the chat sadly
With those humanized I am not a fish person I glanced from time to time I like to
Baltimore but we don't have time
We have our own world
I apologize if you guys feel
Find me already
Nobody
Clip from the 21st to the 23rd
Like I said
This weird-ass 303 payoff for us
Totally
No no I was like no more 45 minutes
Spirit of esoteric Alex on the 21st
And then we got a new
On the 23rd we have a new Alex
The 21st was Friday the 23rd is Sunday
Man
F******
Really like Alex on the 23rd
Spoiler alert
Okay I think that in a different life
Alex Jones
Could have been
3D amazing
At certain things
Alright
Displays
Some of these
Skills
The first
I went back
Back to February 2014
Specifically to try and see if I could figure out what Alex Jones
Just take on Russia Annex
Part of Ukraine was
So
Esoteric
Randall bulshit
But later in the episode
He has an interview with Jerome corsi
Who is at this point
Still just a writer for WorldNetDaily
So he is not even a part of the Infowars full yet but Alex Jones
Considers him
Missouri
Important corrupted
Important piece
The Patriot movement
The only thing I think you need to know before this clip gets going is that
2014 February 24th
The Winter Olympics in Sochi
We're going on
In Russia
So
So that's kind of the backdrop of
Stuff to draw
He's talking about
Complained that he's going to get to is that
On fire right now
As one
What you're seeing in the Olympics
Is it NBC produced
Michelle
The studio show
Weather
Suppression of Rights
Alright
Display
Different flags
James from Rome
Written large and made available on your television
Free People
That'll be the demean the competition in the competitors
You got to realize the political aspect
Joseph
So hold on
You're doing the jack off motion
But this is incredible
Important
Jerome corsi
His
Horrible voice
As you will
What he is saying
My friend in this clip
Is that it is the Ukraine
Versus Putin
Very separate interest and the United States
To support the people
Of Ukraine and the Russians
Who are crying out for help
Against
Putin's totalitarian regime
In Russia
Jerome corsi is 100% the opposite direction
Yeah absolutely if Alex has any
What is a disgrace
Open champion
Government
Russian doll
Well.
But compared to
Asthma
Hillary's ribs
Course
Soros
Alright
Been wrong
It is much as they both believed that the EU and the UN
Need to be broken up there already
Geopolitically on
But you can see at this point I guarantee Alex is not
I have that interview with Russian intelligence
Or at the very least has not been
Nope the Putin listens to the show yet
They haven't lied to him and told him that
Because at this point
Is it
Close
Through that the place that he was at
Ben.
Kleptocrats
Right
He's a hundred percent different than that now
In 2015
We saw it so somewhere between February 2014
It June 2015
Alex Jones
Was flipped by Russia
Intelligence
I guarantee
2018 investigation my friend I think it might be
There we go
The all of our investigations are
When does Alex Jones completely flip on whatever position he has
There's nothing
This is crazy
This is nuts
Like
Eventually gets into like
Everything bad about Russia's Ally
Putin didn't actually blow up those Parliament building
Either great guy
Qatar Olympic
I bet he's going to be huge fan
I don't want to just go to all the Olympic
Text Beatrice
To take stuff down
That's ultimately the point of knowledge fight
Listen to our show
Also I want to give you a quick apology
Beginning
First one was last episode
Drinking a little bit we misspoke a tiny bit
What am I listening to
Sent me a message about it and she was totally right
When we were discussing the Access Hollywood
Trump
Wework
Discussing it
Because we were
Being kind of loose with our language
It made it sound like we were saying it came out in
Was recorded in 25th we were not clear enough about that and I
I meant secondarily
I took out that stuff that we talked about about Daria
Alex's employee Daria on the last episode cuz I realized
About 95%
The stuff that I found
And other stuff that I found since then
But I can't
A hundred percent
Stand behind it
And we need to hold ourselves to a higher stay
So
That that stuff just doesn't belong and I apologize for
Jumping on a little bit of
Unverifiable
That's the trick
That's why it triggered is my friend
One thing I'm glad you didn't take that
Is February 23rd
Dude
So
February 23rd
He'll Sunday
We know that Alex likes to
Let it ride
On Sunday oh yeah
He starts the show
Bye
He's joined team
He's being sarcastic
And I thought this would be
Possibly it was going to be a situation where
Remember a note 20
15 there's episode where
Pretended to jump the
The shark where he was like all Muslims should be deported. Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Do something like that where he was
Entire episode like
I am fully robama guy now if I do an hour-and-a-half of radio like that
He did not
Nevis
Gets
Superfund
Everything is awesome everything is wonderful everything is good
And ObamaCare
Except it's not awesome
Nice
So
Nicely done now that way to drop the hammer there
That's just
Good fun
Now in this
Next clip
Alex lays out what he wants to do on this episode
And
It tickled me to no end
And the way it ends up working out
The progression of this episode
I find
Immensely the life
And you'll see why
At the other end of this
I just figured out what I want we're not going to take first-time caller or long time caller
The thumbs-up to do is only people that disagree at least in the first
Our phone call from the next hour
I want to hear from apologist
Wrong
Tell me how I'm a fraud
Growing worldwide
Monopolistic
Mafia organizations
We giving you the floor
Can you call in and nnn
Attack me for not liking Obama
Do you want to call
Ted Cruz
So
He starts out he's going
You take calls
People
Who are going to say
He noted already started the clip by saying
I'm going to take calls for people who disagree with me and he's trying to say about Obama
Yes
Then at the end it's like also
Apologize
Here's one problem that Alex Jones has in the reason that he's done multiple episodes like this
Can't wait to try and find
Keith self-selecting
From
Hughes audio
No one
Cruise
Intelligent
Listen to Alex.
Like no one who's listening as I
Call that guy
He's very smart
Now if you want to go a step further
No one
Who believes in
Obama believes in
Principles
Andy smart
Is listening to Alex and is going to call it
He's pretty
Secure in that
Gyoza
So he can just put out these challenges and no like
So
We'll see if we get any calls
But
UB Vamps for a while
Complain
Why aren't I getting any calls because
Your audience
Idiots
You are getting calls
But you're probably
In the meantime while he's waiting for a call to come
I'm through he gets into a couple areas
That are Chi
Kind of fun
The first one
It is about
How
Democratic
Represent
By the name of Gary Peters
Representative out of
Is Michigan
Is
Get a
Ipsa
Add taken off
Sierra and Alex
Fascistic encroachment on Free Speech
Sure so we'll get through it
See through
My name is Julie Bowen
I have a 20% chance of surviving this wonderful doctor the Great
Healthcare portal
Obamacare
Are so high it's unaffordable if I do not get my medication I will die
I believe the process
Sodus Point be going
Commercial music
It starts but it's also
Eating with the
Pasa
Commercial
Just come back on the other end of the
Cuz it gets right back to
So
It is heartbreaking for me Congressman locators
Vision to vote for ObamaCare jeopardize my health it is time to listen to me it a time to listen
American citizens out there
Why but I'm here
I want to tell you this
Alex Jones doesn't play the rest of the ad right now
But what he does is
Accidentally debunked
His own narrative
This is really fascinating to watch
For now
Last year as well
Who wants to be
Is also going after television stations airing ads
Threatening
Licenses
Was canceled under Obamacare
Peter's decision
For the law jeopardize my health
Carl Levin
Organizations investigating
Obama
You wouldn't lose your doctor
People just keep defending this Obamacare
I know she has no idea whether she will
Break even with a new plan
Trucker Healthcare
That's the heart of it all
You want to know some truth
Yes I do so that was a commercial that I mean the one they played the Julie Boonstra
For prosperity
I wonder why they would want
Anti-obama
They had a little bit of an issue
Under Obamacare
Affordable Care Act insurance was now unaffordable
Unfortunately
People looked into it
And saw the plans that were available
Terraria
And sound
1200 dollars a year before calpain
She pays less
And other out-of-pocket expenses
The new plan is 11009
152 dollars
Including co-pays and out-of-pocket
That's a savings of more than $1,200 a year
So she actually would not right so here
The other thing
Don't tell me that she was allowed to keep her own doctor
According
According to fact-checkers look at the available plans that were available under the Affordable Care Act
It would have been a slight hassle in order to shift your plans it would have you
But it's not that big a deal
Alright the other thing is
I've done that
The other problem with it is the first ad claimed that it was unaffordable
Then these fact-checkers looked at it
It doesn't make sense
That you would be claiming that it's on a portable
So they made a new ad
The new planned
Doesn't work for her
Which is completely subjective no way cheaper
Of course cuz they knew we just lie to me.
Weed
Maybe she didn't
Look into it or whatever
So Gary Peters wanted people to stop airing
Not because of some
And some like
Probably broke the Federal Trade Commission
Rules
And I'll just quote
If an advertisement such as this
Is likely to mislead consumers acting reasonably
Under the circumstances
And his material
That is important
Consumer's decision to buy or use a product
Particularly when applied to ads that make claims
News about health or safety
That is in violation of federal law
So you're saying
That if she were to go auntie
Claim
That be
Because
The price of
Cheerios
Just went up she is no longer able
How to afford Healthcare
That would be the same thing
As what she
She's doing right now
Stop that lying directly
Order to influence People's Health
That is such a
Perfect example of the
Higher Republican
Sister
They even got
To record an ad
That was against her own in
By believing in the lies that they told her
The very Republican
System is against the FTC
Commissioner the FC
DesiRulez
Yep
Revoke all Republicans
TV also also by the way I was once married to
Mark Boone
Former chair of the Washita County Republican
Richards
That's right
Mark Richards changed his name Raptors
Could be
Into that area
There's really no other alternative
I think that's the
I think we figured that out cuz we kind of gone over before Alex
Complains that all Democrats are racist
I imagine he brings up the fact that southern Democrats prior to
Civil Rights Act where
Couldn't compete
In the South started
As opposed to all of the
The southern Democrats
Flextron Thurman
Went over the Republican side because Democrat
Was becoming much more progress
I can't even remember what the name
Better
Flags that Strom Thurmond tried to
Exclusionary pledge
After-school Scott integrated
It's all it's all alone
Which Wich
Passionately
Erases forever
Here we go
Let's go
Who's finally Alex
Man
I'll tell you what
These
This is this is going to be one of my favorite thing you got to just let this play though
Oh okay you stay that Obama's bad and all that I get some of his military policy
Carbon dioxide
Call too bad but
Just because it gets cold
Mean
Warming you've seen in Russia
Record high temperatures for very long time we haven't had freezes
Steer-In
Before it be frozen most of the time you look at the temperatures they're still going
The ice core samples
Carbon dioxide water
Atmosphere
Texas shutdown
Mexico.
No scrubbers
Maybe
Baby
Smokestack
Algora carbon
I guess it doesn't
You really are an Obama supporter
Well yeah I mean we need some
Better access to health
Question
When did you
You sound like you
No
Badcock
What's wrong with you
No I haven't had brain surgery yet
Under a lot of fluoride I've been looking to step up but I don't see the German psychologist I don't see Ray
Russian psychologist
I saw John holder in saying that it would
Be a nice idea to
Reduce population but I didn't see him actually said
Your call man
I just don't know what to say anymore
So that's the first call
Freckles
Fun
What I said
I love this version of Alex
Cuz I think that there is another reality we're in Alex
If you just could
Break Free
From the
The ideology that he lives in
And you just started going off on it colors
It would be amazing
Cuz it's colors are dumb
Write to them to be really stupid I just believe whatever he says I pivot The Narrative this way you come along
Song with me
There is just a herd mentality among them
So when someone calls in a little bit
You're f****** stupid
Cuz I don't like his callers either
I don't find that fun I don't like his
Assholery being turned loose on real human being I will say this
Fused amongst all of his listeners as opposed to the full force of it funneled on 21
Killman frontierland
The next call is not as fun what
Call his ass homelessness of the next call is not nearly as fun
Because it's
You'll see why it's very misogyny
Edit it still
It's still like
Unbelievable on some levels
But it is
Unarmed man
Bad guy with an imaginary sword
Still an infant
I love them
So did you get them just under a lot of
Fluoride
Also the idea that scrubbers do all that much
No it's just like a few guys
Describe it
All the cold when it comes out there like
Reduce
To some extent
No I don't know
Scrubbing is the process only removes unwanted Subs
From the exhaust gases
It turns them into a liquid solution
Solid paint or powder form
This must be disposed of safely
If it cannot be reused
Which generally
Like Mercury you just end up
Running the risk of
Getting a bunch
Through toxic Mercury the
You've got to put it somewhere
It's all water right
To clean coal
Completely way off and he's pretending
That
Just being able to say scrubbers he's able to stop this idiot who's on the phone
I'm seeing this on the message I don't think so
I think that guy was kind
I get the sense that
Southern accent like that being wrong
Is like
But I think he probably could have
Other things that were reasonable to say a reasonable point
Bring up Lex
Defrost
Not coming
Is is frequently as they used to
The idea that John P holdren
He's a textbook doesn't say what Alex says it says
He would have been able to say something
Alex made him into a stupid person
Through the way
Bullies rhetoric
Call Linda
Cuz you act like that
Reply I would never call in
I could I could
Did I bring up things that
I know you guys I do not think
It's fake it would only we can only confirm it's bake whenever somebody says
Well first off I really love
Superman Vitality for anybody who plugs his
We're like this
It's even worse cuz I heard to call the other day where the guy was like
Weird your shirts
So now we get to the next call Wonder
Fabric American.
It was next clip
This is not the fun version of Alex being a dick
Mayonnaise
Okay
Thank you
Listen to get along
And the reason I wanted him
To win
Address
Go ahead
I don't know how that is
I'm not real political
I just know what I know for myself
He goes along to get along and that's why he's in power if they didn't want it then power
The real oligarchy
Baywood
Not have him in there
You know Ron Paul they shut out because he said it like it was
Family improved
I can't find it I'm going to have to withdraw from the race
He was lying about that.
Obama is it could be so much worse
Somebody else
He is willing to walk the tightrope
And try to balance what
With the people can
Riverwest and and what the oligarchy
What they now call the
Viola Garden
Oh my God
So he's not as mean yet
But he does
Suggest that she has Stockholm Syndrome
Really funny
Considering how much he does for Trump
Wytheville you like
He's not perfect
You're not perfect but he's the only one who can save us
Cuz that lady was
I kind of like her take knowing she had a good time for an Infowars caller that was an amazing called
The idea of it
He is a compromised
The powers-that-be didn't want to be in power
He wouldn't be a power I mean
That's a little paranoid and can
Conspiracy theories
I think all of the all of the available evidence would support her
I bought I want her to be president
She shall be but before she does that she's got to come back
Cute crush
Here we go we're coming back from the
Commercial break we'll see if he goes back to
He does
Have you
Thanks for ruining the mystery does
Let's see if he goes back to her
He does and he's
So abusive
Gross
Okay
Obama
Tell me about
Cupcake sweetie pie Obama
I don't think you I don't
I don't think he wants to
Blimey mean I think he just was willing to go along
Those who are really running the show
Obama what's going on
What's going on right now is
It's okay that's all that's a good word for them I guess they run the show there there
They want to leave the people in the direction that they want them to go which means they want them to vote for someone like
Like Romney
Or or
More money to Romney
Obama
Because he's a darling cupcake
I don't think so I think I think the internet
First ran
You been conned
Right now in Obama
All I know is that the insurers were in the business of denying claims
Army
Is Obama wanted to take you out
It's hard to keep them out bushes
Obama
Keeping us up
You know how we are of War
After these last a year
He just put his foot down on that issue
Obamacare
What is your nickname for Obama
My nickname for Obama
Someone who would lead us into war
Oculus Quest
No I get it I understand
Flatbush was so bad I was kind of neutron Obama and McCain
Obama is one of the few things I was wrong about
Respect
Alex has been wrong about
Apologize
I am underestimated the level of evil
Because he's got this the spiritual Shield of fraud around
My dear
Believe me he's the worst we've ever been hit by
He's a closer like
Close things right now
Patriot come from Alex didn't come on Obama
Look like a gif
We need to identify the true animated story
Problem
Obama's not the true enemy
Said yourself
No he's a luscious cupcake
Is the real question
I'm not going to say I like cuz I don't go I'm not the end
Eagles cupcake
That was nice
That was amazing that was amazing
That dismissive of a woman in front of me
And I like I think I I think she's the smartest
Infowars caller I've ever heard while he's being abusive to her
Go down that road
I mean he's
That you wouldn't say those things
Of course not
That's so little app
If you wouldn't engage with any of her arguments except for the ones that he already had preloaded lines ready to go
With the ndaa 1007
A massive that it was undone and let's not forget that
Sabotage peace talks in order to win an election
To go getting
Thousands upon thousands
M5000
The people killed
Who did not need to be killed
All of the crimes vixen.cim
We got Nixon on was
Nothing
Compared to the crimes that he committed
Capone situation
I wanted to play that whole clip on it uninterrupted
Because
She handles herself
With class and aplomb as Alex being just like
You offer Obama
He's a horrible person
Piece of s***
Like you can't engage with any of her points so the only thing he
You can go to is
You want to f***
Maybe that's why he glommed onto Trump so much
Is because that's essentially
Does misogyny this attack
You saw the presidential debates
You're the one
You're the you're the pope puppet
You're the puppet puppet puppet
If you want if you recalled food to cupcakes
Bojangles
Why don't you get like even engaged
Doesn't even seem to like Obama.
She's like you know
I know you're complaining about Obama but the real issue is the oligarchy and I'm like
F*** yeah lady you're right on it and she didn't call them globalist
No more reasonable and doesn't have the
Catchy is she thinks it is but it's still pretty good I have all the archaic antisemitism of bloodline
Have attached to it so
Unchecked capitalism is bad
But you wouldn't dare say
He does get another caller
This one's a bit more fun
Cuz this guy is just dumb and Alex T's office
We don't have to feel bad about it being
Piece of s*** because someone's a woman
Our weekend like
Not and not just because
To being mean to a woman
Because she
For specific for somebody who is so fake
Obsessed with being honorable and treating women appropriately
Yeah you're not you're not good at it Sherry had been saying a bunch of really
Aldi's
Hey you want to f*** Obama don't you
Come on you want to talk about
That's all it is you're not a human being with feelings
You're just thinking with your f******
Yep
Yeah and so like this
This one is
Just a guy who's stupid
And Alex gets mad
Come on down
Tell me how I'm wrong
Alright Alex
Are you really ready for this
Obamacare you got to look at it very simple
There's 310 million people that don't get a vote in anything
Those are the people that have a healthy
Insurance policy that is provided by the
Another 26
40 million people
You don't get it for dinner
How many people did he figure actually in the sky
But Alex
At this point well the guy is still talking Alex's darting his eyes around the room like
Through their employees
That's why Alex hasn't but
Look look look
What the f*** got going on here
They think those are the people that are between
310 million people that have health insurance provided by their employer
People in the country
Alright
Okay there's 310 million people
Health insurance
Provided by their employers.
Between 1 and
Percent that cannot be accounted for
Those are between 3 and 9 million people
That's what they want to put on that done the
Affordable Healthcare Act
I'll be ready to talk about this thing
You have a chicken that says you're going to
Gwynedd is 31 Oz
First of all I love that moment where he's like
These numbers meaning nothing about that insurance company alive
You have a card with 32 102
There's you can see in his face like
You so f****** over but then.
There's like 15 seconds left of this
And the way he ended the call is
Is the f****** funniest
When you going by the house today at horse care ticket but if everybody understands both
Chick-fil-A
Going to go down to 141
41 Salix
You and I agree
Unequivocally
No no f****** strings attached Alex you and I are 100
Board together
Horse carriage
We're scared that if you get injured you get shot
If you get injured they put you down
So he's not actually a fan of Obamacare
No
Math
Play
Alex cannot lie
Roughly 123
Percent
Cannot be accounted
Now that's
329 million call that 15 million
Cut it in half
At 7.5 million
That makes me laugh so hard
Until I die
All Is Lost
Except for D'Angelo songs
And veterans
I will die
This Alex
So much like the Alex's
Who's right there he's on the cusp of being like what the f*** have I done
Do that cuz you presenting
Colors are Obama's
Supporters
Not his listeners there his listeners most of them don't support Obama
Sherry who
Abused for being a woman
She didn't really support Obama either the first guy unclear what he was talking about
Cuz Alex kept turning him into an idiot
Like it was unclear what his position was Buddy
This point have been Obama supporters
But all three have been Alex Jones listener
Here's our new show
Return Alex
Into a force for
We're good we're in Alex does nothing but take calls
And your s*** all over his leg
I would love that if that like cuz I don't necessarily think he deserves
Some sort of horrible pun
She's done but I think it was
To make him
Like be a part of the private prison in
Industry like cuz he should go to Jay
Will put him in one of these private prison
You can work for a dollar a day
Taking phone calls
Produce dumbass
Yes yeah there has to be restrictions on the MP Leslie call erisa expound on whatever they want
Sylvania to listen to
What
Like he's close to that moment but he never get we spend so long asking if we could we didn't
Basketball
Another call from a guy who doesn't
Like Obama and probably just wants to hook him up with a hook
Okay here's the end of that call
Voicemail
Monstrous
Pokemon
And they're threatening blocking release
His number
Aquascape
He's just straight-up it was staged
No
In the
In the interest of fairness I don't have all the calls
But he took because
A couple of them working
Completely nonsense
Like one of them as opposed to 310 million
That one wasn't completely nonsensical one of them a cutout
3 is 1 is a guy calling about how socialized medicine work
He's like Canada's Great what about these Nordic countries
They don't
Seem to be doing all right and they don't have any
Total difference Vermont
Moral
That's probably what you're saying about you
Nicole is too short nose wasn't good argument
Duck
So
Just two other people don't really like Obama at all and they just wanted
Talk to him
So
One more call to listen
Alex
This guy disagrees with him
Disagrees about that
What about something else
Call Gisela spank you
I disagree with you in several ways
Before I get to one of those I noticed that you challenge Piers Morgan to a bare-knuckle
Can you alter challenge
Two cops
That took killed Kelly,
Michaels in Las Vegas
Thank you I'll take you I'll take that challenge
No I'm not one of those people but I'll Stand in for them
Promotion or make any money for charity
So now much like when that guy said there's 310 people at ten million people in America
Insurance
Alex is looking around the room like
Is going on
Geico it I said I wanted to fight those
It's for prep
And I love Tim Alex Jones
We're both
Cowards and backed out
She should have done everybody would have loved
Both of them
Get their asses.
This color is
I like this
Spirit of it just been like
Pittsburgh
Alex's confusion is Meredith
I'll do it no no no I bet that's okay if you don't if you don't want to fight me that's okay but I can't Rihanna
First of all
You talk about Jesus and you say that you're a Christian
Jesus dictated the solution to the problem that we're in in the Book of Revelation
In Revelation 13
Elvis very clearly that the Pepsi
Is the first be
260 year reign
Revelation 13 says that the second beast
Have all the power of the first B
Obamacare
So want to be clear
That's the beginning of the show
So anyway
He's like let's get Adam revelation
And you lied you didn't call in
Obamacare you want to beat my brains out
Let's just be honest about it
Across-the-board that's what I am
Okay so if you believe
No I don't
The solution the solution is in Revelation 13 we're not supposed to use a name
Or number and writing it sell
Yeah
Paying taxes
Are you going to take taxes from your employer
Don't go pay income tax
I don't give people advice that I wouldn't do myself
Following Jesus I'm saying follow Jesus
If the government will put you in jail for not worshipping the government
That's exactly what they want
Crazy
Is
His logic is much better than Alex is good
Jesus does you will be persecuted for following me
That's orders
And Alex all the
Mom says you'll know it
Tree by its fruit quotes that all the greatest
Applications why he's
Supports Trump
And so the idea
I would never tell my listeners to not pay taxes
You have many times had the son of a guy who said
Don't pay tax
Talked about how
Are you referring to
Peter Schiff his son was on the show all the time
He's like a political prisoner he was murdered by the state if you believe
You have to believe
It's great and the idea that you don't tell your audience to do things
You don't do yourself
Horseshit
Yeah Alec
You don't bite
Before we get to it
We forgot to play the out of
Now is a great time
Is Alex most accurate prediction today that is great
So this is the last clip that we have
Disaster Alex
Is done talking
To these really frustrating callers
Play the Sesame
A little
Obama supported
Poor guy
He just misrepresented
The colors we just left
The guy didn't say use a secret Vatican operator
No. I didn't say you wanted to beat him up
Are you looking to fight
And none of them really said that Obama would save us
BrightStar of the
The evening
Yes
Actually that guy talking about the religious stuff
He probably was pretty smart but he's not
I think it's probably high functioning brain power there but he
I think there is a
Okay because he is using decent logic music
Pieces of Alex's mythology
Religion is he understands
Necessarily stupid as much as it is misguided
Here's my ears my
Deposit
To you
Imagine our imagine our heroic woman
Staying to Alice
Let me talk
Now whatever crazy dude said it
Alex
Shut up
Alex had a good 5 Seconds
They just kind of shut down
If she had done that would he have done
The same thing
The studio
Super male vitality
You know some sort of thing where it's like
You know I just
Why women like massage
Everyone wants
Here the daddy shark
Clip in the chat room
Well there's that
I'm not
For a second I'll find it
Let's get it
To the real me
If you guys until Christmas
What I want to talk
If you guys want to send an email to knowledge fight at
Gmail.com
Can send you the empty
Three of it
So you can have it for yourself
I shouldn't do that should sell that
Are you shiting me
I don't know look
I don't have the wherewithal or The Willpower to be like
I'm going to hold this hostage
Also I don't think we can sell it
Copyright issue
Respect map agreements
I guess I can't really sell it so can you go
Amelia baby shark
EDD
If you want to email to gmail.com
We can find all sorts of stuff
This year
Thinking about it down like
120 episodes of the show
We've recorded
250 3:00
Content probably
I'm at reflect we've written
Thousands upon thousands upon thousands
The words
And that reflects light
Even just a 300 hours of recording
WhatsApp
600 hours of editing
Research
No sorts of things
Consider that adds together to be about 9
2:00
Of work over the course of the year
40 hours a week
Is that for every 4 hours a week
I don't know how to do
Descenders 50 weeks in a year
900 / 50
What's 40
I know it's 18
Can you work full time goddamnit
How much time we take
How much we jumped in
Yeah
Delved
Through these
Sickening Waters
No matter how much
There's there's always going to be the part of us
Dislike
The fact that so many people
To us talk
About Alex Jones for 3:00 in the last
Here it's crazy
It's me and I really appreciate it we're pretending
Episode of the year
Can go up
So now now there's a certain part of it that's like
If we ever recorded law
Usher
Address for route
Before this chat room number goddamnit
Thank you very much
Everybody who supports the show donate
Huge difference
I never would have thought that anyone would give a
Looks like about this show
For nobody and granted we're not doing it
But we're still way more than I expected
Yeah now thank you so much
We love you all so very much
I'm also just a fair warning next year we will be retiring the Sasha Banks
A song as the intro music
Look to the show for the livestream
New song will be debuting
Just a shout out to the legit boss
Big Ups thanks for taking us
Along on this ride
You know 2018.
What's the new
Also burn down rich people's homes
You sure
Huh
Probably get rid of this
Jon rappoport
Either that or we got to re-up on hating him
We haven't listened to John Wright
I was talking about me in the listeners goddamn I listen to them it's just still boring
I don't know what left
Reflect on that maybe will choose a new Infowars personality
To really hate
In the Jon rappoport maybe we'll go to
Or something like that
True it's difficult
Turn on Hayden's room corsi listening to his voicemail
Makes me want to kill him
Politically
We will look into Jerome corsi a little bit closer
And every shows himself
Certainly but for now
I'll just go fight on Facebook we're on iTunes
Thank you for
Subscribing end table
To be able to say
Jon rappoport
Goflight
Type 4
First of all
Go away
Suck a lemon
Expression
While sucking 11
She has legs
Only see him sitting down
You at least have a wider angle where they will cancel
See you legs maybe I don't have legs
All right Dad
Maybe me and Jon rappoport have that in common it if that is the case you're getting rambling at the end of this episode
Possibly legless people
Holding
Alex