Alexandra Thurston color
Forgot playlist from my laptop as opposed to from my phone you want to kill me off entirely
Becky Lynch.
Around
Is knowledge fight
I guess we like sit around and talk a little bit that's pretty much what
For the last time
Yes
What the f*** is this
I know a lot about Alex
Gutta Gutta had a real nice time
And some beers and some
Might have argued about big fish
Coming out on New Year's Eve
We're going to count it down
The best thing to do is play this playlist
Podcast
Roughly what are you thinking hour and 45 minutes before
3 + 1/2
Started today I want to take
I like to thank everybody you know
If you want to become a policy
Website.com
Wikipedia Sports
You have done we very much appreciate it
You so much and I can graduations on becoming a policy wonk
Louis thank you very much
Congratulations on becoming a
Polly
We got an interesting
Episode
Klipsch sure very interested in one clip
Okay
You did tell me that before the show and I still kind of don't believe actually I lied a little but
Investigation episodes
In February
The path of Alex Jones
Takeoff
And so I kept looking
I kept digging
On
On the day after what we covered so be like February
24th
The entire show is about Piers Morgan
Years after he went on Piers Morgan show
What's 8
He just goes off on this life
F*** off. Morgan you got fired suck it is just real agree without
No cuz I don't have clips of that episode it's so boring
Oh well it's just him gloating and being like some beers I win
Ryan
I don't disagree with that entirely at all
There wasn't much really to go on
It means episode on the 24th
I have millions of fans
I think is kind of in
Add the little bit of light on Alex's
Self-made passed
Clip that I have for February
Time Warner
AOL hundred billion dollar company
$20,000 on the first luckily got a local radio show
Nothing nothing
Nothing everybody has access
$20,000 loan
He had nothing
He pulled himself up by his Rich that bootstrap
Perfectly clear
I don't really think there's anything super native about getting help and I don't think that Alex
Is wrong
I've gotten help
Anything like that
It's wrong for him not to recognize
The position that you would lucky enough to be in
Came from nothing
Is such
Bulshit
Yeah cuz the amount of money your parents have to have a second just drop 20 grand
Is ridiculous
Broadcast out of a property that was owned by his dad
Like an office building at his dad owned
And his first
To get a radio show so like all of these
Not wrong
Stupid
Anyway
It's not like I said
It's all shooting
He was an orphan I would have been
Totally fine
If he says he came from nothing into you
No parents
I'm on board
Much more reason
There's one there's one part that's really funny
And I I don't
I'm trying to find
Clip and I can't find it
Explain it
There's a whole thing
They offered me every TV show in the world
And everything
Before they gave it to Joe Rogan
They wanted me to host Jessica Ferrell
And I know for a fact that from 2008
Alex has Jesse on when they're about
To start filming
And he's basically just like
Bagan Jeffy
His co-host
He looked like I don't know how funny would it be if I was like
I wish I had find the clips but for now I just wanted to point out like
Feeling like a real
Sucking like
On top of the world headspace
Why was listening to it I know he was almost Chandler Bing
He's going to be in friends was also almost
Both roll
Great Haircuts
Can you imagine all the girls going
Cody Wild
I was listening to this episode
Complain about Piers Morgan the whole time I agree with you
Yeah
I realized it I don't know if I've ever listened to the entire Piers Morgan
Are we listening to the entire Piers Morgan interview oh yeah we are
13 minutes
I realize that most people
That would be great episode if we just
Play that and then
Happy New Year guys and that was that we just called
It's
One of these things where like
It's stupid
And you don't like Piers Morgan to begin with
Buckhead
Whatever you think about the person who's interviewing him
Heads or whatever people are like
People ask me if I would like
Interview Ali
And it's it's things like this that we're going to be going over with
Is why my answer is
Categorically know who never wanted
Even if you have a command of fact he's never going to let you play the game
That you want to play
This is from
January 7th 2030
Alex Jones
Went on
Piers Morgan
Show
And made the rounds
Afterwards viral
He was still on the BBC at the
Alex Jones
Morgan was on
Alex Jones went on his show and was like
Oh man we were being followed all around New York
They're people too
Gang stalking
There was s*** all over the bathroom walls
I don't know about that
Cooperation
On the bathroom walls
And I'm not saying like 8.
He's saying it's on the bathroom
He creates like a really a
Christine
Sort of
Cover story
What is trip
Just mythologizing
They had to have gangstalkers follow me around talking to their sleeves
Like it some kind of cartoon it wasn't just like regular people
Stocking
BFDI
I like three times
Because of his gaze
I feel like you're disinclined
To enjoy this
I'm on board the Big Clip
Screaming at him 17
1876 will commence again if you try and take our guns
No I did not know that
I've never seen this
Like when we started this podcast nothing about alley
I'm not allowed to look up Alex
It has to be
Something that you introduced
Otherwise I
Not know anything about
Because important
Is mythology
Important piece of
His story
And it's really expensive where he broke through a lot more
He had before
Like he gained a lot of notoriety
A lot of promise
After this
Because you made a f****** ass
And soaked
Going to jump
And I
Hit me with the high sign
Piers Morgan and Alex Jones
Anyways watch this show
Petition
On the White House official website
6 + 5
No you Alex Jones did that
Started a petition to drink a Morgan
Deportes
I just
Piers Morgan is sucking
As a means of
Introducing Alex
Cool thing to do
What
Years of effort
Years of training in
Preparation to get all the way to the whitehouse.gov website
Put a petition
I would have signed up at 8
100000 people or something
104 thousand people assigned
Find Abbott
Station Alex Jones yesterday
Alex Jones Show
Starts off
Starsoft
Let's see how long
Either find text
That we have all these farmers and the Russian government official Chinese government
That this is globalism
Hanover
Swish
You know what I don't really I don't really have
Say more about that
Irene
Don't don't get me wrong I ice Doug Taylor
But there is a good point
Militarization
For your gun will now you're making gun.
You can come when the police come for your guns
Back at the dorm you're starting 2018 full-on militia sympathizer
Careful
I'm saying is Maybe
Bread lightly friend
Not the worst idea
In the world I don't know
We it look
It progressed
All got together
And just bought a lot of guns
I think that'll be fine communist
I've never admired David koresh
That's makes you and Alex different
I would say that it's important to point out those are the things that he's described
Specifically like
Jade Helm adjacent narrative
Yeah yeah yeah
It's all that it's all that
They're so that's I don't think I like that the Swiss get a shout-out don't think the Swiss and the Americans are the only people allowed
How to have gun
I don't know that everybody like most countries
Where it's like
Everybody has a gun
There a lot of country
I just because a couple of them have been remarkably successful
And I curtailing gun ownership and gun violence
It doesn't mean that there aren't
30 still
I don't want to do
The Second Amendment isn't there
Protect
I don't recall part of the second amendment being about
I don't know I don't remember George
Being like
We can't allow British
People to be quartered
Right
Street thugs
Little do you know that there is a provision in the Second Amendment about the knockout game
I mean
Spent like
Variability
To protect your property and stuff like that
I get the application that Alex would make their butt
I mean
Close
Zimmerman I think that there is there is code
Announce
George Zimmerman was railroaded
Your other is like
He doesn't fix it
We did not agree with the mainstream
Perception of George Zimmerman's website
Yeah
Getting into the idea of there being a lot of rape
Very much water deposit before
Secure that so here we go
Jumping back in
Because the police
20 + 4 Prime drop in
Means
16 years ago
Not true either
Mystics is as we know that much more
In-depth study was done by a lot of
A lot more crime there's an increase in violent crime
The parallel course
Everybody has guns
Right right
For example
The Republic
So
You know that's that's really him working himself into a friend
The Republic will rise
If you try to take
So the Republic
What is the Republic
Doesn't it doesn't A-Team
I like
Counterintuitive it requires somebody to take the gun
Before the Republic Rises
What is an interesting light bulb what are they what are we doing right now as far as
The Republic goes are we like hey
As long as I got my guns
I don't care if this f****** Republic Valderrama
Just stroking a f******
The idea that I think Alex and a lot of people like
Kim have that is
The guns are the only thing
That matters
And so yeah absolutely
In their conception
Which is not
What are you saying
Confederate Circle
He is royalty
Which actually comes into play it right about now
Dwyane Wade
My family was at the core of both sides
Does that mean
My family was the winner and the loser of the Santa Ana battle
What
My family started that
Right
People over there
My family are agent provocateurs from the Texas Revolution days we have always been gun
Runners
I mean will I make more money on guns then you got like my family was involved in the Texas
Revolution in Santa Ana related to David Bedford Forrest and related to The Tudors
He was Cleopatra in a former life
Roleplay
He's LARPing as Alex Jones
I would I would point out that the show is taped in New York so he's already
Now there's bad
Can you only become an American
Go to app
Is that part of the citizen
Boy boy so counterintuitive
He hates immigrants so much
That goes back to the
Depositing earlier that we sort of skipped over a little bit
His ideas are the women in India wanting gun
Okay I mean they should be able to protect
Themselves absolutely put the bigger issue is the people who are doing the rape
Seems like the larger issue over them having guns
A lot of interest in talking about
We only give women
Okay
Fine
Move Along
He finished
Yes I am finished
I don't know
You just hurt his
You want to cut that off.
Anytime you
Constant looking off camera like approval we like
I don't want
So
How many gun murders were there in America lost
Most remarkable things that you
Come away at I mean
I still don't like
Piers Morgan
Listen to this
And it's not because I don't like Alex I'm on his side
Because he's just trying to
Call Dad
Calm down
Why would you
Why would you have Alex Jones on your show
If you don't know what Alex Jones is going
To do on your
To be fair I think that is
I think he knew
Whole reason they booked out
Right
For millions of people to watch this
Be like
And it got like after Alex leaves in the next segment Alan dershowitz on
Marriott
Amanda Piper
Conversation about how like Alex Jones
Jesus
Important for why people shouldn't have done
And so there is a little bit of like I think they were trying
To trap him a little
But at the same time you can see a bargain
How to do a child's violin
Bud Draper
The correct amount of
Spoiler alert
VR
Whatever
Many gun murders
Is there are
America
How many people
Weather in Brentwood
How many gun murders
Alex has
Like that's a nice little dick move right there I figured you'd prepare for this
I've never prepared for any
Alex has like maybe 6
Pieces of loose
Paper
I almost couldn't write a funny or so
Right
So performative you can tell he doesn't he's not the only arguments he has
Reflections like what
What about staph infections at hospitals what doing what about all day
Because
What about
Staph infection
Yes there are regulations about Queen and Hospital like people
People work really hard to limit the the infections
But you can be exposed to
In a hospital
Well
Apply
Necessitate
Regulation
Images that are caused by a gun regulations
That tyranny and then you know what
I don't want any Hospital regulation
And either
Issue if you
Hospital infections
I agree I agree we need some mental Revolution people try and stop us from getting
Try and limit my access to
Great white shark
Where would you like the regulations to stop with great white shark
I want to come over regulation want to roll it back
If you want you're an adult you're an American
You ever god-given right it's
Third amendment to we're having a bunch
Well here's what I would think
Constitution
Absolutely
You are not there you are not legally obligated however
2 house
Is a British
Great white shark
Now.
Loud noise
Lower
Not
Doing a good job
But like I said I clearly thrown off a little bit of it is intentional to use him as a prop later
I think there is
And God bless him for it cuz I mean you know
When you had someone with Alex it is
Probably the best actor
Victor just let him playing
I meant just hope
Everyone is watching
See through it and see like
This guy is
Unhinged
He's crazy
He doesn't actually know any of the statistics
Does Pierce do a lot of camera takes
A couple
Zack from Saved by the Bell at where he's like okay pause
And then and then they go right back to it
Timeout
I would have I would have if I
What's the sketch that I was directing
Turn off scenery
Little Slugger
That's on the front that's on Sergeant Pepper's Lonely
Jolly Old Queen comes out with a decree you will be arrested If you defend yourself
Especially
If you are an old lady
Everyday I want an old lady's brain food
This is the cost of not having guns and we love it
People burning down buildings and beating up old women
Train
Street thugs
Swimming everyday of the week
Resume that street thugs are responsible for beating within the old women to death every day
This is one of the least advertised
Things about Brett
Constant old lady Thunder
Hunger Games
Mix
It's a movie I do all the 80s movie about killing old people
Hunger Games
Scanners the movie that you were thinking about
What world did Piers Morgan
He's a tough guy
None
Logan's Run
Jesus alright
Presented now
Is the Piers Morgan wanted to beat him up
You're very clearly he's like
Hey
How about I come back and we fighting
I don't know if
Approve something
I do love the idea though of it there but what
Subduing
How about you come back
Boxing ring
All wearing American flag you are Union
Responsibility
Okay
You were right in a lot of
Tremendous way
I really like seeing this kind of misery on someone
That I don't like
Stop
How many
He's very well
You said hundreds
G35
Bowser
No one wants to ban
Knives
That's that's a gross Miss representation
They want to do they want to use their hands
I asked you this
Sir
How are you going to put cream cheese on a bagel
Without.
Grab some
To tear apart
And you also
The same thing has to be done with bread
You can't fly spray
Giant sandwich
From one side to the other
Lather cream cheese with
Your hand all over
Yeah yeah yeah
Shoot it with a
For Christmas my dad got like
Wolverine
Blades basically
Like 4 cuz he does alot of grilling BBQ
I'm so like
Yeah it's cool
Just have these
Wolverine claws
Punching to the Moon
Like as opposed to having today
And I would imagine those my the first time I've ever wanted
Doobie Wolverine
Pretty sure you can even have those in Britain
Let's move our back in the Wolverine is the only superhero I can pick up who is total
What about Rogue
She's like all of them are street legal
It's not illegal to touch somebody
I don't think
The book
I think I think that we will have a drastically redefined
Definition of scrutiny
Public Storage
Do you want to spend
Yes
Semi-autos
Okay almost aren't even coming
Which weapon
Predominantly used in the Aurora movie theater shooting
Yeah okay
Alright
This is this is why.
I think he's trying though
He's
He had no idea
Or at least
What you going up
The idea of
Coming at Alex
Something
Look at these two things
Is silly
Alex news
That there are two things
And he's going
To make it a million
So any argument
Where's Morgan has
Is
Purely dilute
Yeah
Really to dance with him
Like
Prepare to deal with diversion you can't really get a central thesis
But at the same time.
Devastating if Alex
Engaged with it but he's just not going to
Well I mean
The issue
The issue with
Piers Morgan
You built he's trying to do this whole build thing
Here is an interesting fact
Another fact
You can't build an argument with
You have to do is
Bright
We're relatively
Ballistic boxing match for truth
Actual and I don't think they would
You should wear the Union
Don't really feel.
You should have to wear the queen
The actual Queen also I think
This is just fun because we on our last episode from 2014
We had the guy call in to be like
You said you wanted a box Piers Morgan
Alex is super confused now he trying to have a little bit of a context for why that was the case
Anyway
The single biggest
Shooting in the history of American Sons
People hit by shooter
Alex's legit just denying reality
At this point
Statistically true as of 2014
Terms of shooting
And I was like
No that's not it
That's not even
Unique
Anymore
Plano
Any interview
Interview with one of those people hard right people is always going to be like them
Who's ahead of the game
This was the single
Biggest
Mass shooting
Oregon Shopping Mall
I understand
Terminally ill
Answer the question
He's not going to but
Sometimes it makes a fair point
Generally speaking
With the idea that just because there's criminals you don't
Get punished for it
Fresh thyme
You're right
Contingent on living in
Society Society
One way it wants to operate
What you would prefer to do
Sorry about what about like
Vnsa in the picture
The ideas because we have terrorists
We're going to
Remove people's rights
I agree with that
Just because there are criminals
Semi automatic
Doesn't mean we shouldn't all have
Video game
First of all
Cuz I mean
Like you know I've been playing Skyrim and I can't tell you how many people I've cut down with a flame
Sword in real life
What's crazy
Flaming swords
Dawn
Flaming sword
Jurassic
Can we can we go over this point at nauseam but the idea that he's blaming
Serotonin reuptake inhibitors
Like
Psychoactive
Drugs
A dangerous precedent
Decide because
With
You would see
Much more
Violin
Most likely
People on medication
If they had
Some sort of access
To medication
Maybe we have a difference
Conversation about
X I don't know
I don't know
Supposed to taste
Generally speaking a lot of the time
People who are on
Psychoactive
Medication
When you see the people who commit suicide
Generally I have fallen off
The medic
So
Now that's that's in that's another good
To have is
Another good
To have it is
How effective are they
AR with
Drawls are worse than
Conversation
Answer my question
So that
Commercial with him just a gallon
The moment he realizes they're commercially
Pierce we're doing a great job
Yeah like that British shower
You know I take issue with the idea of
Reality
Statistics being referred to as
Factoids
In a in a dismissive because Morgan is doing it like you
Sandwiches
The losers strategy
He's laying out
Like building blocks of an
Using statistics studies facts
Alex
Oh yeah you have this crime statistics
What it what are we doing we're just going back and forth with
With stats on each other
To talk about that
I just don't talk anymore
Did you know that
90% of horses
Commercial
Kick him off
Herobrine producers like this is gold
Real baby
I need somebody done to you
I'm going to ask you some
Question
This is not
You already bought
Not a good strategy to deal with
You never like with someone who has such an
Defiant stance
Redlyfe
You don't approach them with like
Here's the deal
Here's what we're going to do
Belgrade
Is the
The show supposed to be
Yeah it's not really respecting the social contract except
What's fascinating about this
Is this is
Exactly like whenever he
He plays a video on a show
We're going to have to restart
Because I can't handle this piece of s***
You would totally do that
In the spirit of the property
What's the question
He's he's mad that you're Morgan has notecards you're hosting the gel you're bringing that little
A note
Why don't you have hair
Right right right
I mean I know Alex's
Obsessed with the idea of like being off
Teleprompters and stuff like that
I don't know why he's so triggered by the idea that he has no cards
It's the difference
Between a professional operation
Extemporaneous nonsense
Off the top of the head
It's weird
What equipment we don't have no cards
What happens if you should respect
He's switch
From
A switch
From being like
To being calm
Immediately like
No matter how
Little nationalist you are
There's something American
About hating a guy a British guy condescending
That's quintessentially built into America like
One Spears did that I was like
Go get him Alex like I don't know what happened I don't know what happen
He's very satisfied by what
Violent crime
I don't know in the in the show
They're probably should
There's so many bodyguards on his set
Videos about like we try to take away our guns
I don't know if there's more
Has bodyguards but I would assume a lot of numbers
Security guards
Christian
Bodyguards for sale
Anything like that
It's a dumb argument
Because people who are
Security guard
Regina really
License
You know
That's a good point though other than Powers cop
If we do get rid of guns
Maybe we won't need bodyguards
We're not creating jobs
Tell that to the old ladies in England
They need bodyguards
Certainly
Create a robust economy around old lady security guards
Retirement age nonsense
Protect us
Alright
It is always
Sandy Hook
Great Point Alex
Rhetoric
M3 route
Is trying to employ is
Beating back against Alex's argument that
I was just trying to bring up the
Large
Shooting
Generally are automatic weapons which undercuts
Which undercuts the argument that most
Shootings
What have you
Statistically but those are
Whataburger
As opposed to
Whatever it's it's hard it's hard to hurt
Kill people with
I think it's not that hard
I've never tried
Like it you you can't
It's like there's
They need they tell you to shoot
Center Mass
And all of that s*** is not how they trained cops no idea
Probably
Pretty pretty stoked about that proud of you
A surprising number of gunshot
Shooting you back
Rat you fly backwards
Be that as it may
I think more often than not
You find black people get lucky
Yeah I don't I don't know man
I don't care that's not a
Really no it's not
Do you understand what I'm getting at
These large-scale trash
These are the ones
Always
Seem to use automatic weapons semi-automatic weapons
And that's the reason that there is an issue
That's the reason why people
The problem with what.
Stewing is that
He needs to have realized by now
Yes
Alex doesn't understand
Why
What are you thinking
You understand
Type of weapon
Open was used
Velocity
Vin Diesel
Being rude I'm trying to be civil
Some of the question
Why do people need civilian
Need an alpha
15 time
Don't understand it
Set alarm clock
I believe
Explaining
Play
If you don't understand it I'll lay it out as best I can
From from what
His point is that
Because the media
Sensationalizing
These mass shootings
And makes them such a
Story
That means that copy
Seekatz are arising
Bright
In order to
To create these
Which wood is s***
But it's also a
Fairly interesting
Argument
Is because yes
The media does
To benefit from
In the same way that gun manufacturers
And to benefit for
Is a philosophical cultural idea that was
Thoroughly explored in the Edward Burns movie 15 minutes
And we can move past this Tara I do I just don't I don't think there's much
Creep
To that argument is
Being like
Explanatory
There's someone on that in the chat room saying that we are very ignorant about guns
I copped to that
And that
I grew up in Central Missouri
I had a lot of friends who have guns
I know enough
About them
I-22
Have an opinion
Beyond that sure I don't know the finer points
5 gun laws in various States
I don't
And II
Whatever
I don't know if that's important
But
Don't necessarily think that a clear understanding of how guns work
And that kind of thing
Is necessary to
To saying that
Assault
Assault rifle
Apples are probably not
Yes
I agree anyway
People needs
University
Statistically
Countries in the world
And you have twins
Yeah
Perfectly clear
Don't have a problem with people haven't got
I want to make that abundantly clear less anyone
You're a little bit out
The military
I think Ivan can of worms
Getting that's as good as you can do
15 minutes
Great movie the FBI number
Number one
So that that that idea goes back to a lot of his aunt
Evax ideas
Google side effect dude
But that's just how it medicine
People's biology's are all different
People have different
Responses
To various
Just how it goes
I wonder I wonder what it would be like
Cheers
Was
Willing to just fly with
You know just like roll with the punches
Don't stick
In one debate area where like
It's coming at you with pills
Merry crisis
Is it a big deal to do you think that we should legalize drugs and then he be like
And then the show with that
Everything would be fine
Everyone would go home Happy
I'm not sure I'm not sure I agree with that assessment would go
Absolutely
Biscuit
Let me ask you one question
You'll believe it
Jubilee restaurant is the under the second
Your real concern
Is the evil be overrun by
Are they from
Summerella
The world
Maybe we should legalize drugs
35 gum
All Misfits
He
Alex has told mentality that where there are like
He's misattributed
Correlation
Causation
With the idea that there are more guns
Is now and the crime rates are going down
He assumes they must be linked
Right and that's just not the case
Especially you see like there's a article I was reading the other day about how I New York
His head like a
50 year
Hello
Brother crime
And
Because there's
Street thugs
They all moved out it's like the opposite of
The streets are Uggs all went over to
To the suburbs
50 fun
The suburbs
Fine
Anyway
I'm serious
You have a very very big
Platform
You are Thinkin 63 Networks
There we go
The stuff
Talk about them pills Alex get that in there. Here's where we get to the dismount
Interview
Really brings it home and he does the nice little gymnastic
Kind of like
Boy
No
Who do you believe was behind
BBC reporter
Who do you believe is behind
The mass shooting
Operation gladio
What behind 911
Even met 3 News reported
That the hijackers will order to be allowed in the United States
They have the Visa Department
Was part of the conspiracy
Martial law
Conveyed
50 firearms
Many of them are increased in value 230 even four times
I sleep very comfortably
Outside Austin Texas
Okay
Whatever
Commercial
So I don't know what will you achieve
Here
But
It's it's interesting to me because there is there is a little bit of that Alex Jones being
Complete a****** in a
Sort of funny way the British accent
You didn't like that there was a horn on that a mile away
That's again
My problems are my fault
Because I already made
Comparison to him
Watching one of those clips on his own show
Always
Always does the mocking axe
I don't know it's interesting that the other way Alex presents
In his own
Apologizing
His past is
Is that you know he goes in there and he slayed the
The Beast
That is Piers Morgan and destroyed his ratings
To be the globalist
Jill that he is right
And a Morgan wanted to fight him
Couldn't handle Alex Jones is brilliant
Being a what about Aesthetics hold upon related
Information in order to
Dodge points
Piers Morgan
So the reality does not really match up with his mythology
It's fun anyway
Springs
Here here 2017
Everybody for coming along with us
Interesting
I agree
I would say so
Christine
But if you want to check
About what
Give me one
Give me one prediction
What to do in Media
Type thing at the end of the year you're supposed to be
Be like well we've learned
Coin
Will be the preferred current
In America Max Keiser master
That would be an inch
Why not
Hedge your bets
Imagine if you'd been on the ground floor B
Write a billionaire
Next week
The stock market
Quita Quita roller coaster
I don't know
Everything is awesome everything is weird
That's my prediction
Let's
Let's go let's go odds
What do you
Think the midterm
The sense that I get I think
A lot of the polling
Wildly
Competitive
I think Democrat
That's probably take
You think so
I think at least enough
Maybe I don't know
That's where a lot of the things I'm saying
But at the same time
I don't f****** know
Possible for the Democrats
To get a supermajority a two-thirds vote in the Sun
I'm not entirely sure on that
But I don't know where I can we can't make any predictions
Noah
Far enough away Villa
I don't know what kind of smear campaign people like
Crnkovich are going to try and
Float it's a movie Anything Could Happen
I didn't think it would be
Be close with Roy Moore
It was fun
Closest ship
No idea my suspicions
Prediction
Straight white dudes
Still going to be off
I think that's probably mean if history is Prelude
It looks like that is a good prediction
Statistics of the Roy Moore vote
Especially when you when you factor in straight white
70% of straight
Something like that
Voted for
Or not
Just wait
Other weekend
If you're a Republican
Supermajority
It is not possible
That would have been nice
To be able to override veto only prediction
My only prediction is
White people are not going to learn but I got to be like
White people are still going to vote
Is going to
Maine
We need to commit white gem
If you
Killer whale
Will rise again
Another prediction is Nolan
What's up people will start going to our website
Plug-in Auto
Yeah you can go to the website
You can click support the show
Knowledge underscore fight
We are
Vagina
Exploring couple other
Podcast
Tribute
I've gotten a couple emails from people who have like
Androids
I don't know man
Podcast app
Interested
Ungrateful
Infowars
On the Alex Jones Show on December
January 7th
The day
That Alex
New York for the
To tape what we do
Just listen to
Guess what
John rapper
Support was co-hosting with a fill-in hopes
Yeah Alex
Alex had a fill-in host
Who is that
Little crazy
Jon rappoport
Songs beard
In 2013
What's it was upsetting
It didn't take
A long time for him to grow the weird beard that he has right now might be 3 years running a boy
That's a very quick turnaround for
The other thing
I checked it out
Thursday John Rappaport was in fourth hours during 4th hour
Get this
Picture was hung
No
However
He was not
Talking about
HIV
He was not talking about the facts
Are you talkin about
Tom DeLonge
UFOs are false
Swag
Oh that's right I forgot about you they're real
Apparently this is nonsense in order to make people scared of space busy
And there's one thing that I was thrilled to
But then also
I got to hear John Rappaport say
Jim semivan
Made me pretty happy
And it's still weird to have this like
You know there are spiritual
Connections
Between Project Camelot
Clean-shaven like no beard at offsetting
Not upsetting to look at
Weird
Very much so
Just to look at him say
John Rappaport
Go fuc yourself
Happy New Year
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work