Alex
Think about how we started
Drinking
3 bottles of wine every night
Would survive longer know a lot about Alex
A year ago literally knew nothing
Yes does the show ray
Drinkopoly belgians are buttocks down
I was thinking about it and it is our anniversary
Maybe 52 episodes
I guess what I like 20 something or whatever we put out like 140
Episode
This is ridiculous I don't know what we're trying to prove here pretty big
And I realized
Notice
Albert I was thinking back about it I realized
To reflect on
Is it had that first episode on January 2nd
2017 what it was
I don't know if we would have continued
I'd like to take a moment to replay what I think is the clip
That made us end up doing this show
We might have given up had it not been
For this clip
Talk about
If they weren't planning to
Good bad ugly
Red Alert this is getting crazy
This is so freaking out of control
Please help us
There's a decent chance that we would like just as just an angry insane person
Going down this road as we have I remember that now I lost my
Nothing better than
Long pause
Here in the 2018
Different
Show the show itself Implement that I think will help us moving forward
And one of them is I'm taking too much
Closer look at a lot of Alex Jones as primary sources and villain
For sure
Slate.com we have the first post up
It is an exploration of
The club of Rome
There's some sort of evil globalist
I want read a bunch of their document discuss why he's a liar about them
And it'll be way more of this
In this year I'm very excited
I hope people come along for the ride even more inadequate I post
Once a week and you're like okay
I'll put six
212 articles every single day
Do all the research myself as well it's not that Alex in present-day is boring
More fun for me to dive back into the primary sources I can try and actually find some little turtles
And figure out where he is why he is misrepresenting various things
Scream about nothing
Which
It is
A day's time
Also update
We started researching
For our first
Will be doing endgame
Okay cuz that's what he brings up the post
Let me tell you Jordan
I got 60 seconds into the documentary before I head to go read an entire book
Revolution driving into
Anyway
You got a lot of stuff coming down the pike
Exciting
Pike pike
Pipe
Is that what you all have you always
Coming down the pike
Now we don't know
We can be going over the January 2nd 20
18 episode today
Beer on Tuesday
Shout out to
Someone has very much
Thank you so much
Don't get mad and tell your brother thank you so much
Do you like foreign policy walking
We all get to hear about a bag full of poop
Today
January 2nd
We have not encountered the present for a little bit because
And
Is Alex
Nope maybe maybe
You decide what he
Really wanted to do
Was
Relative
Zoe is not do that today is Arnold Palmer half and half zero
Calories
Stop grilling
That's about it
Anyway let's get to the show we got it
Start things off
Which is actually out Jones dressing
Okay
Alright
I mean
I guess
Is his position on it you could sum up as we've all known those UFOs exist
They just dropped
A hundred percent is going it's a gone
Dates after they
All of their tax
Holographic
Anyway
Spyder leader
Throw that be great
This whole time save it spider leadership is not a big deal
Is in a weird place
Little bit
Little hungover
Worth a couple billion dollars of liquid cash
Buildings and infrastructure
But
Billionaire
10 years ago
But if you look at the
He wants it America First policy
Thanks by the way
Does well off of Americans doing well
He does well
Bible prosperity
But the president
New York State returns or his New Jersey
Shape returns to show
Yeah that's not good
Turn off the year with like
You should release your tax return
Completely different level does on a
The exact opposite of what you're doing it wrong
Tax Returns come
If Alex Jones is correct
Who sang
In terms of like
Oh yeah
Losing so much money on this tax bill
Master the internet with Ozark
And the fact that that hasn't happened
None of it has happened
Rodger Stone
Memes
Call not true
Absolutely not true
Spell really does hurt
Because he
Actually is almost worth as much as URI
And everything is dead
Tech tech
Brooks laich these hacks things don't affect me at all cuz I'm worth shitt
You can still do not pay taxes because
Exempt from less than 5,000
The only way it does affect us is insofar as we will not
Sure there will be infrastructure problems
Alex brings up that in his
Calculus
What what makes
Can do well as well on a
Propertybase
Service economy which
Sync means
He likes it when
People working his
I guess I would help us understand what he probably puts back
You know his businesses
Show that he's largely just shifting dad around
That's more what its business model is broke constantly rips off contractors constantly abused
The people who
Fight back
Much like Alex
Stealing the Ellery
Prison bumper sticker from
Is that that you really start to get the send
But there's so much more of a spiritual connection
Between Trump and Alex Jones and terms
Kind of scam artists
But I don't necessarily tapped into early on
But I think there's a lot more of that then
Liquid cash
Alex or Trump trump
Like if you if you are welcome
If you ask Trump to buy you a cup of coffee would he be like
Let me check my let me check my credit card to see
How do you think about
Folgers
And that the other thing in that Clipper
It is fast
I think is really fantastic
Is this
Prospectus
No
Because then leave shows you rich
Rich enough
Compared to these globalist billionaires
Consider lower down on the list
I don't either but I think it's what Rodger told him
I think that that's a that's a reasonable
Psychopathic
Explanation for it is like billionaires probably do know considering they probably own
Play that's the that's the thing that makes the most
Billionaires are looking at Trump ban
What an a******
Billionaire
You say you're a billionaire
You aren't now
Never going to have
Episode goes on and get back to it later
Tiffany should release
The taxes
As time would you like
Everything that's not too
That's something you talked off
But I was like
Going back and forth through most of the episode while I was listening to it like going to cover this they're going to go back to
To the past where we going to do
And one of the things that really encourage me like now we got to go over the
Is that
Today
Is a day
Full of Alex Jones
Alright
A lot of people now I'm in like
Are you coming in hot. I don't know what happened over the holiday this is like
I got to get some boys I can work
I got to come back on in Fort Worth
I got to make Beauty and the Beast Gaston
Bad guy
Cuz I'm not sure if you
It is next clip he lies a bit about China and tax
Incentive
But they have I put into place which will discuss on the other end of the clip
But then he jumps into a prolonged
No thankfully
Just saying you know what
There's still a FANUC problems I assume that I just didn't want to hear anything that sounded very similar to
Ching chong bing bong it's going to have
One of these days
With
0 baby you come here
You come here
Your Apple and Facebook and Twitter
Champs Pro tax
Vernix
Guess what
It goes on another 40 seconds hold on
Philly
What would you call
Like the the dumb guy and act like he's mentally challenged
Stand up
Ecosoc
Swindle University have six houses in hundred thousand dollars
$300 per gallon
$300 wool jacket we looked up
So this goes on
But also but he slips in there accidentally I have looked up how much Bernie
Sanders clothes
Erase all this
What do you raise all that Alex I should be clear
He never answers his own question
He doesn't
Blind a lot about is this
The situation with China
I'll read here from The New York Times article
Temporarily exempt foreign companies
Paying tax on their earnings
Bibs keep American businesses from taking their profits out of China following washing
Overhaul of the United States text
There is however a catch
To be eligible for and companies must invest those earnings and sectors and Courage by China's government
Including technology in agriculture
According to a statement
From the finance
Babes
One where companies from around the world to set up operation
The tap into a highly-skilled Workforce
And strong infrastructure
On top of the standard corporate tax rate of 25%
Companies are required to make social
Security contributions and other payment other country
So
Text issues
You're not a good way to approach
Write the China business
They go to China because they get very skilled workers that they can pay very little
Is a wash
Chuy's not really necessarily one
One of the big guy
The businesses have
Bernie Sanders
Disco costumes
Could you read the whole article about boys
Cuz I'm about to read everything and I voice
Credible
What is that
Improv people to sketch actors to
Saturday Night Live Larry David
Peter John Burns there's no way
Regardless government's latest measures would
Be significant enough to keep many American company from repatriating Bravo
Sounds about right so it in the end
Experts
It's not really
Big deal
Because they're all there's other tax issues
Chinese bunch of new laws in the last year
Then if made
Like
Getting money out of the country
Incredibly complicated
If you want to keep your business
So there's all kinds of other things
Play Alex
Other interesting why would they
Why would they vent
Make that
Knowing
At least
Having been told I would assume
That it won't make it
I don't know I think if they're hoping it will make some
Different
What other plays Campbell
You know
Where's the
Vista this article also lays out like rules on how much money flows out of the country as a way of control
The value of its currency
Signal Financial
System stable
Significant repatriation of foreign earned
Set off a broader Capital flight
And weaken the country's current
Following the current
Spark of vicious cycle with even more company
And possibly individuals looking to minimize losses
By moving their money out of
And then you get
Hyperinflation going on today we're in real trouble
I mean at the end of the day with their doing is just trying to mitigate whatever damage that's going to
Patriot
Come back again
Anyway it how many of us is absurd it's all just going to go back to
Yo-yos
Maybe investment
Companies but not in the other
What they're doing with all of that money is
Then inflating the value of their own company
None of it is real it's all imaginary
Like everything's in there.
Is Magic
Like there's no nothing
It's not like they're building a thing
If we move money over here money becomes
Here like it doesn't make any sense
So let's move along though cuz we
You can spend this entire episode talking about creation
There might be some more points you can bring out by whatever you like
On this episode
And that is that there's an article in the Metro
The UK publication
About how adult
Should buy their children
But that is just a launching point
For another impression
This one
This one is
Not as a defensive
From an audio standpoint
The word Starbucks
Just fairness
No it's a real question what happened I apologize literally asking us to question
What happened I finally start the wrong click
Columnist says parents should buy their kids check toys
That is the big newspaper
London the Metro
Church
Watch kindergarten
Help
Jessie saint
Show me the Muslim
What was lovely
Play Notorious lovers of sex
Pac-Man
So that was Bugsy Elders what was that
I don't know of the elders the pedophile
I mean great character
It goes back to Jasmine Alders just saying that maybe masturbation is up against
Should be taught it's even like after she got fired she got interviewed about it be clarified just like I wasn't
Like people are taking this way out of context I was just saying
People shouldn't
Teach kids that it's wrong
Maybe instead of a how to do it
Putting putting a lifetime of Shame onto your fourteen-year-old
Who really can't control himself
Or even 10
Through puberty
We're starting to have those feeling it was until it wasn't the backwash
4 years of
Shame
Came out that I was like
Masturbating forever that's what I'm doing
But bedtime
Yeah lying about Jocelyn Elders he's like why we has that clip nut
Clip
Oh that's another great quote over Johnson Elders that I found when I was looking through all this
Noah Cordova like anybody who thinks children needs
Be taught how to masturbated never change
From what I understand I talked to parents before kids
Just play with themselves
You do it for me
Incredible young age
Yeah absolutely doesn't matter
Yeah so
I got to be honest
March
We had a we had a weird show as a pedophile
Underground
He and Alex
Stories about what we f*****
What what non-sentient things we Foxx on stage it was very strange that the three of you didn't start a podcast
So I don't know everything about it that's our off Street
This article from Metro
Here in a little bit cuz it gets much more in-depth at it and that's a more appropriate time
To dive into that but for now
He's lying about Jocelyn elders
He pretending there's a clip
You can play
Boy
I won't lie I think he does it again like
Clip where Alex
Pretend that Donald Trump has raised taxes
2018 the year of the impress
Spanish
What happened
Bernie Sanders Usual Suspects
He's blowing Richmond
To ship our jobs to China
And you know that
And you're playing with dumb down
Pot kettle
It's not free
I want it I want to save it like I think the positions are a little more nuanced than that but I do
Fair is fair
Critiques to be made
Against him on a lot of that stuff
If you want to talk about pie-in-the-sky stuff
You're talking about Med beds
Except like that you're talking about
The secrets of the universe and curing all diseases that Trump has it all at his disposal this secret bases on Mars
Already exists and somehow are also already filled with pedophile Alex has not said that he's allowed ever
But that's the thing about that criticism that drives me in
Insane about the the Bernie sander
Oh you just saying we're going to give it
For everybody
Free
How that works
Know what it is is we do need to ask
That there have been
Plenty of debt forgiveness program
Over Donuts
Everything and every time one of those debt forgiveness
Is programs go on
What happened
To those people who get all that
Money back they reinvested in the actual
Economy they built
They do all of this stuff
My generation
Like they always talk about why don't Millennials buy houses and because I fucken college loans cost
What is March
I have imagined every morning $40,000
Because I was sold when I was 17 or whatever that
If I don't get that
Well I would love to buy a house
If I had that $40,000 back
Is a down payment
You have all of these
These people buying houses
That creates
More jobs in for the economy
Willits Peaks
Why would I want I want you to make
I was just going to double down and reinforce that you're saying that like
When you're living under undue burden
Whether it be
From not being in
In control of your own
Destiny because of
Like overwhelming debt
Control your own reproductive
Choices those who really live in Freedom
It's not we're not really free
Slavery everybody lives under that
To some degree
And
People could use help
Another
Dxp of the
Isaiah is so long called
Where
Could get out from under
Misapplied self
Yourself but you did it because you were mislead
Those are
I wasn't entirely misled without that college degree I wouldn't have been able to get
Get so many
Maybe
What type of jobs are also a lie exactly
Right
High school diploma
Degree in English to be able to do it
I have a lot of friends
No one's ever check
Who cares
Crazy
Anyway that's what I encourage I think most of our lives are college-educated
Why
Morality is whatever you feel like
You were saying
Turns out it's a Democrat
Here Comes
But that is where I got a little backup message
Stuff like that
Is about $10,000
Play gentleman if you got a $500,000 house
Austin is the highest in Texas
School
Little Scamp
Iran
.
Values
Loving
System
Turn on rig
In terms of Alex
Is 100-percent synonymous with Robert Davi
So amusing that terminology
Is kind of like a little wing
The guy who did say that there are bars
Children sex slave
Guaranteed $100 in property taxes
And
Selectively release
Just a shower body
New York New Jersey
Oh my God
Alright
As far as that stuff goes
Prediction Alex is making
Let's see
I don't believe that that is a
At all
What any Economist but I've read
Believe is going to happen
Do you have your position
We will see
The idea behind what he
He saying is
As far as proper
Prior to
Prior to this
Rewriting of the worst loss
You could deduct your
State and local
Property tax
Right
Do that
Now all the sudden
You can't afford
The cities are going to start
Like what it is what the text Bill really is
It's essentially like stealing money
From large cities
Putting it in
Rich people
Robin
Well more like
Robbing give Rick Palmer
I don't know if that
Was it real
You know what I want the apostles to release their tax
Yeah that's what I know I need to know
I know that one guy was attacked
Collector in any change
Solitaire
Salt Tarsus
Call Paul
Back to the
Get back to something else we touch down already
And then I gets into
Ecova a liberal
Media figure
I don't know we'll see how much I agree with
Farm Company
Did a great job
There is however
Railways technology
January 1st this year
It's zero.
Always pays hero
Subhuman
He says that
Unchivalrous piles of Filth
Alright lyrics
Touchdown
Ruger
Situation here
Turks
AR
Fun
Bye
The Islamic
Gulf States by crowds
Sorcerer
Claims
Might be partially
Heaven also they just had 20 million dollar Venture capitalism run
SO3 Venture capitalism for Avatar
Literally run out of
Gulf States
Pitched in
And they're going to
Play because of it
Inflow of
VCU money
Which
You guys look into it
Might be
We got we got programming baby
Just throw whatever it's a while see what sticks time I don't know if I necessarily want to be involved because with Alex Jones
Something not real
And I used to be a bit conservative
Back when he was younger in college
Was a conservative
Stuff that we're pretty bird
Article in the hill
The founder
The founder of the Progressive online Channel The Young Turks apologize on Thursday after making sex
Derogatory remarks on his blog
Texas opening up
Here's a quote from
Obviously the genes of women are flawed they're poorly designed creatures who don't want to have sex as often as needed for the human race to get along
Longford Leanne
Peacefully
In another post called the rules of dating
You can explain
What is the dating process
I don't want to hear that women
Ignore these rules about rule number
41 there must be some serious making out by the 3rd date if I if I haven't things are not about to laugh
Much longer
If you don't get back on track by the 4th date you're done
Number to Northstar must be orgasm by the 5th
Unspecified
Is he talking about a handy
15 is probably too late for Hindi
Opposed
Do this but then at the same time
I am opposed to all of it
At the same time
When addressing a
He apologized
The stuff I wrote back
Hugo said
If you read that today what I wrote 18 years ago you're offended by it you're a hundred percent right
And anyone who subjected to that material I apologized
I deeply regret having written that stuff when I was a
Free guy
If someone said that today I would heavily criticized them on the
Michelle
And I have
I've criticized myself over the years
Not yet matured
Still conservative
We thought that stuff was
Politically Incorrect
An edgy when you read it now it looks really
Honestly ugly
Very uncomfortable
So the reason that I am not giving him a pass for writing that stuff necessarily but I do give him a tip
The proverbial hat
In the sense that he owned up for it
And he took responsibility and apologize
Which is the
More
Adult thing to do in that situation
I would not like to be
Be taken to account for
For some of the jokes that I wrote when I was starting
Comedy
Their number things that I
Frey
Don't come to life it's not like I yelled the n-word like I'm Michael Richards or some s*** there a lot of unevolved position
Rules for dating
But I did it
You know I mean
I'll be honest I didn't realize
Rainey was a bad word
D'usse
I didn't have Anti Trans
Material
But I didn't realize that that was a pejorative horrible words
There's a difference
Between
The reason
The word ignorant
Is important
You didn't
No no
You didn't have access
Like there's a lot of situation
I could have known better and that is on me for being
But at the same time
I didn't know any better
There's if there's
Like it's hard to hold yourself accountable for being able to know everything that might
The purpose of that is
To just be like oh
This was a phantom
Okay cool I'm not
Going to say it anymore
The guys were like
Let's just talk
Is gone wild it's like no just
Political correctness is just like
Don't be a dick
Like it doesn't hurt you
To say it and it hurts them when you say it so why are you saying
Generally speaking I don't I'm not a uber thing I don't watch The Young Turks or anything like
Like that
Is a whole situation yes the stuff you wrote is terrible apologize
Go ahead and accept his apology
Is 18 years ago and there's nothing
Current weather
Stuff like that
I'm inclined to believe
He has
Learned
Seems like
You doing ever
I don't know I don't know
Exactly platform
God damned if he isn't against that type of I don't know the man so I don't have any idea
Uno
But I do know that
The thing is too though like he grew up and I in a Muslim household but he came to America when
You lived here
Right and he is an eighth
He's a devout 80
He's made it very
Very clear
That is
Where his
His heart lies
He thinks that women are subhuman and of course he does cuz he's an islamist
Is Ally on like three point
I don't need to I don't want to take this much time to f****** defend Genki Kerr
Deconstructing the
Little pieces of Alex Jones
How much he can lie in one sentence
Really spectacular
It's fascinating
It seems like every noun
And it's
Descriptor adjectives
Lice
Every single one
I don't think his article
Kohl's relies like re-up
I don't think that's a lie
But everything else pretty
The indefinite articles
Library there's no
Welearn
But not just Janke
Evil people
Vicious
They're just solace
Greedy trash
Smartro timer
Vicious
Vicious vicious Criminal
Will be back
I kept Charlotte
Guitarist
I hate your family entertainment
That's as Jerry gets the block.
So I don't know man I think when you speak in terms
I know the last time you did was like
2 seconds
I would say only when I'm
Antagonizing my cat
Right or my radiator
They hit a little bit and sometimes I will scream at them in the middle of the night
Xavier like
It's time to speak to
Perhaps you can understand
Kept up all night by radiators
Just below bed bugs
In terms of like losing your mind
Damn radiator
Will not shut up
I don't hear from the general
Every time
He's telling a story about meeting
Somebody else
It feels like
He's just running up to them holding loose leaf paper
Surprised when people push him out of the way like
Alex
No thank you
It's because you're afraid of the truth
Your large
And that's loose leaf paper that you hand wrote in Crash
Yeah
The other thing I always think about when I hear him say those things
Those sorts of
You got to be a little more specific
When you're talking about
It was like what I made with democratic
Controllers
The f*** are you talking about credit controllers
Second of all
Like it's the same things like global
Senior Alex
You're coming out of there going like
Number one
It was the movie clue I was actually just watching the movie
Horse bucking sneaking of wire we're wired one of these things
This b******* you claim this
The problem with that is that it would just be too much
You couldn't beat you couldn't be able you couldn't understand where is there
Fastest route
Tactic
KC Hawaii
Understand is that all democratic
Controllers are
Create background noise
You know what this is one of those things that I think it's really going to talk to me
My point is
Add Arizona there's a lot of
Prince's wear
Number these other things
We talkin about
Actual things that we can make
Alex is lying about ex-wife
But in the same when he does stuff like this
Important to really
Discuss this first second
Right where do you say these things like all Liberals are evil when you talked
Democratic
Controllers are all hissing and Evil
We don't even have to
No it's just go to a lot more parties intellectual discipline that we
You require in order to push back against that is just say
No they don't
And we have succeeded
NFL
It's the show
Dufferin
Send a text to Alex Jones
Peohe's
Position at current is that the Russia investigation is
Completely Fallen apart and everything is off the rails
Everyone is already admitted that it's not real
And all this
Get back to bash
His favorite boys
The man
Mueller
Do them get to hit the little buckshot
Here in this Mexico
Social media
Infowars.com
Newswars.com
Ethical leadership
Governor Clinton
Charlie McCarthy
We went over a lot
Sleeping over a lot of that stuff so we don't need
Do I really go over why he's lying
You know I'm not going
Sitting here and go to bed for literally everything, did
There's some bothersome answers
But at the same time
Not
I'm sort of
Evil bagman or Russia or whatever his uranium narrative
Amazing how that narrative
Have that story
Just like
Everybody knows that
That isn't true
Except for people who only listen
Conservative news
Right and we can adjust repeat it loudly with no evidence whatsoever
And then it's like
A month later
And you hear that story again you're like well
They're still talking about it I assume they gave evidence
The first time that they
They never did
Magic of the way Alex Jones
Declare something and then use later that's kind of operations
Hannity's list
We don't need to address any of those things
James Comey
Ventriloquist dummy
And then personal
Just got to wash over me
Well of course
Call Eddie at home
Ventriloquist doll
But we need to get back to uranium one is
The personal insults
Just looks like a pervert I'm sorry looking
Slime bags
Supposed to be Sharp
Look just perfect
Danger Will Robinson
Are horrible jokes
The restaurant
I think that is probably how I was doing watching the restroom
Right
Issues
T20
Address as it relates to his narrative
Dealer
Miller does have an Ethics waiver
Special counsel
Investigating
Trump's campaign
Well I'm reading this here from an article in Politico because
What
Ethics waiver really is
The boj wants
And the reason
Most people think it is
Is that the waiver is believed to relate to Mueller's work in recent years as a partner at Wilmer Hale Law Firm
Which also represented former Trump campaign chairman
Ed White House adviser Jared Kushner
Who is also Donald Trump
Essentially it's a
Pinterest
Absolutely not have that ethics waiver
And he proceeded to court
Like God Kushner or all they would have to do is get a wilmerhale attorney
Represent them in the case
Ambulance would have to be out and so
That's in the same way that so many of them have ethics
Neighbors that we don't hear about like Kushner has an Ethics waiver
Like all of these guys that work for Trump
Wind up having those same waiver
Because the only way to get around that is by saying
You're good and there is
Bear is a
No just did a colonel to this that is
That's the right
That's the right thing to do to cover your bases
If they if they were acting like God they just would have
Like all those like the Amicus brief was filed
Like that was clear like
Committed the crime
But we were just like well we
Just arrested
There's an interesting quote in this article in Politico from Richard painter
I think it's sloppy
The conspiratorial side of me thinks
Somebody jumped
For the waiver because they want to create the impression
Robert Mueller has a problem
When Robert Mueller does not have
Have a problem
This is going to lead to Fox News conspiracy talk
Specifically gave him that waiver
As a way to
To undermine his credibility
The refusal to explain why
Admit abilities because
Mueller worked at wilmerhale
Manafort
Kushner
ORD sessions
CNN report
Wilmerhale Mueller works very briefly
For a company involved in a nuclear energy project
Champion by Michael Flynn
The retired defense
Intelligence
I want to serve for as trumps National Security advisor
It's unclear whether the 17
Waiver
From schools covers
Terrible sentence
What was reported to be less than an hour's work Mueller Bill to The Firm
Towers work
There's a company that was involved with Michael Flynn
Could present a conflict of interest
Under the wrong Circle
So
I don't know I'm more inclined to believe it's something like that then something along the lines of
He was in bed with Russia ever gave him
That
That's it
Ethics waiver to be throwing around so much of the Republican argument
About
FBI investigation
Boils down to
I know you are but what am I
Right like there's just repeating that over and over and over again
Yeah yeah yeah
SMS
Well I think there's a lot of fun
You can have with uncertainties
I'd life
You know I
Because no one knows
What the waiver is for
Alex has been free to say whatever
I'm also there's an article
Some articles that came out
Newsweek
That was last month
Trying to pull up
This report I don't know I don't know
Nevermind
I don't want a response
Probably throw something out there let's move along
Alex Jones
Eid idea
I know you are but what am I getting paid
Here we go
Supporters donated 700,000
Over a year ago don't we broke again 2 weeks ago
Can come out all these women had been paid off
Infowars.com
Everywhere else it's only you
Only you can stop
Forest fire
Another
Those links
Haven't been a very
I think it's possible that Alex Jones
Can't pay for
Advertise
Did you guys this
Valley City weather
Hillary and New York Times
Roberts to knots
Pacifica
About women making accusations
Like I'm definitely sure
Down to this hill article
He says the Clinton supporters gave $700,000
And when you really get down to it what it is
Who gave a bunch of money
There's David Brock
Gave $200,000
Then fashion entrepreneur
Buell
500 South
Now Alex Jones is not read this article
Because immediately after this
Immediately after this breakdown
It says
The effort did not result in any women coming forward according to the time
Bloom at Lisa Bloom
Is $2000000 for her story
Assumption was unwilling to offer
She wasn't trying to be this woman
So Democratic donors familiar with blooms efforts a tableau for the 200,000
From the American
Refunded the $500,000 from Buhl
Some 500,000
Back
So any statement bloom tonight at the Hillary Clinton campaign had any knowledge of her efforts or that she collaborated with
Devon energy
She also denied the payments were needed before the women would come
Come forward
Quote it doesn't cost anything to publicly are allegations
Security relocation are expensive
We're sorely needed in the case of this magnitude
In a country filled with so much anger hate
Violence
So yeah you know there's
There is a lot to say about
Trump supporters
Being told
That these women are liars and they're getting
Pay it off
And then they know where they are and they know their name
Republican all the sudden you ever wrestle
Deathreats
Absolutely
Ultimately
Murder and rape threats
Yeah online bill good
Writing about
Ultimate irony
Scroll down a little bit further in this article in the hill
Right-wing activist Mike cernovich
The times noted
Michigan
He could have just
Go to just done that new year
So I mean if you want to go down that road
You see it in in
The details of that article is that
First of all the $2000000 thing was
Some person
But that's their price
Return
Beer
Money not
Leading to anyone coming forward
And even Lisa Bloom has gone on record to say we do
Support
The money isn't needed to bring about allegations
Ford protect
People who have made allegations
Completely accurate and then Mike cernovich also
Gives out money
I know you are
Something like that
So this point we're going to get in
2 we're not calling
20 team can start with the resurrection of call Larry Nichols not happy about that
To show what we end up getting into the
8 minutes
Vijaya just split up into
Pieces
It goes all over
With
We get some good impression
Any impression that there are
Istanbul
Okay
Bandits first one Alex I believe it was like a month or so ago the show Alex is really
Bought it about how people kept saying
He was attacking the gay folks
Because he says the people want to have sex with cars
He's very mad about that
I got to defend himself but that can't go well
Accidentally
Morkie weigh
Might have accidentally done that
No type
Washington Street
I saw the article
This is social engineering
And all this other stuff
To the LGBT agenda whatever you want to say and it's agenda
Problem the problem
No I never said
I just said that the lgbtq wants
Will know cuz he
He's being even dicier than that pick that piece apart
Cuz what you saying is first of all
There's a
Secondarily
Now I guess because of these Democratic controllers that he goes and hangs out with
Co-opted
The gay agenda to include f****** cars and that's
Brendan so put in the process of
Talking the ends up saying that no that is kind of what it is now
What are you doing
Alex tries to defend himself
And in the process of talking does the opposite that's a blanket statement for just about anything Alex
Headstone
You going to accidentally The Condemned himself from the grave somehow I'm sure
I'm so in this next clip we get to
I'm not the one by Jocelyn Elders before
Surgeon General operations
Will
They don't
Helpful
Controversy that you are entirely misrepresenting
But here's today little transgender shop
Generals for little girls
Do you know why they do that
Do you know why they offer fake genitals or transgender
People
I assume
So I know I do
I have a bunch of possibilities but I don't know the
The actual
Understanding
The feeling of having
The
Believe so you feel like you're going to feel like you're more comfortable in your own body
Exactly I don't think that's
Necessarily
Sexualization
Don't think that's necessarily
Some sort of perverse
But Alex
Pretty sure they're not giving you strap on
I would guess they're giving you it's like a it's like a pregnancy
Flashlight
Back in the day
Not worth it
Westlake has a line of like a bunch of
You know yet
Vagina
Mild
And what have you
Olympia or something like that
Salad
And from my understanding I didn't understand
Explain it to me
It's something to be worn sort of
Externally
That's how people
Experience
Physical sensation
Wait
Never there
I don't understand it fully but that
The explanation
I've gotten four
People
Ask about it and that satisfies all
Alex
Anything with genitals bad
Patient
I got
Do you have been turned into a
I don't care about the story I don't particularly care about the story that seems like a
There was one person in England who had male genitalia
I think that's what he's saying
I guess
I don't
I don't really I think that's a local issue
London Hospital
Right so anyway y'all politics
More nonsense it doesn't matter
The real question is
Do you have a thorn in your
And I do have a thorn in my phone
Straight up
A little bit of
Conversation
Can be had in terms of what you think it is
Appropriate what age
It is appropriate to
Have conversation
Children
I don't know I don't have any kids I'm not
I'm not super well-versed
In that and I don't think that there's a hard-and-fast line
So it is a little bit more of Murphy
Do territory
Institution
California get arrested for
So
Again
Crazy screaming man
Pointing the finger
I'm not particularly about being out of
I'm not particularly interested in
Rehashing
Tavistock Institute versus Tavistock
Confusion that we've gone over in the past
You can't say brother
In the world
Once it once again we get back to
You can look into this
In the right-wing blogosphere
Discrimination of lgbtq
Seniors at California's long
Is one step from becoming a pastor
On Governor Jerry Brown
The measure known as the lgbtq
Senior Bill of Rights
Senate bill
Wood banister hoodies from
Denying admission
Transferring a resident
On the basis of their sexual orientation
Gender gender identity gender expression
Or HIV
That sounds
Pretty great
Yeah it's I think it's
Probably important
Those are those are good reasons
Deny someone care or to arbitrarily
You fix them
So the issue is a lot of these right-wing groups
Alex among them say that
You if you just call someone by the wrong
Then they're going to erect
Cuz the bill at it does have I think $1,000 fine
It's possible
Or up to you
County Jail
What do you mean
I mean for for calling somebody the wrong gender
Courtney Joslin
Heather said the bar for criminal proper
Locution regarding this bill would be
Extremely high
Quote the bill is very very clear that
If it is the willful engagement
And repeated engagement
Indiscriminate
Contacts
Against LG
So if someone makes a mistake or doesn't know a person's gender identity is
And use the incorrect pronoun that
He's not a violation
Statute
Willful and repeated violations alone
I wouldn't lead to criminal prosecution jobs
They would likely be punished with a
Criminal charges would only follow she said
If a violation reached a level that was shown to
Because the risk
Death or serious physical harm
In accordance
Existing penalty structure
Health and safety code violations
Long-term
The person who pushed through the Bell who is writing
Hesed purposely using the wrong pronoun
Smoking ban
He'll be treated as a minor violation
But no one is going
So
Hey
Bright
Supposed to somebody who'd be committing a crime like
If you were to go up
To somebody
Cupcake cupcake for a long. Of time even after you
Right right
Is what it is
Harassment or exclusion or differential care of things are really what the bill is
What's 6
To address
We might have had the little
Technical snafu
Not entirely sure I hope this is
Still going out there but
8 Minute clip
Alex ranting about a lot
Sex
Course I would say
So we get to this next
Clip
Where Alex
Like we said
We've already dressed on a recent show
Alex
Understand that I believe was in the sixties
Tavistock
Students have stock
Completely dissociated
Just believe that they the same thing because he sees the name Tavistock
And
I was
Really interested to hear this next but I cut out nothing
This is all just straight talk
Stickman team
Next
Surprising
Explains where he's based
A lot of these ideas
Not good
Psychologist or psychiatrist
I had dinner with a former psychiatrist that work for the state department
20 years ago Minnesota
You want me to make the station on
The guy
Very intelligent very smart guy and I looked it up he was famous
So
Here's what we have
We got Ted Anderson
Old Time by Ron Paul libertarian
Midas resources operative
As it were
Alex Jones
Obscurity probably around this time
He's going to Minnesota
Might be one of the early meeting
Anderson
Still I the lights
Justin Trudeau
But
This guy
Psychiatrist
Psychologist of some sort
Without
A radio station
Mission of some sort
And is also famous
I think the details
I don't think so cuz I
I'm not sure the person's real I have no idea
I've heard a lot of famous psychiatrist go into buying radio
Celebrity
That's but that's one of the lay of the land
The context is important this is probably when Alex is nobody
And
He just said Alex just start research want to go to the kids because I can't tell you but he goes he started cussing
In the families confuse everything good teaching
Convenient
It's a couple thing
First
Blah blah blah
Hear that
I already knew about
You didn't and
It about
20 seconds in this clip he's going to say
That was way too far out for me
The other the other piece of this is like
Why wouldn't you ever have him on your
This is a guy who's telling you
I don't understand why you wouldn't have never heard him mention
I would say either he doesn't
That's a strong possibility
Patchwork of
Angelica
Or the other part of that was
If he was just starting a show back then
He wasn't talking about this
Different
Insane Bolt
But also I could just be one of those persons drink
Wants to talk to you
Bachata station
Is that
I forget that.
But he wasn't all that Shannon
And this is a little extreme for me
He's already
So.
Female nurse for cervical smear
Children are preparing
For sex changes
What's this
In the sixties.
It also shows that audiences
They can't tell the difference
So I don't know what to wear to land on that but if its 19 years ago
Sumo's about
B99 ourselves somewhere in that
Did fairly in the
I don't know I need to work out a more
Specific Alex Jones
Timeline but I think that's probably
Pretty clothes to wear
Do you know this week
Sweet spot is coming out of
Set TV
Getting fired
From his radio gig
But I don't know whether that's an interesting
Something to play
Oh no
So what was going on
Well I look
Too much to my
Other parcel
So earlier the show we had that Alec bring up what was
I told you was going to be a big narrative
For the show that was the idea that
That is nautical
About parents buying
Yes
How in the middle of this
Minute clip 8 Minute rant
Alex Jones
Decides to put his own narrative
And make it far worse
Call someone
Bamboo Beyond debates about sex education in public schools which is really about
Cold reading a Daily Caller article
Cupboard
Great covering the article
Metro
Alan Scott
That does not follow
It shows images of children
Show all of this
At this point
Alex Jones has the document camera
And he's hoping the article
Haha shots of all the pictures in this article that Alex's
Pornographic
We are going to show those on the document cam
Contacts they're certainly not
Little kids playing
ShopRite
This is sick
It showed little girls panties
What's a donor
The Dead
Sexualized
This is 40
Pedophilia p*** masturbating in public
Publishers pedophilia
They just pulled it
Snopes
Screenshots of it all
Sorry
So at that point I went to Infowars
What about the rest of the day to find their right
You got to have this up there they've got to make sure that
Throw this in Snopes Facebook
So I went and I I like I said I went and I got the screenshots of Alex's
Paper
But he has the Arctic
He flips through it
And
Will show hear the the pictures I text them to you so you can
You can see that this first one here is of underwear
Yeah that is
Whatever
Johnny got me talk
As far as what I can
Can read on here
Girls in particular are less likely
Play them boys 2
Pizza Ranch
Where is Boise
Chewy what I say
Think we're seeing here is
I would say probably women a woman
Who is
Uncertain and coming to
To terms with her sexuality
It's like your first. That kind of
It's like
This is gross I don't know what's going on here that Kai
Right there might even be a taken it because
You could die
You could you could see that as being an
Play on
The next one here is just a bunch of dildos
It's just an art display of a bunch of dildos and what have you there
Nothing involving children
There's nothing
Inherently dildos
Weird about it is all of the dildos look like
This is Britain it looks like they're giving the twos up so it has
It's like the Builder Israelites f*** you alright
I'm liking this
So the next one is the only one that I think that Alex Jones might have
Little bit of a decent argument on
In the sense that it is on
Settling
I'm so it means spoilers watching the videos
Little bit
Settling but at the same time
What is depicting is
Something the kids
Playing around with each other I don't know the value of having it in a Metro article necessarily but it's not
I don't think of this picture is
Pornographic
No necessarily
It is
But at the same time mainly because of the Infowars logo at the bottom right
Coors logo is weird
Especially since
They're the one showing it with the Infowars thing on the bottom right
Check this
Right
Written in the article from what you can tell because by the time Alex was on air
Retro
So I wasn't able to find anybody who would reposted it
But what you can tell from those green cap
Is that the article is talking
About
Child
Be helpful to them
Especially for women
It is much as
It's a female author
She's talking about herself and her friends would use like brushes
Retrofit unsanitary
Exploring their own sexuality
And that is all
Ultimately
If you f****** pillowman
Healthy option
Spell I would say that picture that last one is bit unsettling
They're like like I said
It's in line with the artist
Style of a lot of
The doctor will have you played
It is like one of those sex-ed books where it shows very
The people like
And it's just like
Other articles in the Metro there is that same sort of Art
Textile
Cartoony version
There's another article that I sounded like what things were found in vaginas in 2017
And the picture of a woman
Got with him
Recovering
So I would argue
Possibly
The article or the picture that they put on The Daily Caller article which all-flash up now is more upsetting
I would say that they are upset
Wow I don't know why but I am more unsettled by that
Just a hair
So I don't know what it is it goes from the audio listeners
It goes from a very simple depiction of cartoony
Permanent playing with each other's genitals or grabbing
Clearly
Bright The Daily Caller article has a three-year-old
I don't know I want to say this way cuz I think
I think this game
You can be kind of fun
I don't know
Alex should have gone further
Like
I don't understand why he didn't go ahead and
Just look into what else
This lady has written
Cuz I found Alan Scott entire biography on
On their Metro here's another article
Mom makes fun of her model brother by getting toddler to recreate his poses
Do you scroll down here
I've got a toddler
Pretending to be a model
How is this not sexualizing a child
We could have made hay out of this Alex
I don't know what I'm getting at is
Could have tried harder to make his dump
It took manufacturer
I believe so I believe a little bit
And the tragedy of it is that
The
Issue that the lady does bring up
The article is real
And you can tell from the text
Survive screenshot
Whether it be about the shame
The children experience around their sexuality and have crippling that can be moving forward
Going to stop your children from exploring
By not having any conversations or
That you can offer to them last
You're making a dude and you're living in a certain denial of the idea that your children will ever have a sexual life existence
But I was growing up my parents were like look at all this
There is
You're going to hell if you
Absolutely like that's the biggest issue
That's what they're that's what they're ruining sex with
You're going to hell
Break so
Of course you're going to f***
We get the end of the eight-minute ramp
At this point you sort of
B from
An article
But he disagrees with and wants to
He wants to talk about but not really that bad into being a man
We couldn't find our page but it's working on it
He's talking about the 404 not found page there's a bear riding
Skateboard on
Candy
Tomorrow
The nightmare is upon us
Call
I promise I promise I promise I promise
Covered covered all that all the time
Has been pretending
Ladies and gentlemen
And they're just going to push it
We need
Vitamins and minerals and supplements and the real red pill
It was all
Aledo Tire 8 minutes
Scaring people
About how they're going to try and children
All of the
What's all of the transbay
All of the idea that he's not gay people because he thinks that
The gay agenda
All of it
All of it was to lead to I need your money
F***** up
Real f*****-up is the way that he sells super male Vitality as we remember is like
Bright kids listen to his show
Do we have heard at least like
A fourteen-year-old call in a twelve-year-old call Ann
I made it would it would be right in that that age
Wheelhouse
I would like to be older
I'd like to be more manly that sort of adolescent
Yeah
Hello so and talk more about that Metro article I really want to talk
Talk more about it
Quite frankly
I want to see the biggest
Paper
England
The song even a little bit number to the Daily
Metro's number 327
At least that their readership is at least
So the guardian probably be
Higher two if they
You know what I'm saying
Is the guardian even a printed paper the
The Guardians
Distribution Mercer chelation
Imprint is only 100
Guardian
So know nothing about those
Right wing
Things that always go viral
Conservative blog
Is it always just like
One person
Who's just was just talking
Just balling ideas Indigo Wild
Like and it's always just a random ass dumb thing
Furiated
Which is not to say that it doesn't happen on the left like the outdoors be outraged machine is terrifically stupid
The bipartisan
But I think you have a situation where
Those people who are in the business
To making those
Claims
And then they just sort of snowball.
Downhill you'll have like a crnkovich come out with a narrative that my little roll downhill Alex
Is usually the second
She doesn't make a whole lot of his own
Breitbart Drudge
Incredibly
A lab
All that s***
Alex
Explains that
He's always been
Steelers news
Alex
It'll destroy the country but we're going to stop it
And that
Right
No one even wants to come out because it wouldn't even deeper deeper
Aberdeen
If you know why I think you did
Cuz I think there's a part of his brain glitching
You realize that
You know what anybody who's the thinking person would realize that the
Exact same argument I'm making could be used on me
Orrefors farias accusations of pedophilia ring
Good so serious
That you don't want to not take it
Or something like that
The exact same argument
Works
Cuz it's definitely one of those things where
Also Alex Alex's clearly started to go to like Reddit
Before the storm show moderators
From
Now that
It's f****** the gold
Call my friend
It was less interesting than you think but it was like
Rob do what are you
You doing
What do you rob doing
It was a it was
The reason that it
Ception
Ineffective
The claims of a pedophile ring
Is because
Nobody wants to be the one who
Was wrong
One time
You know like
This is a boy who cried wolf situation
But it's so serious
Nobody wants to be the guy who's like
Yes you were wrong
300 million time
The time you were right
And I didn't act
Part about that kind
Is that it
It's such b*******
Except for the one time it's not and you're like
Well
We should have f****** done something
We should have listened to you
I think you said something about Barron Trump Maybe
Is making up
Should not have said on the radio
What
Cub
So all right
First of all
Alex
Putting business on the street and had autism but got over it
Autism experts
I don't want to talk about that because
It gets into like area where we might be clowning on a kid
Or something like that and I don't like
I don't like that at all
Alex is understanding of medicine and
Is flawed but his understanding of trump is also flawed
Cuz at the end
The truck does not want to run Eugenics operate
Here is a compilation of
Eclipse
Donald Trump talking about how he's into eugenics
Courtesy of The Huffington Post right here we go
Family subscribes to a racehorse Theory
Of human development
Superior people and that if you put together
Superior woman and a superior man you get a superior Offspring you have to have the right there
Jeans
Like the fact is you have to be born and blessed with something up here
It's not myself
I have like a very very high aptitude
Twisted very nicely in English
Maybe
Maybe it's just something you have you know you have the winning Gene Franklin be wonderful if you could develop it but
I'm not so sure you can
I'm glad to have that drink blood
Great stuff
So I mean he's a hummingbird
Guess what
Demons are
Determinate
In something
Right right right I mean
Text Babe
There have been people who've gone and looked at his family history
Subscribe to those believe
Maryland
Whether or not you really want to like
Eliminate
The Jews or anything
You can still have us
Alpheus booty
And it turns out
Barron Trump have autism
Look at everything he said
Entire life
F****** stupid
It's always those guys
Who say like I have great genes
Smart
I'm smart because of my jeans
It's always like you look back
You are born rich
It does seem that there's a lot of overlap
Justify being born rich as not having any
It's not a toy
Exactly. The last generation 2
Why I was born ready
So don't matter you're stupid
So
I'm loving the 2018 the Year of the Dog
Allergy
If it's next clip Alex
The long-time stocks
To do very convoluted plan
And it gets more convoluted
Describes
What key
Call
Who's the triple cross
Great plan triple cross
Global of Solitaire competition
Perspective
IQ
White
Nurture not just the nature
Because
IQ tests are culturally biased on this for years
Control
Inelastic
Even faster
Machines
Triple cross
God
Really appreciate you
Subscribing
The thing that he said they're ten seconds before the end of the clip
Was I read the writing
Thinly veiled and what that means is
Believes that all these things that sting are actually saying something entirely different
Which is why I can go read the primary sources
And understand what they're saying within the context that they're saying them
But he's going to say
Do know what they're actually saying it something entirely different because of my weird paranoid worldview of this
Lacrosse
He thinks they're double-crossing you
And you think they're triple Crossing him
Bye
Not
Finley bailing there are
I don't f****** know what this point that include the triple cross
I don't even know where the
It feels like what he just described though was like
Bad planning
Here's the cross
Okay we're trying
People were trying to dumb down know we can put fluoride that's foreplay
I have to be part of the first cross does a double cross
Telling
White people in the west that were screwing over the third world
Crossbow was they were trying to do that but they accidentally went to Joe
Just the weather
Cuz that was their enemy in the third world
But what I mean an accident in the way that they
Didn't realize that the
The third world then
Woodwright
Triple cross everybody
By lowering everybody equal
Again
Another that your bed planet
Precipitously complicated in terms of like
What Alex Jones six
Skip this next wave cuz it's just a bunch of bulshit he said in the past about Islam spread
And how I acted differently than other powers in the
Wicked World
The pope goes out until Christians if they accept Muslims
Except Christians of their country
Maybe because he's the head of the Catholic Church
Is malice Trump baby
Feels like we could just check that one off the list actually even then wouldn't you
That's because that's a problem
Like
Nothing that's a big issue it right now is
Weird
Not letting them into our country
Like I don't think I'd like
I don't know what the immigration policy on Muslim country
I think part of the immigration issue with Muslim countries is people
I think it's almost
Exclusively out
I don't know I think I think you're going to see not a lot of
People who are like
Explore job opportunities in Nigeria right now
I don't know they're not letting a lot of Christians in
Christians are like
I don't want to
Live under a torturous
Evil regime
Don't think this is a good dude
At the very least
Badministrator
Further point
Is
That the pope has a roll
The rest of the world that isn't part of his
Group
What to do
I think it's
Outside of his purview
Just a thought
Pisco perfect
Absolutely
So that bother me
So a little bit later in the show Alex Jones
On he brings in feet
Traffic to talk about A-Rod
And I believe that the situation that's
Sunfolding it incredibly complicated
Iran
I don't have a full understanding of it I'll admit to that red a little bit on it but I don't really understand what's going on
The way that Steve
Check presented is that we got to support
And Alex believe that
And I don't understand
Necessarily
With the line is
Steve and Alex both being against
The Arab Spring and now be excessive being like this is good this one is good
Well I don't know I don't understand it really ran as a
Anime braniff you tied together Iran's government
With the way that they
Then you can go right back to Obama
Like that's the ideas as far as what I understand what's going on my route
Because of
Really really bad mismanagement
And Corruption
Police brutality
The people
Start at a protest
Hey this is
Killing a song
We need to not do this
Not least of which because
We're not getting paid very much cuz it's corruption
Jet like that right
And then as it grew it turned into more of like a
Hey you know what really causes that corruption you know what's really going on there is the Islamic revolution of
1970s
Maybe that didn't work out so well we got a lot of grievances with the Ayatollah himself and so it's kind of
Expanded there a mass scale protest
And of course
When you have enough pillory tarian regime
That is Steve
Protest happen
Did they listen
To the protest
I think it's a rare
I'm not rare what they do
Kill the Press
Right
Really understand it
My inclination is
David Steve
Is kind of right
But I don't know
Cuz I don't know what the board like
I don't know enough about even where he's coming from
Exactly I don't know it's a super complicated Alex doesn't really get into it too much
Because he doesn't
Earlier about this
Use of timeout
Steve pieczenik
Sometime out because of the Vegas shooting
At this point you needs to let that blow over
And so it's not really a great interview
I accept this little clip
Where I at
Steve pieczenik
It's a little snippy
Then that's something we always laugh
Right now
What
North Korea
What are you expecting to see where the things that are going on with Israel
Reportedly
Just got to love has got a lot of I don't give a fuk Steve Buck
You think about McMath Alex's
Argument there is the master who was poisoning Trump I believe the Diet Cokes
Started allowing Infowars articles to get to
The Trump so Alex is onboard
Is now a globalist again
Funding
Isis in Syria because they still want to break up ice and Roberto she's going against the secret military
Currently signed with Russia
And
Syria right Alex's believe
I'm guessing is that his audience doesn't remember all the McMaster narratives that he's been slipping
So he's now using him as a prop
Remembers
Bulshit
That one didn't last very long
What it is
Is that
Like
He believes that Al-Qaeda just change their name
Tyson
Again McMasters riding it and that's the reconstituting Isis
About Brandeis
Baltimore names
Set letter L
Finger guns
Along with a finger
OB like Prince
We got to run a PR firm
So we got one we got one more clip here left a listen to it and it's when Alex gets around to take him
And I get to call from a lady
And I think
Through the prism of this phone call
We can get
A pretty decent set
Where a lot of people have
From where a lot of the fears that Alex Jones
What do you know it dates back
Eracism of all ages
They're going to take our women
And I also want to talk about
Immigration
We're having
Immigrants from
Come over to America and
They are
Getting our dumb girl
Call Massena Mall
Wonderful things and then taking them back to the Middle East where we all mailed it
I'm wondering
If we could
Possibly
Bactrim some moron immigration in and protecting our young women
Problem
I don't I don't
Think it's necessarily appropriate
Islam
But there are definite problem
Real organization
Try to work on
And you're absolutely right that's going on
Sexy girls
It absolutely makes me feel
You should give your small children 6 toys
Appear in Alaska about
3 days ago
I got a call
Hold on
I want you to know in Alaska
I got a call
I want to I want to take a take a second to what she's about to get into is in Apopka
Full story of
Individual event and I don't know if it's true or not I have no idea
What Alex is doing
Is just throwing back to the narratives that you've built throughout the show don't really place
As building
What were you scribbling down there
Maybe
If you're still worried about
Women being sold in
Slavery in North app
Maybe support the
Fighting again
Maybe
Keep those people where they are
Is Mommy doing
North Africa
Well there's also an issue to it like you know you can find it almost any rule Community I would
Sort of
People through dating marrying them real quick
Examples of people who are
Sort of abusive that
Always
Abusive relation
Just trying to get some
Want to relocate
Cuts off ties to support network Muslim in the
Maybe it's dude
Maybe it's not a religion
Maybe it's due
Bright
So at this turkey
Situation
I'm not I didn't
Really look into it
Rob because
This apocryphal stories from Turkey legalized
Good 9 year old
I didn't really look into it but I just pulled up an article here that is
From August of last year
Turkish Constitution
Mcwhorter's prompted anger a voting to scrap a law that automatically categorizes sexual acts with children
The ages of 12 and 15 is sexual abuse
Judges in the country
High Court voted
Another provision by a narrow margin
Response to an application
From a district court which
Complained the law did not differentiate between
Create group
In cases of child sex
Might be more
Kind of
Still inclined
The complaint also said that the law failed to take into account
Consent of victim
Some cases with a child victim
Between the ages of 12 and 15 enabled under
The meaning of
Sexual acts
The laws removal
Affected
FairPoint Wilson's turkey is a terrible Place automatically
Statutory rape
And then they were like well what if they say yeah
Right and then they decided that it's
Provisionally I think Alex is on the right side of it
I'm going to go ahead and say that without
I'ma give him credit for that
Hey
You got one Alex
From a young girl who said that her friend had met and I'm sure she met him online
Party from the Middle East
Married her within 3 months
Never
Never see her house they never did anything all of a sudden now he wants to take her down to Texas with his brother
And his
First of all that's not bad
Second
The psychology of the
If this is a real person
She's talking about
I know I'm not saying because I don't think she tells the story that there's even anything inherently
Evidentiary
Wrong a girl told me that her friend said
Very specific about people's ages
To choose to do this whether it's wise or not is a completely different
Versation and whether or not
You should know better than to move to a different conversation
Alaska
Totally possum Alaska probably sucks
At least
And we tried everything to keep her up here in Alaska so that
Visa just a heads off
I mine again I'm against then the Middle Eastern men
Christian girls
Shipton
Well
23rd liberalism right where they have it because you have to I don't want to come into the United States I want to protect our younger
The Barbary
Fake love
Now that's just
Isn't it
Crazy that that is like the
Perfect end to this episode
He's braver Ramblin out to break with
Enterprise
When she started the show doing a ton
Impression
Calling back to a narrative that's bulshit video selling earlier
MMA
It's just
It's just a load of bull
The loaded Bowl
Because again that lady all she has to go on is someone mad
Someone who
Maybe Arabic or Muslim and they
Might be moving to
A joke
I don't
I don't really know
I like that is that is rude
To what Alex ends up describing of
Sexual
Slavery white slavery in a third world country
It's just labor just make a really
Define reference in terms of Kosovo
The massive human trafficking problem
Staring weird women in Alaska
Did the thinking that somehow it liberalism
Sexual bondage
It's all such nonsense I mean
Playing on this
Spear of their take
Taking our women is the game that's being
Played with in that
Phone call
And whether or not there are real issues that are touched on Twitch
I think we agree there are
Touchdog poorly
It doesn't matter what does feeling you come away from it
And the feeling that that caller is going to go away
Is the cheese validated writer fear that brown people are trying to take our young white women
That is a f*****-up narrative that has been with us
And is reinforced
So much racism
So much segmenting of the population
As long as we've been
We still make movies about
Mixed race
Like
Holiday dinners ride like you coming home to dinner in but
Look Who's Coming to Dinner remake within the last
Yeah yes
No kidding
With the Warriors
Love Bernie Mac
Pecan pie
Bernie Mac
Barry the funny dude
Original
So yeah I mean I think that's why I got really uncomfortable in the middle they're talking about that article because those pictures
I Wrestled a little bit about whether or not to put those on
Put those up
Disgusting because I do feel a little weird
It is a little bit unsettling
Like there are artistic
Choices that you make when you're laying out of paper that
I think that's Up For Debate
I think it is I thought. But I don't think it is
I wholeheartedly believe
That Alex is wrong
Intentionally
Gering to sexualize children
But I do wonder I do wonder and I'm not interested in censorship I'm not saying they shouldn't have
Supposed to be
But I do I do
I wonder what the value of it is
Wonder you could get away with
Less shocking art in Baker
Point
Think you could at the same time I think one of the central point of that
Is that
We feel so uncomfortable
With the knowledge
That kids be f******
I'm not uncomfortable that knowledge
What that's what's being played with exactly that's that's the feeling that you're getting right there is the question you're having
Ask yourself is like
Am I sexualizing
As opposed to just admitting like
Kids
There is like Dana Point
F*** it
Right right right right
We need to actually deal with this issue
And the reason we
We can't is because of our visceral
Like idea of like
Kitchen be doing that
You know even though even though all of us who like well I did
Kitchen
I guess
Is it is the same thing that I mean I guess maybe are feeling about it or leasing feeling that I'd manifest
Speak now
Is possibly
Result
The shame that we grew up around sexuality
I mean for however
Many years
It wasn't baby
Lunesta
A dirty
That's around
Need to be there
I don't know I don't think anyone
It probably makes it
The boy has the exact right answer on what to do with
You know what I mean like I don't think necessarily
I don't know I can speak for this
This writer
Wrote that article
But I don't think that she necessarily
Would say that she has all the ants
Tongue-in-cheek aspect of UB
Hey by your kids sex toys like that
That's clearly overly shocking in order to maintain
Because ultimately our point is like
Stop shaming kids about sex
Brave
Video
Buy sex toys for your kids is just there to be
Listen to me
Talk
I'm grabbing your attention
What about
Alex's
Alex's Bernie impression
Spot
I don't get Bernie wrong everybody can do a burn
I hope he continues
100 pressure
For the rest of the year and drops all the story boy bulshit nonsense
All Impressions all the time he gets down
Do a
Segment on his show at Justice
Why don't you like Comedy Bang Bang
Play get rainbow snatch in there to interview.
Great
Against this is what this is the world I want to live in
Do you like to check out to anything Bora lotto.com
Document is up now more in-depth
Reports
The show please
And I didn't want to say that
The beginning of the episode but
Continue listening
We if we can get
Total that we're making a month
And donations
$100
By the end of the month
February 1st
We will release
The beginning of the documentary breakdown
Oven game in
Will commit to that putting that out
That's it that's just a goal
We can get there
We're already up I think $7
In the month of January
Get us up to that point and donations
In the subscription
I will commit to you that we will put that out will begin that
I don't know how f****** long it's going to be
Doing the entire documentary
What's your plan
Are you going to cut clips of that
I don't know
Doubt within that month on the off-chance
Commitment
Who has donated
The show
Throughout our existence already I feel very uncomfortable even sitting out a plan
Set goals
Broke
In my brain
Anyways sorry sorry sorry about God
I apologize if you want
Subscribe to my
Twitter
You can just go to 93 more dollars
If you cannot follow us on Twitter right now it's underscore 5
Run Facebook
If you want to avoid us there
Drive Riverview do the whole shebang please
If you like
But then
2018 now we got to get over our John Rappaport of
We don't have an exit
Who do we hate most
Logan Paul
Yeah
And brother Jake
F*** you too
Alex