Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work
Sit around drink novelty beverages
Scrappy show
Details
All right in that case I would like to welcome
These are foreign policy
Best bumped up their donation walk status so
Come to the foreign policy ranks
I am thank you so much
Really appreciate it
So good
Hey congratulations on becoming
Foreign policy wonk
Part of me is like
Just don't want to hear this clipboard
Be just
Funniness of Steve pieczenik scabby nose
Is that it'll never grow old
What is a crate
Perfect
People don't respond to Alex saying like
I was always
Like 9/11 I was right about that.
If you know it's even better because Alex
It never gets that s*** from his gas now never ever like
Turn it down to go f*** yourself not-so-great you dick
Love it
Go to knowledge fight.com
Quicksupport the show
As I mentioned the end of the last episode we are trying to bump up the donations $100 this month
And I'm thrilled to report Within
One episode we are up
$28 in donation holy so we really think everybody and if you'd like to join in on that
If we can get
That to that Mark if we can reach our goal by the end of
January
We will start releasing
Documentary
Coverage
I guess Alex Jones's film endgame
That will be devastating and exhaustive
For everybody that's true it's a two-and-a-half-hour documentary
Will probably take
Six seven hours
Very happy with it
This will be
I'm sorry Jordan today we're going to be going over the
January 5th 20
Of the Alex Jones Show
You know we're going to have to get into that we're going to do that thing that everybody does every January was like
I'm not used to this 2018 and all that stuff no one writes checks anymore
But
I've been fine with it
Just verbally
There I almost said did I do that all the time back and forth and history it's always
But yeah
One year older
One year wise
Indeed and Alex
Is no different
Do in the Bay area today
Trying to wrestle with
Revelation
Scents that broke
Since that news broke
And I think there's a lot of angles that are being played
I'm really not clear what's going on
Here's my issue with all the angles being
Is that none of the angles that I have seen
So far are similar to my own which is
So everyone stupid
Actually a lot of it on Twitter people being very much like
Who cares
I'm there is some truth to that I think
For everyone who is unaware we talked about
Michael Wolff
A noted
Creative nonfiction writer out of New York covered these social
Media Elites the New York
David Sedaris
Way but probably less funny
It's straight up a saying
It's it's it's
Creative nonfiction
And everybody who is aware of his writing is
Is aware of that
Right it's not yellow journalism cuz he's not trying to
It's not propaganda
It's a style of writing
Play sin magazine original yellow journalist William Ray
Kind of yellow journalism
They operated for specific
Games
For the most part I mean many of their names or just
I guess if you
It's a stretch to me
But if you want to go with that I'm going to allow it
Thank you I'll let you do
In the aftermath of this
He's coming out that Michael Wolfe wrote who wrote This Book fire and fury
Pushed out later now it's out
There was an expert
Came out that included
A quote from Steve Bannon
Kushner
Manafort
Restless coyote Russian lawyer
And in the aftermath of that
Response was
Everyone
Freaked out
All the Liberals
All the people on Twitter all the commentators freaked out about this
Right
No one really took into account that this guy is a great amount
Bariatric
From Splinter like the Rockers Rudolph's
Situations are always
Like The Intercept all of those guys were like
Hold on
Right
People
This is going into by argument that there's no way Trump is not aware of how
Right because he's been covering
Trump World
Essentially
Yes so
Duped by this
Stomach
Okay if you got really serious
Looks like this guy is a liar
But he doesn't understand why he's a liar
So we didn't entire show about this guy but making up quotes
I'm stuffy just looked at his Wikipedia page and didn't understand the nature of the guys actual writing
Okay so he did a really terrible job of it
I'm just like
Locate I want I don't want
Look
Good guys are no liar also
But this guy's a liar
The only person who's doing this right is Rogers
He is just like I don't want
Nope
I'm out on Thursday 4th Rodger Stone was on Wednesday
There was but he was like I've been dealing with Michael Wolfe for a long time
I know what he does
And Alex just couldn't understand couldn't roll with
To figure out
The same time he can go
I think
Choice
Put out that press release the day that this excerpt leak
For this excerpt was released
Do you think
Stanford
Nothing to do with my wind
Put him on the National Security Council
So like
Stupid because of trump coming out and saying that he's lost his mind
The Narrative or full
Understanding of who Michael Wolff is he could have built it up
Ahead of time with like
Hey guys Let's ignore
That should have been his play it was it's not an opportunity for him to be like the media are up
Flyers
Because
Is different
Yeah yeah I am so Alex finds himself in a very strange
Place where he's like
I can't figure out a different way to handle this
I am so excited to hear Alex
Well it's kind of going back to the well a little bit
And doing what he does best
Creative nonfiction response
I think she's stupid argue that it isn't
Read his response
Great
So Alex
On the 5th
He got into
Studio
He decided he was going to open his show
F***** up rant
And this is gone viral
Around you posted on all the site
And generally we like to ignore the things that everyone else talks about Disney
There's not a whole lot of value in it but in this now I have no idea what you're
In this case I think it is worthwhile because he does touch on a number of things that are relevant to our examinations of Alex
Does he start to show at the 10-minute rant
Yeah
Let's get into it I've not cut anything out of the first
Commercial break which is
Wall-to-wall viscera
Okay
I just put it the segment
Adjustability
Gear is
You know Donald Trump over the weekend said something that
Madeleine McCann
Live
It's so true
The truth is powerful
Operate
History
Really needs me to win in 2020
You guys had almost no ratings at a completely imploded
Is your fake news
Look at the economy look it all up
Optimism
30 sensible policies across the board
They are just flipping out
So now let's talk about let's talk about a few things first of all
I think it's a mistake
To ever look at the news
Maybe a systemic problem that we need to address
The bad guy
But also
Arguably correct
That's debatable MSNBC
These ratings are higher now than they were during the election
And who's to say how much of an effect
Directly has on that but the Dark Knight territory without Batman there wouldn't be a Joe
Right right
Whole thing bro now you're looking at Movies allegorical for reality
Point Behind The Dark Knight
Like it was like that's that's choosing to ignore any Arts allegorical
Further
Alex's
Sort of contention that Trump like no other politician before operates based on the truth
Yes isn't ironic thing for him to be talkin about
I got rid of that election Integrity commission that he had started
Probably voted voter fraud
Executive order getting rid of that committee late night
Hoping that no one would notice
Order that came out
Beaded blamed the state they wouldn't give up there
It's obvious
Navigate to sensible policy
I think you stopped there all of his policies
Are berries
You know what he wants
Billion dollars to build a wall no rational
Human being with Zia's
Effective
Be reasonable or c
Enough money
Ridiculous it might be enough money to build
Expect
If they painted the wall with like Bozo the Clown
Perfect I'm way on board without advertising
Is just f****** gold making a mistake that would probably
Of course
So this is the beginning of the ranch
So far we haven't really take
Turn towards
You know what why people are interest
So far it's just a setup of like
Bring it back
A lot of games in terms of
Stock market hours
Have been
These business optimist
Are really just
I make their speculative by business
The same time they are based on
And idea that they will have
Laugh
And be able to not treat their employees better there will be less regulation governing how
Are they screw us
The big things
Whenever anybody talks about the economy going up
Is that
The economy
Is going up
So long as we're still in the realm of imagination
Sure all of the economy going up is
Completely imagine
I like the stock market
Rising once again
These are not tied
Like uber has evaluation of like
8 billion dollars whatever
And it's losing money
Floureon that is going to
Drop-in they're going to explode
Why did it go up so high
Because all the trading is done by algorithms like all of this
Is imaginary money
And none of it is going to be
People who work for a living
Brightright
Sooner or later reality is going to hit
And it's going to hit
People who work for a living
We didn't actually gain anything in the economy
Even whenever everybody said the economy growing under Obama
Normal people who work for a living did not actually gain anything
During those times
Admittedly
We got more jobs during that time because it's
The 2007 Financial
Everybody
Exploded but hey do you remember the 2007 Finance
Do you know why that financial crash happened
So also
I don't think anyone tonight at least the last time I checked on these small business optimism
Most of the
Composite of a bunch of different fact
And some of the factors are things like
Do you think things are going to improve
And there's other ones that are like are you planning on raising inventory
Are you planning on hiring more
Right and those ones that directly affect
People needing jobs
They're needing raises
Those are stagnant
Those has not been growing but the other factors have been growing High Enough
To make the optimism index
Go way up right and that to me is sort of artificial
In terms of
Even that statistic
Because I think that you would look for
Would be are you raising inventory
Are you hiring more people do you have plans to expand
Do you think people are going to buy more
I don't remember if that was actually you know what I'm saying
Do you and I where we employees of these small businesses that are being indexed
Those things aren't necessarily really change
But
You know statistically Alex's
Totally lying
He's just not really dealing with what the reality of those dead
That's me
That's not what people are
No president
In the
Change over. Of the
The first two years
Really has any actual effect
Exactly
Who is really had a
Huge effect on it was Obama's
We bypass
Sing Batman
Almost trillion dollars
Otherwise it's just
Previous administration and its policy
Overrun
Ears it's like
Like it's the same s*** that happens
Reagan had nothing to do with anyway
Let's get to look into greener pastures
We can figure out why
Did this ramp go viral
Wolf
Portsmouth's tuning
He's news reports with outright fabrication
That's not what that what you hang ornaments on a Christmas tree
You festoon ornaments on the car
Christmas Mountain
No no
No way to know if any of its
Headline news from aol.com
And
Great the headline is Michael Wolfe says he can't be sure if parts of his
Explosive Trump book are true
Yes that Alex didn't read this article because
In the second paragraph
Just real close to the top
It says Michael Wolff
Reliability of
Specific
Interests of its pages
A number of his sources
She says we're definitely lying to him
Well some offered accounts that flatly contradicts those of others
They were nonetheless included the Vivid account of the West Winds working
In a process wolf describes as allowing the reader to judge whether they are true
As long as there is that caveat I don't think that it's necessarily wrong
Did Alex doesn't realize what the headline mean
Michael Wolff came out and said
These f****** were lying to me
Which is
He's not saying
I don't know if I made stuff up which is what Alex wants the audience
Is absolutely a complete misrepresentation and Ally if you are
You should absolutely quote the ones who are
Directly
Contradicting
Other people
That's an important
Thing to put in the book
I don't know the context of how we reported it or anything
But if I were doing
Story along those
Like like what he
He's doing right
There I would
You heard
Look at what this guy said
Look at what that guy said
Who might be telling
What their agenda
I haven't read the book at all but I read that long excerpt
New York mag I believe
The one about Trump not wanting
And
Have been saying
The entire time I thought the writing was a bit
Flowers
To be like
Ready
Keep going back to Sedaris but like
He is
Sort of archetype of creative nonfiction
Chinese writing
But it's in order to
To create this ambiance
And like the spiritual truth whatever
And that is the sense that I got from that Decent New York Magazine that there was a lot of Cousin It
Hidden
Assumption
On the level of Alex Jones
He says Megyn Kelly
Thinks she's ugly and wants to go to NBC
Can you pretending that he's a truth-teller
And like I literally never lie to you and that's up
And what he does could be the biggest piece of s*** in the world I have no idea
You earlier I was like
Give me a reason to read this book
And that I can't think of any reason my response was
I don't know I don't know if there's any value in it
I think it could just reinforce a lot of
Ideas with
People already have an issue with every story that's come out
Has complete
Wheatley corroborated what
People want to be true
And there's not there's nothing to say but that's not
True
But I don't know I worry I worry about the the the mentality of getting
Your beliefs
Affirm
When.
Source of that affirmation
Is not
Necessarily
Strictly credible
If somebody who has a history of
Things that you want
Right right
I've looked at because he has been accused of fabricating quotes a number of times throughout his
Career
I looked at some of them and tell him like he's probably lying about this or like
Oh they don't want
Bestowed
There are probably at least there at least a few examples
Because he wrote a book called burn rate
It was about like his time a text later.
Text startup type stuff and he's talking about
Joe's world doing coke
In like we're assholes
Ancient like that
Some of their quotes were
Challenged
Obviously
Obviously they do Coke and say dumb
Yeah I don't find that hard to believe but you know there's a lot of quotes
Both ended up just a random whenever they feel like it
Which is a delay
So you have these guys who are like
I don't know it says a lot.
Medpoint
Just come out and then like I did
Or the fact that
Trump put up at 6
His denial is the best
Proof that was what I was trying to get to it right when we were starting
The beginning of
This was talking about everyone's
Treating it as if it's
Real one that's
You don't need to respond
Alex plays himself a little bit
Not getting it together and figuring out how to approach
The narrative
And I think that they could have guess
And what that has to mean to me I think is that wolf was around
Trump is worried
Did those quotes
And a lot of stuff that's going to be in that are true
Absolute but I don't know I dates it's tough to wargame
Summer trousseau March
You verify that it the very least
Some Archer
You indicate that you're shook
You like
You at least
Show your cards that you're worth
Yes
When it when in all reality all you have to do is
That's all you have to do
Even better if you were just like
This is
This guy is beneath me
I don't need to respond
Are you guys aware of this guy's career like please I'm not going to dignify that with a response
Like oh
Probably would behave
Advise to him by lawyers
Or something like that or maybe not even lawyers people around him being like get ahead of the
The story get ahead of this
I think
Jaundice
I'll do whatever is necessary
To get the story
Again is about
Wolf in journalist clothing
Disingenuous
Guys go to Google images and Brian stelter smiling
It is the most disingenuous wolf-like demon face
I've ever seen and then you look at me
Oh boy
That makes perfect
There's a couple things I want to bring into a real
Sharp Focus
First
Alex Jones has Brian stelter
We've covered this in the past he called him mr. Mister creepy that was the guy with the mustache
But he went on that long Jack talked about how Brian stelter wants to
Get you an advantage it like that
That's not surprising
What is the present to me is that for month
He's been planning on doing a special report about Brian stelter smile
He didn't say
I don't know if selters been in
On the scene
4 years of the thing I think
Have you come to my wearing
I'm going to be honest I'm going back and forth
Pictures of Michael Wolff
Brian stelter
He's got an argument
Cuz they're all
Is oddly similar
Alright fine
Anyway
Deeper into this
Enjoy
Kicks off internet
Oh my God
Movie cover
Seriously Steve scarier looking at it the clown I mean would you let your children
Psychopath psychopath
I mean
And then you look at the photos of wolf smiling
So I can change the still image photo of them smile the same way with that Power Trip look in his eyes
It's a Google Images
World-journal
That's his cover
A10e
I believe he is related to
I would literally
So I mean
This is boring to us
Everyone everyone really loves because it's
It's so much what Alex Tarzan evenheat
Can't get past like
Are you going to
Keep reminding you about the
This is about two men smile
He never can really even address things differently than they think they're better than us
They think they're better than they're so smart
Blah blah blah
It's all it's all so
Insecure
That's all that's all he's got
It is it is fun
It's hard to see what goes viral and
How much
Like even currently we're just like
Okay we'll find we do this so much
Or you could listen to
You could do that I would say that there is still some things that are worth it and pretty fun
Within this viral rant
It Bears mentioning like this is
Not like
This is par for the course
Watch the show Dexter
I'm Petty
I'm worried that I'm not that smart
I lie all the time and therefore I'm worried that this other guy is lying
His psychology boersma
Yes
Yveltal
Thank you
The evil and then Alex makes
The claim that I
Strongly disagree
Wolfenstein
Better than you I'm smarter than you
Piece of garbage
Office wall
Because I want people to know
Believable
You guys still haven't found the one if it's a body shot of
And he's looking down with that
Just that disingenuous
Predator laptop
Not even hiding the fact that I hate everybody and I'm a piece of crap and I want to abuse
He thinks you don't know
No that's not it
And these are photos
I tried to jump photos like this
I can't pull it off
Cuz the eyes vehicle
Google pictures of Alex Jones and look at his creepy as I
Absolutely going to hear it I don't even need to see the video of
Just like these I probably look creepy while he's
Premise of like
I can't even get myself to look evil like these f***
Is so flawed
Any Google image search you have Alex Jones
You're going to be
A real disaster
Okay now hold on
Devastating
Let's try and figure out
Let's party
First off that sentence
I love it
What that liquid
So the first part of that sentence
Is
They know you can see it in their eyes when they're looking at you
I'm lying to you
I'm telling you a false
But then Ulta
There's a disingenuous
Of you don't know
Reindeer games
What even is he described
F****** letting off steam
Is somebody who's eating you what time
Lying to you about thinking that you don't know he's mad that he got launched off on an errand
About Steve Bannon losing his mind and s*** like that
That's going to make his jobs
So much more difficult now
Because
I think he's better about Michael Wolfe I think he's bitter that he didn't do his research on him before he committed to
Abandoned lost
Does mind and has arms
Security around him at all times
He has a paramilitary troops guarding him and s*** like that
I think he's mad about that I think he's probably a little bit mad at Trump
That
Because it boxes him into a corner
Now I don't think
He came.
Credibly
Site Breitbart
What are the major allies
So that means that the entirety of Breitbart
Calls into question the narratives the Breitbart pushed that Alex jumped before
He calls into question Alex
His credibility and he knows that if anyone's paying attention that is a thought that they have to have
He's like hey Aunt Bannon is this manipulative and this f****** crazy
He didn't just get there overnight
Like he's always been
And therefore look at the narratives that we're coming out of Breitbart
Think about whether they're true or not
Think about whether or not you Alex Jones
Got sued by humping hulakai
Chobani yogurt because of stories that you doubled down on that were published in bright
Now is that does that give you any pause
Do you know look at that slightly different Alex Emerick Jones
Do you realize how
Blade
You are taking the second
As we both know is not a possible thing for the World of Alex Jones
He's going to do another Breitbart story
Tomorrow probably does on this show probably
Derita right now I've got some coming out of my collared shirt
I don't I don't understand this level of stupid
I'd like legitimately if we have a source that we really like
And that it came out like other persons.
Probably
Hey sorry we
We covered that South
At the same time calling
Question
The things that were laid
The track that was laid because of
Stories from the stores
We have a source that we really like I feel like we kind of hate
I like primary sources
No I mean lunch credible sources
I do I take everything with a grain of salt
Do you like do you like Greenwald a little bit
The number of times
And I think he's wrong
As much as he's right like app
With a grain of salt early early on on the show I think in particular probably gave too much credibility
Some stuff that it had been on Twitter but the dress that at the time
Apologized
That's what Alex is not doing even people that we've talked about before like a Sarah kendzior
But at the same time I'm going to take everything
She says with a grain of salt
Yeah
Absolutely everybody who is predict
Frustrates in
Predictive predictive
Punditry
I guess if you want to call it that
It seems unfair but
Maybe
If you want to call it that it's
There's the problem of the future
But you can even always have things be right or wrong if you're predicting
That's why I
We're at the end of last year you asked me for years predict
I think I still mail
Probably
Alex Jones
Not nearly done
Different prompts
What are you talkin about I know that I I saw that there are indications
Doesn't mean that everyone
Pick up on the rent
No it's not
It's okay everyone has a superpower where they can tell if you're sick or lying
Now there are little cute
Genuine smile like there's something about the eyebrows
And whatever way I'm certain there is
Cuz I don't give a
The area of study is always been like
Interesting but at the same time I don't want to use it
Body language specialist they have on TV
Boil down interaction to that level
Shut your supercomputer
Your first shallow approximation
Present
Broadcast
Oh my gosh
Hell on Earth
He's struggling now to try and figure out what to talk about other than stelter is weird
Almost
Let's close
Sorry eat pivots from near orgasmic moaning
He wants to run your life he wants to control every aspect of your life
He is a cowardly degenerate
Shaq
Anti Human
Crash
I like a man with him before my father
Yes
He's going to play the time to pray is it a pledge
Brian stelter wants to control everything
High School erbil
You like
I don't think he wants to rule the world have been dreaming about disabling and
Destroying the welfare states in college
Weird thing to dream about that's also a
It's ambitious
Literal
Demon spawn of the pit of Hell
And you know what is better than you if you keep letting it
Pittsburgh
Smiling
.
Devil worshipping
I see you in a minute
You really have a choice of
Just made your bed
This is not like an impressive moral stand
Against
Brian stelter
At the same time like
What are you saying is like these Smiles reveal the Demonic Force that's behind them
So when he says the Brian stelter runs the schools and run at the bank
He's talking about the demon that possesses
We have to get into like a really
Like
But we really have to get into is this gets
It's a frenia because
Really close to David Icke
In terms of David Icke saying the people of shape-shifting lizard and what have you
Whenever he
David Icke we got a divorce
One of the grounds for divorce was that his wife was a lizard
That
No fault because I feel like
I feel like grounds for unlike I don't see is a lizard that is kind of deceptive
I don't know how England's laws work so I can't comment on that
But like Daddy's bed is the sort of mentality that Alex is manifest
Anybody who's against us ice via demon inside them
That's really f***** up
What really no way for us to operate as a society
Okay
What is much as we as much as we clown on Alexandra
No never never never go to that extent
Psychological
Eve
Damaged
From his childhood you probably brain damage depending on
Disorder Oppositional Defiant Disorder or he's a psycho
Don't break the Goldwater rule
I think the broader rule is
The window
Professionals
I just I really I really resent the
I really don't like that sort of
Approach
Cuz it's a dangerous thing it's a dangerous game to play
Cuz you can just apply to any
And almost anybody has an unflattering picture of them that you could dig up somewhere where they look
Evil Uno
Especially with Facebook now just get on someone's Facebook
You can find some
Crazy pictures back
I feel like I don't have any
Pictures where I look
Evil so much
More is like
If you get me from the right angle
And the way my hair is parted I look kind of like app
Like that
Evil
Evil Pimp
I do look like an evil penis
To drive you going to just jump into freaky
Hangout about demon
Disingenuous
Perpetrator
Will pay
You'll understand me know what you think of me
Godfrey
That is something that could be tossed aside as
But as we know from listening to
Genuinely believe that the globalist
Drink children's blood to harvest a different Chrome
And get high off of it which of course is
Apparently and also an archaic anti-semitic card coming back into effect
They're coming for a women
And now is probably a good time for me to bring up the Michael Wolff is Jewish
And now is another good time for me to bring up
Alex thinks that Brian stelter is Jewish
He was raised a Christian is now an atheist
His wife is Jewish
I was wearing Merida in a Jewish ceremony
And I don't think that that's a coincidence
I think that Alex when he's talking about these people looking evil
I think he's responding
Two very smitten
Archetypical
Facial features in the lights
Yeah
That sounds right
I think that's what this is all about
Freeway
Alex
The time to be conscious level level of 10 minutes
At the top of the Show screaming about them being demons slipping into their drunken are children's blood kind of s***
White why is it still touring
Does he have a smile that like Michael wolf
That's it
No I know but the few things that are
Judgmental of trump in the past because he works for CNN who As We Know
But I don't think it's a coincidence that the rent is going on isn't substantiv about wolf at all
He looks evil
And that links him to Brian stelter who also looks evil
If you even said
They could be related you looked at pictures of them
What you're responding to is also
Fairly Jewish
Facial trait you might have been a little bit
Your version is harmful and think they could be related
Facial features that's not my fault Brian stelter isn't Jewish but
I think Alex is operating officer
I don't know
Concerned
You shouldn't be concerned about the fact that's probably what's motivating the Demonic vitriol that Alec
And the fact that he's not addressing any of the real issue
About wolf
If he was really just mad about wolf being a liar and trying to take out his braids
There's a lot more
Valuable approaches
I quite frankly if he were just to go over
His career
If you were to address the idea that this guy is a creative nonfiction writer Bay
I know you spent his life
Manufacturer manufacturing stories that are
Spiritually accurate but not literally accurate
A lot of narratives about like we should just not believe this guy
He has an agenda he could do any of those things
The fact that he's focusing
Sing almost exclusively on appearance
And relating it to Demons
I'm in relating Demons 2
They're drunk on our children blood those things are connected in his brain this appearance
Is a sign of a demon within you that wants to drink our children's blood
That is inexorable in my mind
Now connected
Not to come to Alex defense
Because it was as We Know
That's not a thing I like to do
But
Generally speaking Alex goes after everybody's of
True but often it's like they're ugly
Like with Megyn Kelly he's like she's ugly
It's not that she's a demon and wants to drink your children's blood
Nobody's done that
Right
Andy and disregard at like I think
I think that's just
More of his go-to move
Anytime he feels challenged by anybody intellectually
To cut them down appearance
You're not wrong you're not wrong
I think that I might I might be
Drawing to sharpen connection
Making me I would never make the argument that Alex's
Is aware that this is what he's doing
I just think that it is such a piece of his
Serta worldview
Yeah can't get away from it
I don't think that Alex
Literally believe like I believe this but I don't think he knows
I'm certain that he doesn't understand where these narrative come from
Anything maybe
Just because I don't
Is time
I mixed all of his hate
To specifically single out
No but I
What I would but I would posit is that
He doesn't have the time because if
It would be king
Construct so much of what he believed
Right if you have the time to look into like what
What do I think that these
Elites drink children's blood scare them first
I need like little Google little Google
Something
William of Norwich if he were to do that
He would only have two possible outcomes
One would be ocean
So much of this is based on this blood libel s***
I got it I got to deal with this more realistically you would have to be like
S***
Oh my God
I meant he'd have to turn into David Duke now that would be fun
Bright
I mean no be negative but if all the sudden on his show as a revel Revelation moment
Alright
Let's find out where this chick come out of the closet
Alex just say is that we've known anti-Semitic
If it's early open we can all deal
Announce the time to make clear that Angie
Semitism and being gay are not related at all
Let's let's let's
Everybody else knows that we're kind of against
I'm going to go
100%
Circle back to this Ranch
I forgot I forgot I was so caught up in the the children's blood what have you that I forgot
The true comedy
Girl games
You're so funny
Bueller's Day Off
You've done it again
Amazon Prime now
How to find the photo wolf
Author of the day feel about you
Will and strength against people and recognizing evil and letting know you understand
Ocho real faces
How they just absolutely love to hurt Innocents they just rub their hands together
Steven right there goes back to the protocols of the Elders of Zion
In terms of his conception of
The globalist so
We could do this everyday whenever recover anything
It is valuable to bring up that the destruction of the family lying to everybody
The globalist New World Order conception
That is crafted from the fraudulent text
Language arts
Because even at my worst
Anime
The only
People I can
Think of hoodoo Delight
That kind of
Archer RV
Globalstar serial killers
Even like
In general Psychopaths
Right are murdering us all but it's
Like care about there
Blazer
I don't think the same rate is anyone
There are people who are psychopaths
Through and through
Like you can't
Do I sort of exploitative job whatever
Liking Jon Ronson psychopath test I would probably a higher percentage
In banking and
But I still don't think they Delight in
Torture
In the same way that sir
Serial killers
A lot of psychopaths in the general population who just like
Don't give a s***
You know like that's okay
Yeah I agree
I don't know what I was going to say
Not a robot
How do I
Build their own Universe of fraud this is a compendium of there
Abomination desolation
That's a good rifle
Not really
Explosive
Anyway here's the alto
What I have heard about it
Trump at a certain point they're like
You know all he does is read the headline
That's why
There is there is that thing it was from that excerpt where
Trump was
Quoted as saying you didn't know John Boehner was
And that's not realistic
There's one there's one point where I believe Rodger Ailes
Suggested Boehner is H
Staff
Remember the band trumpet
Who is that
And I don't think that that can possibly be true
Eat like I could
See that being true in more of like a
Sarcastic kind of
Incentive like through even is that
Probably if you're taking that out of context
You could see that as like
Him being a doddering old I think it's I think I'm impossible to
Assertive look at that
Literally true
Like psychic doesn't know
Yeah I don't I don't know babe I just
These are real
Bring up
Conception of globalist
2 Psychopaths
I'm sure it like that
Year especially in
I'm a couple months
Before 2018 hit
I've been reading a lot of
Primary globalist Tech
Yes but Alex Jones puts out as like
These are evil come to the conclusion
What's the correct
I read
Multiple reports from the club of Rome
Yeah I've read
Most of ecoscience fees
16 hundred page book by John pee holder
I've read
How is other thing
Sabri group rosinski book
Right I've read some writings by like a singer
And was one of the things that I'm coming away
No I'm coming away from it with is
Actually a growing
Respect
Piccolo
Will not the global split people in charge like
I'm coming away from it with a very
Expanded respect
For how difficult choices
And how big the world is and how are they especially like we talked about this I think a little bit before but
The club of Rome one of their big things is
They look at the world's problems
Interconnect
And how is he work on one problem often you can hurt another prop
And when you look at the world from that sort of
Holistic
Review
It becomes
Choice it becomes really difficult to
For certain position
Promises of the cereal
Route and then you don't
They generally don't advocate for a certain position are the things that could happen when
XY or scabbing
And it's
Fascinating to me
It makes me feel much more like we're in good hands
To that level of analysis
And I couldn't
Do that
The the
The ultimate failure of the opposite effect on me that you would want to have
Kind of the failure of what Trump really is
He thinks
It's just a guy who can do a thing right and that's just not how it works
I do an onion
I think I I think I can tell you a lot of solutions to problem
But if I were to apply a solution
To April
That would almost certainly
Fuk up another issue
Which
GE variable ABCD
Variable
Which is what
Which is what Obama does did very well
Certain Solutions
The way that
Would have been perhaps
Best anime
As I've read some
Conservative
Publication
Complaints about
Pretty similar thing
Things there
Like I just
Agree with
Position
Yeah but there is certainly not nearly as evil as Alex paint them out to be
Write like even the project for a New American Century
Documents
But if you actually go read it
Convince
That most of their intention wasn't
Create a better situation where the United States could help the world
I don't know if
I don't I don't think it's proof
Alright
There are a lot of really f***** up things I can find
I don't I think that
I think they generally
I don't know
It's weird that I'm starting to have a trust of government
But again these aren't really necessarily the government
Nongovernmental organizations
Actually been coming
Don but have
Been starting to respect
Trump's position on North Korea
I know it's very wild
Just like Nixon's possession of
You want crazy
I'll show you f****** crazy
Oh yeah
There is a certain extent of
Maybe
Just call their f****** Bluff
Like that could be a things like
I don't know like the the issue with that is that it's so high risk
ATMs
It seems in
0 room 4
Is over
You're all in and
Do you have a loser hand
I disagree with you coming around on it
Coming around on it should be a very qualified position
I think I am starting to see
Even by Axel
Because it's clearly by accident there's no
There's no like
Position behind
I've got a bigger dick than you
Right
Same time
Also that really pissed Alex off
Everyone talking about how those tweets were really about Trump today
Really pissed Alex all good like 5-10 minutes
It's talking about how
Come on man
That's not that's why you trying to make this about sexism
Also everybody
That is a paraphrase quote from
Crazy
I agree that there may be some validity to calling Bluffs and what-have-you but at the same time where do you get after
You call that bluff you don't just the situation doesn't become stabilized
The only way you can call the bluff really is
To attack attack then
There is no block
Good idea
I'm saying that there are that I am starting
Toosii
Again like you said
Certain merits concept
They're not
Because I think that actually what's going on
Is
Partially what you're talking about but also also partially
A maintenance of
To the status quo
Because I think with this like war of words that he's having over Twitter
Antagonizing
Of Kim Jeong Hoon
What you have is
A maintenance of the sort of
Attention that we have in the world with these B Rogue state
It wants to attack
And you know we can't really do anything about it cuz they're going to
Has lived with us spent
The Cold War
He's not addressing the situation he's just escalating that status
Is going to be all of us scared all the time
He's going to say the wrong thing
What you're saying is that this is simply a more public version of mutually assured destruction
That you would have seen in you no lates
Sixties with the
Quote Rush
Russian Menace
Somewhat yeah but I also think Skittles be like
I got a bigger on Twitter I still don't think anyone's going to pop off like I still don't think
Either Trump or Moon
Is going to
Nuke anybody
Well it has nothing to do with those two
And everything to do with what happened in Russia multiple times of just like
We're going to prepare for this eventuality
Then there's some kind of
Glitch or whatever rights low-level guy
Is just like
I was told to push this button
And when you're in a regime like North Korea.
Much less chance
That they are going to be as restrained
Ivy Russian
Save the world
Well we know of for this singular Russian
Didn't happen more than 145
Probably happened between 4 and 6
Like that kind of
So
So that the final four accidents is very high
It's it's
You know that trickle-down effect
Everybody is
Italy on Red Alert
And always afraid
Constantly on Red Alert
Eventually you get a
Adrenaline
Exactly
That is something that is very valid
That should be discussed more
Victor but I still think
But when I look at Trump
His behavior
But at the same time
The function of it really doesn't change
The status quo with North Korea it just makes everyone more scared
Make it the ballot and I retract my position
Yes
First retraction of 2018
How to start keeping track directed many from me over the years and I've only got a few
You from you I think we forgot
Keep the running tally it's cuz I'm more reasonable
Your position
I love the passion but it wasn't so much the guy that I am afraid of who might
Accidentally press the button press the button I think it's probably tough for us
Like
You you stake a position and I'm like
When I spend like
Literally almost all of my time
Reading
Bees
I hate to keep going back to the club but like
These documents of like
What you what you see when you restock
AR
Issues
There's an issue there's a problem and then it
100 pages of
What could happen
And Analyze That
It's this gamesmanship in in rhetoric
Text is like
If this then what
And it gets me in my brain space
I don't know why I need to say this but I feel like I do which is that if I were in a position of
Actually making
Decision with
Real world
I would be far more likely
Do what you do let's run for president
You're just more willing to think about these things reasonably in a low-stakes environment
Play situation with such loathsome like
F*** it looks like random ass b******* you know I got a little wine
I'll be chief of staff
Probably be a much better front man and I would just let you make all the decisions
Absolutely
All right so you're one more clip of this rant
And then we'll get to what happened throughout the rest of right after
But this rain to take us out to a commercial break
Mostly by demon
Mitchell Wolfe
Mr. wolf
I guess
Hyperbole or or are you with positioning are you with Devil's Advocate
I don't really believe this
They don't want you to know
Literal
On their bellies
Nebraska
Warren
Exhaust brake
Yes
Where you at where you at on that ramp
Talking about
For us
Interesting conversation
The ramifications of a lot of
Penalty
The rest of the world
Tangents because
To us this
This is kind of run-of-the-mill
Freaking out
I can see why people would say
See this as like a
Define
Anything to glom onto
Mainly because
Now I have
If they are literal on their belly
Right
Do they have
Who makes
Cuz that's the guy we need
All goes back to Amazon absolutely
Find that to be the most reasonable thing that has been said so far tonight
Amazon card as we are
Literal
Belly dwelling snakes
Put a bunch of horseshit
I always get kind of surprised by what capture
People of the tent
In terms of Alex
Like
I mean we go back to this over and over again but like last year on the March 30th episode where he told Adam Schiff
Kick his ass and then the rest of the episode
Sleep
Drunk nonsense it's interesting to me that people glom onto that I'ma kick your ass your p****
As opposed to
Drunk for 3 hours
I love
Bright
And Mexican with
There are four ways
I mean it's interesting to me
I get on one level why people
Like share this like crazy like isn't it funny that he calls Brian stelter
Pretty pretty pretty pretty
I also it's I mean it's important
I think
I genuinely believe that it's important
Because that to point out these things about
The anti-Semitic
Rhetoric that he's spouting
And how
Complaints on this Brant that went viral we're about appearance
Or they were triggered by a.
Is not
Necessarily something I'm seeing being covered
And that kind of bothers me
I think anybody with a grasp of Alex's history was important to him
What you're saying
Will you set a reminder about him criticizing everyone's appearance
Totally valid
But it's not you saying that they're ugly
I want to clarify that in
Specific
Don't chew with your
Analysis and I'm not try
Defend him as a
He's an equal-opportunity
Opportunity kind of hater
My point just being like
That's fair
I don't know
I definitely think that there is absolutely some an
Tamara cleaning
Behind behind
Wouldn't jump that far this
I mean I think as we as we look at stuff like this it is
Defense because whenever I looked at the
Their pictures
They're both bald
Yeah
I don't know man
Very very weird take onto the Iran protests
This is a lot to do with liberals hating you but then he gets into that
I think
Immediately very self
I really wish I had
And said that
God
You're fine
People like Hillary Clinton
Journalist is wolfing henhouse
Michael Wolff
Enjoy the climate of fake news media corporate media
An open season on the truce open season on the president open season on loyal.
Cultural and spiritual life
Is culturally ruling us
Leftist globalism allied with Islam
Yeah about time we can watch combray sit down
Is allied with radical Islam
It is finished
And the women standing up getting shot and killed
Not good
Progressive left
Jeb
Actual feminist in Iran remove it to fight oppression
Some guys just get tortured and killed
Photography
Cushing
Hood over Hatter Kutner General's office Liberal
Because that's what liberals
That sounds right that's poisoning the well narratives that sounds right that's all
What are we doing that's just that's like the poisoning the food poisoning the water the vaccines
Women come so boring
But also this this is
Massive
Misunderstanding of people position
If you want like the Liberals
People on the last
What are you talkin about is like
Linda sarsour
And those type of folks
Their argument is
If you want to wear it at
A job you can I will slip into Alex's
Dumb pronunciation
It's not
It's not anti
Feminist
To wear a hijab
It's not
It's anti-feminist
To be forced
To wear a hijab
Or to be forced
Not too
Those two things are the there the polar sides of the problem
Earliest you isn't with
The force
I grew up with a Muslim family in my neighborhood and I went to school
The number of Muslim children
And my dad is a religious studies professor and so
Wheel well plugged into communities
People growing up
And largely
With girls
It was a choice
Who's to know whether or not that's social pressure or not I'm not entirely sure but it's in no way my place
To say you're making the wrong choice
I choose who I have with Quebec
In Publix
That's crazy
It's crazy
Right
As awful as
Majority Muslim
Passing a if you don't wear a hijab
Your
Alex really wants to be
All this stuff you really have to take issue with the Amish
The Mennonites
Write the all the anabaptists
Well they're allowed
The Jewish people wearing yamaka
Like that I have to recuse myself
There's a trickle down to it
When my family was in a cult
All of the women were forced
To dress the same
Like it is it is certainly a modest but it right time 8
Troll
Whatever
Well if you want to invite you if you want to go into narrative that week
You talked about
With the one dumb lady
From Alaska
He's taking are you taking
Women all the way colorful
That is such a
Consistency
Women can
Controlling
We have to
Protect
We remove any and all of their
We're afraid of their sexuality and
As much as we talk about how much of his stupid chick goes back to 8
Is Medicare
The book of the Bible
No it just goes back to make a decision for yourself
That's that whole fundamentalist tradition of abib
You know like that sort of thing
Automotive in fine if it wasn't for
That's where this
Controlling of women
In religions historically
Routes from
Talking nonsense now go back to
That type of roots
Sober Legend
It did not
Become so male-dominated
Until it became
The early church were like women were The Gatekeepers like
About agriculture
Women were the most spiritual leaders and then get into monotheism
And
Who would have guessed
Men use it to control every
It's almost as if like
Religion isn't bad but
Decentralization
Controller
As a political and social for smoothies
About that rings
What I was trying to get to know more about the Iran protest than I do but
Anybody
Twitter or
Writing op-ed
Being like
These f****** women
Their hijabs
Are way out of line that perspective at all
Score points office already established
Linda sarsour wants you to put on a job for
Event being like they don't support these people in a run
Most people's perspective on
Protest
Pretty complicated
Stuff
It is it is
I don't know it's one of those things that is very similar
The protests in Iran
Voting for Roy Moore
So as far
So when you when you talk about
Once again in Alabama
Because of it
Fundamentalist
Directions to Ed religion
You wind up having
Percent of white women
Voting for a guy who is
Clearly against
Anagen All rights for white
Assertive statistical track for Evangelical
And then you look at it
Iran nuc the counter protest
Does that were run
Bye
Very pro-government sources
Supported and put that together and you have that
Kind of
Older women
Situation where it's like
You have to
To do this because that is the
Tradition
Even though they are the ones who have been most subjugate
Anytime there's a protest
Of the poor and the Young
Everybody gets
Like that's that's the situation that is going on in Iran right now
It is the poor
And it is the Young
And they are fighting back and they are going to
You get dis
Droid
Because they
Simply aren't allowed
Associate in the way that they should be
Right now in so many universities in Iraq
Tayron
Many of the difference
You find
Pre-emptive arrest
Going on right which are
Roast turkey already
You you destroy or the cultural revolution in China
Kind of ability for
Educated useful people who are also the most unemployed
Iran
You are destroying any ability for them to gather at
And then you can send
Centralized power between
People who use
Tradition and just overwhelming
Forced to
And that's the situation
It is
Should be having that we are all incapable
At the last I had less to do with the Liberals
Two women having their boobs removed
Or liberals being in favor of that or liberal
I think that most liberal folk that I know deuce
Support
In as much as they can
Protest
Better going on
I don't think that there's any real legitimate way for us
It's inexplicable that Nikki Haley would try and draw a
Un conference
To support protests that would
Abject Lee destroy her life if they were to happen here
Because I already know because we are supposed to
It's profitable it's almost like the inverse
Spring to Summer
And it's really interesting
Cialix be very Pro this time
I'm very anti
About others
Where's similar thing
Egypt and Saudi Arabia
Allies
Israel and Iran is our
Call Adam
And that's where you get into trouble
Well that's worth
Their people
It is stupid
Who have
Grievances
Ultimate
Failure of Nash
Nationalism suggest
That
The leaders of a
Are the
When in reality most Americans
Arnot
Trump live
And yet
Buy Trump I know what Mario is I do know a lot
Thirty-seven percent of population
Yeah
I think we're going to start to understand that Dynamic a lot more as time goes
Nations are a failure
Anyways
Benson Veterinary
Sing idea and I kind of agree
But
Be that as it may
The best-case
Scenario in the best like
Look for the world is
Collectivism quite frankly I am
I think we are
I think so I do not I don't poison the water
It is
We we specifically described
People who support the show as
Policy wonk
Foreign policy wonk
And global
Like that is what is tongue-in-cheek
Got a lot of ideas episode
He's got a lot of
Lotta bull s*** like I told you he had
Abandoned but also was couch
Before about
This idea that this guy is a liar
In this next clip we find on the
This Friday he is
Sit back and watch it is attempt to blow up Lighthouse political
Lights fuse
That's opposite distance
Purple Coach bag
Direct quote for
Infowars Powers the Trump movement
That's a little fun
Secondarily
Alex
Don't f****** pretend
Shannon wasn't
Don't f****** pretend he wasn't leaking to Rodger Stone
Through Rogers
All of the narratives that Alex was pitching about how like
Kushner is a globalist and all this stuff
That's directly stuff it obviously had its Genesis with Banner
Food in the White House of
Course was was driving
What's the driving
The whole time that Alex was pitching this narrative that reince priebus was the globe
Liquor was almost certainly
Steve Bannon
Like those two also had a bit of a feud
Bought a few the palace entry not very well
Coordinated
He should not be playing is audience doesn't
Take the time to think about
Most of his narrative game for Bennett
What's interesting
I don't think
Is audience
Forgiveness
Either I do
I think so Brooklyn keep doing this
I don't know
I think that they're fooled into thinking that there is some credibility to it
Cuz I think I think the way that Alex sells it
The palace intrigue
Isn't just dick
It's being dicks
Which is what it is
I think that the way he sells it to his audience in the way.
There is a team of globalist
And then there's a team of trump people and they're doing War
And so this Palace intrigue
Isn't just
You know the I like the idea of your Elite
Having a petty squabble
It's actually one team
Who is trying to save the world versus the bride
So you've been able to wreak
Contextualizing Rebrand
Palace
Which Eliquis probably most accurate
Winners vs loser
They're all losers but
I think in his
In his the way that you make an Alex Jones audience
Interested in this
Palace Inn
Is these are the good guys
Who are winning
Just like we are all bright
If there's a counter counter rabbit
I think it's I think it's
Less winners and losers and more of misappropriation
But isn't that
Isn't that ultimately his
His ID
What his audience
Interested in
They want to see
People win
They want to see the winners
Possibly
I think at the same time he's already
You spend so much time
Time catching like
I got sort of thing so I don't know
We're winning we're the winners were winning all the time
They're still coming after us
And we're losing on all fronts but where the winners were always winning
But we're on the edge of losing it all time
That the fight
Is really more important
The Narrative that the winning or losing
The presentation of winning and losing he can sell either to move product
Ants keep people engaged
But without
Squabble without fight there is no
Way he can keep
His Machine movie
On a political scale tomorrow
You could come out and you could do a shower he's like we are f******
Losing
And he could use that
Right he could use that to his advantage
She couldn't use
All is well everybody is
Everything is operating
Like Trump is doing all the right things and people seem to be enjoying it
That's true there's no way
He needs
False the boogeyman the
Antagonist that is Imagine
In order to fuel his rhetoric
Which then we go back to his art his comment
About
The media needs
Trump right
Like there isn't a
I do think there's an arguable position to support him
In that an ALICE
We'll only about himself
If married immediately fair enough
Cuz I don't think that the media needs somebody to
I mean I remember when I was younger watching
MacNeil Lehrer hour
It was boring as hell but it's
And it was the news that's where your position goes back to the very beginning which is
Venusian carob
About ratings right
Just like
Alex needs to move product
So does the news need to
Advertising
Bigger conversation problem
I mean let's not but
Position
Clearly
No point in them
F***-you River Madara
Murdock
Anyway
Green with the Russia investigation
Sociopaths and Psychopaths
Is that
That's not the case with Wolfie
Skelter
Everybody around them
Andrew Jocelyn elders
Projectionists
Totally there the case they're like he's
Projecting his life
Psychology into another person even to the point of like
I don't want to I don't want to
Bring up the Goldwater rule
Come down on Alex
Because I can
He probably has an abuse and is it like I don't feel like that
Good to tell Mama craving like that but even by his own words
The idea that
Whether or not she actually did
He felt like his mom said he couldn't get love after the age of 5 or 6
Like that
Although we may have information that says
No probably not
That doesn't change that that's how he felt
That doesn't change that emotionally real to him
Right
You're right about the
The fact that
35 years later he's on the radio crying talking about that
Realtor in some form or another
Mtume that indicates
He did not have a great child
Something
Wrong
I'm not begging
Fun of him for that but I am
Saying that
Look at what he
He's saying about
Steve Bannon
You know maybe this is one of these guys who was abused and
After that describing him
Troubling
Immediately
Describing comes
Yeah
Sick want to take down everyone around them to feel like the big man you created
Worldview to fight again
Well not just that but look at the
The people that he has
Surrounded
All of the iPhones
Clearly
He can bully
He can
Superior then
Imagine
Rob news in Alpha
Well imagine if you
Somebody is competition
Maybe impossible man there's no one is
Alright
No I mean I don't mean
Because competent
To Stronger
Bright
I don't know I
Me out because like
The perspective that we have on him
The way he presented
Himself her so like
He's sowing
Consistent with him
I'm self
It's just making me
It's an inch
You often wind up being capable of empathy
With
With the Devil
Or that
Sympathy for the Devil
How many how many
The childhood of a Serial Killer and Ben Li
Man that must
You have empathy
Before them
At the same time they need to be taken
You know
Deer Behavior
Feed the m
Empathy we have for you based on
Your circumstances
Alex
Not a person
Flip ourselves
Victoria Milan
Alex Jones makes it about the globalist
And so they want to ruin and wrecked civilization and they are committed to doing it and they are
Hurting you and your family poisoning or food water
None of them
Aspartame
If the president
Your mother
As they literally
So hold on hold on they still go to malls
Sometimes
Hillary will just go around to a shopping mall and just be like well at least I'm hurting
I didn't
I didn't win the presidency
Interior shopping mall November 9th Bill and Hillary
Reenter walk past a wetzel's pretzels
Very depressed
Very sad many people coming up to them giving them
Accolades
Wishing them well and their next artist bill
Bill
Dialogue
Pretzel with cheese
Hillary dialogue
I don't
I don't feel worthy of a pretzel right now I
I lost an election to Donald Trump
Bill
Now hold on
Look around you
Look to the left look to the right
You just talk to people that you hurt
Keep your chin up, you're hurting these people that's what matters I lost the impressions
Improv
Rough when you are writing script
You are gold my friend you are golf
Stocking ideas just is crazy
Take solace in the fact that I'm hurting
Alright well keep chin up
Statistically that's not the case about people on the last taking vaccines
The largest percentage of people who don't take back right there that is
Do you find that Within
People who have
Especially tea party beliefs
Yep they're the more you know about vaccines
Less likely you are to not
Honest and I find a lot of
People on the left also the people
Are very
Trains
GMOs like that
A different different conversation
Is the same as Max
Camsoda
Diet Coke
Same thing we do what is the same through all of them
Pearl poison
Call boring
Matthew semitism
Prepackaged really thought you were almost
F*** Larry nickel
No no
Yes
This point Alex
Commercial
He's back on the stelter
S*** a little bit
He makes this
This claim that
Raising
This is supported by anything I just I love it
This guy is a known
Charlatan
Simply insane
Just like
His son Brian stelter
Photos of Hillary smiling
Surface
So
So if I understand correctly
Both wolf
Ansell
Are attempting
Individually they are related to each other
No I think my point is
Why are they trying to keep pictures of themselves room
You're missing pronoun
Okay it is about the two of them pictures of them being trying to
Kept off the internet
They were doing it
It's the globalist that are trying to keep us both
Constantly on Google like
Guitarist complete horseshit
I love that idea
He can say stuff and it just be like a toss aside or whatever but even in that case he's like
Furious
Seriously
I know that they're trying
Need to keep pictures of them smiling off the internet
Cuz it shows how evil they are
A lot more work
Why
Would you try and keep
Keep pictures of yourself off the
You would nausea
Themselves with pictures
I just tried to get a picture
There's a picture of him that he took for a magazine or he's like
Screaming at the camera
Seats and everything but
It seems so unimportant
Come to me when I was listening to episodes from like 2014
Capture clip of it but he's just like
Now I wish I would
Get rid of that picture
Okay that's pretty
With
Yeah that's that's crazy
Very strange but I think it's just because he asked
The flex zone
We can't substitute talk about
Like I said we might last
Great name for our new show
The wolf issue
Only shot on Banning and that last couple Clips back or whatever
Able to talk about like
Why
He's not ready to get into like them
Had we been betrayed by one of the
Biggest influences
Of the last
Campaign manager and
What
Whisperer for the first year or for the first
Mom cell
Officer
Campaign manager
There was
Manafort
Indicted
Go to jail Rodger Stone
Alex Jones body
Probably
Eminem
Siri
Who's Lewandowski a manager of campaign or was he just like
Okay
I thought you might have risen to that height
He also apparently sexually assaulted
Makeamericagreatagain dressed
To the the Grammys
Made a big scene out of it and then she was a frequent guest on Alex Jones Show talking about
How bringing Trump into the musical world is going to be
Huge and Lewandowski sexually assaulted like it up loud
I can't remember what it was but she was at
Some big truck party at Lewandowski
He slapped her ass
In-N-Out he slapped her ass again
But also for her
I mean that's not good for her that you sex
I mean cuz f*** it
As we
Just saw a recent
One of the Roy Moore
Accusers
Her house
Has burned down
And it is
Too early to
Speculate and say that it was
Buy a Roy Morris
Supporter
But
Otherwise it
Politico
Who headlined for Anna makeamericagreatagain dress at the Grammys early this year was celebrating the president's first year in office
Holiday party at the Trump
International Hotel in Washington
In late November when Lewandowski slapped her behind
After she objected
He dismissed her concerns
It's laughter behind again
Via said in an interview Friday
Vf-31 said she was circulating in the ballroom of the invite only party with a friend
Who brought her over to introduce her to Lewandowski
Whom she had never met
Her first impression
She said was that he
He seemed dismissive
And he rolled his eyes when he thought she wanted to pose for a photo with him
I said if you're busy don't worry about it we don't have to take a photo via recalling do and telling Lewandowski
Who remains contentious Oval Office
Political strategy
The earlier this week
Deicide another reveler pushed her
Toward him and she ended up standing next
Posing for a photo
Despite his seeming lack of
I'm wearing a silver suit
Stretchy pants
And after the photo we smacked my ass really hard.
Is completely demeaning
Shocking
In the moment via said she
I confronted him I said watch it
Half-joking
I said I can report you for sexual harassment
Lewandowski's response you said was almost as shocking as the original
He said go ahead I work in the private sector
Revia recalled
Smacks my ass again
Vias Recollections against
Was corroborated by a friend who Whitney
Exchange the friends that he wished
To remain anonymous
The part of Louis
In part because of Lewandowski continued
Influence of Trumps
So I'll talk about that I have her on when she's a propaganda tool
I wearing a Maga dress
But he's not willing to treat her like a human
And also this one
And you will be
Whatever it is
Calls into like
Memory of lewandowski's
The salt on that reporter lady
Yep back
The campaign
Remember the timeline of that exactly but
You watch the videos that he absolutely grabs her and
Pretty bad
It's hard to imagine
Can anybody in the
Circle
Not being
Stop
In many ways like even
Look
I get
Probably
He hasn't sexually harassed
Outside of
Marriage
Unless you use Alex Jones about Jim Comey
Oh that's good
You know these guys who are up to they're the ones you got to work
Karen UPS American Psycho
Mike Pence
Does seem to have all the all of the like Dennis hastert
You know I'm saying
Like you've got all of those characteristics
Anything I'm just saying that the parallels but
His positions have
Been played for
Barry Hester
I feel like he's more like that Foley
Thrown off the Hell in a Cell
Congressman
At the surf
For sex with a public bathroom has first name
It's more like that that's the vibe I get more from him
Not abusing people I like
The repressed with a secret
Some sort of secret
Something there
Yeah
Not fully human and
Experian full-on
Bull on conspiracy
I'm going to go I'm going to go out on a full-on limo
Stone is working
I mean I don't think that's that crazy to think at this point
Alex
Straight up
Trump
Lakestone seems like the guy who if I was the FBI I would lean on Stoneham
Sooner be like
Oh s*** yeah I'm going to talk to everybody over I'm
I don't give a fuk
You've had a life of
But self-preservation
Yes to
To navigate
Being
Intimately involved
With
The Amber of scandalous
Keep president disgraced
President
A lot of campaign
Did not work out and he's still able to survive
And have some sort of
Stock
I don't
Thank you do that necessarily by playing
Rat
Stone is Marshall
In that
Stone is much like Beyonce
The Survivor
And he
He has a tattoo of Richard
Sure
Beyonce got that makes
Sometime
I don't obviously I don't think
That I'm I'm I'm going to co-sign your conspiracy theory but if it does come out that he snatched
Like that wouldn't right right
It wouldn't surprise me. Especially because of like
He's the only person who in the Infowars mayou
Like in terms of
Naked with his band and stuff with this wolf
He's the only person who's been on the show he's been like
Like you could almost see him being on video game like
Please stop
Yeah please don't do this
This is unraveling
This is how you unravel is by giving credibility to
This kind of a story
You don't have to
He knows because he has
Decades.
Is there a smarter than everyone else I need to say
Stone is this
Smartest person
That is been around Trump so far
He's the smartest person who's on info
That's not high Bart across the only problem though to Duchess like
A hair trigger
I'm angry about it which is not what a smart person would have
But at the same time like
Freaking out calling women
On Twitter and stuff like that doesn't have the political Rams
Applications
Believing
A creative nonfiction writer
Inexplicably
It doesn't have the same Cottage
Bullock historically and I think about the
Historically
Over the last year or so
Pretty clear that Bannon
Rodger Stone
Aren't working in
Number of times where Rodger Stone has a
Attacked
Van in for various things
And the two of them don't see eye-to-eye on
Immediately after the story came out when Rodger was being interviewed on Infowars
His take on it was
I know
Michael Wolff
This is nonsense
And then beyond that like
Look
Abandoned goes around where to
How many button up shirts
At the same time
We are coworkers
Bruno
I'm going to attack
The enemies
I'm not going to attack our allies
And that is
Text Helen
Cuz he knows
This could on
Uncover some
The only way it's going to uncover anything
Is it
Exactly the people in The Alex Jones propaganda world the people in Trump's
Inner Circle of yourself
Kind of mentality world
Yes the only way things are going to get bad as if they all start freaking out
He's trying to
Keep it together
And Alex Camp
I don't think you can get it I think that he's going to
He's going to lose it
I don't think stone is a mastermind
This isn't Mastermind strategy
I think
How do you hit
And when to
Edwin like
He knows how to turn
Yeah that is very basic
Stop very basic
Anyway
Weird
Compares Donald Trump to a historical
Very interesting
Deliberate
Someone that delivers
But just like the British history books did William Wallace
He wasn't a coward he was an honorable man
Because
Everybody intrinsic knows everything the Isle of garbage
You are the Y
Before I do I'd like
To say that
Nothing
Historically is known about William Wallace except for around
That's pretty much the only. That's known
About him
Everything else comes from an epic poem called The X and deeds of
Sir William Wallace Knight
Erda cierrale.
Written around 1470 by blind
He rewrote from oral Traditions Library the minstrel amazing Ensure
Information about him
Could see perfectly
Could not play
Interesting
Interesting really is like a fake news name
Anyway he came up with this this acting Deeds of Sir William Al's 170 years after William Wallace
Historians think that is
Very unsort 80
Take
On my way
Quotes
Leyden most of the problem is
.
If using traditional
Chivalric
Motifs or borrowed from
Exploits of others
And attributed to William Wallace
The only things that we know about William Wallace or a couple of battles
British noble
Is a Scottish dude was a f****** he was angry there was unrest
At the time and there were the British were imposing a bunch of
Taxes that you didn't like on Scotland
And so he assassinated
The dude
In the telling of blind Harry
And then the movie
With the Great
Great not anti-semitic milk
Hold on
Rain
Okay and I move it.
The story is told as the
This guy was trying to
The kill his wife
Pennysaver his wife
It was in response to that rap battle
It is probably
Just about taxation
Which actually triggers Alex even more than a wife
Sister-in-law
The other thing is the Battle of Falkirk
We're only thing that William Wallace is
Actually known to have
He lost the battle battle of Falkirk
He was very overly confident
The British flag
And
Granted he escaped and I was
Billy murdered
Fusion that they gave him
There is a storical record
That's nuts
Nbad was drawn and quartered if that's not even
Expensive but they caught him but not kill him
They found him and then cut him down
When he was about to go unconscious
Amanda
Fouled him
Right
Yeah but that
No it
Except
Beat the levels to like they kept almost killing him again
Torture
To know how good people used to
They were great they were really good at that
Not good at doctors
Diseases
Goddamn
You could assume that they could have f***** it up
And accidentally kills him early in the tortured they were trying to do and they got lucky and he didn't die
Torturing
Doing it like they would often
I'll up and put them on trial again
It's my understanding
Afterwards
Like you was being disemboweled
But be that as it may
That's sort of
Time machine now we need
To disembowel a guy and see if he can survive that
This
Like to meet
This is the important
That's capital
With excessive
Even for the time
To someone
Memes that this was not just a normal person
Failed in a battle or something like that
It was someone who was the British
For some reason
But unfortunately the historical records that we have don't
Tell exactly what that was
And there's no real reason to think
Play Super honorable person
Most of the accounts that come from that timer
Yeah like use a
Roodle f****** dude
Like he would
If you would behavin way like the British that killed him
I thought my tax
Explain why they did that.
I'm not entirely sure but
History is boring out that he was an honorable person
To know that
Movie
Right it's a movie or if you want to give Alex a little more credibility
Which oral tradition
From this guy who is the Jonathan
It's that it's nice parallel
Is the fake news
So
And Alex Jones
LOL
Alex I got news for you baby
We don't need history
To determine how bad
That's happening concurrently and everyone has
For a while I was just trying to make a metaphor in Spanish
Trash
Express
The highway but you don't want to run up to it
So that's what metaphor Falls is bad from the job but the metaphor is
The globalists are a dead carcass by the side of the road and it grows
You grabbing
Them
Bringing back into bed with you
I guess
So his advice
I guess is that you don't take a seat
Global fine
I know that's metaphorical but I guess what you saying is don't
Globalist
It's it's
It Resort
Metaphors that leave
Way more questions than answers
You see that animal on the side of the road leave it alone
Great dad animal
Fat
I can with you on that metaphor
Yes there's a state department
It's paid for it
Through taxes and regulations
Well not if Trump has
I was going to have to take that
But the big issue to me comes
To like where is the bridge
Like with a metaphor metaphor is only as good as the connection to reality
Sure
Like where is it
Where is the connection to like
The point that he's trying to me
Appointees trying to make is that like globalist
Plate starts with him saying that
These globalist
You shouldn't hate them you should pity
Animal dead by the side of the road
I suppose
To the Animal by the side of the road is dangerous
In some way because it wants to
To take over your life
So the animals back
No
Globalist I don't know
I don't get it
It's trouble
Anyway
Troubling
We can leave that aside we have one more clip Jordan
Alex
Decides to get into hot
The pop Hot Topic
Like Hillary goes to
To say that she
No this is bad
Celebrity
What's the suicide guy
Logan
What are we doing this
Because my prediction was that Alex
Only defending Logan Paul
He's a male
I thought.
Also
Strictly speaking
I support Logan Paul
Making that
Interesting take
But just based on
Free speech
Okay I think you should suffer all the consequences
Cuz of doing it
It's incredibly disgraceful it's
It indicates
A lack of Humanity on your part
But the idea of saying don't do it
Or like
We should stop you from making this video or
Right
Let me night falls right in line with Alex Jones
Principles
Of Defending free speech
And I thought for sure
This is not someone he would
Pink is
Evil I thought for sure Alex would be like
Everyone's trying to come down on Logan Paul we got a dependent
He's a very different take
I'm interested to hear what it's
Squall
Is it standard
No it's
Chaos and then at the end
He gets to
Kisses on the side of the road
He betrays his own positions
For a bit
Out of pettiness
About to play
He slammed
He slam dunk
No to something really suck
Sastre upload suicide forest
Masculine
What then
We show
Army troops
Children
No idea
YouTube
I don't know either I don't know this
Specifics of this but if I had to guess
I would say that I would say
This video also had other piece
I would assume it wasn't just straight video of army
Saving kids I would say that there's probably
Something that broke terms of service
For YouTube to take some
It takes
Or using a song that
If you don't have an audience
I have enough people watching
Then they'll start. Shut that down
Copyright claim
Decent
It's someone who was in that video that Alex
Shot
Or something like that
Infowars
I don't know if that's the case but that's
A possible explanation for it
So like you see why he's kind of pissed off about it
Is that
We have videos taken down down where the f***
Which is not
Free Speech position
Can it's not principle
Culture of little league Twisted people
I mean ours is
Shut up
You can say what they are
Japan turned out for weeks
We're a Romeo Juliet story
Themselves
A big joke
Makes fun of a dead body
Show twisted
Give three more
Get off on somebody's misery and they're rotting dead body
Makes fun of it
And then make money off of it
And do it while you're wearing a hat
Okay
Brickyard
This is what it's all about
That's what it's all about
Yoda do you think he would do this
I need to ask you this question
Alright
Do you think Yoda would do so
Bracelet that wwyd
And I say
Enough
I don't like a very charismatic figure he might do a lot of different
I know the Yoda spend a lot of time and
Hanging out right that's a swamp
Right
A nerd to notice but I remember
Okay swap for a long time just like soda holding his skills and being and hiding waiting for Luke
Show up
I'm sure he
Just a little
But he was practicing along along the way you
Emperor Palpatine
Darth Sidious
He then had to retreat and escape from that but do you think there's a f****** chance you sitting around in that swamp and I'll practice
I'm assuming there was this
Lunch with his lightsaber in the game
He did in the nuts
The show it it's Ava had it real power doesn't need to be Flags
What I'm saying lightsaber at dab
Actually f******
He did not do that
Here's the issue
The issue has had a lot of time on this
That is because
He could have started he could have started a YouTube series if you wanted to and that's how
Now we know canadochly he wouldn't do that
So
Based on the Star Wars Canon
Alex is correct Yoda would not
That's true
It is not a sign
Here is this is not a psyop
Logan Paul's video is not a psyop but that's the perfect Alex Jones things to say
That is the perfect guy
What is that asiop
On
The longest pause in the show's history I have no idea
Hold on let me scroll it back I think it explains it a little bit
And then make money off of it
And do it while you're wearing a Yoda hat
Okay
This is what it's all about
I know 100% what he's talking about
Alex is pretending that Logan Paul wearing a Yoda
Like
Cartoony hat
Is
Some sort of a symbol
That is
To be like
Aq2 the initiated
Of what's going on
Have you read that blog there's a Blog called Vigilant Citizen
The answer before you even ask that question
Is no there's a Blanco Vigilant Citizen is one of the biggest like
Examples of this
There's like
Symbology runs the world
Celebrities
I know the name of the Rose
The name of the Yoda
But the rows do this
But like celebrities putting one hand over their eyes
Anyways for one example
Blocking one of your eyes is a symbol of initiation
Into the Illuminati
That's something everybody knows their whatever
Checkerboard
Floors in a movie that's
The cue to the initiated that like this is a million.
I'm so I think it would Alex's
Was trying to get at without having
To spell it out because he knows his audience goes those blogs and
They're into that conspiracy s*** to
The fact that he wore his hat that
Isn't is an indication to you that all this is
The fuk fuk in
Failure
Fake
Are you it's trying to f*** with
Internal wisdom on it
Don't know if I understand correctly
I suppose
In regards to the turn wisdom on its head
You got Gilda
At the Hat symbol of wisdom hat
Next to dead body
Being warned
Until you're turning wisdom on its head
I already don't follow what you're saying
No okay
All right it was got this weird just saying elements of things
Okay
Yoda hat
And then he goes and I don't know this is one story
Like
So many other stories
Where I went
Nah f*** this I don't give a s*** everybody can die
As soon as I saw.
Heart
Everybody should die I saw this and I was like
Orleans surprised by this
Like at the escalation of people who need a 10
Turn on YouTube is
I mean there's a finite
PewDiePie's already come out done Nazis what are you going to do
Do you want
The right there's no reason to think people wouldn't like
Exploitative wouldn't take that to the next level
Suicide Forest in Japan I can't remember the name
Because I don't remember Devon
Funny words
That's a real place where you can
Definitely
You'll see a dead body if you go in there
Weird yeah I mean I've read a bunch of stuff about it sentence like
Yeah
There's no culture in Japan is a whole different
Wild
There's no
Situation wherein
He could have
I have embarked on
Wood
Soleil
Or it's unplanned
It's not but we don't need to unpack that it's about what Alex is saying
We are to follow along with what Alex
Yoda
The Yoda
Is the symbol of wisdom
Turning on its head
By going into an
A clearly
Exploited
Right having an a******
Steer dead body and do whatever he did
Yoda
Our symbol of wisdom
Is then
Associate
With the a****** doing whatever he did
Well in that case
You see that symbol of wisdom and go well wisdom
And so destroyed
Wisdom
Like I mean go with the more classical Simba
Why would you go to the classic
Millennials
Because they f****** use the Eye of Horus
Millennials are going to Vibe with
YouTube starting then I left my phone on
Like I was done
I think it's fascinating that Alex
I mean
It's clear that is
Complaints come from
About like
Video wire
That that certainly is in play
I meant
I think the issue again for Alex was
And Alex Jones
Justin
A hat
Of Alex Jones
With his mouth
Right here and then is
Okay you pull on a little coordinate screams at people
Like one of those like one of those cards where you open it and go
I love you like that guy
Now I want to know Alex Jones
Do we have endless resources
Things we could make
WWE bad ideas we could make reality that as it may
I'm
F******
Flummox
Buy everything that I was
Because
You should be supporting
Logan Paul
Based on his philosophy
There's nothing that he did
Fit breeches
Free speech
He was in Japan
Right
Which is already your onboard
Give a s*** you don't give a s*** about that person who died in that Forest
Rhetorical points all the time
Breitbart
Yeah you said that
Steve Bannon came into the bunch of money
Disgraced breitbarth reputation
I mean he's using Breitbart as a tool
Perfect using Andrew Breitbart
And now he's at a cabana
Their diet
Right
I don't I don't think
Necessarily there's any law
Videotaping a dead body
I mean
I don't know
I don't know I don't obviously there's no
Yeah exact
Obviously that's not
I mean there's always going to be a fast
Shark with really f***** up
I'm just saying people just like
There's a
I don't know I've never felt
Humanistic
Dudayev somebody when I was in high school was like let's watch faces of death
Let's turn you into one of those faces of death
I don't want to see that
Is it gross and wrong
Would you going to do
Take some sort of high ground it's just I f*** you I don't need
Go to the other room
Yeah
No no no
Your argument there is a fascination with some
I would argue
They're f***** up by
Yeah sure we watch videos and stuff
Cast now is my favorite murder and all they do is talk about
Serial killers like that
Psychology that's
Then
Actually watching
Dead bodies are actually watching people die in the actual death is different than
The circumstances that surrounded
The clues the
Psychology
I just I just don't think it's a fake if I don't get some sort of
Call instead of like wandering into a dead body and then started laughing and clowning a little bit
Off-camera found dead body
And then stay Brazil whole thing
Ortona respectfully sort of
Guide disgust
The experience of it
And then also was like
There's a note buy it cuz a lot of people who kill themselves in that note
There is a way that he could have done it in a my favorite murder
Dial Lori Cahill Style
Respectful to the person who died cuz they didn't
Consent to be a part of his stunts
Or whatever
How to position
I think it would
Respectful to the people who
Cared about the
The moment you die
You don't give you don't you don't exist so go f***
I'm not I'm not clear I agree with you on that but it's
It's absolutely
I think that you're right
Do extend after death
22in
Desecrate your course that already has concession
The issue
I mean there's a lot of issues
And a lot of them are are really
Really Salient about
Like the idea of going in
In case so much more
Who You Are
That's probably
But
I don't think
I don't think it's
Sara Lee YouTube
Placer
Anyone anyone in charge supplies
How to say
I will send
Yeah I'm 90%
On that side
I'm also
Write a hundred percent
That's our
Rue21 take myself out about 7
Because I do think that Grace
I think I think I think
I don't think that governing bodies should be able to tell you what you
But I think we're much more active
Punishing people
Ford stuff that is.
Not this tasteful
But
Raw
Like
There's a
I think I think
Skittles McAdoo
And not
Okay
Both are distasteful
What is
Which one
F*** you
Wind-up going back to it like in this
Particular circumstance
I think I start from the
The place of
As we've
Discuss before with our friend
Being rich is a morally question
How strict wealth are doing
All the way back there and say being
Stars immorally
I mean it's a decision that he made
The child and parent
Sort of reinforced in it
It went to actually like
Logan Paul
Interesting that we can stop here but
Iprint
That made we all agree with the sentiment but she
You just summed it up so perfectly with you
Being wealthy
Choice right
French
All of the all of the words are perfect
Nailed it look her up on Twitter cuz she wrote a very very salient
Concise essay about Logan Paul and about what
Embodies
And there is a lot of that like white
Privilege
That white male privilege wouldn't think for a second that this is wrong to do a
We're sailing away then we can do
Very much
Let's jump off this and just say it's f***** up at Alex Jones doesn't support him
Cuz it's bright support face
And
I think that's just
I don't know why
Figure out
To get more views
That's where we get back to
Recycling let's not let's let's kick out of it
Justin say that Alex Jones Brian stelter
Stupid but at the same time
Yeah makes no sense
Boring
These other things
Trump being like William Wallace
Wolf
I think we talked with We've Ended in the same place we started on the Google earned that
I don't think we learned anything
I think that's where we got back
Strapless episode please go to knowledge feit.com Azure website
Absolutely if you would like to
The banner that says clicks
Port the show
If we what is it $70 for this month
We will mostly
Yes you can follow us on Twitter and knowledge underscore fight go to Facebook
Brought iTunes
Shortly once I get around you will be on some other platforms iPad
Not everybody can find
Through iTunes
I feel bad about that but
Same time
Are you
And then
Do that
Efface
Dura mater
I don't know it's tough to figure out who who today is a pile of garbage
Pile of s***
I'm scrolling through Twitter to see who people are angry
Let's not allow that inputs come in
Unleashed so much s*** you know what
I don't disagree with Michael wolf you're a pile of s***
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color