Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
About Alex Jones
Yeah that's pretty much what we do. Tonight we're drinking Mystic
Give some complaints right off the bat
64 goddamn grams of sugar in it and it's like
Little bit of a mixed beverage for yourself
Is this where we talked about
Like to start
Show off by telling you that we're going to be going over the January 8th
2018 episode today
Monday episode
A lot of weird stuff going on craziness
Ottoville
Save-A-Lot
My feelings
News about s*** being born out
Okay it's a real life
Listen to the music
Scaramucci
Creepy Critters. We talked about the New Jersey Devil
And I have not done a good job of
I got completely forgotten I'm a s*** that I'm sorry but everyone should go check it out it's a great time lot of fun even though I Hate Chris
Cryptids generally
The running B
Cryptids
Refuse to talk about it on my conspiracy theory podcast
Bobcat Goldthwait
No it's not
A regular old
But now he's stupid
He did so before our friend reality TV show
Search for Bigfoot
And he was still talk about
He's a fungi
Speaking of fungi
What's going on up there
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much for joining up
Damn Few are the Blake I knew in high school
I'm afraid I can't
I need you to stop
I don't think it's your black friend to or not friend
I'm not sure
To someone who's that super awesome
Already
Right now I have to create a completely new designation
What are going that direction we're going
Technocrat
Submarine officially a technocrat
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Thank you so much Maria
I've buried
All of that is very mellow I almost lost my mind just adding other things do that I could have done that for
An hour just like
Does adding in nonsense
Sportsman Show
Support the show button
And become a
Of the various
Levels
Please do a Franklin
I've never been happier
Thank you so much technocrat
Indeed I want
A million techno
So yesterday whenever the 5th we talked a little bit about Alex Jones
Brian stelter and Michael Wolff
Talk about it being a literal demon
And they will get back to that today cuz there's a little bit of a blowback
Alex
Yeah about
A little bit over the course of the show
I had stelter made a comment
Yeah he said thanks for using a good picture of me
Solid solid he gets what's going on and isn't engaging with it
Any meaningful way
A little disappointed Jones beef around
Bars in each other that be amazing
I'll bet we could do that as we get to it but you know we have to take Alex as The Show Goes
So here we open up the show what's it the Beaverton Alex Jones is Bond at the beach
Actor to this mystery that be
Known by the name
Oprah Winfrey
Venice Beach last night
Yep
Empower women to stand against Trump
Worldwide
Infowars.com
Bill Gates
Call up to discuss how she's the front
Husband
And she's running a worldwide
She's got a new movie coming out
As a vehicle
They're called the good club
Population there
World population
Report says
They're going to bring in a world government and a world Youth Corps
A world sterilization
Oprah Winfrey is a absolute anti-human
So
Do you want to try and guess what the truth behind that is
First off
What's her new movie coming out I don't know I don't care I don't care at all
Something interesting but I don't really I don't particularly keep up too much with movies
Understand
Correct
Oprah
Go on over yet
Front
For the women sterilization
And she is creating a
Church
Live One World Government source
Something along those lines
Said anything about
You whenever
I bet she has all right I'm done with
What is responding to is that she's been a part of like
Contraception
Effort
Around-the-world limiting the population but not in
In terms of killing
People more in terms of
Being able to control your own life
The stuff that like
It's you talked about would like Ted Turner's evil like
He's crazy population
Stop you're really going to look at it actual quotes
What are you talkin about
It would be good for the population
And to be lower than it is especially in resource deprived environment
Advocate for
Killing
Say it in a very fun
Misinterpreted
Everything weird old man who owns the Atlanta Braves
The quote into a buffalo
And then had
Sting the wrestler Sting a come out with a 30
WCW for a bit
Right
Oh yeah
Melinda Gates
Organization
The Super Evil mixed with them trying to kill off the third world
Really mess with his Narrative of the globalist that he's
Do we listen to the other day or something about them the triple cross
Narrative
The straight-up be targeting
Third world
I don't really understand
It's hard to don't think there's any negative thing about Oprah that I would like
Whatever it is you want to say about Oprah anybody's ever been like
Yeah I don't know I don't know if that's true
I thought her magazine sucked
She's ever been on The View at least like there's a lot of like I don't know what to
Now there's a
A video versus
Screaming at Piers Morgan
Is she still married
That one
Or did he die
Is she married
Is Gaelic
I don't know until
I don't care about her personal life by Frank
It's not my business
A very important thing in her to become
Right now so I've
Thanks but she
She's legitimately running for president
Thanks that everyone is like
And it's the same thing that people do a lot like this with The Rock
And to be fair with The Rock
F******
He said into it a lot more
Then than Oprah is
I think it was it wasn't it Meryl Streep
Last Knights
She's just drafted herself to run for president about the Golden Globes
News about Oprah and they were like
Has like a you guys are
Guys are sick of calling Trump a monster so you're just like
Baby Oprah I got nothing else to write about
About today right I don't have a negative opinion of Oprah
I don't dislike her at all but I I don't think
That she is some sort of
Evil
I think she's evil in as much as
Make a lot of money
Morally questionable decision
She also does seem to give back a lot cheese
Be very
Pull a positive message
Call me when she's done
Time for insider trading
Yeah anyway Alex Jones.
But she's running for office
Everything's if there's something
Nefarious behind it
Aforementioned the Bill and Melinda Gates
Gotcha
God
Disagree
Tells us
Stan's for women
Globalist tool bag of Bill and Melinda Gates
Oh by the way
Will clear messages.
A lot of people are going to die
Absolutely
I didn't shut up
Okay
That's not
Now
Now I just have a
An image of an army of Oprah
Ofra
Oprah Winfrey
So I think about Melinda Gates she was talking about if people don't
Stop lying about vaccines regarding
Speaking to him
Through a television set
Britches
Shut up about them
He never shuts up
Maybe what he should have said it when he said I could I can't shut up about that
You should have qualified with that
Qualified that with
No seriously
I can't somebody please help me I need
This is a cry for help I need to shut up. Or something
Them hot garbage and in the next half-hour Jones
Advice for The Rock
Alright
If we see a rock Oprah primary
I'm going to be
Very happy
And also
Obscure
Hollywood
The number one movie this weekend
Difference
Between the Rock
Hold on 40 is a Republican
The hold on
Replace some of it when we come back it's just been lectured when you know
That this woman is a Monster by Rihanna. Right There
Right
Always have fun with that
Know that The Rock was a Republican
He spoke at the Republican convention in 2000
Ladies and gentlemen
I miss is why we got g w
You coming out
Oh yeah
Drop the people's elbow on Dennis hastert
To speak at the Republican
It's kind of a headache
Speech for the Rocco
18 years ago
Big smooth charismatic man that is now
Some of the catchphrases
Of course I've been turned into Dwayne
Buc-ee's
I need to get in touch with the
And then he's like I got two words for you
Does the eyebrow
I don't like
Absolutely
Frustrated
That what we know about I'm not given the fact
Linda McMahon is in the Trump Administration
Iraq
This once again proves
50 world of politics has turned into professional wrestling
Because the rock is going to turn heel on America
Completely support this tax bill that's what's going to happen you know what else
Cruise Alex
This whole notion about like
You can't be a conservative in Hollywood The Blacklist
Cuz the Rock
At the 2000 convention
And is the biggest
Star in Hollywood
When he spoke at that convention
Wasn't the biggest Hollywood Hollywood
It's his whole career
After himself as a Republican
Did anybody know that
Yeah I think I think people knew that
I just didn't know that
Nobody knew he was serious
Who'd have guessed that he's a Republican
We are doing economically
I respect that he was a corporate for a while that's absolutely some indication
What's too bad
What's up
He said they never heard that before
This is very important
The Rock
Thank you so in the next
Number of clip
We get into Alex trying to
To deconstruct
Oprah Oprah speech
From the Golden Globes
Okay
It sucks
I have studiously avoided any Golden Globes.
I have
One opinion on that
They were doing something
Banggood
I don't have no I have nothing to say I don't care about award shows make
The victim
Visible is great
And found nothing in it
Troubling
Alex on the other hand
Are you doing Belinda Casey she was going to get you
In this first clip Alex
That's exactly how that I'm assuming that's
The camps that they're going to send all of these
Conservatives to our it's just Oprah yelling at them and then the rock giving them the people's elbow
A clip
Seemed really have much of a
Concern
Other than
He just doesn't like
What are the number one anime in the world
Grand Admiral Street
The problem
Media so wonderful Trump so evil
Here is her chicken garbage on the listing
Filth
The Hollywood Foreign Press Association
Because we all know
But we also know the insatiable dedication
What kind of book
Absolute absolute
Say speaking about older
Horse Show Coronavirus
Thus far it just seems like a fine
Seems more like a regular Alex Jones trying to play clip where the moment she's about to say something to eat
Disagrees with
He cuts her off in
She's ugly Brian
And everyone else is old and ugly
Did they hang out with the demons
The songs in the thing
They always comes down on Meryl Streep for like not attacking Roman Polanski
Meryl Streep
Find legitimate complaint to have about somebody expose
It also attacked
Justin Timberlake
Buck Woody Allen Roman Polanski
Doesn't seem to do that much
Boxing match different flag
So let's see how long it takes him to interrupt cavities
He's restarting it of course
Donut from the top
Oh okay
But keeps us from turning a blind eye to corruption
God the media sure to keep us
From the corruption
God
Thank God
So that I'd like to make as the globalist aren't real and the things that he's complaining about the Clinton
Aren't real either things like the uranium one s*** furthermore
With broken by the mainstream media
Even further
Isn't he
Media who says he's fighting against corruption and he's the only voice like mother is that
He's not lying
Okay
I don't know it's stupid either aren't real or are mainly unrelated
Oprah
Right
22 Tyrus and victims
I secret and lies
I want to change
As we try to
Which brings me to this
Sure
Is that speaking your truth
Speak your truth
Your Magic Kingdom
R-Truth
What are the family
It was weird when she said
Trying to kill Pro
By the way no look
We need to support women
You need to speak
The truth that you know because you have been abused and you have been
Absolutely
I mean you see this is a business
Is entirely all he does
Second episode it's like
Some of this is kind of boring
He only heard the words tell your truth right speak your truth any justice
Cermak
To some extent
Myfairpoint
We all have
And inspired by all the women
I didn't know about the Islam assistant
A 1000 men women and children
And the News getting a minion
Are We There Yet the word about Thursday
The world
Is it look good today
I think he's in libel territory here I believe
What are you talkin about
Actress says
Harvey Weinstein use Oprah and Naomi
Seduce me
I mean that's
I guess if he can pull that off
It's a good headline if you don't read the article
Aspiring actresses Harvey Weinstein use Oprah Winfrey and Naomi Campbell to dupe her into thinking he would help her
With her career
Only if you use her for sex
Calling Oprah and say okay
British actress comedian Noble head over heels in France
But you first met wife
Set an event London
Could you hanging out with model Naomi Campbell and it Megastar Oprah swinging off his arm
I thought something amazing in store for me
She said during a
Siri I press conference in
The Manhattan to discuss
Strapping lawsuit
She filed a day earlier against wine
Federal courts
I don't think you're responsible headlight
I think
Cobras association with
Looked at
Implies a level of agent
Very irresponsible headline is
Wrong
Come down immediately
Be fair if the headline is stated in as much as it is like an assertion that this lady
He is making
What's her words don't actually save that Alex is misrepresenting at 8
Second
And saying that she actually was like
Recruiting women
For him and stuff like that
Is a legitimate reading of
That's my that's my
Mine is clearly meant
Tubi
Ambiguous enough for you to go
Wait what the f*** and then click on it and then read the the rest of the article very very responsible
Alex has fallen First 48
To trace back
To a tweet
She put out that says is it just me or is Trump praising to Ronnie and protesters
At the same time also Banning Iranians
From entering the USA
And there's two
Emoticon
Scratching the emoticon
She might have said some other stuff but I don't think so
She's impunity protesters that that's what I can find
The backlash
The alt-right world is having online
And I don't think that's very extreme
Point to make
Not bad but be that as it may
Every Everything Is Not
Everything is fake
Furthermore everything
Is a facade
Right
Forget about
Tomorrow I promise you will get eventually.
Furious and everyone in the room
He's gonna scream
Listen to this being like
I don't
I don't care I don't care
Like you have to say something
It's a daily thing
And I respect that you got hit
F*** off
Don't make me try and have a take on the
To be a news person
And then report that Oprah is
Procuring women
For Harvey Weinstein
By association with her this woman was tricked into thinking
He would help her career
That is
I mean I don't I don't know I don't know what libel and slander like what constitutes especially when you're a public figure
You got to make a really pretty serious case
What Alex does
He should be deeply ashamed of
In terms of
Even for him
Like you should
Keisha probably about
He should probably put out a track
Disassociate
The other thing though is that like this really invalidate
How much he actually knows about his
Flagship issue
Which seems to be his take on pedophiles and sex drive
So he thinks that Oprah it is
Proven to be mixed up with this because of this headline
Adeline
I got bad news
You do nothing
You're making it all up
Which we already knew
Anyway
Oprah speech
His lies per minute right now
Staggering
Speak up
Ensure their personal stories
Each of us in this room
Celebrated
Stories that we tell
Alex doesn't seem to understand
Mediums like Filmer
Storyteller
She's talking about
This room we're celebrating
The stories we've
Film
Hate about what Alec
Alex Jones is turn
There's a massive difference
Between
Feeling guilty
Can people feel guilt
And pointing out people
Guilt right
You know it's not it's not that she's trying to make
Make men
Feel guilty is that
These men are guilty of crime
You shouldn't feel guilty about what all men do
You should point out that
Most men are guilty of crimes
We became the story
But it's not just a story
Thank you for telling us the story
And that's just his way of trying to deflect
Trying to pretend that that's all Trump did was ask anymore
Trying to weave
Using a word with Peach
As a hinge again just trying
Flip something to defend Trump
You cut it
Cut it up
He's doing going by one random password
In every sentence
You come
Completely inoculate your
From understanding the entirety
You can't understand the point at all whenever he's actually afraid of the content of something but feels
She has to cover it usually does it in this way
Whenever it's
Chop chop you can hate without ever actually engaged
You're engaging with random as words you're not engaging with
Teaches you really really bad and poorly thought-out things you can say to you
Your friends on Facebook who posted the speed create all sorts of that
I love I love NE
Postville Oprah
Sarsour
Entertainment industry
It's 1
Geography
Race
Religion
Because you're trying to destroy all that
Okay
I don't think that's what that there's tons of Japanese
For instance
Chinese movies
One world
Movies for mother other cultures that
How are emotionally moving and still resonate
Deeply into something that's
Can bring people together in a meaningful way
It's not that you wanted
Destroy cultures
And make them into a monoculture
I know you do
Go ahead
No I got nothing I just want to talk about it
I'm sure it's Grill Washington
Politics
For workplace
An assault
Because little
Had children just see the building
Hollywood
Hollywood abused woman
Hollywood pedophile
The abused one
It's a good one
We're. Poisonous we're good
Also I hope the Roxbury
I mean look that is a lot of problem
Hollywood in terms of
Systematic power imbalances and people who exploit those power imbalances
Power Balance right right but
Hollywood
Right and it's glamorized
We've had years and years of
Any office building where there's that kind of power imbalance in group
Alex Jones is really pissed off about
Here though is that Oprah
But she's trying to
Claim of Vick's
Status
Which employee can handle that he can't handle that because that's
That's what I do about white
Don't you understand
You can't we just put in on my territory we can't be in the same space
With this
Because
You're Oprah
And I'm just Alex Jones
If you if you occupy Myspace
Dude
I got no shot
I just
It's mutually
It's not mutually exclusive
I have a legitimate claim to some sort of victim standard
And I himself
So it it's just it's a load of hot bulshit
This is one of those things
It's sort of a little bit like why
I
A book about people whose like
It's little things like that that are like okay you got to
Remember those the white victimhood behind.
Everything how dangerous that mentality is
12 a.m. for like that Brian
You got to understand what's behind it and how this is not an isolated incident
It's par for the course
But
I mean what what he
He's really trying to do
His turn
Any kind of alike
Women being victimized
Has victimized
Like anybody else
Who are who is legitimately
Who is legitimately attacked who
Legitimately
Discriminated against
Mentioning.
You make me a victim
Mentioning
Nickelback
I don't want to feel guilty I don't want to make me feel
Alright
Good luck living in a civilization then when you do Patty
Hugo's on
And dreams to pursue
Are there such good people look at them all
Paw Patrol
Are the women
Slave factories or not
The Evil globalist operation telling you I will
Chicken
So I mean
She's
Oprah
Come far in the world
Haha
She started out
As nothing
And got all the way to the center of the globalist operation
Even if even if globalist
Were real
Rags2riches
I don't I don't like those like I mean we could you just play any kind of game like that though like a you don't talk about
Everybody has trouble
What are you making
General examples of women and even though the ones that I don't include are not mention
They are included by
Association
You're right I did not specifically mention
Any member of the ways that women have been victimized maybe that's an issue Alex
You should count you should f******
Hey Jordan
Next eclipse
The wild
This this next clip is the conclusion of his coverage of that
Of the
His hero's journey that's not literally true cuz he does get back to it later
To stop covering it by a commercial break
And
He says some really weird stuff
Working in factories today working restaurants in there and Academia Engineering in medicine and science
Text
This filthy
Real quick
Before we get to the really weird stuff
You think that she would shuttle young women in
That's not what that article says that all
That is absolutely not what it says
Like what
Picture of kissing
His ear
Harvey Weinstein
You could find compromising pictures of
Just about every celebrity because of
You know how big of a mogul
Exactly
Just reported
You are quite the parking
So you got cut off by the break their eyes
I don't like that you have some Humanity in you cuz you like men
Whatever
The implication there and you have to make the application because it's
Where how his mind works
You don't have Humanity on you if you are attracted to the same sex
That's not good
If you're attractive
Ted 2
The women
Wow
I think he's actually reversed asking
Insofar as
Anybody who is not attractive
Native attraction to Matt
I am gay
If you want
To misrepresent his words the way he missed represent
Victorville
Or the way he misrepresents
Melinda Gates
You could say Alex Jones
Just came out here on knowledge fight Alex Jones revealed
You gay or
That's entirely possible the UFO disclosure
To admit that he's an alien
Commercial break
I don't know the lines
Slander and libel.
He seems like he's
Very close to it
I think there might be a
Might be
Hopsewee goes to break
And he comes back and he's like
S***
I got nothing but time
I got to cover this Oprah stuff some more
Sort of
Heteronormative
Chauvinistic
He now decides it's time for me to get race
That's not good
So
Is Oprah rich
Kill Alex G
What destroys Empire
For now I feel like if you're rich enough you get like one or two
I think it would I think it would be dangerous
I think it'd be too dangerous
To in terms of
First of all is wrong
Second grade
A blowback from listeners of his
Stuff like that
Tremendous
Problematic
Anyway you get back to Oprah
And like I said
Lower
At the Golden Globes
Oprah Winfrey
Ricci
Taylor
A name I know and I
Ricci Taylor was a young boy
Add a mother
She's just walking home from the church service
She's attended
When she was abducted by 6
Armed white man raped
Yeah definitely
Insulted by the side of the road
Coming home from church
Peacock but you're not even a black racist lady
This is your controller
You are a Nazi you are part of a group
You didn't you just made weird references to articles you're misrepresenting
Took the reason that you brought up Taylor's cuz she died like a week
She was at 7 years old
Yeah and I was 44
Tim g********* by 6 white men
Despite
Confessions to authorities subsequently denied to indict the man
No charges were ever brought against
I don't want to get into the details
Cuz it's f****** horrifying
A racially-based
Miscarriage of Justice
And the reason that you brought her up is
Because
She died a week ago
There's some
An older there is some positive things you can
Can take away in terms of
Indeed Alabama House of Representatives
In 2001 officially apologize to her on behalf of
The state
So there is there are some things that make
You know
Bright spots in the ER not murdered
Because
You haven't come
Bright white people totally have everything
I look on f****** real
I looked
Who sings a little bit cuz I want to follow along with
F****** point
Who is
I don't give a fuk
Like the race is a f******
Horrifying
Women are abducted
F****** deal with the
That's a big piece of it
That's pretty terrible
It's pretty pretty bad but
I wanted to check out this idea that white men are being killed by black people everyday and the media is
And Publishing at
The girl murders
Victims
In the last
Like couple days
You know in the New Year here
Kansas City North Main accused
To killing another man by shooting him in the chest
That was a white guy
Wisconsin man kills girlfriend used him to kill her mother
Another way you have the whites
Supremacist
Who killed his girlfriend
Eventually
The minor Dan
Is that right
You know and if he were black he would definitely
Have you tried as a minor
Children
Suspected murder-suicide
Husband told police
Before killing Crystal Eastfield noodle
Miss Transamerica
He beat his wife
The hammer
And then stabbed her to death and then went to the store to get alcohol
I'm enrolling
Because she kept being mean to him
All white people
Statistically
True is that like 90% of
Crime is
Not in a row
Read her nightstand
Crime-ridden scheduled for possible plea in double murder case
Now it's all it's all I can all the murders he finds are really there they are
Related
Speeding is a
Dangerous
Their crimes against white people being done by racist minorities all the time
Is just not looking into
Hiding because if you look into the reality of
What crime is going on
It's usually husband
Murphy
Amen
That goes back to the other
Screaming about
So the reality of the world is it Alex's wrong on
Lies per minute
Really hot
Like his lies per minute are now 300 live per second
Square
No matter how many lies you're telling
His lies are accelerating
At the same rate of speed
Alex said that Oprah
Are Oprah because of him
The truth is curved
Operation
He run for president the first time
Call
President
You did
A thunder and President also I just don't know how you can come
Complain about someone talking about eugenics
Being like you strip medically.
I mean I'm just saying that he has four kids right and they're also genetically
Superior
Whoop
If it existed in a vacuum that we want thing and still not great but it exists in the context of everything that Trump
Preside over the years about being a Believer and all that stuff
One of them nice
What is X
He's like
Directly contradicts
Themself
Is big
And he ought will
Accidentally accidentally
She's tough guys
So
Bike race
Serena's next clip we're going to listen to a little bit hard yes on
Alex's Alex
Next
A little bit of an ad
Yeah this is for one of his commercials
And
Problematic
Yeah
Debate
Rationalization
Going on
Look
These are reasonable
I'm the one saying it's inherently University
Fine if you want to come after somebody
Genuinely hate
Dude right on here
Discuss on a livestream but I didn't have the clip of Alex talking
Commercial
A real big proponent
Handing out flyers
On the street to say it's okay to be white
There's an article here from December 30th
Of last year
Portland Community College over Christmas weekend
Just two weeks ago similar Flyers were found near Portland State University
Suggesting an effort to recruit college students
Now you might be asking what what happened really what this was
Printed at the bottom of some of the posters is the website of a group called Patriot front a white supremacist organization that sounded
After the Charlottesville
Virginia unite the right rally
The website offers and American fashion
Manifesto which as the name suggests
Is a declaration of white nationalist
The other plastered messages included swastikas and printouts that red it's okay to be white
Matter
I'm a b****
Fan of
That prove
They're not correct
Like it's okay to be white
Next to a swastika
Is like
Not okay.
Do I reel it in
So when I went over this
The last time
Not okay to be white
Saying it's okay
Alex Jones
Can't be oblivious
This sort of stuff he has to know that they kind of taste
Of the rhetoric
Catchphrases
He made a shirt that the top line is it's okay to be white which happens to be
A major recruitment slogan for Neo-Nazi groups
A little bit about Caddyshack Amanda makes
He makes like a lady with the globalist but is this
Will mu confuse you for sure
Okay
Caddyshack
Mister squirrel Mister rabbit
Big Lots
Nothing
And watch
It's unbelievable that we
To this point
Because
And you're making s*** up like even just in
When recognizes NAMBLA
That's not true at all we been over this
Caddyshack 2
I know I know it's a joke
It's in
To me you know what I mean
You know I had that I've had this experience before like doing stand-up
Someone does a joke someone else's joke
I'm sorry I didn't realize that
And then you know
A month later you see them doing the job still
I don't understand how anyone around Alex could be like hey man look
I know what you're trying to do here
NAMBLA doesn't work with
I know I know you want them too I know that would make your world if you look
Moral
Which is not true
You can't keep saying it
Your narrative is wrong
See but that's when we get back to the house to know that's when we get back to
To do people buy his b*******
Like does he does
Whether or not he buys his own b*******
Now we're into like
Does anybody at Infowars
Do they all by Isabel
I would imagine know what I'm going to guess
Is that
People
Have that have that like oh we're going to
I get rich
We're going to make a lot of money
Something along those lines
Their salaries are
You mean all the employees
Yeah probably not great I know right
If you're making forty Grand a year UK
Handling this NAMBLA b******* Alex Jones
Makes
Way boys
Write the kids walk away is more than his employees
Probably not great
OK Google forever
Going by Alex is also sort of exactly because he run the night
Play news
60 G
Sure
And then he
He's worked his way up over the years
That's a pretty good pay raise
Like he's been there for 12 years or whatever you know I don't know if we'll ever be able to figure out exactly what his employees like
But I will tell you that I know how
Is this right here
Direct deposit
Free market
That's why they're scared
Evil organization on Earth
And she wants to run her mouth about racism
Literally
Boil
Disgusting
Alright
I love videos like at the beginning of that clip he's like
We women operation toothpaste off straight-shooting
I'm going to use manipulative tricks wherein I create a field
Very existence that you have lost your life
These products
Mostly live
Straight-shooting
You don't get more shooting
Straight then deep Earth iodine
I love whenever we get multiple disgraceful add pivots in
But in this next clip
Alex
Have something
You might have learned
And that is
The moral lesson
He thinks
But this whole time
He's been bonding with Trump
I meant the two of them have been vibing
Right
That's what he thought
But it turns out
He recently saw someone on television
Going up against Jake
Realizes they are but
Good spirits
Hold on
Wait for it this is f***** up is
Thirtysomething
You really shouldn't say I researched Miller and
Limbsaver things are about
Do you mean High School
Far they come
To do
Now hold on hold on hold on
Wait cuz I only pause this cuz I wanted you to reset for a second
To hear how this goes out to break
Did he get cut off by the brake
He would have just kept rambling
This is
Had every angle of what they were about to try and what they're about to do and then
It was Miller
What about this
And just goes out to Brett
In the middle of a word
You at break I could not be surprised by what white people
Steven Miller being compared to Martin
Luther King
Junior
Jonathan takes a goddamn
I would say that
Favorite Steve Miller abracadabra
Univision did a really interesting exploration
Into
Miller's life
They found
I found was a buddy Jason Isla's
High School
She got a call
From him
People who knew Miller in high school said he was a bigot back then
Expressed expressly ended childhood friendships with
Latino students over there
Ethnicity
Quote I can't be your friend anymore because you're Latino
No Jason Isla said he was told by Miller December before they began High School
In fact
Journalism from Univision
They covered up instances
Another student Natalie Flores that Miller had quotes
An intense hatred for people of color especially towards the
Problems with Latinos
He thought they lived off welfare said Flores
Now a grad student
The Columbia
Get another student Charles Gould who attended elementary through high school with Stephen Miller called him quote and unabashed
Will continue he was constantly making
Disparaging remarks about the African-American Latino and Asian students at our schools
Multiple former classmates
Including a professional baseball player Cody Decker
I've also spoken out about how Miller was booed off stage by 4,000 students running for class president
Some of Miller's fellow high school students now say they are alarmed by the power he's
Two-wheeled he's very dangerous
What is love
One one thing as a kid who makes inappropriate comments in the high school newspaper
And another is letting him right presidential orders
And they say they recognized Miller's boy
When they listen to Trump speeches
Rosemary and said that the high school
Gave him an eerie feeling
It's like you're reading Trump's words written by a 6
16 year old kid in California
Little confident people from his bastard like as a f****** bigot
Also this one is just for fun
He's the most sanctimonious student I think I ever encountered said John Bernie
Duke's former
Senior vice president of public affairs and government relations
He seems to be
Absolutely sure of his own views in the correctness of them
I've seem to assume that if you were in disagreement with him there was something malevolent or stupid about your thinking
Incredibly
I mean Alex was vibing with
No totally white nationalist
Do recognize each other game recognize game
There's a really fascinating thing there that Alex
Got it
I don't know
Google Doodle
Doubt
Alex Jones is a white nationalist
No Doubt
Either white National
Stephen Miller
You know what's great about him
You can really it look if you're willing to work hard
And you are white racist God damn it if you can't
It's so weird cuz I was like
I thought it was
All this time
Turns out that the squirrel young bigot
If you're going to say anyway
Michael Wolff
F****** look at
A b******* ass
Freedom from a mile away
To me whenever Alex has
These breakthroughs that we think are breakthroughs but are also completely different directions
He's been an antique his whole life
Of course I would have bonded with him and we're like oh my God
Congratulations on their breakthrough
You should take it to the next step you should realize
Just because
He wants white people to have privilege over everybody else
Show me thinks all other races are inferior
Expresses the feeling that he has that he
This is a little bit historical
Glee grandiose
But
I want to really stand
I want my John Hancock
Cuz you're gay Alex Jones
To be the big man
We're going to put ourselves right in the enemies way
Looking for the
He seems to think that he's going to be a new founding father
Either that or the first against the wall when the revolution comes
It's interesting to me because even a
Like I get to little grandiose
He has a little bit of a
The pie-in-the-sky kind of
Conception or chat is like
Trump 1776
2.0 baby
Drudge
Alex Jones
Not anymore money
You get it
They're the ones who were going to be
Credited with creating a new Republic
Do you get your plan
It will be
Right
Do we actually need glue
That would be
Tragic remerica
But the fact that he is
A white nationalist
Bob authoritarian d********** you know he
I don't mean that many
He would folate and authoritarian
With Glee
Right
I'm not jumping in on you or your bandwagon
I could we talk about Alex so negatively I don't want to
Say he's gay cuz it sounds like that's a negative then we're coming
Negative
I'm assuming how people might hear it and I'm getting celkon
Not living the life you should live his truth
Do we actually have to
Start like being like okay
Overthrowing the government
Like a year-and-a-half ago
Call it a counter-coup and I don't know I don't know
Take that are processed
Bees that are in place
Let's just try and live our lives today
Alex
Steam stats
Nationalist Boogeyman wherever
Hugo's lizard
Okay well
Is there lizard people for that bright
These are just evil like this one
And I'm not talking about like misguided or anything like that
I think we're actually good we actually have to say
These are bad human beings
Malevolent
In there
Their act
Only trying
To subjugate others
Human beings
I'm not in a globalist way but in a Raceway
I don't know how to
The problem with
Talking about Alex Jones
You get back into his I know you are but what am I
Like I'm talking to him
Because what he's doing is he's just saying all of the things that are true about him about other people's
And even push it back without being like
The best defense
You can use
In the world is
Whatever someone would use
Against you or describing what people would use again
Cuz then it just becomes a like
How do you how do you even
Listen to Alex Jones say things like
The globalists are trying to divide you based upon race and then
Support Stephen Miller
What's 2 / 0
Like how do you how do you even know how do you even come back
Whenever it's like
Nike what do you say not just support Stephen Miller
The times were there on the same wavelength
Much more than
Support
Anyway I don't know
You know what what we do now
He does we know he goes to Luby's how is Luby's
This is not about love
Diner
Does Alex go to Luby's menu
Start sprinkler
Breadcrumbs
Like on the on the little desk
Like I like an old man
For ducks but it's
For old women
With therapy
Backpack at the bottom of it
Chicken in Moana
Different Diner a little bit of a nostalgic throwback Diner
You saw something
But nobody wants to
I saw a mural
On the wall
Place called Waterloo ice house that's a pretty good little diner
And
I've been doing it for years I really noticed it is because it was just nostalgic Americana
I guess I'm a red X Beer Red Cross
And a woman with his
Golf cart
His wife is pissing
It's also nationalistic
Webster said oh yeah you're crazy lucky loggers not even around anymore
As if that even matter
And does any of this matter Alex
Blender
I don't even know what he's talking
I don't know when
Hard pass. You have this with whatever it is you want this to be fun
Confide start dying your hair
How to talk
Take a swig and you start talking I'm like
But what are you trying to do is deflect about ideas
I think the people have about representation and just trying to create a straw man
Mystically posted on
Where are you still in Columbia
63 Diner
It was like that it was like that kind of Dino that strobe
Nostalgia
Yeah it's a little creepy but not because it's all mostly it is
It's just a little creepy cuz it's like
Like people to recreate the
Weird
But I wouldn't like it
But also the other thing is
Although now that I think about it the Saved by the
Lot of white people in that one
He's misrepresenting to that like people talk about
Phyno
Minority
An adze
Okay family
People complaining
About those eyes
People rely
Why is there a gay couple in my Cheerios commercial
The people who are complaining about stuff is not Christmas
See your whole lot of people who are like
No
Well I mean
Real grief
Chatsworth
How many how many women directors have won
Best Director of course
Of course that's
Nobody is it in terms of
Oppressive complaints
I would argue that
The people who are mad
About black family
Commercials
To complain a bit more
It all went downhill
I was all over after that
Beginning of YouTube
You can make the argument that Janet Jackson at the Superbowl destroyed the world
Peripheral
Triple
Justin Timberlake is responsible for the destruction of the world and the rise of white nationalism
That sounds right correlation causation
That f*****
Sojourn now we're going to jump into a little bit of business
Was he
NSYNC or
NSYNC Chris Kirkpatrick
Call Dan Joey Fatone
Is right I know all the members of NSYNC problem from the
Beginning now Backstreet Boys
I'm just going to point this out alright
Did the temptation
Race war
They didn't
Delete to a temporal
See there we go
Black boy bands all the time
Jordan
I don't want to say that
The weird thing to say
My last episode
We talked about
Doo-wop group
You want done
Episode we talked about ranting about Brian
And one of the things that we know
From
Knowing Alex
Is that there was a lot of
Anti-semitism
We know that
We also know that he just doesn't like Brian Stelzer.
We also know that
Some of it was fairly
In terms of his performative aspect Wrench It Like That
Gametime
The level of anger that he was
Expressing
Visceral
Whether or not
Is the best actor in the world
He
Was really feeling anger like he was actually angry
Certainly
Here's the argument that I want to make
There's two possibilities actually Bryan seltzer
Know what is the lightest real response
He is like
That and that is not very
Eloquent
Certainly
He's kind of
Kind of a gross creep
And then the other alternative inclusion
That one's true
Write the other alternative is
And that is
He was trolling peep
It was Fat Tire
Satire is the literal world
Tire attire
Are you sure he wasn't saying he was playing the sitar
No you said it's satire and that he was trolling
What are the article about it
The argument that he makes
Is that he was having fun
And he was letting himself off the
Just letting himself loose off
Off the train
And if that's the case that. Still not set
No certainly not use notes at
Himself off the tree
Cuz then when you get off the chain
You spout
Anti-semitism
So if you're saying that I just let myself go and sort of.
Then what you feel
Is anti-Semitic bigot
That's a problem
Also
Still not.
I mean
This is not this
Family fun but it'll be what it is
Because here's what
Alex Jones covers
The Young Turks
Covering
At the third hour of the show
Alex Jones
Breakdowns them breaking down his
Which That Could Be Santa
Then but then are we going to
Breaking down the
Turks breaking him
I hope no never
Never going Gaspard
Send him breaking down
About him breaking down The Young Turks breaking him down
Breaking him down
Inevitably breaking down his breakdown of their brain
I just want to know when somebody's going to covered our breakdown
I went over your break
Alex is literal breakdown wearing he let himself up
Hookah
So
At what point does Alex Jones become a crypt
Now this is a good Quest request
In the first clip of the ranch
Is where he he says that it's at
Again we can
Very much disagree with that cuz no matter what it is
It's not session
Culture he wants to control the media
I think he thinks
Better metaphor is satire
That's the only thing I've got to go on so far or hyperbole
Possibly
What else
If you want want to try and use that literary Trump wear
For the entirety of the
Alex did not bring up Jared from Subway at all during that rap now claiming
We got the receipt
He's claiming that like it was that tire I just talked about how he looks weird and it's like the whole media also I was bringing up
Good-looking f****** weird nope
It was only about Michael Wolff
Why does filter looks
Okay
Having some fun is
Ladies and gentlemen
Yes I believe shelter people
Fun
Having fun
That makes it even less clear
Cuz I really do believe these things
I was having fun
No
Well it was satire
Right
I mean I mean what I said
Bright
And also I was yelling about it
Do people think
I don't mean what I say that I'm acting
No I believe what I said
And I let myself off the chain
To say it louder like I mean
Chief example of satire Borrego Springs
Just say what he meant
Aggressively
Or even if it was
YouTube
I don't understand like I get what I think
He think
And that is that like a I was goofing around I was hoping to get more attention to myself and Hate
Cuz it sounds smart and I don't really know why
It went when these dumb dudes
Say they were being satirical what they really mean to say is
I thought I was joking
Or at least
Tell you that I was joking even though I was telling the truth
But if I say I was joking
Sounds like I'm kind of an idiot implies it also implies that anytime I show passion
Or these like
Fake crying and stuff like that I'm faking it and I kind of invalidates a lot of my passions
To the audience
Okay here's a here's the new here's the new thing if we ever do interview
We won't
No question
Just
The definition of satire
Blighted ovum
I mean just like
Justice be like
Here you go
End of interview
Like
A good interview with Trump
Should be
Space questions
And feels like do you know not even not even a question about everything
The Electoral College is the UN right much more Illuminating
Prove the globalist
Exist
Horse
Strategy
Like a hawk
Small chunks
A lot of
Open places right
At the beginning
But he was trigger
It's delger triggers
Which implies that it was
Celestron Tire reaction of
I don't know
He gets to starting his coverage of
The Young Turks talking about him
Really Treasures me
From golf
Are you sick
Heartland
Really concerned me the most
A good point was made in the chat room that they're already wasn't America
I'm psycho 20-something it's okay
That's a good point
Take a look at the video
Laughing over his
Children done too far down the rabbit hole
It's like a
The only reason I kept that in there is because you can hear him laughing in the background
In his work but there's also I mean
I study Alex Jones
30 language
What is body language
I don't know such a gifted liar that it's
Very difficult to tell what's insecure right there was a look of like
Like there was a discomfort on his right
I think he loves to watch himself I think there was a discomfort and I think it's because he understands that this
Tire argument is just
Babe
I will give him credit for that
I think he was aware that people going to share the s*** out of this
You went on an unhinged
Systematic Ranch
And I wish you'd listen
Shobha
She would have
Really been afraid of Alex Jones a long time
Ana kasparian
Say a little bit
He brings up the anti-semitism
Rings
He doesn't bring a blood libel in a
It's proper,
He brings it up as a Nazi rhetorical
No
Scream
News about drink
He says this
Kim
Think about
I'm at everything I said but I realize
Bulshit why would I be surprised
Words are not
If this is a reaction
He claims
With the 10-minute
Unhinged hits on
I want to go pick was Muggsy look like the Joker everywhere
Alex Jones
I just watched your audience well
Facebook
Rifle streams are podcast already
Station's ratings
Punch the globalist of the nose
And say stuff like
He did not that that
It wasn't what you were saying at all
If it was
I don't know I could be different
But
It would have gotten as many views that's
Possibly
I don't think
That that
Sara Lee
Is gold
I would make this argument
Babies audience well
It might be because of people who
Resonate with
One of the more negative
Pieces of it I don't think it's very difficult to grow your audience
Dog whistle
Really hard
Like I don't think that that is that difficult I think you'll be snoozes number one the ratings for a long time baby
I don't think
Don't
I think if we
Are you saying we should do I'm not a hypothetical
If we did unhinge the rants that were vaguely
I guess
Technically not
Racist but bigoted
We just did like
Durant
I think we could probably grow this a lot
And look
Call Mike
Go
Be fair you have something is Rancid
White well yeah
Flights
Henderson's balancing
Quite frankly
White people have everything
Do it that I
I think that white people are the cause of all of our prop
Alex
Text Jones
He did this during the actual episode the rant was in from the 5th
He claims that he can't do that evil smile
Dolphin
To smile they always
I love Liberty
Marshall Lee
What let me try
Nice trying to do the smile
And while he's doing it
On the screen there flashing up pictures of stelter
Then Jared
Subway
Stelter
Jared from Subway
Subconscious attempt
To combine the two and your head
He's moved on from
He looks like Mike Wolfe
Now it's
Now it's Jared
Subway
Like a disclaimer on the bottom like may cause
No but it wasn't that bad
But also it's intentional listen to have equipment
I'm still trying
Together
A door wanting to date your daughter
That's
Ridiculous
That's absurd
Yeah
First of all
Second of all
He's trying to create
Uncouple the association
Jared Fogle who is a pedophile and belongs in
Right
Who Alex just
Disagrees with
Active
I don't know I died
Again nothing about
Oprah I think
Is close to legally actionable
This is repugnant
But totally
Allowable totally get away with it
In terms of someone who claims to be running a
Operation
Straight-shooting I don't like with a p
Pedophile
So in this next clip
So throughout the season
Quite a bit
And it's hard
Get away from the idea that
Drink
Is someone
Arabic
Tough to get away from the fact that
Alex
Cuz he does
And he's not
But
Alex thinks
Season islamist
And that
Might be
Right but that
Might be informing
Kind of mad about it and why you
Covering their coverage
Cuz they could it could have chosen a bunch of people like
Brown
Something
Barry f*****-up
Because
He's responding
Defensively about
The West
And he says that
Male race
What you having
Anti-female
System
Christian and Judea
Goddess worship
Are the women
Spiritual ugly creature
You're telling us
Is how you're going to take
Because you expected
Do your phone
Now he's Tire
Projection
So it's definitely projection
You're disgusting Fallen blob
But also that the whole thing is
That's weird that is such an infantile version of like
Okay I will.
The class
Jordan
So
Judeo-christianity never had any issues with women
Question retracted
And of course Islam is based on hating women
But as everybody knows
What America and the West
Is really about
Just a regular one
Spell Europe named after Europa
Right
I don't know the full Aeneid
I always thought that America was named after Amerigo Vespucci
Now it's not I always thought that
Heard it sometime I just agreed
I'm still at
Ey America's gold America
Like I could be the dude named America could be you're going with this
I got to apologize to the best as well today like the name until I'm keeping
I think that it's infantilizing
To certain degree this idea of
First of all the idea that our civilization is based on goddess
Worship apply to
Old-time version
The chivalry which are
Middle Ages
Which is controlling
It's a controlling worldview as much as
You complained about in the in the east
Making it
Impossible for her to
Be your ego
I am handicapped Punisher
There's a very fun game to play with the aggressive chivalry
But I've never heard weird things for him
To say when he's like
And you're trying to control your telling us how to control women's like I didn't know
Very very messed up
In this next clip
Alex
You know he's big on personal responsibility we know that
Part of his world
For everybody
Right cuz in this Cliff he blames literally everybody for his custard
City battle other than himself
And I said I shouldn't have kids and he's very show set it
Wife is a CPS
Chicago public
Scumbags
He's talking about the young
Yeah that
When
You
You can't possibly think that's
Reality
You and your behavior
I've got you where you are
You and your ex-wife
You got
And that's just a regular thing it is
Like that's a thing
It is
Kind of a part of it
And I don't know the truth of it cuz I don't really
I don't particularly care about
People's personal lives because there's so many variables you really know what's going on
It's impossible to make comment on stuff like
Maybe he is a good father
Possible possible
If this all isn't it
I don't know the thing that comes down to for me is the only two possibilities
Either
Desertion
His ex-wife is made
Radar true
Or they're not
And he was still married to her for 8 years
Or whatever 10 years
And this is
Unfortunately a piece that comes along with that
So
None of my business
The liberal media they came down to try and take your kids
Own up to your life
Taken away from him
I want to
Livelihood
His home
And everything he's ever known and loved
Oh no I think I I think I
I think I'm on this
I got his eyes
Constantinople intern
But the guy whose ancestors
Chucktown
To Noble
History
He doesn't because it was taken over by people
Consistently throughout history
Very strategically important
Christian
Savannah
Break about the actual
Muslims
He's talking about here he goes on a lot of stuff about how they're named after people who were
Like involved in the Armenian Genocide
And stuff like that I don't want to unpack that
I don't I don't
Look I don't I'm not sitting here defending Jank
Not necessarily I don't know
Even talked about that thing about his right from when he was younger
Die except
Accept his apology I wasn't Wrong by
But is apology seems
Credible bit at same time
Not off the hook for that it seems very weird that he named his organization The Young Turks
But you know what
Rod Stewart had a song called Young Turks
Young hearts be free
Now
Possible also another theory
Jackie Hubert named his channel
After a Rod Stewart song I don't know I get to the bottom of
It's only important because it feeds into this next
Very nice
Scary and concerning level of paranoia
I know you hate
Is that satire
I mean he was exhibiting the
Is that tire
You know what go back to Istanbul
No that's racism
Do you know what I could actually you could make a case for that being said
Because because he's very paranoid
Satirically
I'm going to I'm going to go with
You've got
I'm going to go with a maybe they'll hold on cuz
There's a level of fear and paranoia and he goes
You think I'm scared of you like always going to control
Yeah
The point that he's trying to make I'm not saying
Satirical
I'm saying that
In a vacuum
I get that
But I'm saying
If we apply his
Belief about himself that he's using satire
Then the only conclusion come away from
That being satire
These Young Turks
Right but also we talked about there is when Jimmy Dore spit on it
During all Young Turks
It was during the campaign and there was
Maybe during one of the conventions
Something like that
And I all right
I think was horrible did he spit on Alex Jones but also
I wouldn't I think
Now that does bordering
To assault territory
Anyway I don't support Jimmy Dore necessarily so I'm not going to
Other than Alex
You got to do better that with your screaming then
I was in control because that makes me think you're not now nor were you
What's the doodle Alex
Is talking
About
He kind of admit
Being
Theatrical
Which
But you also
I'll just tell you ahead of time
Keeps calling
Huger son
Weird twist
For his verbiage
I don't
I don't like that I don't think it's necessarily like
Maybe not intentionally but again it goes back to like that is a that's
Free dog whistling
Yep cuz he doesn't usually call people son
Doesn't usually do that kind of
Step away from boy
That's what I do son
You were just giving your stuff by Gulf States
Propped up
Google
Successful
Also just for fun sounds
Archive page of infowars.com
1899 or 98
And someone else
Austin Austin
So even I don't even know even that is kind of
Very difficult to dig that up at this point
You don't you don't understand running around
You understand
Avinash collaborate for Sora
Oh
I don't know
I don't know I don't really care
Anymore he's not self-made this is all such nonsense
The next one
Allergies is a serious straw man
What drug is it
On the actual clip
Alex watch the whole thing
He knows that eventually drink
Brings up Ludlow
Any brings up how
All of the things that Alex's
Using all these deceitful betrayer backstabber
These are also have historical characterization
Yes and it's not coincidental that
Most of the rant was appearance
And so
On that
Side I think it a pretty decent job
Tossing out what was going on
In terms of
I got off track on
Some of their assessment like Alex calls them broke back
And they're like that means calling them gay
Taking things in the proper context
But they do decent job of that like I said he brings up the blood libel
The least is a nice
Start Alex has to know that that's
Coming up events
And so he cuts off
The clip
Strawman
Those guys
You seen in history
Oh my gosh
Free shipping is coming up
What's fascinating about it though to is that like
What he's doing is he's allowing Jank to
To save that
But not to explain what do you mean
Just bring up
These historical characterization
So he's allowed this sound bites
To be a mischaracterization
Ogle Jenkins
And then he just like
They think Alex is laughing the soffits
Weather
Explain what Alec
Is more aware of this than I
We pick
I think he might be
Pretty well aware
That most of his rhetoric has
A very much
I think that for a long time we've been
Giving a pass
To like the it being
He's oblivious to the history of the narratives
He's spitting but I am not sure we can give him that pass
Well I don't know
Regardless of that at the very least
He's aware of
How damaging it would be
To have those
Play Don Ho
Show
Certainly
Really come up with a rebuttal
To that like if
If he played it on his own show
It's difficult
To be like a pecan
Really wrestle with the ID
Idea that
Why do you think these people
Prove that
What do you have that proves that
And the only thing he could point to is
Conspiracy sites
That all are informed by the arcade
So that's the only thing he could go on
He can't wrestle with that passed
That's not a good defense
I know they drink blood
Listen to these anti-semites over here tell
Don't throw the baby out with the bathwater
Book broken anti-semites can be right twice
I'm sure there will be some sort of rationalization
Here's the last clip and I think it's a
Wraparound
Is all of this horseshit
Free shipping
The future
If we simply
Embrace God's plan
And be good decent honorable people adopt me going to church and telling people
Richard Gere
Not being a scumbag
And not being jealous of people for no reason
Of the sinking Yung turd
System
They're falling
Because we carry the light in the darkness of the night and we're willing to execute and not give up
And not giving up and not falter and not waver at not
Tower
So he's presenting Infowars as a victim their butt
The other thing is
Yeah most
News organizations aren't
Being investigated in
Put it under the microscope
Because most
Aren't
Committing
Well they even cry Prime decide they aren't just
Spouting
Consistent
Atria like there's no other way to tie
Take so much of
The stuff he says
It's all white identity all white victimhood all-male for
Fragility
All the all the
That is underneath
Those things
People care what you say Alex
Marcus anyone thinks you're right
Don't even think you're right or bigots
I love the
I mean I think
He is telling the truth when
He says he tries
People the way he want
Yeah okay I think I think he does
Like I think
Genuinely feels like this is
How he deserves
Oh yeah that's possible what are those pdsa
He's definitely got like a
No this is how you communicate love
Cuz I forgot to play the out-of-context drop from earlier
I want to play a
Because I think it really sums up why people
Student
Casually address Alex Jones
Like
I think you need to know what he's talking about in order to have a conversation about him or else
You're going to fall into his trap
This is from a commercially plays on the show where he and Rodger Stone go shooting
Until they're shooting a bunch of gun
And
That sums it up
Great is really excited about the idea that him want to trigger lips
Rodger Stone charged with guns
And in that which is great but when he gets triggered
Muslim for criticizing about it
At Freight
Website
Do you want status
Anyway we were both acknowledge underscore fight
What's that other place were on the
That's right
That's where you can find us download subscribe leave reviews all that go
Good stuff
I mean who is he
Who is it
Just today
Steve Miller
Steve Miller can go f*** himself
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work