Alex
In color
Doesn't talk a little bit about Alex Jones
What is the novelty beverage address it up top is Bell's Two Hearted Ale
Jordan
What's up
The chatroom be like
Talking stick to the rules as it's become a thing where there's like chance that get going of like
What's the beverage
I don't want
The hook is a 1993 song by John popper is rock and roll
I know what I was doing you know nothing about him and our fun welcome back
Welcome back everyone listening
Thrilled to be here I've been chomping at the bit
You you've been texting me like a giddy schoolgirl for the past couple of days just like
That wasn't so much that I almost had a panic attack listening to Alex yesterday
She said he was getting into and how much I wanted to talk about it you were busy last night we couldn't do it actually
I'm thrilled that you couldn't do it as it turns out because having the context of today
To yesterday show makes the narrative so much more robots
So we are at
Another one in the
Apologies to Jordan you're right circumstance
If anything
But
Oh my God I am going to put a check in the column out of 8 people I'd like to say thank you.
What's going on out there I can graduation song
Thank you so much appreciate it so very much
You have to
DS2 off board a little money also another
He is a foreign policy wonk but I unfortunately forgot to load up that sound effect
Dammit
The only foreign policy wonk
Will be getting the salutation of a technocrat
Someone's someone
Sodomites
Has a Caribbean
Fair enough Jordan
Good Times
If you would like to become a few would like to become a policy wonk and Trigger sound effects like that
You may do so by going to our website knowledge feit.com and couldn't support the show
We really appreciated a little update
We had set out that we needed to try and bump up a donation
$200 by the end of the month
Starting on January 1st
And we are definitely on track to do that and I really appreciate everyone
Keep rolling a weekend hit this goal
And it's only January
11th Avenue recording guide
Ahead of crack
Welfare
A little bit ahead of track so it really really appreciate it
A big difference
If we hit our goal we will start breaking down
Endgame
Alex Jones's dogs
12 and a half hour long episode
It will be
Devastating
A couple of things I've read like
QuickBooks 50 me covered 10 minutes
Now I don't want to reach the goal because I want all of that work to aventurine
That'll be very cruel
So you don't have to listen
The show if you don't like it
I just donated a little bit more so we can all hear those
That's what it is
We will be going over today event
The transpired on the January 10th and January 11th
2018 episode of The Alex Jones Show
But
What we're really going to be going over cuz I'm going to skip a lot of the bulshit like on the 11th
Joe Arpaio was on the screen for half an hour about how you the monster
Headphones
But he's on cuz he's running for congress
Project Veritas
Chiefs game on because they had an undercover investigation of Twitter
I know Twitter Shadow Banning conservatives
And so they played the video and it's the softest
You should have ever seen in my life
It's very clear from the context of these interviews that they have that they're secretly recording
Like there's just a guy who's a
Explaining what shadowbanning is that they forgot to cut out the guy
I don't know if Twitter even does that anymore
And there's another one
Tracy because of course he had to say that
He can't get you
Tell him that
You should have cut that out
He's crafty
It's terrible
I don't know
It's going on on the episodes we're not going to talk about that because we need to talk about a more robust
Issue
Is being
Expose I
Think pretty clearly
And that is what Alex Jones has
What I would officially call his lofted
Not have a Caribbean black accents
Direction
Spell races Transformers
So here's the deal Alex
This is the point where Alex
Has lost his mind
But I think he's lost his mind at a very specific Alex Jones away
He's become
Reasonable no no
Geez renounce
All of his previous statements and he's decided that now
Is the time
To open up
Small independent books
No
Although he'll be interested in being angry at book store where no one reads anything
Covers
Book jacket
Every spine those books
What I mean by this I believe that
Defining characteristics of Alex Jones
Is jealousy and pettiness
And bitterness
I think
Is it Alex
Have become
Aware of the conspiracy World outside of himself
Okay and you starting to lose his mind
Alright because he's being out.
Okay and I know this will flush out as we go along but my first piece of evidence
Interpret
That will inform the rest of this episode
I have to take you back
Do a special report
Did Alex Jones recorded
On Christmas Eve
But I somehow missed in the shuffle
Because I don't watch all of his special report
Okay
Insinuate
But he's recording this at 3 in the morning
I'm guessing that's not true
It's unclear cuz he says
Did Rob do is there he's the kind of guy who can call it 3 in the morning I will come down to the studio
He might have just been saying that is a general thing
Watch
So it isn't that you know
His wife are they an hour earlier than Central
10 hour Earth Mountain
Yeah
Clarify for
He says that his wife is there with him like she's waiting outside Rob dude wife and kid are there
This why are you
Depressant
Christmas at
Alex Jones is a shity version of Ebenezer Scrooge
It's very depressing the first clip
Decided to
To come into the studio
On Christmas Eve to record a special
Library
It's Christmas Eve
Emergency
If this doesn't
Greece
Emergency alert
Alright
Really
Now
I have
Anonymous
And a lot of what
The sources are in
If he gives
If you give those three examples like I got it for my White House sources
The FBI's phone
Can over the internet
Already have known
For everyone who doesn't know I don't know a bunch of looking into this and it's not really worth too much of a
Discussion but qanon is another one of these account
Videos posting
Cryptic messages and stuff like that trying to get people to think
That they have inside information
What are some of the accounts that have existed on Reddit and unfortunate over the years that have been like
Men like all these people who do just play around as if they have
Insider
I'm so this is Chris
This is another one
I am so
What's going on here
Is Alex
Is Vic
King of conspiracy
Right
Historically
Turn on the radio
And he is the king of conspiracy
Most
I would say the most popular
Conspiracy theorist use the Walmart of conspiracy theories
For the last couple months
You've been pitching this narrative where this guy named Zach
Comes on
Over the phone
What is an FBI intelligence agency
Feeding him information like they were shooting from helicopters
I've lost Vegas shooting shirt like that
Qanon
Is okay
To the point where Rob do has interviewed people who moderate
The subreddit
XO Alex
God dammit
Are you shiting me
I get to f*** with Alex
Jones directly
Yes 100% interview
Alex cannot handle
The fact that you being outdone by random people f****** around on Facebook
Fortune
So it took point where even
F****** Jerome corsi is basically writing a book
Online decoding qanon message
I love it I love it I love it
Here is here's the clip where I think would really demonstrate
His true feelings
About that about that
The situation
Some little comment
Qanon
That's great
This guy's known to us who he is
Say by the Bell
Stop exposed
Torres
He's saying the qanon isn't real but
This can be so mad in The Last Jedi whatever
Yoda says to Luke that
Fate of the teachers for
For there
My students to out
Right
I guess
Make as many Star Wars The Last Jedi reference
How would it go
So in this in this next court again for Christmas Eve
$300 will do a breakdown of The Last Jedi
In this next clip Alex Jones in trying to get authenticity papers for him
His hope
His intelligence fake guy
What do you need
What he's accidentally doesn't equip is very clearly out who this guy is
If he's real
One of those
Florida
Nationality
But also a defining characteristic
He is now
We're so serious
Morocco
Keto not with Nick
Urgent
Casablanca
I have
Very very
They haven't
What's Ocean View
Protect
What does que
We say who they are
Bella Notte
There wasn't
Because you have made a bunch of defining characteristics
It is at the Aspen
Attitude is Clapper and Brennan together with Wolf Blitzer
I found this clip actually I found it on Alex Jones Channel
I found
Keep saying I found a video that he put out himself called former CIA director
Calls for coup against Trump
Let's listen to what Alex plays of the
Is where the work of
Another special counsel
Apps
We both work with him for a long time when he was
Spire choice
Who is a straight shooter and will not be intimidated
I really hope
Stop making apology
Jesus chooses
LeBlanc
Open you say enough is enough
Aspire
Presence
But if he's fired
What would you want
Paul Ryan to hang
It's the obligation
Some of these orders
Again
With what sodas
Companies all about
Butter
This is not going to
Partisan issue
That's Republic
Democrats are going to see
So that was Alex plays on this former CIA director calls for a coup against Trump
There's nothing there's nothing there
Technically does not break the law however
Completely destroys any pot
Possibility of believing that he is colluding
Person investigating him for his
Can of Justice then it's a good idea for Congress to
Overthrow the government
So you see what's going on
Qanon
And Zack
These guys
I had said that there was a plot to overthrow Trump
In November which is indicated by The Clapper
Dude having to talk about overthrowing
None of this makes sense
Is all just random b******* right and making
Connections where they aren't
Do you think understand words
Probably
At least
Is a literal wolf
I'm not entirely sure what you're trying to say
So it gets weird
It gets weirder
Here is some information that Alex Jones got
From his source
About
Indicted
Remember
Of the trumpet
So real
When was
By others
Do what
Flynn
Resurgence
He is describing
Describing
To get everyone against the wall
Flynn
Into the government
In order to Rendezvous with Alexa
With that he's a big fan of making America great again
What does means you commit in Arabic
That's absurd
Is completely absurd
So qanon is going on
On the internet
Don't quite match the
The outside Charizard crazy loud right now
Alex is down
Sorry I bumped up Alex
Qanon post on
About him and he or she would post
Before the storm which is a reference to that weird, that Trump made
With a bunch of generals when they were having a picture
Taken before the storm gentleman
Whichever one assumed
You were about to attack North Korea which is probably
More accurate to his mentality than
As opposed to being like
Hey let's get a weird internet meme going
Call Zach before the attack
It would be like
Zach is so real you guys
F*** you
For real though
But like
Sew-ins next clip Alex
Really expresses what
Kiipix about
The Calm before the
The storm
It's called America
The bad babe
It's called
Fulfilling
He's called
Skip 3 more exam
He's through the storm
This is all about the whole time
Omad
Come on
Guys guys come on
He's in a weird place where he's like I got
B I got f****** b b
Forget you guys do you understand me
Can't jump on
Like completely blow-up and millions of people
You'll get mixed up in
Qanon stop
The hottest thing on the internet
Qanon shirt
The f*** is wrong with me
Can't handle this
It's for Hillary for prison
Bright it's not more Papi
I'm going over there
This Christmas Eve stuff because I think it's important
Really established
What is buying Savage no I don't know any of it
Find out pretty easily if you just Google it
I've looked into it and I can't explain it
You have a lot of really cryptic
Vague clues about stuff that if you want to read into after-the-fact
Oh my God he was trying to get us to look at this
Reverend that I get of a lot of it
Which is the same thing that happened
Hawaiian they only take Max should start doing every episode
Mexican update
I think it's currently worth like a tenth of a cent
Currency is going to explode
In this next clip
We get to a prediction
Zach
Christmas Eve
And whether or not this is
Serious
Stop
It's good strong
You
And they're never going to stop
You must
Give them
No Quarter
I mean to kill them
That's what's going on
Yourself
The word is
Trump
On the president
Show
Attempted
Okay
Again
There he is saying like this needs to get more views
I should be burning
He's Furious
But we now are you recording this on January 11th
So far
0qu
0 attacks on Trump plays this fun game replays all the time that is because we were
Absolutely this guy is able to do
Or whenever something is like
And you should thank us
Right
Well thank us
You don't know how f****** hard we work for Atlanta runaway to Morocco
This next clip is gross and it's about
Alex
This sucks
The next group is Alex Jones lying about the Trump
Peter Lorre
Is not a good
Jocelyn Elders level
Decide this next clip Jordan
Is Christmas Eve
It's gross and it's just Alex Jones lying about Trump busting a pedophile Networks
Then I only want to play
Because
Listen to this
And keep in mind that he is forced
Rob Dyrdek's wife
Rob Dyrdek
And Alex's wife
Infowars Studios
Christmas Eve
Screaming out like a petty little child about how she hopes and getting enough attention
Save this
The storm is real
The removal
Whipped
6 month old baby
Coming out
You take one of these arrests
Chanel a100
Florida
Just real quick
I only reason is because that
Hundreds arrested in La wasn't going back to The Narrative of the year
7 month
Slater
Using that same article in KTLA
Certification for his bulshit narrative about Trump going after pedophiles
I've done so much research in the last week
Into the reality or falsity of those claims
Be coming out real soon about it
Edit
It's amazing the work that is going on and how much Alex is lying
Disgust
Biggest question that I have
Pedophilia is
Is awful
Is anybody in 2016
I don't want I mean I don't know what else to say I don't know rubbing it on you right like there's nothing else
To do I don't know
I don't know I think the depravity of the human mind Knows No Limits
We need to get our own
Let's not
I will be a Jordan project
So here's the rest of the Gods give me the best ones
Because they don't want you to know
News
They don't want you
Troll
Who wanted to have sex
Children
Also Merry Christmas
Kill
And so
Wish you would have come back
Pause would like
Merry Christmas Rob Ben's child
You could probably see his brain going
That's not
True
I should have said that
Where
I'm getting to the point where even The Young Turks
Deeply anti-semitic narrative specifically it's not just a small podcast called
It's getting it anymore
I shouldn't have said that on Christmas
Boy Little Drummer Boy
Keep going
Meddlesome up Christmas Eve for you
And things
Do you mean in general
Like with that was that bore of like a holistic
Christmas Eve honestly
That was better than Microsoft
That's true you sent me some very Alex Jones
That studio over where I was
You think I need you to take away I think
The things that we've
We've discussed in that is
Alex's incredibly curious
That more people aren't paying attention
Everyone loves qanon he thinks millions of hits and he's not cuz everyone is hurt
Alex crywolf so many goddamn times
In his attempt
To bolster Zacks reputation
What is ended up doing is
Number one
Anyone who knows
If he's a real person
If it's not just a month
I believe it's a month
Do you know how I know he isn't
Nobody has ever been hired by the FBI or the
CIA
Do you spell zit vaq
Alright okay so again
What's motivating it
Is Alex having buyer's remorse
For not getting in on the ground floor
Much like he kind of feels now into
Bitcoin
He feels a bit like that
I don't know
I don't fucken understand
Pizzagate
Not willing to get on board with qanon
And now it's too late
Got screwed by Y2K goes all the way back
So anyway
Now we get to January 10th
We are now in
Enter January 10th
Just fun
Reminder of the world exist
Outside of
Alex's
Psychodrama that he's having
Currently
And that is
Sikorsky
He's talking about Steve Bannon
2 by himself
Other people
That's not a good thing to say Rodger you should not have pointed that out
Because once again that is something that is under
You should definitely not have been like hey Robert by the way I know Trump really well and he has been stealing people's money
For a long time
He's not allowed to take money from Americans any more like if we were super conspiracy-minded
Inclined to think that's Rodger Stone trying to publicly like lay track
Be like
That's like him trying to not know he was mobbed up
He's a master of music
The f*** off
Why would you abbreviate that if you're about to say exactly what the abbreviation
What the abbreviation
It's not like it's not a common abbreviation
Walking around money
I know that I know
Well maybe that's what he's going with OPP other people's property
Pretty sure
It's talking about f****** other people's girlfriend
I just meant
Rodger Stone wasn't going okay
Remember the clip-ins
Oh yeah okay
Also before
Who cares
Indicates that it's absolutely obvious that Rodger Stone
Source
Information he was feeding to Alex over the course
How's that going to last year-and-a-half
Because they now start using
The narratives that
Work in the past throw Bannon under the bus
Okay
That's PetSmart
It's not a smart idea it's not bad but they never bring up
Right
Maybe one day we'll do is I'll put together an entire report on
All of those receipts
Cracked you actually get to Trump and your
You're a you're dropped if you become a truck.
A long list of things that Rodger stone is
No cuz though
All of our donors are
Good thing
Policy wonks foreign policy wonk technocrats globalist
They're all good things restraint Technologies
Advances in society in a great way
I just know I don't think that
The crap part that
I guess everybody in
Susan. This is worth debating
So Jordan
Now
We're going to jump in
To the narrative
But Alex Jones cell
The Narrative you have been masturbating
Mooreland path.
The show on
The tent is not all that eventful
What you end up seeing is Rodger Stone throwing
Saying the band is responsible for all the globalist
That were in the administration
Like Rex Tillerson
Rex Tillerson is neck
All that sort of stuff
She does that
And then
Evan Rex Ryan is after him
After that your ex is after them
When I was five
That
Alex Jones has this guy who owns a gun shop in Washington on the show
Who had a transgender antifa member
Come into the shop and throw a Bible around or something like that
It's nonsense
Excuse me for 40 minutes
Read interviews the guy about her for 40 minutes
Is a
And was like
You guys do anything illegal
No
In the name of passive aggressive conversation
On the way out customer is like
One of these is going on here in the guys like
Holy Bible
You can take it if you want
She's like
We what I would do
Alex is Joe he's just going on and on about how like
Yeah and that was that so
I watched the video and Madeline of being a dick absolute
Customer was being a dick
But it's enough
Has it, but it's a 0
H20
So I don't really care all that much
Minutes
Crazy
Nothing
Third hour
Rolls around
Yeah
Are we getting
Emeritus
That almost
Almost ruined
Right
Finally feeling like Christmas
No
Three weeks later though
Alex
Jumpsend
And
Alfred form
Both in Europe the third world
Document
George soros's son who does honcho
Most of the women's marches
Led by Linda sorcerer with her
Ulcers
Skittermander is wrong
We're showing
So you picking up on what's going on yet
I'm not sure
Okay what's your sense of it
My sense of it is that
His narrative
Terrible
What if we put them all together in a big narrative
Right
Everything that I've been yelling about
Magically
Has proved
What if
We find the MacGuffin
What if we find exactly
Well if you
Understand
Fiction I think it has
His soul
Briefcase right other we get a little glimpse of some stall here but let's get it
Explains a little bit more what he's talkin about
The documents report to show
Disclosure agreements and contracts
Baltimore
Civil
Martial law Nationwide
Martial law
What we know
Providence of the documents
Bi
The Grudge
No you f******
But first of all want to go anywhere near the FBI right now
Someone cares
Wouldn't report this without figuring it out
Get on air
Before you knew over the documents
So what we're working with Joey is in the Christmas
Spirit it's the Lord's prophet
Indeed so what are your thoughts so far
In what way would an NBA for
The antifa members to call civil rights
Civil unrest
Any legal legal action abilities
Cuz crime and NBA's don't cover that
That would be first of all
Alright what have you sign this non-disclosure agreement for the murders you're about to commit
Now that's a Contract Killers
But have them sign an NDA
In this context what it would be is
Absolutely
Causing deaths causing property damage
Potentially overthrowing the government
If you have them sign in NBA that only makes you more
Rite Aid no one wouldn't know when you would do that
You still got some sort of deniability but if it's like
Also I'm going to put my signature on here telling you to commit crimes
Completely forgot what I was going
I blank
No
Linda sarsour
You know the NBAA NBA that's Alex
There
Tournament March Madness is amazing the ndaa Runza
A very amazing truck cuz I do my impression of the NBA
Snitches get stitches
Exactly this is
Medium is next clip
Talked a little bit more about these documents
He gets into
Some complaints
About what
Is doing today
Documents
This never ends is
That's the end of
The interview with the gun store owner who maybe had a Bible thrown at
Maybe
Probably never ends never ends
He's trying not to get that Bible throat
Incredible
Rally Pro Trump rally
Cuz if they are you staring at their finger on the trigger
I just can't do it
So there's a video of Owen Shroyer from a couple months back where he went to a
There was
A rally that would be put together about Katie
That's a woman who was accidentally killed
By an illegal immigrants
Who's gone
Fired and hit the ground everybody was like
F****** crazy that was a freak accident
That's crazy and he ended up being
Not guilty because
He wasn't guilty of murder
Yeah and so people had a reactionary rally about that
And so I watched the entire video there's just a bunch of people who have shields
Owen Shroyer from getting through
Yeah I'm are there standing there and behind the people
Brooke Shields
Has a rifle
He has a point downward he hasn't pointed downward and his hand is towards the trigger
It's unclear if its fingers on the trigger or not
But it is near where the trigger is
Like one of the guys with the shield
Are you scared
You're shaking
Probably wasn't even
Instead of gun is later on
He's like you guys have guns
Second Amendment
Expect that from you
Blazy anytime somebody has a pro-gun rally or like
Hands down the idea that this guy was brandishing the gun
He wasn't
Just having a gun brand
Just for fun I went through a bunch
Videos of open carry rally
At least 15 images of people carrying a gun exact
Play the same way.
A lot of people doing
They were also brandish
Their weapons
They are saying that the legal definition of brand
Threatening someone to directly with a gun
It was pointed at Owen Shroyer and it wasn't
Legal definition of probably I don't know
Weird I don't care enough because I found
Exactly the same behavior
Being done by people Healthcare.
I just
Reverse
Wish I did
That
Shaw
The bully knowing that I just felt guilty that I just can't handle it more
These people are the scum of the earth literally funded by
And then
Dozens of countries
I gave billion dollars
Does the spirit cooking Aleister Crowley
I guess that's how the cow ate the cabbage
So the only thing I really want to bring out of that cuz we go over this all the time
Collaborate
A very unfair characterization of what
He did to survive
If you want to paint him in the worst
Possible light
He went along with his godparents
When they went and
Took possession
From people who are already been taken to camp
Skull
Somehow it
Traitor to the Jewish population
Or that he rounded up Jews
Is a storage lien accurate
And Alex uses back
ABC news interview to defend himself
Selectively edited
Just the parts
What sound
Make Soros sound the most
And that's the reason people take issue with
His betrayal
What was Alex
It wasn't very anti
Who's pretty anti-putin
Exactly
Politician
And Ukraine
Was being ousted from Power
Is now
And that's the reason that he he brings that up as an example
George Soros didn't overthrow their government he may have given some support
To financial support or logistical support to
Movements that already existed their butt
That doesn't mean you overthrew the government
In the same way he didn't crash economy
Play the stock
Malaysian plane
Is the equivalent of
Or something like that is absurd and you know what dates back to
The Rothschilds
Do you know about this
Oh my God
Okay I might have to pull up a couple notes Here
Nathan Nathan Rothschild
It was the Battle of Waterloo
It was a situation this is the story that's told over and over again
Messenger
Battle of Waterloo
And was going to lose
He was able to get the message back
Nathan Rothschild
Who is able to use that information
To trick people into
Stock market
So he could buy everything up
Right right right
The truth of it is
That
Comes from a 1940 Nazi
Propaganda
Of course of course
Why would
The Nazis
Statutory
Set story legitimately has
No historical basis
Outside of this movie
From 1940 that Hitler Commission
It was the first
Piece of Nazi propaganda
That was put out
Official
Production
At the problem with girdles
Mega Mega Movie lasting effects so that mentality persist to this day
And Alex is manifesting
In terms of George Soros
In his idea that he shorts these Market
Play in order to
Destroyed
We'll just
Comparison just like Steve Carell in The Big Short was the one who caused the financial crash right like that
That worked
Are we going to know I didn't
I have no I had a note of the name of the movie and I wanted to get it right so I didn't sound like an idiot
The Nazi propaganda from 1940s called die Rothschild Waterloo
I believe it's
De Rothschild
That's something
Anyway the point is another example of a mother
But it's just another example of classic anti-semitic narratives
Flanders that have perpetuated over and over the years
Metallica
22in is a piece of his world
And is a piece of what he believes about the global
Anyway
Going to get worse
Was Alex going to screen some more about George Soros complaining
It's somehow these
I'm in 30 seconds later
Slanders George Soros
In a legal way
Because of his free speech
So it's really ironic that he's complaining about these things while manifesting
What gives
Can cover
Enjoy it
It gets a little lamb
Alex Jones made it out the George Soros isn't was a Nazi collaborator
It's not even a bad you know what, Danny
Probably Charlie Sheen
And I'm like wow
Not that they would have killed him if he didn't do it
They would have killed him
If they would have figured out who he was
The little different
He was rounding up to
Position is
I'm not going to lift a finger up
I'm going to go help the Nazis
Help them
Worse than the Nazi
Point of order
It's not Soros
I'm calling you
Because you're so much like stranger old people today
Deep creep you're looking
Where do they get the
Creepy Town Alex
Are you really ready to go on another ramp
About the appearance of a Jewish person
At least he's got a track record
I mean
That time on the bad ones
Do you really need to know
No
Ate ate something that was tied up in pizza
The gate
Cystic
Experience
Where people have like a model
And stuff like that may pretend that they're eating
Parts of their body
Sushi thing but he just elevated to another creepier level
Great I believe Maria
The artist was involved in some of that stuff
That's why Alex has he
Satanic cooking with breastmilk or mental
Or something like that
But who Among Us is not
What's more likely is more likely is that there is like similes of Mensa
Which
I would like to remind Alex of uber
You are exactly right.
Did not need to know it's all it's all accepted only people care about because
Artistic wingdings doing dinner party
It's basically like if you're really rich
You don't want to have a Murder Mystery Dinner Party
If you're poor you also don't want to have a burger
But if your me
Let's do it
I want to invite over three dinner party once and I end up having
Play two characters cuz I'm going to show up and the other didn't
Murder Mystery Dinner
No I was like friends having a Murder Mystery Dinner Party
Carillon behind
About
Cultural psychology
Add just understands it
He thinks he's going to beat you
Jew
Out of
Mines
And look at that narcissism
Smile
Alex Soros smiling
Big Bad Wolf
That makes sense munchkin and added sugar
Give me a break
Sure
I'll give you a break
Did you take that bar no I knew that was coming so we only think I'm going to break you did it before I could
Stinks
It stinks bad
Well I mean that you look like it's not as overt as the drunk on the children's block
You're a backstabber
Even in that language even throughout that last clip he's talking about
Alex Soros is appearance
He's relating that
Who is
Which means that he's thinking about them the same way
Ugly it's not
Maybe it's not
And maybe it's more Alex
Doesn't understand how smiles
That's possible because he doesn't know how to
Experience human Joy maybe it's just
Like maybe that's more what it is never seen Barons teeth
There we go
We just figured out the way hold on I don't care I don't care I've seen pictures of Alex Soros my
I don't think it looks all that creepy
Young and rich or if you're rich
Yourself I don't give a s*** like
Send him a lot of it comes from
I wish I could
I think a lot of it comes more for my self-righteous bulshit
Wherein I am filled with loathing
For me
Jealousy
Sauropod
Add point
The Battle of Waterloo I did
So I just introduced the
Documents
Even from the jump you can tell it's kind of weeks over to the Linda sarsour
Narratives are going to leave your women
Because they wanted slave your women and then getting into Soros screaming about like
Launches into a
And so you know it's fun though is that he's using rhetoric
Very similar to Jackie Mason
Which is like
I'm in the Linda sarsour and then the thing and then
It's very fascinating to me that he's even
A prominent Jewish
Absolutely not intention
Alex gets back to the doctor
Probably save himself from getting sued in about a week
And then
Proof of organized crime and terrorism
Convertible
That's why
In the Playbook
Manufactured by
B
This is huge
So the timeline that doesn't quite work
Cuz in August
Alright
So
Right
Fails
Because America
Two came together which
I don't think anybody believe
Snow
Because of the Houston
Hurricane Harvey
But I've been in August of 2017
A good
Nion what would that be
10 weeks 7 months
The laptop is yet
I don't understand how that work
Cuz it wasn't even Obama's Department of Justice
It was still there
Such a blessing to take an ovary fired Sally Yates
I don't know
I honestly don't know what that mean first of all
Good call Alex on the
If these are real
Them at all if you don't know if they're real that's clunky and
Amateurish
But
You might be in Safe Harbor as long as you don't
Renault
Overwhelmingly present them as true to your audio
As long as you avoid that you'll be
Probably lawsuit
Yes
Tell
You got to make more
If they're real
Here's what I was going to say
Here's what Alex wants to see happen if they're true
Soros and others give the documents reveal
He's already earlier said you can't give him any quarter I had obviously probably italics Joneses conception means that you got to kill him
Well obviously if they are true
No Doubt
Alex
We do agree in Asia
Certainly will. I made his statement like if you look at it from just a pure logic perspective absolutely saying a truth
Good argument as much as if true you must act
Fortunate
If Rainbow Brite
Comes to life in the form of a doll and murders my best
Yeah
You might need to ask
You must get revenge
Absolutely
I'm so
Earlier
In this episode we heard
Alex coming in from break
Do Rammstein
America which is my new favorite song I realize that later in the episode
Alex comes back from break with another ROM
Current song I think
He's getting into a
Little weird to me a little weird I'm not comfortable with it right but he gets into it
If this is so f****** funny to me
Because he missed Translate
What do hasta mean
Smoking ribs
I love you
Helping the Nazis rounded 1000
George Soros
But don't worry
So Alex says that means I hate you.
You hate me
Is Alex
If soros's love letter to the world
I mean it is
From his perspective
Besoros could sing Du Hast Mich
That's why it's so stupid Alex could probably sing it back to him
I don't think so Rose cares
Probably
Cuz he's going to get someone killed
He's going to get cirrhosis
Kids killed or something like that
But that's a little stupid
It's so bad
Also
My heart goes out much more strongly.
To all the people who are on the ground
You are being affected by
It's cruel
You know but
Misrepresenting with George Soros live through in the hall
Holocaust
I think that it's really important
Exactly what the quote was
But there's a quote I read about
Who is dealing with
Soros's experience
The Holocaust
And it was
It was something to the tune of
You have no idea what it's like
To live through something like that
None of us possibly can
At this point especially as Americans
In our exist
You better f****** are on the side of being understanding
The part that is like
I was I was just thinking that other of like
No matter how innocuous dated I have become to Alex Jones is b*******
There is never not going to be part of it
Coming after a guy who survived the Holocaust
When when
F*** you Alex you have
Nothing
Had to survive
Hiding from the Nazis
By having his family broken up
Different countries
With Ford
Papers
In order for them to survive
Alex Jones was a s*** head
In Rockwall Texas wealthy suburb of Dallas
Text with 150 women before the age of 16
And
Even if you cry talk is true
Can you imagine the f****** monsters emotional toll it would take on you
To be like
I'm going to survive at all costs
Means that I'm going to do whatever it is I need
Deserve
And now I'm
Listen in all of the
This f****** a truck but I don't take
I don't I don't give a goddamn
Holocaust
Go fuc yourself
I don't really think that he had to adjust his morals all that
What Alex says is true
To be true
Still be like
F*** you Alex you're living in a horror movie
That you would stand up for yourself or you would run or something like that
Human beings
We know that
Probably not going to have
No
More prone to survive at any cost
Then we'd like to imagine like I'm enough to have
Parent who's able to get you forged documents who is willing to take you in as fake
You being there song
Yeah why would you upset the status quo
Running and hiding
When you are
13 years old and put in that situation
It's completely absurd
It's it's
Then it's Menace level whatever George Soros has done in his life I'm sure
He's not a saint
But they are largely just like
Capitalism
Yeah sucks but that's capitalism
All of it's irrelevant to what he had to endure when he was a
Like a preteen
The young team
Logo
It makes me so mad George Soros
No
When someone's being made out to be like the most evil person in the world
Especially based on this sort of like
Misrepresentation
The backstory it just makes me so mad
Sew-ins next with Alex Jones but he said earlier it's these documents are
True
Now Alex Jones
Into suggesting a
Couple possibilities
About these.
Operator
Document
He has people
He has
Heavy quotes
People are the antifa Alex thinks that they're soros's foot soldiers
Adidas dress in Black
Who are
Little bit
We have bruising
During Halloween dresses like a Nazi
Maybe that hat
Especially
Sandra Bullock
Terrorism
Declared terrorist by Homeland Security
What is all types
Bombshell
Show me what is a forgery someone took what they said and done
I just look
I look forward to urinalysis
Possibility
Surreal
Which it is
Or it's someone who knows
So much
About antifa
Put this together as a elaborate brilliant but only
In order to prove what antifa really is about
So if I understand correctly Sandra Bullock
Almost a year.
Nobody believed she is actually a nut
Is a nut
So if I understand the possibilities correctly
It's either they're true
For their spiritually true yes but one is a fraud
Yeah but
What is also correct right and he doesn't really
Are all that much
Even if it's a fraud
He's been saying course of what we're seeing here already Alex's
Confronted
Information
He is deciding like
And I didn't
Really blew it On Keepin On
Should have gotten in on the ground floor that I think he's kind of wrestling with this a little bit like
Do I jump on this
Music
I got cover my bases what you did earlier said if it's true
Now we'll see we'll see how this goes along
Rochester Pops in for a minute
Phone call
And the makeup tips
T.i. still mad at Banning but he has this to say which is just a delightful break from the
Narrative that were on
I hear nothing
And where are you it was only days ago when Alex Jone
The climb in the ring with Alex Jones
Is
The demon spawn why do we hear nothing but
I'm going to double down
I will be Alex
Jones this second I'm laying down the challenge to Jake also known as
Only seconds ago on your screen
Million-dollar
I'm not riding with me I will be Alex Jones is
Checking my guess the boys house
Cojones to face.
It's going to be it's going to be Rodger Stone and Alex Jones taking on the roles of Macho Man Randy
Savage and Hulk Hogan in the dungeon of Four Horsemen
WCW the news of all the
Everything that I have ever seen in this entire year that we have spent doing this
The only thing I am sure of it
Is Rodger stone is living his best life absolutely assuming especially that closed
Your testimony
Some committee like I hope that
I imagine he probably spilled
How far is it from
Free of legal obligations they're not
Nobody's going to do this
Billion dollars in for a long time
Be really excited to shoot promo on Jake
A reason
You can ring with Jake Tapper
Drip drip by virtue of age you going to work your bag
Stocks
It's dignity
What group has it
The other doesn't
Tom Arnold
Experienced when Mike cernovich and Alex Jones were trying to fight him
F*** yes I will absolutely
I have dignity
If you beat me up we make money for charity I don't give a s***
Oh that's
Dignity
I just
The only character in our
Sevierville that I am like actively like
Alright dude your women is
2018 the first 11 days so far me that I do think
Going to get out okay
I think he knows something
He has a piece of information that he's even hiding
In terms of like he has some safety
I think he has a long list of things
Absolutely there's something there
I do agree with you I enjoy his job David
I enjoy his freedom
Clearly doesn't give a s*** about the narrative
I'm not in the petulant way of a Steve pieczenik raised like
I'm trying to get to what I want
Yeah let's roll with the punches dude I got what I got time I'm not doing anything but this is something that comes back over and over again in my
Meijer
Analysis
I keep coming back just like all these people are are mammoths
And they're all evil
The zombie parade but there's different degrees of principle
In them and it's fascinating to me because I sincerely believe
Did Steve pieczenik probably believe most of the
The stuff
At least what
Be kind most of the stuff
That he
And there's a there's a much lower incidence
What's of the like race narrative
Generally speaking
There is just
Fear of the intelligence state
It's full of s*** bunch.
Hook being fake
Vegas being
A fake butt
The rest of it he's
You can do within the realm of like a guy who has a point
Yeah don't just seems like
Something but he also he also really wants to have a good time
Rodger Stones chaotic
Living his best life
Yeah and I love it and Alex's
Drunk evil
No bass nothing
Absolutely no Center.
He's just evil evil
So now we jump back
Into the neck
We get back into the
The the
Alex Jones
Discusses
In the area
Panda
Document
Hair on the back of my neck stand up
Remember
8 years ago vomiting office about a year-and-a-half
We got documents from
Federal Marshals
And then when I
Police officer
In California
Information
What's exact center
I know how to look at
I don't think
That your conclusion
Matches your support for your conclusion
Any sense at all
Someone else contacted me
From California who sent me
Slightly different document
PLC was behind it
Therefore
I know.
Google doc out there
And sent it back to me
B*******
There's a lot of capabilities
In terms of vibe
Fake things
Back here and Alec reiterate
Position that he emailed a little bit earlier in the show and I just want to play this again
Cuz we got a track
His perspective
This is
Maybe 20 minutes into the third hour on these
I read over these new ones are so huge
Either somebody super smart
Well we can already roll that up
George Soros
That quarterback
So that's
It's exactly
Soldier is real for real
I read these documents
Withholding a number of these thoughts for a specific reason
You f****** tea
I'm not teasing because I ate this is sort of a lead into this next clip
There's a very important
Holding a piece of information.
These documents
Paris
Fortune
Washington Post
This is real
This is a Smoking Gun because we know their funding sources
New York Times on November
Starting November 4th
We're allowed to 20
Kill the cops this is what they push
I want to refuse fascism. Org
That's not on there I read their front page it really just seems more about
Refusing to being out in public notice being out
There's a bump is a listing of events
A listing
Protest
It's like there's one coming up
Chicago on the 14th
An abortion rights
Pictures of people with signs and what-have-you picture of people dressed up like the
I tried to find any invitations
I mean I've even explored Democratic socialists
I've been to their website of you are officially a Democrat
As much as anybody there are at least
There's not even anything
Violence being entitled because of the evils of capitalism or anything like that
You and me
Baby word baby
Very violet
Clearly I have never done
That
My dude
How do you feel about that
Everything I've ever seen unfortunate Zack
Yeah
What's going on here
What's up
Fortune be like is there a is there a thread going on about these documents
There wasn't must have been like earlier than the day before
What I did find is
Lots of
A lot of black stuff
A lot of very yet but most of the threads there are full of
Racism people just telling stories
A lot of fake stuff
Footboard
I was just checking on Pole
I've only gone today
Nevermind okay
You do be too specific
But also there's a lot of it is a
I don't want to say anything negative
I don't want our website to
But also
I don't think that's a
I think generally do not go there
And at the same time like there's
There's a certain sort of
I don't know it's not admiration but more like respective
Hey man
Free Speech can go too far but it's still free speech I guess I don't know what to say
With only a very few
Instances where I
Agree with that
You've got this and I'm going to use as a slight cliffhanger
Have to go to the bathroom
We are going to make it make
Incredibly rare intermission
Alex Jones
It's presenting as either real or created by someone
Music apps
He happened to find on 4chan
Where does he go with a narrative
Find out when knowledge fly Preserve
Castle
Bareback sorry about that
F*** you Jordan
Squires
Controlling a bladder
We're not professionals we are amateurs
Qualify for the Olympics that is a very good point
Now I wish there was an Olympics got it
You know what you know how Sports
Category in this year's Olympics
64 South Korea like they have something like that right let's go to go to South Korea at this point
Saw that be great
If you're just joining us
So we've established that Alex Jones
Unfortunate researchers have
And he's presenting them as either
Kids
I hope her accident going to 4chan
He's next.
Rex Chapman has dunk
Sunday is a great job trying to work on the opioid crisis and we appreciate if God bless your ex cabin
Where's the next clip
Tell you my man
The Steele dossier
Bulshit
More and more true everyday
The documents he has just found on 4chan
Probably
The material in the Russian dossier is too old
Nope
Definitely not
Documents.
Non-disclosure document
And contract
Typos mean it's true again
We go back to your immediate response
Something I wanted to bring up and I'm so thrilled you picked up on it immediately
The idea of an MBA in this situation is ridiculous
It is only something that someone trying to slander or speaker somebody
Once we get into the details of what is intestine
There should be red flag
Literally everywhere
He brings never heard on the show
The researcher
He gets into breaks out
He starts off on a decent foot
He trips
Almost immediately
But his perspective on his is first
Look
Get the documents
I kind of agree with
Please
George soros's
Alexander Soros
The Smoking Gun and
Figure out whether or not these are authentic
What
It sounds like
Absolutely
You're not you're misrepresenting comments that people have made in order to build up a narrative and now this
Obviously fake document his come out
Happens to mysteriously match
Deepfake version of things that you've experienced
And I like
That's the thing that's
Gets me is like
These the idea of any anytime I hear something that sounds like some
Something that I want to be a mediately like
F*** off I'm going to do as much research as I can because if I want this
To be true that means I'm going to be taken in by these messages online
Do you want to come over and have sex and my response back block
This is a trap that's the kind of mentality that really should be
Call this researcher
But like I said he has a second of it
What do you mean really Falls over
He goes along with whatever Alex's version of it is
This is
Buck Michael Steele
A lifelong spy
No I didn't say proven track record at a great history of something
4chan never heard of it
So you might be asking yourself about this
What is a story
I am actually asking myself that
Steel back on what is
Spirit locking or whatever
It's complicated
Evans next clip we will get into the
It's backstory
But first
Alex Jones
Pugn
The very idea
But African-American communities
Have a right to a voice
Craigslist
I apologize
Great
I think they collaborate
Baltimore riots
Black lives matter
So
Stuff posted are probably but
Traveling around the United States
So this guy who
Very big misrepresentation
22 program
Proof of
Of his money
Looking for a certain proof that his brothers may be involved in something
She took a picture of
I wish your cell phone in person before chance
That's a s*** story
I would say
4 number
I'm sold so far
True
There's a guy
Yep
Searching for what
Find these documents
Wright State of being like
Probably a good idea to call the FBI
Probably a good idea
Pictures of these
And post them
To a place where people troll like crazy
Postalease
To the most
Lying place there's ever been
I'm going to write a legitimate
As opposed to just
You know he's not interviewing anybody that's one of his insurance or his research guide
I don't understand Harrison something I've never heard of on the show before
And I don't you said it was Harrison
Smith earlier
You did
I don't know what that to be true is Harrison something I don't I don't know Batman
Little bit of
A Bridge Too Far
Yeah this idea of that backstory
I've been I've been unfortunate enough times to know that
Threads that get started on there
Thursday
A lot of big old titties threads on there but there's a lot of
There's a lot of threads were people are trying to basically workout
I got work out but like some sort of
Doing an exercise in
Conviction doing some sort of like emursive interactive fiction Experian
4chan is like an open mic with the worse
First people
On the planet
Kind of just like an open my
Yeah
So anyway there's a little bit more that Harrison w
Explain about
These documents
PennDOT to get into it
And it's an action document from the friends of democracy which is a
Pact
B
That
Its mission statement is to get money out of politics
I did not even bother
But
Hard pass
But this is action BWI 04 1815
04 18th is April 18th
Started and it says that the action oversight Committee of the French democracy has determined
Saturday operation
To seize as much momentum as possible from current civil unrest in the Baltimore area
Friendly officials in various administrative agencies
He says that says
Literally says that
It does
Literally
Confirm something that is literally zelk
Okay alright of describing everything
How do you act
Going to have a specific
That's not a problem at all
Ironically
What you do is agitprop
Baltimore officials and law enforcement
That is not
I confirmed it all
Man man oh man
Alex seems to have zero grasp of
What this segment is going to be about
Like his intern does all of this research
He's done it no leg work in terms of Journalism
You know what you get documents like this
There's a Hatter on there
Who created
There is an organization can you reach out to the organization
For ComEd
You try and see my crazy real document that
Came out of your organs
Of course not
That that by the way
Spoiler alert
That information is not going to be addressed on this episode
Butt tattoo in there but they've tried to work into the narrative is
The cops are in
Which makes perfect
Right that was the cops
Commit
You started the plant Jordan
I'm getting it now and ironically you're starting
Got it
I'm so in the next clip Alex takes a little bit of a little bit of
I don't know if I'd call it an adolescent step
It's not a baby step it's not. But it's a step of some sort words
I just outright
They have signatures at the bottom
That don't seem like they come from different hands
I need to restart this
Because
It's still I believe these are
He's still hiding behind the
I know they are still like legal there still
Wiggle room is doing
Material
Signatures at the bottom
That all seems like they come from different hands would be hard to fake all these
Left
There's a bunch of spinach
And let me be clear I was I saw these documents I went and looked and read all of them and there is an
I'd like
Yeah they're not like
Photocopies of something
It isn't like the idea is
This guy who has a loser brother who has money
Parking
Straight up documents
That were hand sign reliable
Rick
Not not Alex Soros doesn't have the original copy
Course I miss guy has the
Right
I think the only the only thing
Thing I can tell you for sure right now is that this in turn will not be on arrogant Alex's clearly
He just gave every employee hasn't says they're getting new shows like Oprah
Basically
Sorry I was getting around show
I know he wants to go 24 hours and he probably will at some point but not a good idea
Like just in terms of
Views on YouTube
The massive drop-off
Between Alex Jones and David Knight or room
Alex cannot imagine
Hiring somebody who is a Potential Threat to his
He's kind of like a John Cena
In some ways
Yeah let me spell that out for you I just want to live in a world where Alex
Has Tina has Alex's face
Plaster for a long time John Cena has had like a narrative the storyline that
He's been in this like I run the show
Yeah I'm the big guy here
And I'm waiting for someone
Come along and Dethrone
I would love it
If someone came along if you throwing me
The courses behavior isn't in line with that he
You know he
Insist on winning over hot new people and stuff like that
But I wish someone would come along and be better than me
Meanwhile everyone is better than him
Like legitimately would be a way better version of Alex than Alex
Because he wouldn't fall for this kind of s***
You wouldn't fall for a lot of Israel
Which is why he
He can't be
Recently gone back and watch some scary stuff and he's wrong a lot of the time
But it's such a breath of fresh air
Like an Infowars logo behind
Yeah cuz he's
Nice
Sounds like
He seems like
I'm not I know I have
Just f****** with
I think of any any other employees
Of their past that I
I don't think there are any everything that we've looked into Rapaport everything
Everything we've looked into about Jakari Jackson
Post Infowars like
You seem like a pretty cool dude man we can hang out
Even though there are a lot of
But I'll be there in
Get on to the next one
Harrison
Who will have his own show
Gibson Court believes to be the most
Troubling
In this
Most important one
It's post
It is
Ideal objective outcome
Civil unrest of Martial law like policies for Baltimore
Literally
Inspire police response
Now I ask you
Who the f*** would put that in a contract
I don't understand
Explain to me why you would put that at
Do you know what what I just signed a contract with my with my new employer
My entire job is
Murdering everybody who comes into the office wow
This is so happy
Did such nonsense any idea that okay so if you if you want to go down Alex Jones
You have to believe there is a shadowy global trying to create these
All of these race war riots and what-have-you in Orchard hours
Secretly
Why the f*** with this organization that allegedly has 18 billion dollars of George Soros his money right
So f****** stupid that they put in a document
Literally no reason here's our end goal
Let's try can get people to fight with the police
Well one part of it is that
He is fighting against
The most incompetent
Organization
Ever
Turn the history of ever it is an organization
Equivalent to mr. Magoo
Air quotes
You are
You are going to bed
It don't we all have to choose our own subjugation like
That's nonsense
Are you sure yes
Have you ever sign the Apple iTunes license
I have
Done great
Done
Completely forgot something I meant to do earlier
Sign the Apple iTunes group
Explain to you what
Zach
Narrative
Gotten through
The first day
Straight up a punch
I feel like I might have given away a little bit too much
Do all of our live viewers on Twitch
It'll be released as a podcast I have no qualms about what's going
On right now
At this point right now Alex Jones
Is going to explain
You are possessed
Course
Harrison
He's an amateur
Time in India
Alex Jones
Is annex
Can we get Rodger Stone back
I want to punch
Here's another interesting real or someone
Profile
Impressive that they were able to fake tan
Black lives matter Seattle
Initiative
So again
You still skirting
Like
Like legal issue
Probably
In terms of being like
This is real or
Realer than real
Ted not beer
If it sucks clip
Discusses there was a New York
Times full page ad that got put out
About protests
And advocating violence at all
They have come and gone
Sam's Fannin
Route no real virus
Because happened
Snow White
November 4th narrative that Alex is pushing it was a bunch of bulshit
That we can have about the massive amount of money and
Such that is spent on protests that have
Done
It looks conversation to have later
You're coming from WhatsApp
Bring that up is because
Discusses this
New York Times
Full page
And
I can't take this clip
Is being anything other than Alex Jones
Pussyfooting around the idea of outlawing protest
What's 1000
Is word for word from that
This really quick it word for word
Is not from
No it's not similar to the ad at all
It's not similar to refuse fascism. Org at all
Escalation of civil unrest in the provocation of hostile to say hostile
Law enforcement
Which is interesting in contact indicator
Philosophy is built around
They're coming for our women
Well and more ironic evens it on inauguration weekend there were so many videos of him drunk
Screaming
Fixing that I noticed
Is that his
Interns language like that
The things that he's describing of like
This is house
This is what they're saying
It's all couch
Military language
That makes sense as military language
Only watch
Movies
About military life
Is all of this nonsense buzzwords
2 News weather
You're just
You're just giving up the game
This is all
Fake bulshit
Uat watch
London Has Fallen
Yeah
So in this one more
In this next clip Harrison gets to talking about another thing that you learn
From reading these documents
Little surprising
Get off my plane
Different
Sorry
The funding how they're paid
On this guy who the documents belong to
Which seems to be $26,000 for one person has one event
That sounds right
Consider that
Thousand dollars
For one person at one of them if you multiply 26
Right
You get $18
I guess so
Seems like seems like a dumb money
Seems like a nouveau-riche
Buying a couple boats
Oh man
Are you shiting me
I mean I don't want to be involved in treason necessarily I don't be involved in that I want to do Mexican
Terror
In Spectre
Oh okay it was all fake I take it
Norah O'Donnell
A billion next time
Actually hit a brother up
Need 26 Grand
At that point
Alex hears this
He's like
Alright that contract says 20
6 G
That is absurd
Can't be like
Come on man
You've got a pivot a little bit the terms being like
He decides to makeup ideas
This guy's brother is
Create
Getting tire fixed
Right must be
Who created entire picture
Turn around like
Why he must be getting this amount of money
Is this
On the sheets
You can even find these all I might post all the images of these on our website
I don't know why I would though you can say I don't know why you can find him if you look for him there
Level seven
Which is super easy to fake
To not be true Alex Jones decided this guy is level seven
In terms of the organization as if that means
He's a Mason he knows what that means
So this next clip is in
Entirely
Jumped
Fantasy scenario
Must be just keep in mind
This is Harrison and Alex Jones
Just making stuff
Jesus Squad
Operator
Are the operator level operator
Actually have them of what they're involved in
Only level 8 people.
Secret codes
Someone never end
The taxes and all that stuff on there and it doesn't mean it handles it on
Your
It does preposterous
What do you think
Okay so this guy's level 7
So that means he's below the adjutant how are the six
Who are the six levels levels does it go higher
20 levels
It's probably it's probably indefinite
Soros
Level 69
Finally got my five out of you
Just the very idea that this guy's layabout loser brother who happens
To just leave
A
Let's call it
Treasonous lead damning document
Laying around the house
Happens to be level
Like on the seventh level of this scam
Sasquatch
That's level seven
Would be I can only think of maybe two levels beneath
Logistic
Well I mean level one
Right like we're dumb dumb
Do you have
Killer crab
Right like that's how that works right
That's what I've heard
Okay
Level three is you join the Masonic Lodge
Level four
Is you leave the Masonic
Level-5 is you go against your programming
If you snitch
Level 6 is you go against your
Against your programming
Against your stitches
Right
And then give him stitches level 7-Eleven
Lucky Number Slevin actually
I don't understand it I don't I don't think that there is room within
Logistics
Of the organization
There is a bad for there to be literally Seven Levels
Before
A squad General in the
I think so I think it would be for private Hugo and then others
And then your gender
Private
Colonel or Colonel might be Colonel might be above General
General you know what I'll be honest
I know nothing about the military
I know nothing about that organization
Kernels and
It's fine cuz we're making this up as we go along cuz so is Alex about
Approved practices which
Below the neck and above the belt
Probably say props was just means weapons
Not your food over it's all in there just following instructions not doing anything you know
For themselves
I guess he'll Alex's Alex's idea of
What's going on is they just
Like you get
A plate of food
Knock it over right because it's in your torso area and it's fine
Middle
I don't think it'll happen
I've never seen you be assaulted Mark was literally ever
Yeah
I have no idea but
I mean
Probably more like
So in the next one time and all the old ladies
Joke is on level 7 you get the kit
Music
Who is that in the NBA it's too much of a motion to do right
Punch somebody
No one's the wiser
How do you like a mule
I feel like Bruce Lee is way higher than levels of faces such b*******
Enter the Dragon levels
Every single piece of analysis of these documents
There's nothing responsible about this
It's it
It's literally
Alex Jones
I can't be
Clear about this
The reason I started this episode with
Episode like that thing
From Christmas Eve is
You can see how f******
About missing the boat all right this comes up and he's like
I got to go in let's go
What one foot
Nah this is confirmed she doesn't matter
Cuz I'm not level 7 but I can jump
As it goes along your seeing him losing
If this is true
And now it's becoming more of course this is f****** true
He's getting
So in this next clip
Alex Jones
For the longest time
His wondered
Goldie's protest why doesn't anyone talk to me
Got everyone drinks first
First Take podcast history
Took
11 days
So if he's wondering why
Talk to me
It's in the document
What other operatic shopping
Winning crowd
Play acting
If it works really good
It's just obvious
I watched so many videos of him out of protest
Like I ordered his people out there and most of the time they're like
Yeah but that Cindy a talk it's just people in like ski mask
You have like an Owen Shroyer trying to get
Start to break the line of those Shield Ray
You suck
Did they have shields or was it more like just like
Little signs of dead
No thank you no
Then that smart
This is way better
But if we're going to talk about superheroes and the way it is
Describe things
I think
Democratic socialists in ant
Antifa
Is like the Captain America
We're about when you throw it
It's not like Roman Reigns Dean Ambrose and Seth Rollins
Alexia
I just think we should
No thank you Owen Shroyer on them
Dana in
Like before the show like an hour and a half or so before the show I was watching
The video cuz I wanted to figure out the truth
About
An hour and a half before the show
Seven and a half hours ago give or take
Because I'm trying to figure out that that narrative
Someone putting a gun on until I watch the video of them
Is David Knight was gay
Commentary
What they're doing
Zoom
You're not doing great now
Do it more boards
I can't do I don't speak.
Voice I'm just saying
Be as boring as you can be these
Leftist
Slay
I don't know I don't I don't
Buc-ee's
Standing in formation
And Owen troyer's cameraman walking closer to them and back and close the Diamondback
And making it appear that
You being in some way her and Mike cernovich doing these videos
Where he has like his
His selfie stick
Camera coming back
There's like 10 people behind him just
Standing there a getting into a protest
And him walking
And then following behind him so they eat
Double back
And him being like they're harassing me they're harassing me
Yeah like
Definitely
It's a load of horseshit
Iblog
Google
Well bit because I'm there
I get
Why people don't want to talk
Alex Jones
I'm so the fact that it confuses him so much
A me so much that he's confused like
These people want to talk to
Fun I like
I like a good time
Pure personal insecurities
No he thinks it's that liberals can't express their positions and they're all brainwashed Dum Dums
Bentley like once you get he does all that stuff take a little personal
If you build up a narrative of
NBA
People from
Talking to you
Paranoid
Personal insecurities right
It sure I mean it's like the
That's the sad guy who has like a
Conspiracy about why his
Broke up with him
Back to me
Efferent mean that's still like
The NBA keeps people from talking to
Is still
On some
Mark
More interesting
It's less interesting to me then
Nmda
Keeps people
From talking about
Booking
Trying to get martial law
Write any f****** idiot real life
Exposed
Well do you know what the biggest issue in American history
John Wilkes Booth
Signed an NDA
True
Well known fact
So it is next with Alex Jones County
Kind of sucks it up
Quesadilla
Really really believe these documents
More than 10 countries
Nazi war criminal
The cops
Address for
Harrison other key points things we should recap
Marshall Law three years ago back in 2015
Which state is Obama
What's funny
Didn't work
I don't feel pretty good about that as we all know America definitely stop
I think we've all come
Come to an agreement
Trump has a 100% approval rating
Can't we stop fighting with each other and we just
Accepted
That he's
Prosper
Galaxy
So what are your thoughts
Where are your thoughts at
Dude
Listening mission of just gone
Now you guys
You guys have your fun like
Like this is going to see a
Bad improv group like Second City first year
Class
Is like
We're going to do a bar show to go
Yeah they're like nah dude I'm out
Okay
Well
It's good then we only have a few more Clips. They're only going to see gas and a few more time
OK Google about as much
Alex Jones
Information from
If it's true
Get weird with a narrative
It's time to pray
He does not let the fourth hour host
Get on air
Who's going to host
The 4th
I don't know
Because they don't get in
I think it might have been Owen Shroyer and then he just does the the War Room
I'm not entirely sure
Alex Dixit out
Cuz he is just f****** he's got a bee in his Bonnet here and he's going
He says two things at the end of this episode that I think are like
You're losing
This is f***** up
The first one
The groups that are literally when they launched
When we go out in the ocean start
Each person supposed to shoot five cops tonight
Alright fair enough
So if I understand this correctly
It's in it's in the contract you should five tops of night
Also
The cop
Unions are in on this
Absolutely
It's nonsense
Such nonsense
Giving me information
Okay all right
Well I mean you want to
Routing number
Berkshire
There's always an even number of antifa members
Another one gets stabbed
But you also have to kill
An odd number of cops right right right
So that you can always
Have a prime number
Just to chat room
We will do the
The
We have got it setup we have a Discord thing going on
We are knowledge fight on Discord
So if you want to get your Discord together like I don't know if you have to download it or just getting the count
We are knowledge fight on their friend
So just wanted to call in
I'm out here
Is the second thing that Alex says.
Stupid
Funny guys hit on you
Bright
He's basically asking for like sex off
Of course
I don't know
A women do together f****** start seducing Democrats at bars so I can get your formation or something
Yeah there is a Discord Channel 80s knowledge B is the name of it
So what
Monitored Alex Jones is
Is website
I went to infowars.com
No no
I wanted to get from
See how his audience
Responded
This narrative
He was spinning
His idea that he had
Prove
Connection between Sora
Create all this Division and what have you and they were like
None of us are women
Hear that you're the guy pulled like 10 comment
I read them to you
And I haven't read them since yesterday when I told them I'm going to have to try and censor myself
Oh boy
Are we going to are we going to get a lot of a lot of n words
Tossed around
No but you will get some weird
Very clear race
If your European Americans were aware of the number of black riot
Tax dollars that breed black
Nope people taxes are just to pay for the criminality the corruption of the damage blacks 22nd City
The percentage of black on white violence this nonsense with end immediately
Great your someone named Salisbury
Soldier
If these documents are legit Alex Soros and his daddy should be a green light
To every Patriot in the nation
Someone with more technical skills than I should organize a watch on both
Disease so they don't leave it a moment's notice
They can be found 24/7
The tracking Soros
Some patriot who has enough will utilize this info
Right
Citizen X
Nothing will happen till summer when the climate is more African like in the Goombas can have their native elements
I had a great time tonight it's time for me to go home here is a quote from
Kimball the black love me
The black woman a piss-poor excuse for a mayor the told those Riders to go out and eat some more was on Obama
A payroll
This was all designed to embarrass the Republicans as
The country geared up for like
Haven't too long here's an extra one is from not-so-new
Is why you never catch me without my old trusty Browning 9 mm under my shirt
Thanks for the documents I just loaded I just down
Downloaded and printed for my defense attorney in the event you want to test your dedication
You're very stupid cause
That's actually
These documents
Catcher in the Rye kills a protester
Chris Potter
The other comment with left-liberal Dems
Those pesky Jews
Is a comment from
In the midst of all of that vile
There's the word
Pesky like this is like this is a Scooby-Doo right right right
Metalink
Sears
Trader Trader Slayer
Traders Slayer
Howard Hughes a hero who comments
Soros should have been Swinging From The Gallows a long time ago we all allowed to happen
Administrator
Henry Strater
Yeah there's no there's no there's no like a punctuation there
So here is a comment from last of the Patriots
If it happens again because of sorry-ass Soros and his clan
Americans will United and capture any family scum of sorry-ass Toro
They will be
Tried by the people!
They will be convicted by the people!!
By the people all caps
America America are getting very tired of the shenanigans going on in our country and we will
All caps! And get these people
Their time on Earth is getting shorter and each passing day
None will exist
Donkey
I think
The biggest thing that we're taking away from this
Is that you and I
Have more of an issue with their
Grammar. Will Exist by the end of this year and America will be a great nation again 3
Mission Point
War is on the horizon
Okay here's good boy good boy as a comment
Will someone would someone please kill both soros's
Here's a guy that's a very straightforward
He is a pretentious douche
I don't know who that is but
Sounds like
Freddie gray and Trayvon Martin were both know we're both cuz we're both completely
Coco events when nobody died
Going to
Is it
I just want you to know the reality of what people are
I would everybody got understand
The reason I'm bringing this up and
But like
The reason I'm
I'm I'm doing that I want to bring that really into focus is that this is the response
That people have
That narratives that we just laughed about
Right
A good
Hour-and-a-half
And it's absurd
There's no critical thinking skills being employed by the people who were listening
Into the show their immediate response is
Vitriol
Anti-semitism
Against blacks
Again because
We live in a world that is
Post parrot
Like that
Is legitimately hilarious
But people believe that
Lego
That wasn't real like if you were writing a
Reactions
Comments that I pulled clearly bought tonight
Of course
No it's just like it's just like it at you know as a comic I don't right
Trump jokes
Because there's
What what
What's the escalation that you can go right you know like this whole thing is beyond reality
And listen to these comments is like
That is
Hilarious
And in other people who believe that
Comfrey
What it takes
6! Is okay
What's the part of like that
! part of tragedy that's
Funny some level that is you have to kind of laugh
We never deal with the idea of the comment section
Site and I felt like this was an appropriate time to do that
Because this is all
Such b******* right and that's how these people
This is not true
Yeah it's all
Either directed towards
Anti-semitism
Flash Soros needs to die Fred suck these black people they're so stupid
Is it those are the two directions the end up going at the same time
This is a weird
Singing to I don't I don't
Think this is
It's so much as it is
Like if you
Watch AIDS
Twitch stream of
Video games
Video game twitch stream like a very popular one
Right you're going to find there's a lot of weird racist ass comment
Thankfully not ours
Because
Like for some reason comments sections are a
Nightmarish place for people who are
Clearly damaged
For them to express some sort of pain
Yeah like I don't know what to
To tell you but also at the same time
You're letting
Alex
And his ilk off the
The hook a little bit because they curate that I'm not the reason that we don't have people spewing
97 Tesla race
Watching the show live is awesome
So I'm never going to not love that
And
This is why I'm glad
That we waited a day
To discuss this narrative cuz I would have loved it
Discussed this yesterday
Clearly
You
You really
Hammered that thought
Zip
I didn't
Because
On the 10th
Yes Alex
Was reporting irresponsibly because
Still saying I believe this but not saying it's
If it's true it would be damning
Yes so you give it a day
He's he's
Couched it
Union protectively you give it a day
And the next day on the show
There's literally no reason for him not to have a definitive answer
Right because that's our research
You could just Google it
This seems to be the most important issue it would
Clearly proved
Some sort of domestic
Terrorism being carried out by your biggest enemy you have the document
He spent his whole show
He's got
All of this conversation
Taken care of
Important narratives that
You could possibly
Because this is me
The end of the Republic
Cuz we know absolutely
All of your time if this is real
I would agree with him you need to
You spend all of your time fighting against
It's the only thing to do
Right
I assume for the next
12 weeks
He's going to do this every single day
No he Treads water on the January 11th show for the first 58 minutes
Saying
Nothing of course
There's nothing
Victim narrative
Victim b*******
0 nothing
Not even related to the doctor
White people are under 58 minutes
Assessment
I remember that
And I should have read the show
Cam
Obama plan to use for the Soros funding
Race war
Martial law
Loretta
Initiative
So now he's presenting it as quickly as real
He is just
Nothing is not checked on it
Because if he had
What he would say is
We reached out to them
No comment from them at this time
They wouldn't get back to us
We reached out to the open societies and I do we read all the Alex Soros did not comment on this
Any of those things
Would be able be able to use them to his Advantage he doesn't do that he doesn't take all the steps
You didn't do any of that he just comes on air and pretends it's f****** steak documents from 4-channel real
He couches it the first day and then the next day is like there's an article up there and
Any presented as if it's real
Yeah now I thought that was
I thought that was
I had no idea
I thought you know
Okay
Alex is going to f******
Or whatever like we did this he's going to use it as a waypoint later
Considering the situation
Shouldn't have said that last clip
But if he works
Smart idea clip still works with pump
Right if you can use it for like we always do you remember when the document
Rhetoric
Trying to remember that
Remember how it was a fake hoax
On Fortune
You had a good day
Now
20 minutes later
I realized
But Alex Jones
He might be
He might be playing some angles
Okay
He might have been overdoing it
Intentionally
First of all because of that
Missing out the boat
On qanon
And because he knew
Who was going to be books
On the show the neck
Oh no
Sell me on this
The next day
January 11th
Chuck Norris's son
Sit back down
Who was the director of amerigeddon that Alex Jones is in
Is on the show and Alex Jones knew that the day before
Also Alex Jones
Keep saying throughout the show
Said he's trying to get Chuck on
He's like a little bird told me Chuck might be coming on
Play it later
I'm so
Listen
To this
Laming b*******
Crossroads of Hunter Wyatt
A near-future film of the second American Civil War
A spiritual war
Everything's fine art out there who
The real quick just to give you some contacts
All you need to know about this movie I watched
The trailer all you need to know
It's like
A gun white family
I was like
Under Siege and they're really Christian
And the bad guys mysteriously black
Course
Enchanting is got a grip on the town
Long time ago
Enough
If we close our eyes to what's going on
Praying to kill but nothing compared to the battle vest
We fight against spiritual wickedness in high places
AAA
So they spend
40 minutes of the show trying to pimp this movie
Biggest Venom
Movie promo
F*** off
Dammit
Chris Hemsworth
Pivot
Who's two stages 2013 stages
But then be part of it that I was discussing earlier about Alex Jones
Really being pissed off that he missed the boat on the last internet hoax
Is that in there too
Lakers versus not wholly preparing the audience
For this
Chuck Norris's Son movie that he knows he pimping the next
That a little bit cuz also spoiler alert that movie on DVDs being sold on infowars.com
It's being sold on infowars.com
I mean like he has a financial stake in it to a certain amount
It's crazy it's crazy
10 million dollars into night in donations by the end of January
We will absolutely watch that movie
I want the movie for free I shouldn't have said that
Also like
Somebody needs to watch this movie come on
And also when you're in the mid
Stuff like this weird Patriot
White identity
Sort of world we live in now
A little f***
Can clunky the name your antagonist
Hunter Wild
A little on-the-nose
That trailer people should watch it
Cuz there's weird spiritual b******* going on in it also like
Clearly allegorical for
Being scared of
It's crazy
I saw the movie
I thought
Three of those movies
All the movie I need to see you ever seen left
Also that that one drop in there this way out of place
We shouldn't have been raptured
That was my favorite that was why are you saying that why are you in
Are you in the story that is were raptured right
Maybe that character is delusional
But it also
Character is in heaven
No he's not an Oscar Wilde reference
They they don't even
How to chat room.
It's a it's a reference to those two words
Bobbing about being
Ian Whyte
Free
To some extent that I knew that was coming
The whole time
But it's out of a bit at the same time I believe I believe wholeheartedly in.
But Alex Jones operating system where he believed that the internet and all their scams
And their hoaxes are working
Better than him
Insecure and very pissed off about that
When this drops
You clearly f****** fake documents
On Fortune
He like I got a jump on this
I got to jump on this and then on top of that
He uses it
To push
Harder
Chuck Norris's Son movie
Also
Norris's
Suns
5 minute commercial on air
For Chuck Norris's new
Brand of water
The Water Horse
Force apologize this is taking this long but
Get through this
Perfect Buntline Cheese's
Price of tomatoes
This is worse than an admin episode of Alex Jones
To get to this ad pivot she doesn't talk about the documents at all
The rest of the show
That's it
Well that's already
Yeah it's crazy
Time to let that Never Be Shaken never
Be allowed off the hook
But he can't
You don't have to keep reminding him like
They've already got trick by that b*******
But unfortunately no one really cares all that much appreciate very much
I'd like
Auto automatic
Alex Jones
Career would be over
I think Within
Courts because of this sort of b*******
Believing internet scams
Hoaxes
Probably going
To continue
I have to assume it's not going to
Mission accomplished Banner Bhai
Yeah so I assume whatever comes next will be worth
But at least at the end of the day
Delightful in the in the
And in terms of like what he advocated for
The kill Soros and all but
At least at the end of that episode he was just saying like
A guy's a women go f*** democrats for info
And horrible it's not like
It's not violent I would rather super male Vitality on my burger then watch that
Sunnyway Jordan Weaver website.com
I always do everything for a third party
First issue that a third-party should have is
And I
I think this is the most important issue that
Is
Unaddressed today is
Equality for women
I think once we get there was over
With that
There is it like once we have equality for women
I think there's such a
Huge
Deluge of things that will change
Because of that and once you start having this conversation
Ernest said you
You can't help but have the other conversations that are equally important that
Come along
To support the trail we leave out
We need your help
Don't f****** give us any
You can't afford to
Give us
We appreciate every donation bit if you
You can't
And you enjoy the show
Jesus f****** enough
We appreciate you just listening
But if you have money
Knowledge fight
Colon
If you got money
Give it
No reason to fending you Soros give me money
Also we're on Twitter
Al.com
That's something like I use I've been sending out a bunch of like
Also if you want but
Email us at that email address
I've been
I've been told that girl
Sell them or just give them away
Email address to knowledge fight at gmail.com will take care of her too
Please do I also run Facebook
We are Drew clicks
Expandshare an episode
Liebherr review
You can do all of it I feel like the last like two or three episodes I've chosen
The person say was piece of s***
I feel really guilty
Give you the honors
Oh man needs to go fuc
I'm selves.
Episode
All days
I will tell you who needs to go f*** themselves with a little bit of that
It's the first time
I think it's maybe the first time
And I think
Important
Step for our equality
Nancy Pelosi
F*** yourself
Fair enough
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color