Alex
Birthstone colors
And I don't know anything about Alex
To be doing those two things public
Indeed for the first time ever
Chicago
Did you want to give out ticket dreads
Microsoft Belmont
Halsted & Belmont that's where we are going to be 10:30 p.m. I believe tickets are $5
Might be able to sneak in a tube baby
Beaba that's that's great we'll have some beers for folks for walk
And also hilarious comedian mcburrows will be opening up the
Can't believe we got it
Very busy schedule is flying a back into town
Still happen timing workout that way but
M a hilarious dude needs my old partner from a referral to have him
If you can
Delis
Please come out
If you don't I understand
Sonja over there
Some of our Australian peeps they don't need to come you know
Because who knows when they'll get to see you again
Like if you are around
Come out it means a lot and I do come out
It will open up the possibility of us
In the future
So this first run
Is particularly important
Villagio
How dare you
Fun fun time
That's
Someone we love
Perfect clunky with smooth transition
Congratulations
We appreciate it so much
Great rookie for the Dodgers know
38 home runs
I also I'd like to give her a congratulation
To one of my dearest friends
Congratulations on being a global at Smith
Someone sodomites
Get me a bucket of poop
Congratulations and thank you so much
Thank you so much babe
You're the best
I want to feel in the audience on how difficult this episode was to make
We're getting a lot of work done up top
This episode today was
A disaster
We met up last night
Rent a couple drinks
At the bar trying to figure out what are we going to cover
Number possibilities
And the one that I was most excited about
Was a day
I was May 31st
Bowe Bergdahl
Got the traded with some Guantanamo Bay prisoners right
Yes
I got really excited about that possibility I was like holy Schmidt I looked over on a calendar
And it turns out that that was a Saturday
So that mean
Someday when Alex Jones comes back to do his show
He's going to hurt both of those things obvious lady
He's got to talk Slenderman must going to be the best
And so I changed in with Bo Bergdahl because
The Slender Man did negotiate that.
Where we got into all this trouble in the first place exactly
I was hoping for something like that and so I get back from the bar I'm a little buzzed
Turn on that episode
I don't like
This is the craziest thing
In the world there's a lot of gas
And what it is
He's a murderer's row
Of Alex Jones
F****** lunatic
So we were talking Larry Pratt
Yaki's be had of the
Irgun loving NRA
Citizens guns or something like that they love it
We got Paul Craig Roberts
Who Alex Jones bills as the father of Reaganomics
The father of Jesus Bible is type guy
So there's that
Then
Jon rappoport
Holyshit
Cherry on top
Steve pieczenik
I'm like oh no I'd like we accidentally stumbled into the motherlode Slenderman
Don't see
You think about
Bowe Bergdahl
You know what they talk about
Elliot Rodger
The guy
Who ended up shooting up a bunch of people in California because
He couldn't get laid
Right that guy
So the whole time
A lot of the time
Just talk about Putin BJ
But Jon rappoport
And Steve pieczenik are both talking about how it was fake
Course it was and it made me so bummed
That's why I went back yet
Big big pile of bass shootings are false Flags is not a great live show
Excuse all white crime
Hey so I went back and I listen to a couple of shows the celebration of life
Well at least the pointing the finger at it but be that as it may I went back I listen to a little bit more
Actor Elliot Rodger
It'll take a week earlier Volkswagen out the gate
Really
But over the course of one episode he does anyway
I've learned a lot about his position on Elliot Rodger and it's
I can't use this for the cuz no Slenderman no Bowe Bergdahl
Like 5 hours of hours at Elliot Rodger and I don't want to tell you about it
What am I going to do
I texted you or like
I can't I can't do this I can't use this episode
Slenderman
No good luck sign
Something else but for today's episode 1
To keep up
I like just send me a f****** random date send me random
You send me a Saturday
Cuz I'm a failure
Disappointment in
And that you sent me a Saturday was August 11th
And so that's a Saturday
Thankfully
Because it's Saturday
A bunch of other episodes
Near that date show up
Indeed the search
High speed
16th of
Looking at this gas place
We might be able to make this work
I'm so
Without spoiling
We have
One of the most bizarre things that has ever happened before
It's actually this episode
August
16th 2012
The weirdest things ever
And one of them involves the other involves
A special report that Alex does
What is
Cannot wait to tell you about this starts the show this is literally
Really the beginning of the show
All right ladies and gentlemen I just got off the phone with
Garage
ABC CBS everything you are
Commented
Contacts to make a big deal out of
Show we need to get
That decision myself
Dave Mustaine
Just got off the phone with
Celebrity
Cuz no one remembers this
No one remembers I understand correctly what what happened at this time
Was Dave Mustaine
Came out
And that Obama false Flags
Well that's what you just heard from the clip remember that
Stone Rivers Dave Mustaine news
The headline of the Megadeth concert to share his instinct
Conspiracy theories about the president
Already
Grilling
You had oil my friend
In a video posted to YouTube by a fan
Video shop in put a few to buy a fan those picked up a week later by a metal news
Whose website called blabbermouth.net
Mustang pauses between songs by The Fan
For checking a Chuck Taylor in his general direction
Holy what's wrong with you
The quote
The weather then accuses the president of the United States
The movie theater in Aurora
Colorado mvic temple in Oak Creek Wisconsin
Quotes
My president
Here do you mind
Themself making himself bar
Like all serious speakers of Truth to power do from time
I'll bring this from a Grantland article license a chops here
The gun ban
Restaging all of these murders like the Fast and Furious thing down at the border and Aurora Colorado and all the people that were killed
And now the beautiful people at the Sikh temple
Pause
God
I don't know where I'm going to live with Americans going it's going
But it looks like it's
Turning into Nazi America
Right
This is fun
Because
It's strange to me that he would both
Be like Obama's false flagging all of us to get rid of guns
While at the same time being like
The 6th
People are
People are a beautiful and wonderful
Yeah we don't see that type of accept
And conspiracy theory in the same set
It's rare but Dave Mustaine
Weather
Volkswagen deicide
Cuz that's nonsense
Furious is a really calm
Complicated thing
But
Wasn't that the one where the
Actually
Gays guns away
Have you taken across the border B cutout clearly buying them for
Illegal purposes in Mexico
And ostensibly the idea was that they would have these illegal guns
Be able to roll up
The people
Who ended up taking possession of the gun
Cuz they had
Space
In their own ability to use
It wouldn't end up
You're leading to the death of
A bunch of a later discovered should not have had faith in their capabilities
Whatsoever
Incredibly complicated is a
Do the emails in the document
Instead of come out about the people
Used to say that it's
False
Eric Holder in the
The boj we're just trying to
False flagging around in order to get gun ban
And it just doesn't really it doesn't really work
All that well for a number of reasons
The first of all is that
Though Fast and Furious as it
It was
Known started in 2000
It was based on and
Continuation of
Something called operation
Receiver
Butcher started in 2006
When Alberto
Gonzales
Charge of the doj
Operation
It's been happening
Down in the Southwest
To some extent
I am
Absolutely not happy about it
The same time I do understand the motivation
Incredibly misguided way to do things
But from the sense I get
There is at there is a bit of like
Okay
He's just dumb law enforcement
Volkswagen in order to get people killed
It's just
Send it.
Seems like they were like okay well
The same thing right
Right make sense
But be that as it may stand people
I'm fairly against
Right but I also understand the reasoning
In extreme situation
That using
Maybe unconventional
Conventional
Technique
At the same time I don't know
I can't unpack it
All I know is that Alex Jones is wrong about it
I meant Eric Holder did
He may have lied about it
Underoath
Or may have lied about
What he knew
And I'm not
Defend Eric Holder
Doesn't matter what team you're on your way I don't know but there's also
Possibility that this stuff was going on
Was unaware of it because it's
I don't know I don't know how the organization of these like
Doj goes
There's probably some stuff that goes on
But not everybody's aware of
I don't know I don't know what the compartmentalization of everybody's jobs are
I don't know
So I don't know how malicious the lie was
How much it was just a mission or whatever
All the emails the talk about like
Maybe we can get that too
Regulation
Purchases and stuff like that
Yeah I don't
It's not a propaganda campaign
But be that as it may
You might not also remember what that
Shooting was
I do not remember
That was one that people forgot about pretty
Pretty easily
Wisconsin
Two Fair there's a guy named Wade Michael page
Who was a 40-year old white dude
He walked into a Sikh temple
Six people and wounded four other people
Yeah it's not like
Murdering
But it made me really bummed out cuz everyone
It was between 39 and 84
He's killing a bunch of just old people trying to
Practice her faith
It's not like age matters
I don't I don't know it doesn't
For some reason
Michael page had a very deep connection
Two white supremacists
Groups
The number of
You might call his white supremacist power bands
You got it
Nope
He was and apathy
In 2005
And played in the band
Definite hate
Is blue-eyed devils
Okay
Yeah I guess so
Do the Army dude he was in the Army discharge
General discharge
Neither neither honorable or dishonorable because
Pattern
Misconduct
Drunk driving
Dishonorably discharged
Yeah it up by becoming radicalized at some point maybe already was when he was in the army
Man that fell in with white supremacist groups
And ended up going to
Killing
Six people and injuring others four others
Subway really super wild is that like this part
Blew my f****** mind
Yeah it's
Not a positive but it made
Ended up
No showing up
And
He ended up I think it was his gun
Duck shooting
The Wade
Waited up killing himself after he got shot by the cops
Yeah
Ryan Murphy
Ended up getting shot by this dude
This guy a******
Yeah he shot him
15 time
Close range
15 * 50 *
Close range include
In the back of the head
And the dude survive
Yeah Brian Murphy Murphy survive
I told you people can with jingle a surprising number of gunshots
New york-based
Pledged a $10,000 award to Murphy
To seek residents of Yuba City California donated another hundred thousand dollars
Officer Murphy and praise
My God this is kind of a nice nice piece of how good these people are
Respond
To such tragedy
This way
In this situation
I don't know anyways
Again mysteriously it is a white supremacist guy murdering minority
It's very fascinating to me
To be real and their work
So anyway let's get on to this next clip
Wie geht's
It's more about David
Amanda Alex makes a dumb prediction
Mustang
Asia a few days ago in California
And
Obama
Lamp shades
Aurora and in Wisconsin
It's a big National story
Also
I need to dump Biden
Omni gets elected
How did Nappa die
I don't think I have
Biden
Still in play
You did not get dropped
Notebook
Some shooting
That's part of what
There's another shooting
Or is another incident
Gets into it
A little bit here
It's very
Very different
Situation
Family research Council
Weather in shot some people
Mustang and a terrorist
This
Is Ally was going to say that sounds very faults
July
Reasons and I don't support
Guy who ran into
The family research
Console with a gun
But one of the reasons
But it's probably less than
Severe and maybe not
Cena is a horrible acts of terrorism is that no one with
I don't think anyone was even seriously injured
It wasn't good guy with a gun
Someone wrestled the gun away from
From the guy
Halo good guy
Attica
But it wasn't the good guy with a gun that's not brave enough
To step up and I mean I don't
I don't think that you need to really
I don't know I don't know if it's healthy to
Glamorise rental
People think it's a smart thing to do
Not have done that it
Probably would have been
I am so I think the reason
Is the severity of it is
Much lower than
A Sikh temple which is
We targeted for
They're religious an F
Ethnic minority
That multiple people were murdered
Write a police officer was shot 50
Cooking times
That was more terrorists
And the guy was a member of The Hague
That seems like a big part of being terrorists
Having a Ed entire ideology behind you
You can easily make the argument and I'll go along with you halfway
You split the guy who win
The family research Council
Some sort of like
Maybe he was part of some life group
Possible I don't know I don't know either
Just seems like it was a guy who didn't like people
Supporting Chick-fil-A
That's a little bit
Papa's
Are brilliant
Very
So I remember if you recall correctly when we talked about Alex's coverage
Chick-fil-A billboard
But if you understand this
You are bored
Understand everything
So now
In the middle of this episode
Alex Jones
Play the specials
And I want you to
Brian guess
What this special report is
Is about I'm going to play
This first clip
And see if you have any idea what he's about to talk about
Alex Jones
Any ideas
How Dave Mustaine should never been kicked out of Metallica not to eat
There is ever talk
Do you want another clue before you go
This information is very closely held
Want you
Understanding
Okay so it's both
Andeli Corporation
Yes
Keeps us all in chain
Brighton
Edgewater
Interesting gas I'll give you another clue
Large swathes of the global population
DIA
The real geopolitical paradigm
In the battle for 21st century global
Hegemony
What blood did you have any idea what he's about to talk about
Any idea
I mean he's always talked about
Who really rules
Usher
The General
I mean
Okay what do you think
He's about
Think it's about to become the
Here's the issue
Where's the beef
What's the most successful at Camp Wendy's ever had
And it's red hair b****
Nah
This is the most
Import
Information Alex
Has ever had
Closely-held information
It has to do with
And the global hegemony
That is all
At all times
Do you have any idea
Okay
Get ready for this
Illustration
Look at these symptoms of
Ultimate living
Cesare Borgia
The game of Risk
A game of Monopoly
Important because otherwise we're going to have
Harbor Freight clamp
Find a control
Maui
Boys are blue girl.
This isn't Candyland everybody we're not going to have fun doing that
Shoot a ladder
Is
Crazy
This is so crazy
I can't even explain to you how much ice
Huh
It indicates to me a couple things
It's Bill time
Do you think his audience
Really stupid
Like the idea that it's like okay I'm going to explain
My bizarre theories about like
Global
Board games
Just like how it's like
Like a comet comes up with an open microphone at their place in there just kind of looking around
This
Superman
He was sitting there like he was whacked out of his mind
Who's on cocaine
So let's
Patton Oswalt about
Let me explain lucky
Now the rainbows
In the clovers
They're sweet
Traditional pagan
Symbols
The weed stuff
Is a cross
Said it's all that
What they're trying to tell you
Is that the path
The good
Bland
Tasteless
That's smarter
Alex Jones
Starts his analysis
About Chess
And I'm not talking about
Musical
Includes the great song One Night in Bangkok
This is
Musical was about the game chess
Anyway here's h
I'm going to use a chef set
Forms of government
Domination
If you look at this
Doesn't even have a child on the bottom
Beginnings of civilization more than 6000 years ago
The black sacrifice was the model
Warfare
Between
Warfare and politics was carried out
She's already off base a little bit there
Vig
Her like until very recently
Didn't play a big role in
Tribal
Nation
They have the right to be called Nation
Complicated
Between each other
That sucks
It goes a long way back the phrase the enemy of my enemy is my friend
Right and even if you consider like to talk about
Eastern
Cuz that's even more
Understand what goal is and that's never going to happen
Right he's already started off his analysis with her like a pretty productive
View of
Complex
Denver overtime
Yeah it let's see let's see
Is the fact that
Sometimes
Against each other
When they had rebellions at home
The population of young male
Jobs
How does that relate to chess
Call the ponds
Freeloaders
Economy
They're unemployed
The manufacturing bases
That's what I learned
From Chattanooga to protect the learned about prosperity
I mean I guess if you want to do a really wild interpretation
You could say that
But I don't
I don't think that relates to
Jobs
Well you know you're trying to get rid of your religious powers
They're the ones who are causing all of this insurrection
They're the ones who are going to leave the
People that are
Do you know what
I'm over on Alex
Side right now I know
When using cats as their model for global domination
For thousands of years you're probably right
Multiple
Parker Brothers
It's hard for me to take this seriously when it's the same uses to sell Beyond Tangy Tangerine
But
Their financing
Starting on the 17th
Factions
Because all of them
After the war
They were not allowed to pass go
And collect $200
But like did we already discussed on the last episode The anti-semitic nature of his relationship
The Rothschilds
And with cats apparel
And about the history of their their family
It's 08
It's difficult
Take too much that he says about them
Seriously and also when you look at this history that he's talking
About funding both sides of a war
That is
You believe that everyone is on the same team and they're all global
Cuz if you talk about like
Bread Coke or Prescott Bush
Or IRA Ford supporting the Nazis
In World War II
If you can see both of them on the same side
5 people who supported
Ben
I guess they're controlling both sides but if you don't if you look at them as
Conflicting operations
That have
Intertwined business interests
So they don't kill each other or whatever cuz
You'll date
Still running business
But our guests but artwork
Getting together in some weird oneworld globalist operation
But they're not
Okay fine but this also goes to like
Just the history of
Kind of stupid Lee supporting
Factions in wardsville no business
Which is something that unfortunately
We have been involved with a lot
Pretty much
It's not like we have a
Refinance and taking over
Gun manufacturers
Everybody
Alright
Guatemala
In Bosnia during the during World War
Churchill was a piece of s*** about it and then
Territory
Death-squad
He has a fair point if
If you believe
The central premise
That there are global
And they're all working
Together
You don't believe that new think the world's a little more
Complicated
And you think there are people
Both sides
Running operation
Sam's and stuff like that
To further their own in
That are at odds with each other
Start to look at the world I think
In a more realistic what come into the show
With something prepared
Good for you
And I'm going to play you a recording of
Of how I explain how Henry Ford
Kissinger
Who are the three main players in the globalist Empire
Okay.
Okay
Rap God that's fine cuz at this point Alex Jones Mouzon to risk
Distill down
Human conflict and domination
Jerry's all have basically
Are you reading the rules
What is the temperature
Was it worth
I can't understand conflict
Can we boil it down into a game I can play in a few hours
I sure sure but we're going to need to have Dyson cards
How many immediately does a
There is no discussion here
I'm looking at the real model
We are under today
The game of Monopoly
Let's
That's all he says about video game
Streamers on Twitch
He's got a whole nother career
Pivot to I'm just him scribing board games
Set alarm
Monopoly by himself
Alex Jones start it up
Errors in your favor are actually
Standard
In the game of Monopoly
New York City
Already talked it up if it landed City Atlantic City
Already started
But good analysis so far
You know it it's those sorts of things that are like
I mean
When you don't know the basic
Pieces of something
And that you're trying to deeply analyze it so it fits your version of the world it makes me think that you don't
You don't care enough to understand your subject
He threw this together whenever he was sitting in his study like I don't have it
Time to sell
Always win at Monopoly
SalusCare
Monopoly
Strategy
Pictures of the real system
Grounded Rockefeller
Competition
Is it real quick
Fairly misunderstood
I believe
From what I can tell
A better way to
Sort of unpack that
Is VIP
Diaz it is everybody's
Competing for the same thing
There's no money
That the quote is actually in the context of supporting innovation
I'm changing the model of what you're doing
In order so you're not competing with people everybody cancel
6 Yvette
If everybody is trying
Innovate
And constantly doing other things
They won't be in direct competition with each other
Spiritual version of competition
But it's really just about like a
If you and I are trying to do literally the exact same thing
And Myra
Wind takes away from you
It's not good for either of us
What does I'm going to either be motivated on keeping you down one of us has to lose
It's nonsense
Do the same time
Betrothed so true
Particular though is
Political power
The barrel of a gun quotes that are taking everybody knows them but they don't really know the
Contact
I don't like Alex
Is just misusing
EXO
I mean whatever
That's again
Monopoly is in New York kind of stuff
It's just a while willful lack of
Engaging with
The things he's
So you're the last clip
Now this is
It's designed that board
Monopoly
Drop a chessboard on top of an overlay
I'm in
4:10 report but like the last four minutes we can just
Rambling and has nothing to do with board games anymore
Pertinent to
The report
Monopoly
Describe
Shelters
You think
Houses and apartments
Park Place in for the electric company
How to get out of jail free card
Control
What happened
Country
The African nation
Play the Monopoly game
The modern
Master System based in London and New York
Alright
Disagree with what he's
Trying to say
Silly and stupid
He then launches into a long thing about
Like
Hayden Al-Qaeda to destabilize countries in
But like the part of it
You've established your trying to use board games board game references
It's just like this
Brett
Hey people to invade countries in Risk
The top hat who's controlling your gay
And the bank doesn't win in Monopoly
The bank is not a character in the game
Like there's no point at which nothing
Snowman games at the bank
They're playing their winning every game
I guess so
The game Monopoly
This whole thing goes all the way back
To The Rock
Fellers
Our globe
And let me get back in
Chairman Mao
Right this is where we getting
The game of Risk
You know what German Mauser
Milton Bradley
Great leader Milton Bradley
I just
I just don't know man
I just don't know what you
You doing
But it tickled me a little bit
So we're done with that whatever he was just
Crazy
Yeah it is any kind of refreshing
Prior to this week
Temple ideas like
Terrorist
Because he was going up a
Their side
To bring home
Real f****** clue
Is that even back then
He still suffered from the same problems that we complain about now
No one cared about him back then
He didn't have a real
Dangerous effect on
Affiliation to the point of subservient
With a
Racist
Eddie Taiwan
Yeah
Alright so we put the board game away we broken down the leg
Find out why did you play that 10-minute special report that made no sense
Here's why
There are
Thousands of articles
Thousand
The Rock's albums
The president the criminal a liar a few weeks ago on the show
Special Report
Interview with
It's a video interview
We will Eric hear on the radio
Movies
Researcher
Richard Belzer Hellyeah
TV star researcher
Isabel
He's not going to throw, can there
He was the original opening comics
For Saturday Night Live
He was in the first ever episode of Saturday Night Live as a like extra
Absolutely
He's written a couple books about JFK
UFO books
Play conspiracy books
I've read a couple of engaging writer
I'm not sure if I believe any of them
We're not going to listen to really any of Richard Belzer on the show cuz
He's on and all it is is him talking about JFK stop and for my money
Those things that are covered on Alex Jones Show
JFK's the closest to real
And it's not that interesting to me because
Richard Belzer comes in with a lot of specifics in a lot of things that he's looked and there's a lot of questions that he has
And Alex really can't hang with specific music
And it's not really all that fun
So we're not going to listen to that but big shout out
What's up Richard Belzer order universes
John Munch
Character ever
How did you get on Arrested Development
You're on The Simpsons that means cartoons and real-life are the same
A robot
In this next clip Alex
The bunch of his narrative
Then turns them all into
Is weird
Bouillabaisse of First Amendment complaints
Temple shooting we have that
Family research Council shooting
They're all sort of combined into one
Something along with
Chick-fil-A
It is a visit a mess
A cold
Stupidest just ice cream gone wrong I think that's the truth Bass
Call Beyond
Multiple
People chasing eyewitnesses
Real quick
First account
Generally are the most unreliable things
In terms of
Shootings in America
No generally In the Heat of the Moment you misinterpret all kinds of cues and things that you
You see because
You're in shock
Your adrenaline is Hanover charge
Some people thought there were four shooters
To me doesn't mean any
Especially
Westgate
No one's like
We need to look at that sweet be idiots
I just breaking just like
With the Dixie Chicks sing the interview with the war they're trying to cancel it
Chick-fil-A
You've got to support the First Amendment with these bullies
Has shot up the family research
Family
Research Council
Saturday
Launch Chick-fil-A
You got to support the First Amendment
And we'll have that exclusive Dave Mustaine statement
The 1st of July is the boardwalk
The guy who shot up
The Sikh temple
But the guy who didn't
Kill anybody
The family research Council
Terrorist
Two faults to be a
True false
Then First Amendment
Issues are the dicks
Whatever the Dixie Chicks are doing that he was very very not happy
I don't know cuz he hates George Bush 2 though so I mean it's it's entirely possible I'm willing to believe
He very well may have
I've been again
What is a compelling argument without going back to that I am not willing
Going to make a prediction
Can because I would not be surprised
If you supported
Because
Kihei to George W bush.
So that's possible I don't know
But those two things are a little
Chick-fil-A
Being like
We don't like gays coming in
Note 4
I don't feel like it is
Discrimination and that's where the libertarian stuff gets
Get money
In with him
Because
I mean
Businesses
Are that you run your business
And what have you but it is a
Public space
It's not a private
Space
Necessarily
Decide if you want to know what the free market is going to be
Takes you down
It's definitely not going to be supported by all of your other races
These people
You're not going to have Dave Mustaine getting weaved in on it
MMA
Two chicks getting thrown in for no reason
If that's a weird thing that Dave Mustaine also said in China
At that,
Have you guys been to this no black people allowed Diner over there it's
Amazing
Brighten and you know like
In the name of
Free Speech Alex Jones
Chick-fil-A
Are you gotta support dating
I don't see why you wouldn't make that argument
Based on the logic if someone
Aladdin restaurant
Makeup set from races
It's whenever they are
They're against the Civil Rights Act
Encroachment
That's what it is
Wild violets
It's just like with this cake
Situation
Let's go to the Supreme Court of like
We don't have
His free speech
Specifically because you're gay
You could have lied
You could have just lied and everyone have been everybody would have known that it was discrimination but we wouldn't have taken it to this
Supreme Court
Text Leah question about literally this situation
Probably
This is not one of those issues
We the bad guys
It does
Lehigh
Right now
Are you have this attitude like you've got all these libertarian fooling you while you're high
Look
Before Richard Belzer Hells Bells comes in
Another gas
Gentleman by the name of Gerald Celente
From the trends research whatever
Usually just
And of course it always usually revolves around a common theme
Which is the right here
The real
Crashing
The Indian rupee
I love his voice
Oh he's a ghoul
Is solute
Is he safe
Alex
Giving me credit for calling all of this s***
I'm smarter than Soros
No no no you talk about other people who are like oh now Soros is buying gold we should buy gold what about
Sing it forever
Kind of a problem because you're on a sucking radio show
Brought
Mutations
That is run by Ted Anderson
Is on the show frequently selling gold on the show Gerald
That's why
Cuz you're part of a scam operation that's right
It's not about the golden itself per se it's more
Select
Talenti
I would
I don't remember my own name most of the type I would have the same complaints about George Soros
If you was going on a radio show that was run by gold sale operation
They didn't he made up the whole story about that instead he had a radio show told nothing to buy gold
It was basically like a good morning Vietnam but it WWII
Tragical history of PG wodehouse
WWII
Operation Dumbo Drop
Gerald Celente
Next clip
About a minute and a half
Describe
He is getting good and are you having a rant
About to have you globulus
And then
You don't roll
Mni you gets done with his
And Alex doesn't know what to do
She's very very funny
Robert Reed
What are you
REI
You know how I say
Everybody
Presidency
Reality show
Hold on
Romney Ryan right
Do you hear what he said there
He said this is like a reality show president
Interesting in hi-fi
Interesting in Heights
Everybody else
As the brown noser of a disputed traffic
President
Keystone
A little
Started laughing cuz you got to hear this
This ball drop here
Brother
Clearly the red
No keep going keep going let me try
Gather my thoughts Subway sandwich
Sure Gerald's Darrell shooting on everybody
Last train to awesome at this,
Google
Boo Buie
You can't I can't take him seriously
Play I can't take his voice serious
Abdullah music
Sparingly on the show
Almost all the time it comes on the show it just ends of him screaming
Somehow relates back to you should buy gold that's pretty much the trends that he's
But
This Kardashian app
You know what the golden Kardashian ABS is
That's why you got to buy real gold
In the Marvel heroes of the universe app
That's a much better game
They sell it at Midas
We're entering the home stretch
Ruining this planet I wouldn't be surprised
Just a little bit of a shorter episode cuz there's a lot of
Is Richard Belzer off the phone
Cuz he realizes
Run
Mustang
Basically.
That's a good statement by mistake
Furious was a thing they faked the Aurora shooting why wouldn't is all beef
Try to take our guns
Is the comeback
Commercial yet
During the Richard Belzer interview
Something really f*****
I'm at my friends
I'm with my friend Chris walking was doing
He doesn't have
A computer
Ticketmaster
Wow
At all
Republic
So supposed to Christopher Walken
Yeah who's private
Computer so Google exactly
Richard Belzer
Christopher Walken's house
And of course
You know what this leads to
This conversation had to have happened
Hold on Chris
I got to go talk to Alex Jones Infowars you know what happen
Chris is going to show Christopher Walken appears on
Yes
Oliver
Inject it into my veins Dan
I got to be clear
It would be to think that this was someone doing a Christopher Walken impression
It is not
He is on video
It is on video Christopher Walken
It looks like sitting on Richard Belzer's wife
Which is another reason for things that could happen in Christopher Walken
And I just have the full clip will have to pause at some point but like
It is a masterclass in someone who doesn't give a f*** about Alex
Well I feel like I should say more cowbell
Blackmail
On the line with us he's the author of
The author coming in
Call Mike
I'm going to release that is a short film
For second movie of my nose
If it's ready don't go
You can also just be Alex be like
I do not know how to cut in I have no idea what to do
Christopher Wilde
I don't know why
Plus he's
There is a calculator
You can see him for going over his head
Christopher Walken
Richard Belzer
Willingly
Crazyshit with me getting Christopher Walken
Regular
Now I got to get walking
This is
This is strange guest episode very strange
Image
Brazil
So there's talking about
There's talk about lunch
Tomato
That's all
Walking
When you come to town
Arugula salad is schedule
Richard Belzer trying to leave Alex in somehow
But Alex is even that really can't you ever come to New York
Like as if it's a trap
Comfortable
New York to stay away from
Today we got an arugula salad now that's in the mix
Tomatoes
Parmesan
Search rock
They're probably drunk
Great great at interview
Krystal's at Gourmet
Mishawaka
I hear you
Fisher walking we are learning Mr Bill's reviews on the world
Richard and Chris
What is what is your view on what's happening in the world right now with
I want to know so bad
Do you think he's going to give him a real answer
You know what
Absolutely not
I was hearing that you don't have all the little Spa
I have no idea
Tuba
Is found to be have that rebirth technology that we all know he wanted to know where we are
You're almost invading you right now like an Alien Probe
Mishawaka know what do you think
That they want to have an Iran War
Thank you so much walking
I'm sorry
I was one of the least successful interviews I've ever heard
Christopher Walken love making chicken with a red wine and arugula salad with two kinds
Eatzi's in there cooking book
Cookbook
What do you think about them
Who
We have no idea
No interest in playing
Doesn't give a f*** I was kind of disappointed cuz when I pulled up the episode when I saw Christopher Walken I was like
This could be crazy
But I was kind of hoping it would be
It's just like
Wondered what Christopher Walken
Until now it which
I want to know everything he thinks about the world
I still don't really care this is good enough for me
That's pretty much a little bit more about JFK
And you know it's that not really all that interests
16th 2012
At the end of a at the end of the interview Bells
Christopher Walken's room where he's wearing those blackouts
Bells is like
Siri going to read this book about JFK
Hope
No
And it is
I don't know
4 in the afternoon right now
And then I cook
Living a great life
Christopher Walken
Making a movie about Joseph
Any goes right back home like this really not much
Talkabouttd
It's fun as hell but there's not much to talk about outside of Alex being a
Completely impotent interviewer
It was at
270 road map
The fake strfkr laugh is baby my favor
Between the Mustang
Stop and that it
It's just like this is a
Graceful look
For Alex
Trajectory he comes back from the next commercial break with Don't Fear the Reaper
Quarters more cowbell joke
I got this one day of celebrity Worship in board game analysis
The most
It's one of the weirdest episodes
Well you know what
I think you covered it
You got all the subjects he needed to cover so what else is there in the world besides
Chest Monopoly and the game Risk
What is 20 think about something
There you go that's a show
Listening
Everybody underestimated the movie
Christopher Walken
It was at
The guy from the first Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles was in it
I love
I'm playing
We're going to check out our website acknowledge 5.com
We will be like
At the playground feeder Saturday
January 20th 10:30
Your friend
For some reason we chose for our first live show a place
City 150 people
Which
To help us can we get 50
If anybody was there please tell your friends at
Look if you
Want to have like a booze night on the show it's a perfect example
Over that
It won't be too bad
But it would be really really really appreciate anybody who helps get the word out to Spread spread some
Things on Twitter pretty soon and get some
The duck
Bright
Donald the Duck
Don McDonald done
Something
Like something like that
Max Murphy
The Blues Brothers Band
Charles Murphy
So what else on Twitter knowledge underscore fight
So you can do that there
Are you make your pod
Podcast app
Absolutely
Who do we hate
I hate myself
What is episode being so short
But I will
Let's go with
24 year old guy
Go fuc yourself badass hole
Who's this yeah you didn't know this 24 year old who's in charge of 20
You still try to get his master
Alexandra Thurston color