Alexandra Thurston color
Too much Alex Jones in particular
And I have no idea what the
Rango
Much like a wrestler out there on the on the plane
Clips from Publix Wild
And that brutal
Discuss the implications of the insanity
To be found therein I'd like to thank everybody who is following us on Twitter
Like thank all of the people who are getting onboard or numbers are through
Really
Statistically speaking yes lost them all whatever you did that last bit right
What language is that from Kansas
I tell you what
Slack-jawed Hillbillies I used to do karaoke with
For what episode
In the whole time not once just put up the episode in character the next
Episode again
Never mentioned that donate to patreon a picture
Fire hillbilly episode
News radio episodes were suddenly they were on the Titanic
Hillbillies season finale to a knowledge fight
Cuz we're not sure we're getting picked up for another season
Well we might die
Neither is America America's not sure yet whether or not we're going to do things
Until FairPoint
The studios
Still talkin
It's
It's going to be a fight
But much like Billy episode special episode
The David light episode that we did had no Alex in it
No no tragically
There's a little Alex
Magically have no Alex in it
Denoted is a tragedy no matter how good this goes
Okay that's a good point
This is a situation where
Alex everyday
I've mentioned this before every day
Leaves
During 4th hour
Someone else
Fourth hour
This week
For this last week
Thursday
He had a gentleman by the name of John Rappaport
Who is hosting the fourth hour called No More fake news
Dot-com
Why would you can go to and it looks like an angel cities paid
It looks like something from their Myspace
Like a very old clunky bad looking site
D-Link
To a number of things or you know they're fake news
This is
Underground
Reality coming directly
Play 2-U
Through
Aol.com
Absolutely
He is a guy who
HIV causes AIDS
He's a guy who has some literal belief in The Matrix
These sorts of things are you can pay $125
And he will send you a huge 10-hour presentation
On any of these
For an hourly rate
That's not good
Labor to bring you these
Conspiracy theory
Do you like
Hundreds of pages of documents
But now he Outsourcing to the Unabomber
Turtles Brodsky
Of the man where you can find on his
Is is
Hiv-aids denial
Weird one why would weird
Cuz he's found sources that proofing
Yeah but I mean
Good is that
Lest we go down this path Flushing
Fire website
This gentleman has a ridiculous greybeard and
Broadcast
Into Alex's show I'm going to post
A picture of what it looks like when he's broadcasting over on our new Tumblr
Tumblr.com
I'll post a picture of Jon rappoport
And if you look to the
The bottom
Left hand side of the screen
There's a picture
A framed picture
And it's been sitting for about 9 months
If you watch
If you watch him regularly
The same place
The entire time
You just dismembered put it up
Can I put it up it's amazing
All right no more fake news no more putting off putting up his picture
So anyway John Rappaport gets in there and he
A bombshell story
Infowars.com
Absolutely you like a little busy bee
Yeah and he has the story that is about
University
And what's really going on on college campuses
If you don't report
Perfectly Infowars
Leader readers and listeners would have hated that did you know that
The new way to have sex
In the butt hole in your anus
Jon rappoport
Report
Why the f*** are recovering this
We're in Alex Jones Centric podcast
I like this is Dutch
Inoffensive horrible thing
That is being broadcast on the air
Is a parable
I feel like I'm going
Figure it out real quick
I think it's time now we've established our format
And you know we're pretty comfortable
That it might be time to start dipping our toe into
Who are they
Cadre of weirdos
Okay Alex always has on his show
Cuz
We're working on exposing
The bullshitted valley
Right should be like
Open
I'm just focus on the
The Don
Let's call him the dog
Yeah
Is one of his Chapo's
Jon rappoport
Thigh with his
Breaking
Bombshell report
College campus
Chris's I'm vamping
Because my
Clip is loading
Professional podcast
Oh no
Dad
That would be a great
That would be the best
Shepherd for the Final Jeopardy
I take as a personal attack but so here's Jon rappoport take it away baby
Jon rappoport sitting in here for Alex in the fourth hour
Oh yeah recently no more fake news
The number one
Mind control program at us colleges
Everybody knows about this insane
Triggering safe spaces microaggression
Trend
Movement
Halloween costume
Let's be clear about the Halloween costumes
That's what he's talkin to
Thinking
He was talking about 7
No I'm triggered
A people dressing in blackface
Because it came up earlier
But you should be mad at
Agree
Alright
So so we've established
First before we go any further blackface bat
Plexus back
Even though that guy Yonder the last show we did had a slightly weird
If you see these things
Iona College campus
Offended by stuff
And then what's going to happen is you're going to have to
He's describing
The comfort room when you lose a misspelling
He's describing in the National Spelling Bee whenever they whenever the kids who are
I don't know how old they are they like 68-43
Work for years and then their dreams are
Crushed so spectacularly in such a
National Television
They take him to the comfort room where they do exactly that
So I'm assuming
It's I think it's amazing
Making about only spelling bee related issues on
I think maybe he was in a spelling bee years ago or whatever
Based on this report he was not good at spelling
It's something it's a mix between the comfort room that you're describing in like a chill out
It's somewhere in the middle there buddy
Nothing
Also
Even if it did it's not a bad thing it sounds pretty awesome
I was like wait
You know what
Instead of getting angry and
Projecting this outward I'm going to go to this room over here where I get my
Ya know I've been
This whole thing is invalidated I want those before we go any further we will them
A higher institution of learning
Many colleges
Corsica
You know people are just boggled by this
What are you stupid
Did you ask that all the time don't you
Yeah that's
No longer
What is this
What it what is this rap
Character of it
6070 year old guy
The changing evolution of culture
Like people having a greater understanding of each other to angry old man on a rack
We're about to dive into
Spirit but it's being presented as
Yeah it's the truth
It's not a light
Like if on your local news channel instead of meteorology was just as old dude
Just gone
Well my joints are swelling up so we all know what that
Mandalorian for a good so probably going to be wet later and we're getting closer and closer
Billy dad.
I have a difficulty getting
Hillbilly pocket and not going to the Bayou close
It's real touch-and-go but so
The thing that offends
Give me a little bit about
Just the beginning of it
Is that
He's not a
He should be
If he believes what he saying
He's at he is going to reading it like one of those 60 Minutes producer
He's giving you that like
Screen of abject
Activity
The passion listen
Observer reporting that other
By what Young
Yeah it is cowardly Dodge
But you still
It's still a little vague what he's trying to
Space space
How did it start
White people in the shadows for a couple years
Have yourself is lurking around of the Shadows
Shut up
We know he's not dressing up as like
Excuse me fellow College
How are you today
Normal Age based Soul Man
But also it's never been kissing
He's doing the Never Been Kissed thing also
Rapport
Stop lurking in Shadows put that goddamn picture also if you've seen what he looks like
You know you don't want him lurking Shadows anywhere
No
Metaphorically but Tuesday
Rapport
Is better for openly starts out evil
Piling up information on Dish
And I needed a few final pieces and I finally got them
NFL lunch place so I'm going to tell you
Play where all the stuff came from
National Alliance on Mental Illness
Comes this
Statistic
20%
Of all college students in the US
Have either been diagnosed with a mental disorder
Or treated for a mental disorder
Before
Across the u.s.
In college or College
Okay I have a number of things
To do bunk that
Yeah
I can't
That National Association of mental illness
But I can't trust their sourcing
I have no idea
But like
You I don't know where you're going to get that information
From number one
Number two
Can't you knock
It seems like a lot of it would have privacy issues
What would you go to
Because here's the bigger picture
That number if it does exist for statistic
Hacks to by definition includes
People who are seeking behaviors
People who were going to try and get
Adderal and s*** like that
Yeah I have to include that subset of the population
Yeah it also has to include anybody who
Gone and gotten
They just go in and get my health center and then don't pursue it
That one in four statistic is meaningless
No it seems like it's very very scary I was going to go with its back
Let's flip this one in four
Dorian Ford
Which who the f*** are those kids getting through that s*** every ever been to college
So like this
Creepy man lurking in the shadows
Paranoid delusion about that
Xanax to get through the rest of your life after you see this man
It's a meaningless
Statistic for those reasons
VIP of people going to
To try and get pills
I know what number of people
Did my college days
After college days
Yellow days of me who is constantly looking for pills
Crazy meme
Who that girl
Is included in that 25
It's like you need to be a little bit more specific
With your numbers
Or else your
To be as big as possible in order to scare as many people as you
You can't exactly
No more fake news
Sell like Survival Products
Spells
Continuing to get polio vaccine
Sinclair
Universities have been turned into psychiatric clinics
Shaky
That conclusion does not follow from the premise
All colleges
Are psychiatric
Okay
Great Jon rappoport colleges should have
Now if you are turning all colleges
To psychiatric
The clinic
I don't think so either but
I think he thinks it's like
Arkham City
All colleges are Arkham
If he is
Continuing
Call dr. Hugo Strange in Batman
I mean come on
That's the story
That's the underlying story
For clinical depression or bipolar
Or you know whatever it is
And the treatment was highly
Highly active toxic trucks
Back in my day we used to
Hit people
How to get a spanking
Jimboy's
The p****
That's why I that's why I
Tell me I shouldn't hit my kids no you don't see the problem
When those boys came back from World War
I mean to kill themselves and never spoke about it again already
Everything like that matter
Superman in there were fewer of
That creates a complete culture of victimhood
I don't care what Hillary Clinton
Advocates or
Creepy laugh
Consider themselves
And so what's the next step
Because
Wait was that him staying
Use roleplay
Alright but it's also a little chicken egg
You know the man
It's like
What does diagnosis and now you're a victim so you can excuse all your behaviors like
Maybe
Knossos was I suffered from panic attacks we couldn't leave my house
Does he think
People are being triggered without having anything to trigger
I'm like the whole point of
Let me know that trigger warning is
And this will bring up those bad memory right it's the idea of you you were sexually assaulted and
Hear some graphic content
Describing a sexual assault
You don't want to preserve spaces are like
You don't have to deal
You're in a situation where
People who are on
You weren't on the level
We're going to just get in the way
Exclude
0 train cars that are safe space
Let's put it that way
Absolutely
I don't know look I don't want to sit here it understands
The entirety of safespace trigger warning culture
But I know that it's based on something
And it's not crazy people know based on people being oppressed
It's based on
Taking
Things that are being forced
Stop on other
The people most against that whole concept
A trigger warning
Generally cause p
I'm off the hook
Problems studying don't know who or how to introduce myself
Kid doesn't know what to do all of this
Got the answer
Because these problems
Or the infirmary whatever in the first place and then all of a sudden before he knew it
Fourth we ask you a few questions
Or psychologist
Always a good idea if you feel like you need to see if the house or psychiatrist
Go see one Church of good idea
It's never a bad idea
Which is never the case
No one ever unless you're like suicidal or you're threatening to hurt somebody
No one ever forces you to go see a therapist
Yeah
Literally illegal
Idea about therapy and psychiatric help that is like
You go in for a little minor problem that's when they Shanghai
Is it can basically you're being kidnapped
No the only way that anybody can Forza
To do anything is
If you present a legitimate danger to yourself or others
And even that it's really hard
Yeah because
Scary
Otherworld system if you could just be forced into
It would be
To go back
All the way back to like 30 years ago when you
Could do that too with
Yeah for being hysterical
To those time
Stay out so Fargo
It's right there you can play it anytime you want to well I couldn't turn in the assignment
Mental disorder
OK Google
For your skull
Get it through your skull
But that number is meaningless
Grayscale
Otherwise
See I mean that there is
There is an interest
In conversation
Possibly to be had about
Idea people being able to get away with stuff member of the mental illness
Community
Because
We're willing
To talk about it now
Yeah
To fight against Batman
There is
There is the Quan
Over-diagnosing
Because that's always
Concern with any kind of medical
Message within the community is something that we all
Consider
Something that's really important
Because
With all the side effects that
Your medications
Can have
If you get a wrong diagnosis
Very serious
But
That said
It's generally
Not as big of an issue as the
Always very very small percentage of cases
People are keenly aware of
Something that
There is a debate
Also over-prescription of stuff
Real world thing
But it's not
Real the way Batman
Is describing it
Now that's what it is
Trigger warning
Some s***
With that underlying
You see
How easy is it to from there into
Student
We're students getting together insane
Triggering
There was there was
If there was a Nazi propaganda painted on
Jefferson
I went to the student at the University of Missouri
Yeah yeah
Back when I went to the university
See Missouri there was a situation where
A bunch of cotton
Was put outside like
Just thrown out at side.
The office of the Legion of black Collegian
You know that guy
The people who did it
Taken care of
But if I'd administrator
They were
From the Vegas Mafia
They got very short Graves out the desert took out.
Got expelled the facts but that's how I remember go down
More severe punishment
Sara Lee a 3-foot
Something happens a lot
And that sort of thing
Is not
People respond to that it's not mental illness
It's causing them to respond
It's that they should be very offended
Well
It's it's a threat
You're being fresh
If you do not look for a safe space after being threatened
Then I mean
That's that
Why aren't the guys
Perpetrating the race
Mental illness
I don't know what will they the ones who believe that mental illness is wicked.
Mental illnesses
Get the help that they probably mean
Desperately
And put it outside a black building out of work
Racism is a lot of
Work indicates
Something is not working right
India brain-dead what if there was let's
Let's say there was a
Even better yet
Again
We could just Pump It
Too heavily race
Still against
Admittedly I agree with you
Now
I will say that
The side effects of this gas
In my head are your legs don't work
So we don't have to worry about
So you're not mobile
Yeah exactly how about we just make you dick way to bed
It said of no egg just pick you pick comically large
That's the that's the ironic twist
Now it's like careful what you wish for
Revealing
And
Shares some thoughts
Scientology
Unfortunate way
Great
Get it
Because we already have a mental disorder you see somewhere a little bit off chemical imbalance in the brain whatever
Ever whatever whatever
You can't. You can just whatever whatever whatever
You can't like yada yada yada
Hard-hitting investigative
Now we have a right
To begin talking this crazy language and we need to save space in a room as teachers and staff
And we can regress back into being children
Because we've already been diagnosed by a mental health professional
As having a mental disorder
I hope
This is the key to understanding
What is going on not only going on at us colleges and universities but what is eating out the country from
The inside
Profession of Psychiatry and I'm going to break down for you
Andrew said this investigative report
He doesn't
Okay
I'm like
We're going to go down to the medication is
Change
Thing right
Shades of
If you will
Where where is this going
Poquoson places you don't
Of course
If it does get to those places we've got to deal with him being a little bit but it's worth listening to this
Because
Of
You'll see
Paragraphs
He's a complete ass
You don't get to do that I don't know him
He just generalized every us College
Yes
That's the whole
Like that the fight that's so funny
Conservatives have because
Cuz they they
Have that thing where they send their
You know Chris Christian conservative brainwash kids
The universe
Other
Surprisingly enough they come back with from their tiny ass
Maybe they smoke a little smoke
Oh my God
Sort of person over that camp
Maybe you maybe
You matter gay person you're everything I've been taught About You Is Wrong
Is always that
It's always that whole b******* like
If we could just
Bubble like
Occult
If we could keep that like every small town should just be called a
Because that little bubble they have of those p
And I grew up in a small town
Probably will.
But at least it'll be enough
Bathroom stall of a bar
Keep that short small View
And the moment somebody goes away and
Comes back with a
They blame the universe
As though as though the universe
He wasn't just
A collection of
From other places it's full of crazies
And Psychiatry is to blame
Oh okay
BMX
Thanks so much easier because it's Arkham campus
That you not
Dress in blackface.
Misgender people
People are crazy for demanding
Yeah and I guess if that's your argument I can't
I can't really argue with you except to say I completely disagree
People though are always the ones who are all the most against
Deformity
So it's always like
These people demand something that goes against what I think
Think is what everyone
Should be
Individualism the libertarian ideas
Everybody's individual
Actually he's going to get to individuality in a little bit I bet he's right on
Totally now you can see
How this whole business came
And how gorgeous destroying the country because it's a majority of the best and the brightest
Attending colleges and universities 25%
That's not a majority
The 45% of
A hundred percent
Write notes
What is the
I don't know I just learned all this liberal hippy-dippy I don't know about math
San College
Then already at such a young age or being diagnosed
Drug is highly toxic
Brain scrambling drugs
Naturally
Halloween costume
Nothing things are related
Into each other ideas
They're talking
Specifically about black
Is always minimizing it if you rename it
2 something
Locker room talk
Right
It's the Battle of language
It's not it's not black face
The Halloween costume
You and I know everybody wears Halloween
Which means everybody wears
Haysville Halloween
Sure
Well
We're f****** blackface
On the last episode
Little bit of the Halloween
Totally cool
So don't even reach right it totally
But this is so great because
Spouting this stuff and he's about to make a really smooth strands
You bet
And the drugs then sell
Create a distorted perception of reality
The drugs
Okay
Yeah I'm getting a little worked up about this I've been on this case for 20 years now
Funny years
Before I guess the next
Gigantic
Make sure that you know
Infowarsstore.com
You can get Rodger Stones new book
The making of the president
Now available
20% off
He goes on for like 3 minutes
We all know that he goes on 23 minutes or so selling Rodger Stones books
But it's great because this is a show that does have commercials
I love I love what the f*** are you doing you're in the middle of a report about how psychology isn't real in the enemy
Huge bumps but you know we got to talk about
I love how worked up he is
By his voice being like
And I
Real angry about that
Be Sedated opening with
I'm a little hyper
Yeah yeah
Some of these herbs we can buy on Infowars
Psychiatrist
Totally fine but he's psychotropic drugs from the psychiatrist
Well you know what
I will say that they do have a greater propensity
Because they're real
So anything that's real is of course much more likely to be high risk
Exactly or more like Lolo low-risk
Hyrule
I'm ready to get to the bombshell
I want to be clear
Okay I'm not sure
Forgetting the Bob
Okay
Next
Peace here
Okay
If you go to the psychiatric Bible
Famous DSM
The diagnostic and statistical Manual of mental disorders
What was by the American Psychiatric association about that because he's activated
You don't have to
Because he's got so little
He's got
Yeah but
Still it's like
It's going to appeal
To people who are dumb
Who's going to hear him
Sarcastically
He's been
It's
You don't have any information you just like and that's what he's doing
Pinterest
Vegas
Fairly sizable
Simulating you guys go
Go to parties I know you don't
The updated every few years you will find
That there is a list
Description
Ready
300 separate and distinct
Mental disorders
Finance
Defiance disorder attention deficit hyperactivity disorder
Clinical depression
Obviously the vast majority you never heard of 300
Okay
Now what
Revelation revelation
There is no and listen carefully here
Every word is important
Physical
Diagnostic test
Of any kind
For any of those 300
So cold mental disorder
That's not true
Jessica
It's horrible complete lie
Memes I think
Cuz I'm going to be generous in one set
If you have
TBH
Was like that there was a specific a Tubi TV
Yes you can take that test it'll tell you yes or no if you have
There is no test like that
Depression
Per say or schizophrenia
Anything like
But
Dora
Physical test
Very important information that lead doctors to those diagnosed
I consulted
With my gums
Who is a real-life doctor and I asked him
Bleeding gums Murphy
And
I asked
Just absolutely
Incorrect there's so many physical tests that are
The go into psychiatric diagnosis
There are
Panels
There are any kind of brain scans
There's other physical test
Basic even movement test
It doesn't in the same way as
TBH yes or no
It's not the same
But this is such an elementary understanding what physical test
Three other or here's the other angle on why
From this angle
Especially if there's a
7000 years old
Or however old
Is that
Is Brothers Methuselah's
The heart
Part about the hill
History of
Marianne psychology
Is that
There was such a
Play push for a long
Into a
Will sign
Message
Which
For the longer
Longest time it was just
You know a guy like Freud saying
You dream weird how about that your mother
Crazyshit so you can
Understand if somebody had only
Only read Freud thinking
That's what
Psychology or
That means you
You haven't look
Looked at
Any cycle
Length of time you've
Warriors
Did some stuff in your not really recognize it
The DSM
Regularly
Blown away he was by
7 billion people there are
Seven billion within that 300 there's like five
Different sorts of
Depression
That's the treatment
Depressed
Which again if you're dealing with
Was misdiagnosed
Cuz medication
Very toxic
You know like I'm destroying my liver so I don't know
60 years from now have a good life while good life as possible or do you want to be eight
Yeah
Who do you want to live like you have
In terrible pain in your life
But the other thing that I think it's super important is
Ndsm
Is statistical
Cuz it's based
Unreal observations of
People
Tons of patience
That Dave Dave
Diagnosed
Categorized
Mental disorders
And found what works
Statistically
Complicated
Read the new Michael Lewis book
They were everyone doesn't believe in coincidences isolated
Actually talk
Somebody earlier about
Where is
Is that whole myth
Well people Goku
Full moon
Look at it from a
When you realize do they do
When somebody goes crazy
And there's the phone
You associate
Wait we talked about
When somebody doesn't go or when somebody goes crazy in there
There's no full moon
You don't register
Cuz there wasn't a
Well it's like suicides Rising around the holidays we always hear about
Intuitive sense
The full moon
Is
Yeah so unusual things
Should happen
Whilst holidays
RC
And you should kill yourself
Spell statistics are like a science that's desperately in need of a story to make them
Yeah so you have the like full moon story
Whether it's true or not
Storytellers
That's what we are that's the only way we under
Story
Batman
Got a blood test
AR test not saliva test out of urine test not a brain scan out of genetic
Nothing
Lucero's zilch nada nothing
Secret
In the psychiatric community
You going into the doctor he says you know
You've got cancer
Yeah
I think you got cancer
You going to run any tests
No we don't actually have any tests
But from what you say and looking at you I would say that you got cancer
And it's now time
You know
We could start an hour
Rounds of chemotherapy
It was your course will stop the reproduction of all your cells and we hope it'll kill the tumors before it kills you
We don't really have any chest that would be like that
It wouldn't be like that also kind of insinuating
Cancer
Treatment is bad for you
He probably would
In like
It seems like
He's really mad because
Can somebody diagnose
That's how I lost
Well you got you
You guys will see the picture
Holyshit
Ulta
If I was diagnosed
Play on
And I heard that song
I would be totally cool I love the idea of like trying to figure out when they send
Your ear deep in this metaphor that we know you're not going to find your way out of the woods
Skipping music
There is never been a break or that Muse
Close
Like they never end on a
They're always going to break
The middle of
And if you got diagnosed
Like no
Play something
Appropriate
Something like a dirge
Exactly
Not true
Gospel Choir
You're gone
That is like
That's just not true
But then the other I'm being extra.
Come to him here by proposing
Do some of these tests
It's like you answered
Conditions have an underlying condition
That is causing
Derelict sometimes depression is caused by hyper hypothyroidism
Or something like that and you can confirm the depression another condition
Special Report
The other thing that I feel like it is
His main like
Completed
In other message
Which is always you guys think
An outside thing
Happening
To me that makes
Yeah
It's really the depression
Me happy
Yes it comes
Within and then radiator
It causes
To interpret everything around us
Andover
Is not accurate
Exactly
Say it
I've said the
Another Mormon
Mentally illness
Podcast
But it is always
You know well
Ben's dad
There's like no
You had things that made
You have never felt a deep and unending sadness come from
From within you
Trying to eat
Much like other people of that
I'm accusing others
Well now you have a secondary diagnosis
Batman goes on to say
Bombshell
Display out in
And Ivanka pretty hot
Jon rappoport back talking about the number one mind control program at u.s. colleges
So-called
The moment that came into the left
So-called so-called that that
Undermine
How could you have any confidence
In literally any
Somebody is call
What is the so-called investigative report
Also I noticed
He's doing a lot of this
And the Trump does all the time
Play Trump stolen from Ikea
Cast
Whatsoever
For any of them
That defines any of the show
Psychiatrist can diagnose you
Your child student at a college with anything that he wants to
Square
Emmaus Hammer is drugs
And in case you're thinking of trying to worm out of my argument here and say what we know
But all these mental disorders are chemical imbalances in the brain
First of all
Baseline normal
Cast for
What a normal Baseline chemical balance in the brain is
FairPoint
There is no necessary way to
To tell what is normal
But that does not prove his point
It's a fair point but it's
Not don't prove anything
And I've documented through a mission
By dr. Ronald pies who is she know one of these erudite psychiatry
So fake
Resume this long retired now Emeritus editor
Until want who said
So that doesn't even hold up
Are you saying that doctor pies called something I looked into this I found the article that he took the
Best rum
A visit from the psychiatric times
This was
An article called psychology
Psychiatrist new Bryant
And the legend of chemical imbalance it's from 2011
I did a chemical imbalance
Being responsible
Holy for mental illness
Is
An urban legend never Theory seriously propounded by well-informed psychiatry
But he goes on to explain
He's quoting
National Institute
Mental health director
Thomas
As Intel describes
Is the new model
Conditions such as schizophrenia or bipolar disorder
Genetic variation
Delete dysfunction in multiple complex
Complex brains
However the particular symptomatic manifestations in a given
Is phenotype
Is partly dependent on the person
We met hypothesize
This is
The giving developmental eBay
In various neural
The young boy or girl may be predisposed to the use of certain dysfunctional cognitive strategies
For example viewing everyone in the environment
Is uniformly
Or rejecting
Wow that's a really well said really well-thought-out really well
I don't think
Now
You know
Paint me wrong
I don't think that
Was very well represented
No
Six way of pointing out every
Is that
Even if you have the
Genetic
What
Whether or not you would call it a
Dysfunctional
There are certain
Trade-offs
With my experience
There's always been
It gives you power up
If you think that you suck
Sometimes you'll work harder than everyone else
Too complacent
But the other things
Is that it
Is
Relevant
Where You Are
Growing up in
Is the blasting
Whatever you know
You can have a Layton
Psychiatric
Conditioned it'll never be set off because you
Live the right Circle
The same condition
Somebody
Lately different world a maybe
Genetics
But you're going to react
Different symptoms
Cuz you're dealing with it
An environment that
Coming out in his
Insert
Situations
Even if
In even if
About those College
Feels like it's in a
Somebody may have
One illness
Or another one
But they're both exhibit
Symptoms
X wear
If you go through the
Bipolar disorder
It's really hard
To diagnose because
It may be that you're so
Symptoms are exact
Disease or exactly the same as that busy
And so you wind up going through all these do
Because
You don't actually know what your
Underlined Pro
You just know s***
Yeah
Yeah yeah yeah
So it's a well-thought-out
And you should be the M rated as editor of
Black shut up.
You do good work I wish you didn't drive it
Car with so many clouds
Batman
What he's saying is
Is a really bad representation of what doctor pies
More or less out of context because the actual quote sounds good for
Has is saying is essentially
That the idea of a chemical imbalance
Is a simplistic inaccurate way to look at it
These are the brain that would cause
Chemical differ
So it isn't it isn't a reputation of
Did the idea that your brain chemistry is different
It's just that the brain chemistry
Is not really what we're talkin about
Not really rapper
Preventative
My point is
In the way he is
Doing that for
For 20 years a tornado
Why wouldn't he at least have read the full article if you did pull out the
First five
It was the first leg he got what he wanted and then did not bother to read the rest
Case for 20 years what are you
Why you call him and ask him what he meant by that instead of pulling out of context quote
What are you actually do some investigation
What do you what do you doing how could you get ahold of doctor
A great tweet that was
Is the picture of Jeff sessions
Sessions looks like a baby who is turned old by which BS
Show all these college students
And everybody really are
Completely submerge see the psychiatrist who will say
The antidepressants Prozac Zoloft Paxil and so forth
In my article
Which is up now at Infowars
Number one
Mind control program u.s. colleges you can see
The effects of these drugs
As cited in study after study after study and there
Influence how they push people over the edge into committing violence
Violet drink
Tequila yes could be throwing a rock through a window
But it could also be murder
Could also be mass murder could also be suicide which walking serious stuff here as
The result of these
SSRI as they're called antidepressants
And that's just one class of drug
What
Barrel roll
Major tranquilizers
Sword neuroleptics
The first of which was
It's unfortunate because there is
Reality
Some people
Often times in a little bit later in the his special report
Dangerous to go off of medication
But you end up seeing Revo with people who have fallen off my
So that was very accurate
There are negative responses to medication
Negative
Responses to not
Searching out
To be a
There's not going to be
You are no and even then
If you are going
You seek out medic
You're not doing
Girls are not doing a good someone Shanghai
Because you're struggling
Unless you're on
TV show
TV show yet
Getting help all of them literally every reality show
But like
I know a number of people who are mentally ill
Consider getting help and I always tell them you know I can't tell you what to do
I really think
But there's help you want to go I'll give you some
Resources
When I try and help people as much as I
Never follow through
Bia
Is is Bizarro
You can go in
Laughing Gopher One session in the never go back even then
I'm not going to say
I think I see
The way that he's putting
Force
Is such a Negative
One of the hardest parts about having
Mental illnesses
Sometimes
Phresher
And that's not
Feeling like your
Forced to go
But that's like your no your
Your friends are putting this
The pressure on you
You should go get help and it makes
Feel
It makes you feel like you're
Yeah but they want actually putting it is more like
Guys out there with butterfly net
He's a he's a
No he's been
He's very he's very much angry
Right now in my monotone voice
This next clip is where it spins into a little bit of like wacky
Conspiracy territory
They are creating
Just because it was just because of where the eclipse started when he says they bought the drugs not
I want a psychiatrist to give him the drugs
Look I want to be sure that I'm not giving him like false contacts
Right
This with gun
Psychiatrist with tail shape
Is that mean
That means that your ability
Physiologically as a human
The great reference on this is Peter break-ins book toxic Psychiatry 1991 Saint Martin's press
Which should be on every bookshelf
No
U.s. colleges
Control
Psychiatry is basically a mind-control operation MK Ultra
Arbitrary
Giving you the sense that you have a mental disorder and now you're a victim and therefore you have sir
Privileges and rights and so forth I'm triggered I need to say space microaggressions
The drugs are in fact scrambling your brains
What else do you need
Display
Psychiatry is a mind control program
HD MK Ultra
Of the CIA
Not even trying to hide it anymore they're just giving it to you here we are
There's something called the Freedom of Information Act
They would love to
Still be hiding at no no no he's talking about just like
Reminder driving mainly about MKUltra a program that Andre back in the 70s
Even trying to hide it anymore
Like
Totally understand
If we live
In the 19
Yep cuz you do have those
People who are out of f******
Movies
For twenty years
Conspiracy blogs
It like that
Who wins if you have Motors
Who's who's winning
Why is it always nobody wins everybody just loses
Possible paths he wants the argument to go down and never really gets
The first paralysis or whatever in your f***** up then you
Just become like
That's what they want
Population
About to bring Dead zombies
People to do she know it's silly
But then the other one
You take these pills
They scramble your brain
And because you have this
Mentally ill victim mentality
You go out and you start yelling the black lives matter
And you're going to end up causing a race war
I think that's the other argument that he can't fully flashout
But that's kind of what he
That's kind of dog whistle be within your right
Black Saturn
Rates is really bad transmission
Right cuz he's an old scared
He's an old
Scared man who's mad that
That was
What was The Dark Knight Rises
God damn picture
Cuz it's too much for one man to
Everytime I hang out on the couch
Nobody
A picture and everybody take
I've been waiting for a really long time just
Because of how much I'm fascinated by that picture
I want to get a really high pixel version of it so I can zoom in and see what the payment is
The TV show then had then
And hence I want it I want to get a really slick a megapixel version of it
Make a shirt of that
Precursor of the picture
Where is
Where is he
I have no f****** idea he's in the middle of
It looks like
He's in the bayou himself
He's got bodies in his f****** shed
He is one of like all of these dudes
New Skype
And how's the fourth hour
Anthony cumia has it on
Studio and stuff like that
But the rest of them Skype Tower or just in rooms
Like it's it's weird and his room is the most
Baron its God
How great would it be if they were all in the same house I just had different oh my God
Like like confessional on a reality
Weirdos who are Alec Alex Jones Associates living under one house
Babe.
They are already doing that
How long before they eat each other
Put all of the conspiracy
People in the same house
Econo Lodge Poconos
Sooner or later they're going to eat one of
Right
What are yeah I made if you cut them off from the outside world like they do in Big Brother
I have to assume that everything is
Okay so I think a lot of people who are into the
Conspiracy narrative
Have I don't know what
Bias would be
But they believe that things are moving faster than they actually are
Okay crash
The Temper of their like
Interfere
Coming
You cut them off from news
I think their natural fear that things are moving fast
Quit within a week
Fibula
We're cut off from the outside world
Cut off the Second Amendment right
Start what with the amount of
What time Alex Jones talks about cannibalism there is a part of me that thinks
He's always like this closed
Tappan Lake
Special report about that new show The Saint
The Clarita diet
What's that
Apparently a show starring
Don't don't worry about it
Michael
Mike know who's that Drew Barrymore
Drew Barrymore
Okay
Normalizing
No that's pretty much
That's pretty much as far away from normalizing cannibalism is
You know what I think I think
Different by differ
Okay because you know like your ass would be like a much more fatty
Roosevelt
What humans taste like
Your bicep
Rihanna
Yeah it would be more like
The white meat
Okay I had a long conversation with my doctor
And like
Lost his teeth eating people
Because
Most of their bodies muscles
If it's the superior me
A lot of muscles are slow twitch muscle they don't have to move
Okay I'm so there's are the fat marble
That's why you have the red meat there
I think your ass would be like red meat
And maybe your thighs
I meant your ear like bicep would be white meat
I would probably go by
YouTube I think so
I'm a chicken poultry kind of got everybody
What type of what part of a man would you eat
The new corner on this
I got a high five
Alright alright we got to come back to the center also hit us up on Twitter at knowledge
Underscore
Alright
Fun
You talk to more b******* and then he goes to break
He introduces a
Clip
We're not going to listen to but it's cliff
That goes back to
Fears about agenda
20%
College students in the US are being diagnosed or treated for mental inventory
These are nothing more than psychiatric clinics
They are
Little produce violence and craziness and insanity
That's why
Where the insanity begins
That word comes up
Okay
Take a break in a couple minutes but I want to tell you
After we come back from the break stay with us because
What I'm talking about is my control
What Rob do in his report which is coming right up is talking about
Is over
Our physical world
Through Agenda 21
That's actually some pretty good music
The clothes out on the
He's right the Mind Control mask
Masters 2020
That's the little bit like Max Fury Road it's a little bit like the guy on the guitar
I noticed some Bumper Music that he plays like Alex Jones plays on the show
You assume the artists
Don't know
Feather being used with mobizen
Extreme Ways
Spelling of music
Commercials and stuff
Money to charity
You can't do that
Play Store we can do that do that with
Without movies cancer
I don't know yeah he might have some sort of a deal with
Music deal where you can
It's about that
Kia's
Morrissey
Yeah
That's the only way.
Support mental illness more than this special reports is play some f****** motivation
Commercial to come back and they play this long
Special Report by Rob do about
Right
It's more completely unfounded bulshit
Want to put you into inner-city ghettos
Then where you'll have a cough and apartments all the same
You want to look into Agenda 21 I have no
Nursing cover get on the show
Read up on it
Realize why it's all bulshit
Not
Suggest
About the age that pee
Should be allowed to drink
It's a terrible name
So comes back from break after this
Special Report
A case study
About what
That everyone should f****** listen to
Scared accordingly
Excellent
John report back so you saw that
Traffic report by Rob
That was a terrific
Completely unrelated
Now you going to have people
Desperate
And somebody's going to say well you should really see somebody
You should talk to a professional
If you are desperate
Please talk to me
What is a is a tabby there is
That Agenda 21 is going to make people sad and then people will be like you should go to a therapist
So like
The sad world is going to be happening
Because the elites are going to force us into inner-city ghettos with no choice
Therapist will
I don't know
It's dumb
Scientology psychiatrist control the world
Are the elites also
I don't I don't
Propping up the Psychiatry industry
As a front
For their mind
Controlpro
You what
Not wrestle with at all like why
Speculative
A couple possibilities
The endgame for the psychology
As we get into so many times
We all get into trouble
Sota Ken's NY
I hate to sound like Young Jeezy
But then what
Point what's you have a brain-dead population that is
Is unable to work
Yeah
So now you just have potatoes who's got a whole world of potatoes
The economy then is an image in his head
I guess what I'm at
Psychiatrist
Delighting
It hurting people really good question does he think psychiatry
Start in on it or does he think that
That they're just
Like they're just the Nazis at Auschwitz
Just like
Thinking they're going to work everyday like regular Joes I sincerely don't know and I don't think he does
I really don't think he knows what is argument
Man
Popeyes
Next episode
What's happening outside in the world
What do you say
Join the crowd everybody loves you. We're all getting diagnosed this week
This is diagnosis Suites
Skeletal figure
And they're all saying what Hillary Clinton
It takes a village to get
Population
Faces and making you a
Destroying the middle class
And basically
You know gutting the nation
It's time to get diagnosed spokes
It really takes
A village to get diagnosed
It's weird how everything he saying is correct
Even though he thinks
If you saying it
Like you should get that nut
It's a good idea to have a support structure
Yeah I've also
Known some people
Interesting thing that I just realized
I've known a couple people who've gone to therapist and psychiatrist
And they be like
It's not
Every
Psychiatrist that doesn't
I want to find an issue that they can try and help with medication
Appropriate I think maybe you should talk to somebody
Did that does exist in the world
Not everybody's trying to get everyone in on a shell game like you have high blood pressure but maybe you
You should just stop eating garbage
He's about to get to this case study and I'd like you to remember
I'm going to try so hard
This case study is anecdotal
It's from a book
Which means it's
Always the most reliable information
Probably there's a name given but it's obviously it's a good thing
It's a good thing that you're going to do case studies or protect privacy but also this book was written
26 years ago
Before he even started his investigation before
These State pills we have now.
Discovered back then
Think about therapies that we've developed didn't exist 26
There's a lot
Banking was still a legitimate therapy
Corporal punishment
Yeah
Crazy now right
Nuts that seems bananas
Nice was weird
That's a story for another day
You may have to blast
Damaged are we going to get into a trigger warning for you right now
This case study is to
Takes a village mentality
A global village mentality
Mind-blowing I'm going to try to raise a document up here for myself you will not see it hopefully
Technology
I don't think you understand what's
Scream like that what's
The Skype connection was actually being relayed
Video camera
I'm not sure he knows so he thinks every move something on his
Green it will play on it
Infowars.com
And that's not like
But also
Where is Alfred Alfred
Okay we're still here
I'm your basic Primitives
Brighter okay. He sounds like it's a short passage from Peter brigands
1991 book toxic Psychiatry 1991 scissor Revelation okay
I'm just a little bit
When she first became depressed and sought psychiatric help with the recommendation
University Health Service right talk about Agenda 21
When was Agenda 21
Stream
The Proto
Animes that you came up with
Look at my note there
Look at my no right there
There we go
Book before agenda Social Club
I had that note just in case I forgot I could so eat that was so obvious
Yeah yeah
Analogy
Nothing
Trying to shift back
Whatever conclusion you already have in your mind
Bugattis so sleepy
I mean I don't know times or anything but it has to be like
3 p.m.
And well
A lot of stress instead of moral support and insight
Haldol
Antipsychotic
Major tranquilizer those are all names for that class of drugs over the next four years
Physicians watched her deteriorate neurological
Dyskinesia
Motor brain damage
The diagnosis
Even when she was overtly twitching in her arms and legs instead they switched her from one neuroleptic to another
Including the stelazine in Thorazine
Actually rebuilt
Made the diagnosis
Permanently physically disabled
With a 30%
And then bragging says my medical evaluation described her condition
Grossly disfigured
Severely disabled human being who can no longer control her body
Involving the face neck head shoulders
Nearly the entire body
Difficult
Be standing sitting or lying down and the difficulties worsen as she attempts to carry out voluntary actions
Nearby furniture
She could hold the lip to a couple only with great difficulty at cetera at cetera
Seriously afflicted
Drugs
Can't have anything remotely resembling
A normal
Life
That's that's tragic
That's really sad
I mean
That can happen
Literally anywhere with
Just about anything
Sure
But if you want something she could have tripped
It is one of those things where
She's dealing with such a
Unique Circa
Hey such a
Such a rare
Always
Crushes me
Hey
We had one guy
This happen
And it is a tragedy
It really is
Worst case scenario kind of
Bad drug reactions
And that it's
That that happened
It really is
It's not indicative of the
Psychiatry is a hole
So I was thinking there's how many it's it's one of those things where it is like
How many pesos
Per year are killed by doctor
Error as opposed to what's going
A lot of pee
People are killed by doctor
There are a lot of that is like in surgery
Yeah or or just any number of
Misdiagnosis
All of the all of the
Please different possible out
Still rather go to a f****** doctor then.
What if it's dr. Wallach
If it's not your Wallach I would take my cat
He's a really good Veterinary apparently it
Yeah it's somebody else's cat super strong
Also the use of case studies is
Illustrative of
You know points you want to make but it's not necessarily it's it doesn't
It's not really a fair way to make an
Because like if you want to pin all of that on
Like
The art of Psychiatry if you want to make the argument a there are some
No one's going to no one's going to just before Point good
My uncle was a psychiatrist
Kill Roberto
You didn't
Okay are we sure
Yeah
I don't I don't know how much I want to say about him
How to spell this out
Okay
I'm not sure I want to tell you
I don't know his business
I agree I don't I don't know how much is PS4
Publix
I took
With your weiner
Was
And I think he still is
Psychiatrist
And he had a bunch of books about multiple personalities
Which is
Really
Like hot.
Yeah it's now dissociative
Understanding of what it is
His whole thing and you wrote like two or three books about it
He believed
It is clinical opinion
That
Multiple personality disorder is caused by Satanic ritual abuse
And the Cure is G
Right
So he has these books
And they're full of case study
They're full of case studies with a pseudonym
And these horrifying stories
And then Jesus
Helping out
Anti gay conversion therapy
Hobo
If you knew more about how much avail
But the point I'm trying to make is that like when you have these case studies they can sort of
Tell the narrative that you want
To tell without it actually being really based
In
Butta Butta
Short Circuit
We love the story tell me the story I get all caught up
Got a middle of got it
Another human being sure
And instead
Warp your perception but then
Go to the word
Statistics
In the diagnostic manual
Still in Port
Very small
Some people have said they were
Cured
Because of an
Anti-gay Kim
Sure some of them have
Whether or not they have is they probably haven't but they said
Do you know where you can point to those case studies
As being
Oh
This works
Large
Majority
Are not help
Only damn
Only hurt by people
Hurting
People with that narrative
It is a narrative that deserves
I agree
But it is
Is a f****** damaging their deal with
Reality it deals with the story you want to tell
Story that my uncle and want to tell is that this people
He love Chinese letters
Fievel Goes Up there's no cats in America the story
Where's my uncle would want to tell these people told him about
The tricomp want to tell you there's no cats over here
Data is your telling a story that fits
The store you've already
Decided to tell the truth
Dictate where The Story Goes
Confirmation bias
Batman
Love
Confirmation bias
Where do you get the little bit real with it
He warns you that withdrawals are real thing
The wrong
Do not suddenly stop taking your medication absolutely not
Your psychiatrist
If you are going
Haitian please do so respond
Things they will help you they don't will there
You're going to do what they're going to try and help you
They like it
Yeah
Directions I don't want to do that imagine being a doctor
And having
Some parent come up to you
Beyonce
Oh I don't want my kid
Can you imagine
How frustrated
You would be most angry moment I get angry now whenever I
Hear somebody say
I'm not sure about vaccine
I'm not sure
Makes me want to f******
Punchable face
Yeah no no
F****** hate did you do you have polio shut up
Yeah
Everyday you don't have polio you should thank a vaccine
Do vaccines
Is mumps and rubella
Vaccine Awareness Day
Warren's and I want you to make sure you understand
Withdrawing
Rapidly from any psychiatric drug can be worse
Been taking the drug we're talkin about
Agreed
Very dangerous and even life-threatening
Problems
So this is in no way a recommendation to anybody who may be on one of these drugs to just get it off of it
Reagan.com breggin calm is the website
Peter breggin
He's writing a book about withdrawing from psychiatric drugs you recommend should be done by a professional
Nose
So I think you're probably getting the message now and its investigative report on the number one mind control
Program the colleges
Psychiatrist
Jesus superblue
Fluoride free toothpaste my wife read about this she was very enthusiastic
After being sold out for Infowars life.com its back
Gums Research indicates contribute to the development can contribute to development of heart disease heart
Heart attacks
When bacteria infect your gums you can enter the bloodstream and even contribute to blood clots
He goes on for like 3 minutes about this great toothpaste
Hey and you know what
If you stop using that toothpaste
No negative side effects or withdrawal regular toothpaste
Super Bowl
It's created by Alex Jones
You know they do they
They get it from Tom's of Maine
Alex keep doing this
We get it from the top organic you know what's up in the name
Vulnerable
Subcon
Space from Tom's of Maine and then he puts
Colloidal silver and iodine
In the toothpaste
Along with
Peppermint oil and tea tree oil
Dangerous than the colloidal silver when the iodine
X
The peppermint is a little too strong for kids
So the coming out with a bubble gum flavor
Do you know
It's it's coming
Bubble gum flavor was very important to me taking medication
It wasn't
So important
They actually had like Radioactive
Toothpaste
Did not know that everything everything was Radioactive
The people are like oh look at how amazing all of these are radioactive Things Are
The people would actually have glow-in-the-dark teeth you would clean your floor with glow-in-the-dark because it was Radioactive
Open had
They would detonate a nuclear
A nuclear bomb right
And the
Thinking about is
After that
When you have that giant cloud
Maybe we should have an army
March through that
So they ask
Sew-in no just to hide
Just to hide in the smoke
Okay so
Thousands of soldiers
Wild up having all kinds of radioactive
Diseases
Because they didn't understand
That was bad for you
So people lost their teeth because they did all of this shed
Now
You know why we don't learn about that
Or that globalist probably globalism
Man I wish I could
I wish I had that
Ameridial
He has
This this life is just about the fear
This is fear-mongering not the movie Fear
Nordstrom
It's just the fear
He wants you to be scared
And also
He has this
Awesome roleplay
Videos of the fake doctor
Thank God his role play so far has been one
Confusing
So many different ways
Okay
What else on this merry Voyage Through Insanity created by
You'll see in the article
That I wrote about this
Puppet Infowars and also at no more fake news
Even trucks
Can have sent a Stickley
Dangerous effects
Psychotic breaks
Literally all drugs
All the drugs
And think about this
This so-called you know idhd everybody's getting it get so no drugs
The drugs
Are very very closely related to
Do you mean Other Drug
AR
Amphetamine type drugs
Boys in Forest now have it up on the screen of some of the effects of Ritalin paranoid delusions paranoid
Psychosis
Visual hallucinations auditory hallucinations
Can surpass LSD
Introducing bizarre experiences
That sounds fun
I want to check in here
Radioactive
It was a song by the
Firm supergroup made up of Paul Rodgers
From Bad Company
Yes guitarist Jimmy Page
Chris Lane
Manfred Mann's Earth band
Manfred Mann's Earth band is now my favorite band
Revved up like a deuce if you don't want to I don't want to believe that they made me
I want to just believe it was people called Medford man
Earth band
Just needed to prove that Radioactive
Time radio app
Started screaming aggressiveness insomnia
Decreased REM sleep
On and on
He's a listening side effects
They are very small
0 I don't know if I've ever seen any
Drug that had like
Hey
No side effects Norco
Perfect
Placebos work
By the way
Super male Vitality is right next to the words placebo
It's probably
Hypertension seizures
Convulsions
Who's
Familiar with in phetamine track drug
I really wish
This is where we need like a babadook
Hanging toe
Fisherman's elbow
That if you take them for a certain length of time
After the initial
Wow where's our flight boy I've got increased Clarity this is terrific I can study and someone so on
He's on
I was lost with r
Did you ever see an evening out occurs
A crash occurs in many people
They crash
A speed crashes what they used to call it on the street
The person is in
Huddling in a corner
Considerate
Considering that situation
Accomplished
Back to the
What is the psychiatrist say well
You're saying here
It's obvious to me
That you
Are really suffering
Clinical depression
Yeah
Well I mean
I'm assuming that's related to the drug that you gave me for ADHD of course not
It couldn't be any relationship to the draw
3D HD no this is the emergence of a new
Condition
Clinical depression and so I'm going to put you on Zoloft
The Xenomorph
The brain destroying mine destroying circus moves in two-faced
Because now what we're talkin about here
Is the person the child
It's in the system
And I'll give you a potential face
Wait so nobody would you like
This is a potential
He's just
Making up face right think he's giving you what could happen
It sounds like you said maybe nobody's ever made
Super Mario Brothers is real I think there's a part of him that is sort of wrestling with internet
I don't have any
For what I'm saying
Pencil P3 is kind of the little cracks
In the armor showing of like
You hear anybody on Infowars do that thing where they're like
Consider the person
The child
The college student is like
You only needed to say one of those things
Yeah I'm staying all of those things
You're doing some b******* Phyllis
Your your chances are size of your font
214 instead of
You're pretending you're me talkin about the firm
Brian anti-depression
Down back to the psychiatrist psychiatrist
Cream band
Behind all of this is bipolar that's what's going on
We used to call manic depression
You have your ups and you have your down
Doctor's exam
I love I love having my mental illness
You got your UPS
You got your Downs
You definitely don't have two weeks where you're f****** lunatic
You being crazy these also sort of making the argument that like
Amphetamines
Eminem Zoloft which
Doesn't bring you down
The UPS of amphetamine
Not at all not at all
Very
Dumb
Uninformed
Yeah it's it's like he's never talked to anybody who has mental illness
Anyways you know it was okay
He'll talk to
One person who has
Mental illness
I'm talkin about what Batman looks into the mirror he sees the joker I'm not sure that he's ever really had a conversation
Never had a conversation with anybody else married
I found that out
Alright
Let's meet her
I would love to
Has she ever written anything for a
He's pissed off that he doesn't put up that picture
Skyping with your friend it put up that goddamn pickle
What is this
I'm just an old
I have to assume she's like 70 also right
Not banging around the twenty-year-old
John
Please come down
Stairs
I put you on my picture John Rappaport
Slightly domineering wife
Because John Franklin Rappaport the third Michael Rapaport
I'm doing my research I'm up here in my ad and you have been working on this for 20 years
Don't forget to call
Vera's Bakery
Very analytical
I got nothing
But respect
Deliver this man
You'll find out
I'm the professional here we get such an idea
Some crazy stuff somewhere
Medicines used to treat them here
So now we get into valproate
These are much heavier drugs
Is much heavier
Potential effects
And the circus goes on
You a texter
I'm toxic Psychiatry about the suit
Very well.
You've got kids with colleges going
Anywhere they don't know
To the left to the right
Just about the end of the Special Report
So you know
He doesn't long fantasy role-play with a doctor where do you like
Maybe these drugs that you're giving me or make me feel bad and they're creating new things
Long roleplay
Do you know
Situations
Heavier and heavier medication
And then you heard that from that book from 26 years ago
But if it's not the outcome
You could be on campus being crazy
You're not making a gateway drug marijuana thing
He know who he wishes
He's not even close to that making a point
There's nothing there
No his point is that literally anything can happen at any time and you should always be afraid
Respect scientologists more than this
Just stand on their origin
I know it.
Secret about how much they hate
Psychiatrist that's what I'm say
Well
I think the pill
L.ron Hubbard
Wasn't allowed to be
Become a psychiatrist
And so Scientology was born
And purely out of spite
Scientology
Scientology is bad
But you do have to respect a religion that was not built
On anything other
Then pure spice
Yeah sure
That's badass got to give him credit for that
The fact that man is
Noozhawk
If you synthesize his ark
It is
Trigger culture
Space space I completely forgot we started with trigger right there's no way that that has anything to do with
What because that's where his argument begins
There's no such thing as
If you're okay
It's also
Because all you read
Yeah version of the world
Oh look at these uppity black
Is there still mad that people want to put on top really wish you hadn't so happy
Bums me out whenever she know
Aesthetic
Yeah
Scatman Crothers
Give me the video for Scatman John.
Also
Yeah
Well he died at the end
The Shining
If
If we get to the point
Where we can speak to Scatman Crothers
No
Get to the point
Where there are no Nations to this show
God
I will legally change my name to Scatman cat
I will I swear to God I will hold you to that
I will hold you to that
Look
I will take never I never wanted
6 / this
More that I do right now
I also get a scat.
Tattoo
VIP codes to get a discount right now
All right so close this out with a sort of sympathy
This conclusion
Looks good jobs
If you ever leave
He didn't show I need to find out how many people in Congress are on psychiatric drugs
You're watching that
I think that's the next step
Because
Who played
He's talking about all this
Crazy Bowls
It's irrelevant
We are nearing the end of the shower
Takeaways
The number one mind control program u.s. colleges psychiatry
25% of all college students in the US
Mental disorder
Explain
The bar that doesn't card
Yeah
What is it
The are a man
He's really trying to hold you down
The raas event
Can smoke weed in my room now hunt you've never been a little Bodega
Charged
To get snacks
Maybe it's that maybe that's brain control maybe I don't know I certainly use a lot of it when I was in college
Bookstore
Because
The bookstore
Exactly books in there
Is the book watch
I would go there
And I would get like
And I was drunk
And I would charge
My student
It would show up to my parents
It was a student book
Store I do never question that brain control
The triggering thing in the whole movie
I'm a victim
So I can just
Be
Victimized by anything
The grand scheme
Is C-section the psychiatric drugs scrambling brain chemistry that make kids
And say
The strangest things
David
Spring Jam
As they're developing
Not kidding around here folks
Chemical warfare
It is just
Your Generation by generation now
Cool Monopoly Packer Mental Health
That's where we're at
Roanoke
Thanks John
See you next time
I think he lost it when he was like
This needs to be thrown over the right way
Special Report
We didn't spend any time really address
Racist homophobic
Sexist
All of it is
It's basically
Basically his entire argument is anytime
People do things that
She doesn't think
Are appropriate behavior and that includes
Literally everyone but him and other old white man other group standing up against
Integrated
Costumes is just short for
Literally
Wait a second
These kids don't want to use the bathroom
Gender that they were born with
Guess what that is psychiatrist in drugs
Drugs
Do you know where black people
Came from drugs
He's at
Cuz you know
People have different opinions alive different opinions
And someone who hears this and thinks
All this triggering stuff is a bunch of pussies
What have you
Let's even take a step back
He didn't make
Bombshell there was an hour of him
On the are actual sources we looked into the sources
The underpinning of 25% of the population at campuses
It has a diagnosis
Which doesn't mean anything
If it's not literally true it's not accurate because a lot of people go to doctors to get Adderall
Very least
It is a gross mischaracterization of
What the problem Act
Etsy
Very least
Now
If you add in all the things we know about him
It is most likely a
Huge shitshow of entitled white male b*******
And big
And then the other step we have to take
Oh yeah we can surround
But the other piece of it
Is the
Advise he's giving
Or the assessment
Is literally Dane
Yeah you and I are both people who struggle with mental illness throughout our lives
I don't want to end this on a Saturday
I think it's I think it's a hopeful note to say that quite literally
I would be dead if I had not gone to see if
Exactly what I was going to say I was going
To say had friends who have killed
Yes
A lot of it had to do with them not
Seeking help the way they need
And that's real
Isn't that good
What you're doing is a disservice to people who need help
When you look at it realistically and say hey you know what there is overdiagnosed
6 / 4
Prescription
That's a realist
Discussion to have
System that has
Flaws and you point those out and you search to correct those
That is good
When you say a system has flaws so that mean
Every single part of that is wrong
You get
The
Government we have now
Yeah and that's why I wanted to cover this
A little bit outside of what we normally do but it's just like
You're such a f****** a****** in this is what Alex Jones chooses to put on his show
So it is still him
Yeah it's not like
It wasn't literally him saying these things
He was tacitly endorsing these two days he was talking about how this is some of the most powerful
Important information
God and it's not information
We we would like
One thing that I do like about this
That I do like
I find this I find this to be fun thing
Yeah but occasionally there is something it's like
Oh I
I think we
Are fighting this f****** horrifying monster
Like
Alex Jones is a wackadoo crazy cat
In a way that is
Farless
Fun
It doesn't matter cuz no one listens
David goddamn the only platforms
F****** Jon rappoport has is his
Angelfire
Bulshit
And then also the fourth hour of Alex Jones
Turn it off for the 4th
I would hope so
Irresponsible
I'm very dangerous
It's not irresponsible it's an active
Attack
It really is
But the attack is he response
Yeah
And if you responsible for anyone to broadcast
That and I apologize
We just did
But we did with commentary
Anytime somebody broadcast
Fifty Shades
The movie irresponsible irresponsible
As long as we're making fun of it though
Pretty great
Guys the bottom line is if you need help go I'll talk to somebody
If you don't feel about it
No one is going to force you down some weird rabbit hole
You don't want to take a pill
Don't take
You have your own agency
The proliferation of the internet being tons of information you can find out about any pill that someone wants
Are prescribed for you
And you can
Yeah look it up and decide for yourself
If it's a path you want to go down
But
And it's also you shouldn't diagnose yourself
No you can come in you can go into a conversation with somebody thinking that you have
A basic understanding of
But it should be a conversation
Yeah
It's not a dominant thing from one side or the other
Find a psychiatrist who wants to work with you
And not tell you what to do and also don't tell the psychiatrist went to
But that's that's the bottom line
Dirty I've bailed on a couple many
Many in my life
Popeyes
Seems like a cool dude he seems like a cold there but anyway the most the Emirate as editor of blank
Yada yada yada
Have you found a
Please
Look into it
I love you
Third world needs you
Thanks for listening Jordan I love you
I love you
Has been so much fun
F***
Sport universe that's not a literal thing that we're asking
I hate it did not look like he would enjoy it I am
The best started
You were trying to wrap up the episode and then you wanted to everybody
Physical therapy in my face
Oh no why did I start saying that Jesus
Email us at knowledge gmail.com
Twitter and knowledge please repost WhatsApp
Give us a Michael Michael gave us a nice five star review
We're just a couple of policy
Yes
Alexandra Thurston color