Alexandra Thurston color
Is there a
Just because you got to say it up top
Turn off now but you won't get the rest
Because I got some stuff to play for you
We're going to plug just ignore this part
Ignore
This isn't for you at 10:30 p.m. tickets
I don't know
Playground cedar.com knowledge
Dash fight
Just be playground.
The playground.
Hell if I know this
I'm still not entirely sure what episode of Alex Jones will be covering still up in the air
To a certain degree
Dash fights
Set the alarm to get to go to the playground theater.com
Figure it out
Cedar later you'll be able to
Arnold Palmer
We're going with light
Roku
The zero calories if you have been drinking that bit in the past
Four different types
Regular
One-third less calories
2/3 less calories
0 caliber
Tons so much
Not nearly that much not a Mystic level
Miss
I know
He is a horrible he went to prison for aggravated sexual assault
Mystikal Mystikal
Very different feel to that one line of his as I can't
Exactly but
Look it look it was shut up
Jordan
The hell
What's up
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
You so much Hannah your sister
Starboy
I'd like to also give a shout out to.
I get it
Say thank you very much
Someone sodomites
I really appreciate it so much thank you
I don't this isn't about money
I just want to have one episode we're like 10 different people decide to become globalist
And we just play that
Forever
We're putting together
We're well on our way toward making that goal
We are on Pace
To make the goal which will force us to start doing
If we join
February 1st we will begin
Breaking down Alex Jones
And my sleep
Schedule
Young Thug
On the broadcast if you have the plug
Now is the time to start
Every mentioned on the last show
We got together this weekend
Try to compile a list of potential things to cover
For live show Saturday 10:30 p.m.
Stingray
Write included on that list was the day ratzinger the old
Pope stepped out
Amazing
And there was a guest host today I don't know if you knew this
Alex Jones is a card
The other another one was the Year in 2012 year
He might get weird about that about the calendar and end overages and shortages
We like to deal with absolutely
Leap years are globalist
Unfortunately I went back to that.
Ron Paul
Good still
Youth in Louisiana
Broadcast
From my hotel room it's terrible is an awful show
To these possibilities and they're just not
No good
But one of them stuck out in my mind
There's like this is going to be a good one
And it turns out it is a good one
And that is
The day after LaVoy finicum
Got shot by the police
Ian that Oregon Oregon Wildlife Preserve
All right there by new Alex would be freaking out
Exact
Coincidence
Listening to old
I listened
That episode earlier today
I won't get into the actual speed
I wouldn't understand why we would have to deal with it
Slightly briefly
I just because they get
Super race
Sad about it but at the same time
Just about a 1/2 bunch of weird false
Military
Occupying a bird Reserve
Get racist is really fascinating and I'm excited to talk about it
Morphis
I don't know what's going on
But he says a couple of things in this episode
That are Beyond The Pale
I told you this before the show
Yeah I stand by it
You have to look at Alex Jones
Completely differently
After you hear a couple of things he says I'm an episode
Just some of the beliefs he has
Where they come from
And how stupid
So we will do that
Climate change is good well that's actually the episode
Nails today
The beginning of the episode Alex Jones talking about how
He doesn't want
Get hot
He doesn't want it to be a hot War
Red Dead
Not shooting
These people to preserve our amateurs
And
Did shouldn't get into a viola
War
Let's not do that
I'm glad you qualified it with
The now
Well that he's into that but also he ends up saying
About his mentality
His personal
Feeling about his place in the world this is this isn't weird stuff
To start out with
The Mormons are littoral birds
I got put the energy for 21 years
Of someone willing to die
Information
Bully
Put present
Martyr
If he says Martin Luther King jr.
But you have to
Build consciousness
Personality
Three months
Surprise
And make the sacrifice
When it's destroyed
As they try to assassinate my character as they try to kill my name
It's already a martyr level
Which humans admire
So
From the jump
We're getting
This idea first of all
Why don't you guys understand that for twenty years I've been building myself up as a
The Martyr that no one will ever murder
I think that's kind of I mean it's indicative of
A real
Mental disorder
Narcissism in there a little
What do you say it isn't like his standard manic
Thing that he gets whenever he gets into
These are
Hyper
Statistic
Bloviating sessions but he gets into
Yeah it's a hundred percent a real thing he believe
I think especially
I think this is him
Externalizing a little bit of stuff
But he generally
Keeps inside
And one of them is that
Don't you guys understand
I'm going to be the hero
When they take me down
I will be the hero
He's creating a stage for himself
To be what
He sees himself to be in his own mind
That's fine
Cuz that's a variant
Interesting psychology
He wants
For the cause
Hold on now
He's making up retard
Right right right
I will
I'm going to make sure
So I look like a victim
Which definitely is in line with all of his at
The fees and what-have-you
This next clip Alex Jones
Gets into how you believe that
The Bundy group has been in
Will traded and there's feds
And s*** like that
Might be
The weird thing is I think he is right
Duwayne
He's like
It's crawling with FEDS
ARS also saying that people who are dressed up like Uncle Sam and all that
They were fed to make people look like assholes
Yeah
Sads
But the Cards Against Humanity
He did that in that
Giant
No he's he's just a
The infiltrator
Middle to end of this clip that
Beagles like code
The bunnies are not them
Operatives
You can listen to him
They're good people
George Washington
They would have been the guy in the trench
They are not
Generals
Think about
You take one good look at him know where they come from they're good people that there was
Redfin
Kronos
Keep talkin about
He's calling himself the general without having to say it them
Ostensibly
Being more active in the same goal
There
Whatever
Can you really disagree with him
Not fully
No he does have a generals
So now
At this point
This is where we start
No certainly not
No
Oh yeah that is true power
No you're not
It's pretty early in the episode
Alex Jones Pitt starts to
To take a pivot
Away from talking about the Bundys specifically
I'm starting to talk about his understanding
Of government
No not that
Is understanding of government
Is understanding
History
And this stuff
Buckin Wild Style
Here's the first one we talked about the intelligence
There's different facts
7 factions we know of Anna CIA
Major factions
Different administrations come in and try to create new faction
CIA
There's Navy versus army that's a football game
Intelligent
Everybody
She's describing Department everybody's
There's a Big Mac
Trying to control manipulated International fax
Alamo
So that that's that's
Inspections
Department
Right and then he expands it without
Ready talked about International tax
The cia's also oversees who knows
Because I would say
For someone in Alex Jones's position
Specific about what he's talking
If there's 7 factions in the CIA
Come out with it
Possible
Look you're in the CIA
This faction
How could there be seven
Infection enough ideological differences
Probably not in the CIA what is it
I want more
BLTs in the lunchroom there's not even enough primary colors for them to all have different colored neckerchief
That's true
If you
The damn green Equity people over there don't do not
Do not set trip
With the f****** factions the CIA
We also know that there's only like
Percent of them killing the rest of our chicken
Cast of Glee
20%
Who cares anyway
This is the most important news of the day
Maybe so far
And not the day the show cuz right
This
Next clip
Foundry f***** up
This put your mic down for this
Oh boy oh boy oh boy
You're about to get
A history lesson
Courtesy
Emerick Jones
I just put that there too
Clear that there's no breakthrough
Lompoc
President Andrew Jackson
A year out
You know they say
Colonel Travis this is inside baseball but it's
Down to the Alamo
To create
A chain reaction
Because they were hard
Hardcore funk
Questions
But they basically followed a rosicrucian
Founding father
Basically
Deal
They really wanted to
They wanted to die
Sacrifice against
They don't really make
Travis
You're all going to die
Step across the line
Across just like the
Year before
And then they found
Some battles
It was a l
On that letter to my family
When he left his shine
My mom side
The other letter
That I'm not giving up
Victory or death
Antenna
And they were going
West Sam Houston
Under the direct
States of America
That was a sovereign
Country
The British Empire
Real planning real sacrifice
Real long-term commitment
He's implying that the M3 of the Merced
A couple questions
The first one I don't have any question
For what
Who is clearly self
Everything about that makes perfect
Do you know anything about Colonel Travis Colonel William Travis
Anybody who
Overrun by thousands
Soldiers because he's bad at
Position
Probably didn't do so well
Interesting
Bye
Get out of San Antonio
Play Pandora
Hickory Old Hickory
Planned
To tell Houston to say that to Travis
So Travis would be like
F*** you and do what
Covert action
Action at this point sections of the CIA 70
Four of them didn't even know
Now I think is the most appropriate time ever to talk a little bit
About Colonel William
Travis I've never heard that song
Before so clearly I must
I'm going to give you a bit of a history lesson
Tickle the s*** out of me today
I initially thought there's no way I'm going to be able to get this episode together
To do it but
I did
This
Is a fun story
So William Travis was born in 1809 in South Carolina
Is born in South Carolina
12 parents move to Cobb County in Alabama
Like a newly
Brent there's a lot of
Steersman chip
His uncle Alexander founded a school in Sparta Alabama
Who's apart of Connor
William
Chance to attend it
He was able to get an education
He go on to be a school teacher teacher's assistant
Different
School where he taught for less than a year
Because of
Coronavirus
16 year olds
So they married
Alabama
They married when she was 16 likely because he got her pregnant
Some time frame record show that you
You probably gave birth before they were married
Before the marriage
I am back then that was
That was not good
At that point
Eastside
Anymore
Answer human-sized wife moved and he just started
Clear Bond
Clairborne Clairborne
Play Bar
Hoof
Name
He's going to start studying law
Rebecca and I was really easy
True
As he was studying law he also started a newspaper called the
Claiborne Harold
It okay for a little while
Made a made a little bit of coin but then it started to not make as much money
I got to support my family I have
Have no idea
Not making enough from
From the paper
And the stress of running the paper got so bad
He kept sucking up the paper
He would print advertisements upside down
I never learned to read expiration date
Complete
And
That would go on
How to mirror his future
That I wrote that I'm thrilled with
Mirror his future at the Alamo he would ask for help with the paper
But reinforcements
Square.com
You kept trying to get financial support Noah was helping him out
Used
Terrible place
He passed his law exam
That point borrows $55
Thirty-seven cents
To order
To start
He also borrows $90 to cover his expenses with the Herald
Unfortunately
He wasn't getting any clients for his Law Firm
Because no one needed a lawyer
It was a small f****** town
Who's already had a lawyer trial
There ain't judges
Who mentored him
Disastrous position where you
Spent all this money he's in debt and now we can't even make money doing log
You get nothing
He's getting
Deeper and deeper into debt
It's so he decides to buy a couple slaves
In order to
Problems back then
Play slaves
Cheyenne help out right
But the irony of this
Is B
Silverline
The tragedy of everybody everybody
Is clearly not happy she's going to
Living with this guy whoever's buying a
Travis is not f****** having a great time and of course is slave or not
Who is Manchester
And now it's interesting that you bring that up because
Gated apartment
Stop
So
Shut up
Would you realize
Immediately after you left was a very bad idea
By the time that you stopped
Practicing law
Here
Participate 6 cases
Idiot made $4
His debt at the time was
834.
Which is
Andy Court you tried to argue that his case should be dismissed
Because of infants
Is it bad luck
Because he was so young to be thrown out of court
And the court
Subway
Everybody
Everybody in the court just started laughing
Like a historical humiliation in court
You still owe me money you little baby
That's it
At that point the court clerk issued an order for his arrest
On March 31st
So
At this point
William
The Alamo
More or less
Every starts a little plan with Andrew Jackson
Nope nope nope I feel like we're going to get there
He heard he hears about Texas
Which is at that point estate
And the Mexican Republic
So he's a speculation
And there's a lot of people out there
Lawyers
Answer you like
The other thing is
Has an order for his arrest Alabama
Go figure that one out he's a lawyer so at this point
Believes his wife who is now pregnant
Leaving the rest
This is
Yeah it's Rob
Is it spectacular
Texas
Center city called clock
I'm not sure if that's okay
At that point you set up alarm practice
He starts a militia
And a start agitating against the Mexican authorities
Because bill has their white people around a lot of next
Always shoot
Absolutely
His militia Behavior
Also being conscripted as a soldier and ordered to raise a company of men
Deport the situation in San Antonio
The situation that would end up being the album
Travis considered this is a quote here from an article on it
Disobeying his orders right to Henry Smith
I am willing they anxious to go to defensive backs are but sir
I'm unwilling to risk my reputation
I can't I'm unwilling to risk my reputation by going off into the enemy's country with such little memes
And with them so badly equipped
This is from an article in Texas monthly
Travis hits Stockton Camp waiting for Smith reply which never came
Eventually had no choice but to try John to San Antonio
He had no military experience
Was until recently
Successful lawyer
It was now the lieutenant colonel in the Texas Cowboys
Of course Alex Jones's family knows him
That's the same
Hey I am going
You
Euro Euro down to San Antonio
Point but you're a little ahead of it
So
The picture of
Proto Alex Jones will be complete
Alex Jones is very clearly
A lot of his personality on William Travis
There is no doubt about that
Completely see-through
Bumbling self-motivated prick
You accidentally a lieutenant colonel
Texas Gallery Travis and James
Are the two men
You are supposed to be in charge
Do the companies that are they
Soldiers
And the other in charge of knives
Pretty quickly
Bowie gets
And for all intensive purposes
Travis
Being in charge of all of the people
At the Alamo
He's in charge of the entire force
Hilarious
Travis ends up dying in what is a hopeless War
Cuz you'd only have like a hundred and something people there until Santa Ana
Enforce
Just 10 days before he died
He sent out the following letter
Going to read you the letter that you wrote
You're not far off there are a number letters that I've read of his also that
Predate this letter by like the week
Couple weeks before it all goes down know they're all just like
We need more people to send more armies
3 Days Later another letter like fake
It's rude for me to ask twice
They're asking for Army's like fries
I'll f****** tsuyu
You know I'm going to put out a full-page ad
This point
Before the end
It is not going to work out
Fellow citizens and compatriots I am besieged by a thousand or more of the Mexicans under Santa Ana
I sustained a continual bombardment
Candidate for 24 hours and if not lost a man
The enemy has demanded a surrender at discretion
Otherwise of Garrison is to be put to the sword if the Ford is taken
The cannon shot
And our flag still waived
Probably from the walls
I shall never Retreat or Surrender then I call on you in the name of the liberty of patriotism and everything dear to the Amer
American character to come to our Aid
With all dispatch
Danny is receiving
Daily and will no doubt increase
Three or four thousand in 45 days
If this call is neglected I am determined to
To sustain myself as long as possible
And die like a soldier who never forgets what he's doing his own honor and that of his country
All caps
Victory or death
William Barret Travis
That's what this letter goes out
Has come
Does this letter goes out
People get really
Fired up
Remington Grill
Is because of the like
Pretty well-written letter
F******
Idiot
Bumbling moron this Mister Magoo
Walking around through life screwing up everything
So this is also from that Texas monthly article about him
Got this diary
They're reading over it
And there's one passage anywhere you setting out this like 2 years before he died
I love to my first man
You are so close
You are shockingly flow
There's a passage in his diary says like I was setting off for some city
And it's the only time I had to do so many bogs
Should I couldn't get through
It's the only time that I
Follow through with
Or whatever
And so here's
View from the Texas monthly article
Should bring everything into Focus
Otherwise
The other than that
The log of his law practice
Personal expenses
A document by an abscessed
He lists his shirts and socks
Anylist is sexual Adventure
Someone named Susanna is recorded as his 59th
Conquest he was in 24
Think about that in terms of Alex
150 women before he was 16 claim
I don't know I don't know
That life brief underlined passage the one about not turning back
Is the only moment of personal
The entire document
There is in those words Travis's unstated reproach if
Himself for letting nature dominate his
Intention
He was a vain Booty Man
Idealistic and romance
He worked hard by day and at night
He gambled or consorted with Prost
Attitudes Salon Reading Sir Walter Scott
He was brainy and ambitious in
I'm filled with passionate energy
He spent all his short life seeking out a stage upon which
Play out his self
Appointed Destin
The only thing he understood about himself was that he would not turn back
He wanted to be a hero and a patriot
He became a hero in a
He wrote his famous letter from the Alamo proclaiming his new role
In the world listen
A few Strokes of a pan made his dreams
Real kid invented himself
An invented
Texas as well
That's Alex
That's a hundred percent Alex Jones
Why is it
Why isn't that amazing
2 Legend
Well because of that great letter he wrote a great letter and that was
The stakes are much lower back
Because of this weird
Serta deal with the military and 7
Do to like his bravery in the face of death Legend out of a man and that sort of thing
That's my ring so f******
True the idea that all his life he was speaking out a stage on which to
Play out his
Self-appointed destiny
Moody
That's stupid that's Alec Jones's entire broadcast career it goes back to the first clip where he's like I'm building
Myself up as a martyr he has his self-appointed beneath that he's forcing his audience
Play out with him
Only
Constellation we have
From all of this
Is the knowledge that there's
No way Alex
Could write a good letter
That's true
Worried about him becoming a legend because his words
Super Bowl stadium
If William
Travis had a broadcast showing you just actually got to listen to the dumb shity says he would not have
Are you coming
Exactly
Do some stuff
I mean it's just fascinated when I started to look into his history as like this unlocked
So much better
The fact that
Nowhere in the historical record is there any indication
That this was a year-long plan
Of some rosicrucian religious ceremony
Where they sacrifice themselves to create a new Atlanta
That's Tuff
Is all bulshit
Conspiracy bulshit
Alex is taken from
On reputable sources
And turned into part of this methodology
Find out later clip
This is your back into it cuz it next month is even more f******
If you was f***** up
This is all
Different
Religious orders
What controls
Luciferian
Copycat
The French Revolution
Adam bike shop
Create
Illuminati
Liberty
Andover George Washington wrote about this at least nine different letters
Before
He died
Probably poison
No they bleeding to death
Movement
The devil worshiping Illuminati out of it
The big secret
This is it
Boom
Lure
They're right
F****** rare
It's given down in a lure
Alex's basically believing oral tradition as literal history you might as well believe everything that
Country
Down from history
That
Bucked up
Yeah and that's a give
Everybody's sort of understanding of what he takes
Now a source
If I understand him correct
That washing
President George Washington
Poison
What poison
Listen to death or at least blood
Illuminati Illuminati Squad
Trying to recreate the lights
In order to overtake the real life
And the reason that they had to kill Washington
Because Washington was leading
The good and he was going to expose it to get rid of
Satanist with India
3 factions of Illuminati is what
Maybe it was a simpler time they didn't even they couldn't
Count to seven
Washington
67 years old
Soldier in the 1700s
So much
There's no way it's help was good there's no way
New business being alive at 67 quite frankly
So on the afternoon of December 13th 1799
After spending most of the day December rain and snow
Supervising activities on his estate
One of the things you should know about George Washington
Hey slaves
They're going to love me like this Travis motherfuker
So are you super
Washington is super big on punctuality
I never showed up late
For dinner and because he was out in the rain and snow Direct
Activities
He showed up for dinner and he didn't have time to change
Just close
Reset for dinner in his wet clothes from the day
Also his wife Martha had just gotten over a really bad cold
The circumstances around complain about it
In the morning
You developed chest
They call for James craik
Dr. James craik
Who was his doctor of
40 years
That doesn't seem like some sort of people trailer
Yeah
George Rawlins who was the overseer of the state
The estate came to his bedside
How to pronounce
Fever
Is it 7:30 in the morning George Rollins
Remove 12 to 14 oz
The blood at Washington
Bleed It
That's what they did back then
Washington requested that
And then afterwards
Y'all should
Text Amor my love
Hazel throughout the morning later take more blood from him and tried to give him an enema the beginning of adrenochrome
They tried all sorts of things they try that
Tea laced with vinegar to gargle work
Some stuff in there to make it worse
Because then it would be like that that's friction there whatever whatever blisters
Call the artificer
Weirdly he did end up regaining some of his strength
But his afternoon came
I knew you wasn't going to make it
He was quoted as saying
Soon enough he was struggling for air doctor
Doctor I Die Hard
But I'm not afraid to go
I believe from my first attack that I should not survive it
My breath cannot last long
Ever the gentleman even in extremes
The general made a point of thanking all three doctors for their health
Washington died at 10:20 p.m.
I guess they make
Did they made with those
Like
We'll shift coming out of them so maybe we should just try and get the s*** out of
It's super fun it's super f***** up is ended up taking out
80 oz of his teeth
That's a lot
Witches witches it's it's
Washington survived as long as he
Because that was really his only accomplishment like
He was it bad General
He wasn't good
Tactics he wasn't
But he looked f****** amazing on a horse
And he should have died like
30 times never did
Kiara
He's got bullet holes in his shirt knows like all weird it off my watch
Like he was that guy
Would not die
People still debate what it was
Killed
Probably
I think it's probably underlying cause of pneumonia
Something like that forgotten about this all about his death
He wasn't poisoned by the Illuminati
Alex brings up the Illuminati
Ladders
Is an indication of the third killed him
As I looked into that
The Illuminati
I know you just recovered from a cold
Uticaod
I get it
I'll get blood by the Illuminati
Guy named ew Snyder sent Washington letter on August 22nd
I'll read the relevant portion of this letter
To you
It was sometime sent that a book fell into my hands and titled proof of a conspiracy by John
Which gives a full account of the Society of
That distinguishes Itself by the name of Illuminati
Whose plan is to overturn a government that all religion
Even natural
Every idea of a Supreme Being and distinguish man from Beast by his shape only
I thought suggested itself to me that some of the lodges in the United States
Might have caught the infection
And my cooperate with the Illuminati or the jacobean club in France
Jose is mentioned by Robison
Remember
And who can doubt if
A day probably
Have not those their confidence in this confidence in this country
They use the same expressions and are generally man of no religion
Reflection I was led
To think that it might be within your power to
Prevent the horrid plan from corrupting the brethren
Of the English Lodge over which you preside
That's why he was bled to death by the Illuminati
Reply
It seems like I kind of
Reload The Illuminati's describing
The right
Varian Illuminati from 1776
Disbanded but everybody's like
Mostly all day
Interested in was like
Rationality over Superstition dimension
Wildly a historical
But George Washington
Did reply to his letter
On September 25th
Nearest MARTA stop
Sending me letters that take my blood magically
Bi-Rite
I have heard much of the nefarious and dangerous playing and doctrines of the Illuminati but never saw the book until you were pleased to send
The same causes which is knowledge in the receipt of your letter have prevented my reading the book
Hitherto namely the multiplicity of matters with pressed upon me before
And debilitated state
In which I was left after a severe fever had been removed
So you was also had a terrible fever a year before he died
Which is
Give me to add a little bored now
Unfavorable sent
Except to correct an error you have run into of my presiding over the English Lodges of this country
The fact is I preside over none
Nor have I ever been in one more than once or twice
Within the last 30 years
I believe notwithstanding that none of the lodges in this country were contaminated with the principles ascribed
Did the Society of the Illuminati
With respect
Your humble servant George Washington
So
From that week
Conclude
George Washington
Ran the Illuminati
Heed
Okay
You're using my Alex logic and I don't appreciate it
So he wasn't killed by the Illuminati
What he says there is I've heard of this stuff which I could say to
Exist
In any meaningful way especially not in 1798 790
Inasmuch as these f******
Dillweed frizzante
Equipment
But that is important
Do we now have
We got we got Washington on record to sing
You f****** f***
It's more like
Come on
Come on man
Like
I'm not
I haven't even been to any
Rademaker
Look
They're not
It's more like
Calm down
How do you get the president to write you a letter
The Illuminati
Sending a lot of letters to the guys like
It's takes up a lot of my time
Writing back to people
Truth
Right now
Aurora places like the Lone Star State
Cyganie just reiterating that
He gets all A's in
Information
In the future
If the enemy was able to take over the rest of the country
This country was founded
When did they
And these are the type of Secrets you learn
It's not the secrets of Solomon
He was dead
Spoiler alert
Soul or
Podcast by what's-his-face
I don't know
Is MattyB a redoubt
These evil forces take over the rest of the country
Which sound
Tumi like lure
It also sounds to me like the grandiosity of
People who are
Nationalistic about their state which Texas certainly is
Similar variations New York to like they have real overblown
Being born in or living in New York
Olivia's long pause
Because your leader that he's like
He's
Bulshit
I disagree with
I think there is that he was like
No no
You like oh no people are going to think I did
Just admitted to being a mason
I think that's what happened did you hear when you're in the right lodges
And the 33rd degree
I don't I don't
Necessary I'm not here to say that Alex Jones
I think I think the deposit is where his brain being like
I know how my audio
Thanks
Dammit
Dearest
Martha
Please do bleed Alex
Jonesy's looking puppy
Today
Probably just hungover
We've now gotten like
Serious
Problems with his ideas about history that he himself has ascribed to lure which is a big problem
He's Reynolds
But you know what's more important
Floor
In the show now Alex Jones
Sort of gets back into a normal show right
It gets to talkin about
Until he drops that George Washington was a
He also was a werewolf
He gets back into normal show with normal-ish headlines
Experienced them a little bit differently
Two clips I believe listen to this
See if you get the
Austrian
Marcia Wallace
Feel better
Are there going to be
60%
Nightmare
I'm here
I'm sorry for our misogynist
I'm sorry for xenophobia
Stone Age
Women
Feminist
Recesses
Islam
Absolutely overrun by demons
So
I don't think it's
I don't think it's possible to not hear those words through new ears
Say they're coming for
Well Texas at the redoubt
Do you know
If you conceived this
Centuries-long fight
Between religious factions
This is insanity
Like this
To the point where
He misrepresents literally every piece of History
30 tries to ascribe
To anything
I don't
No
It kind of feels like
He still thinks we're fighting in the Crusade
I think he does
Yeah
It feels like he goes back that far as like
The Knights Templar were actually my great great great great great grandfather's were they
F*** it f***
Until we got Travis
Travis Newman family
I'm Confederate royalty
References if Alex is related to The Heirs
That is true
But I don't know if he's related to do that family at all
Through his mom side I have no idea but
Colonel Travis
He says I might
I might make it
I could I could make it
But like did the thing is
This friction McGee season this idea that we're being overrun with these false immigrant
I'm sort of a
Plan to destroy the new Atlantis
That's a piece of this bigger stuff
And that bigger stuff
Is
Re-up
F****** lore
Straight up
Fanfiction the people have written about history Reddit trying to explain some very difficult things
Throughout history
It's a convenient excuse for why things that happen
Additionally it's a convenient excuse for trying to scapegoat Jews
Repeatedly throughout history
That those sorts of things
Or even take dues out of it your political opponent
Like those sort of easy
Scapegoat tricks
You see historically throughout the history of the Illuminati lore
And Alex believe all of it
He's making it clear he believes all of it
And he believes
That this
That's what he thinks because the Deep State stuff is
Sonaze
Surprised he loves Trump
If I heard that clip
Write a much earlier I think that I could have peace
A little bit together
In terms of ice
To say something like that in public
S******* country
The more than $130,000
To keep that quiet
In the same way Alex Jones
Steve's Colonel William
Travis
Himself
He's created
His own mythology
The mirroring
Travis's
I think he
Casey's truck
In there too
Cuz the way you
He portrays Trump
Is being up against it
Nothing but enemies
Around
He's he's creating
The Alamo
Around
Trump
The same time it's just more I mean
You could you could say that but it's
I think it's probably more just a situation where it's like
The more enemies Trump
Cruise
The more he likes
Trump
Like he just has to double to some extent only makes him
Like Trump more
Simply because that puts him back
In The Outsider position that we know he loves so much
Like if the person who knows he's up against it
Has no chance of
Coming out alive
Like he believe Colonel Travis was right
Bright
Yeah I guess so
But
Bubbling up
Alex Costa
And prediction that we can look at
Write a letter saying take care of my boy he would write a letter saying
Wait I have kids
Yeah exactly
Hillary Clinton
Obama is
The offering him
Is pure misogynist
Criticizing
Is Peter daou I don't really care
Noah criticizing
Mama's criticizing
What sugar is
We're not against you
We just
We just want to stop
I want a free
Like that
Don't get the metaphor of the Omega
Long-ass
ReliaCard
Frustrated about the Omega Man that I am about anything else
Play weight set
So far tonight
I mean first of all
The only way you understand world is through movies
But then even Beyond
Really really
Women
Take away the idea of any complaints about it
But just the idea
Women are so stupid today just love her cuz she's a woman and scream at me because I have cancer
In his in his Omega Man metaphor
The I have the answer is women shut up
Right
Then they won't listen they won't listen I have the answer and it's stay in your place but that's the problem that I have with
His analysis of the Omega Man
The point of the Omega Man was
She's the month
Right
It's him he's the murderer he's the killer of these people
I guess Alex.
Is asking the wrong way
Is Alex weirdly every now and again he is right and unintentionally
Because I'm the monster
Somebody should have explained that move
I need to stop drinking NyQuil before the movies
Vincent Price
I like the Will Smith version
Next clip
Rambo Joe big
Pizzagate Joe Biggs prewrite comes in
Comes into
The studio cuz they need to talk about the Bundy situation
I've been at the comp
You been
To the Wildlife Preserve
Santa Bunkerville to the original cops
And so Joe Biggs
In conversation
He's really only had one story everywhere
Menus at that their Wildlife Reserve
Paid to eat pizza everyone's got to look it over themselves it is clip
Alex Jones had something
Preposterous
About the Bundys
Demonizes fuses as a
Maybe to set an example for what the government wanted to do two people like this
Two so-called right-wingers
They did get beat
Back in the bottom
What's the standoff on the Bunny Ranch
Pads
Surrender
Deschutes
Lexington Concord
That would have kicked off a revolution
What if we see buddy the revolution techshop in the wrong way and we shoot first
Gives the enemy
So
Willie
To die for the
Text David Knight
Exact on the scene
If they had killed David
Good night my man my man
They could have one but we all do that
If it killed
The hics
When the revolution
Can everybody knows
That's absolutely this is just
Over Monopoly over
Number of arrests
Exactly
Makes perfect
Describe
Coordinates on Martin Luther King Day
Who's got makes me on
Comfortable
But
I'm so glad we didn't do today
I don't know if I can handle hearing more
People compare White
People to
Aman Bundy
Was the Martin Luther King jr. of the Mormon
In this next clip
But this is
So
Barking dog whistle racist
It makes me
Hurts my ears
Like I said I've been a big supporter
Bunnies mother before and things like that and
And in had conversations with them I do believe that they have parent engines
The deep down inside they don't really have any ill intention whatsoever
What they were doing they were truly trying to make another Stan
And I just like I said I thought this was just a knot at the right place
I know but then you have that left again coming out with I don't get stained white tear
You know you have all these people on Twitter coming out last night saying oh great
Black lives matters people
And they also sit there and
They're just disconnected dumb stupid
Today what happened Morrison Tom didn't get the
Probably hardly anybody out there really Manning up late
It's in the middle of nowhere
Lately they quote-unquote break-in at his Federal facility
And what do I see them doing when I'm down there
Sweeping
Cleaning off the sidewalk
Taking care of the property the land
Making sure it's fine
I didn't see any black lives matter and Ferguson break into a store
And rearranging stuff
Running out
So
Awful
Off
For a number of reasons
First of all Alex correctly his reason
If I steal your TV
I'm dusting It Off
Hello
Occupy your home TV
It's snowing out there guys look there's no I own your house now
But you're not going to slip and fall
There's an irony to Alex Jones being like
20 seconds later being like
I didn't seem to clean up all these white people
Reality of that is quite
Trenches full of poop
Malheur National Wildlife Refuge
Ended more than a month ago but yet damage
To get I gathered to protest the federal government's management of Pub
Lance
The total cost of the occupation stands at about six million dollars to the Federal
In addition to $3000000 already pitched in by the state of Oregon
Martha have a lot of backpack
Assistant Regional director of USF
WS
7 million dollars have been flagged just for repairs
And cleaning of the reserve itself
Home warned that nearly two million dollar clean up cost is a moving figure subject change
As the agency
Conduct a thorough inventory of what was broken and what
Missing
So here's where it gets here here's where it gets really important
So
They made those buck
It's a poop and what-have-you right
And that's one thing
A report released in February by the FBI said quote significant amounts of human feces were found on site after the occupier surrender
Next to a sensitive cultural site
Containing artifact sacred to the bird
Tribe
Great is that
Metaphor right there
Bid on the Note Homestead Wildlife Refuge will recover eventually
Concerned that the militia members may have harmed 8 of American artifacts
Or destroyed other records which are irreplaceable
Nature is durable it'll be just fine Homestead
Buildings and property or fixable or replaced
Well they'll be fine
The community will strengthen as a result of
However damages the tribal artifacts
Heinous
Missing lost or missing biological data
Could be impossible to replicate
Already on the job
Bob Library
64 charger
Federal conspiracy
Remind everybody
Scott free
Did cause a lot of damage to Sacred site
Criminal time for
For them to drive home the point that Alex Jones excuse is all white
Behavior here is it
Terrorism is Justified
Fair enough
There would be
Oarfish
At the meeting
I've had them no exaggeration
Bustime
I don't know about that
If true
We got a Hardison better
For real
Not a good one
Hey Alec
Go blow up the police station
If you're living the kind of life
We're 30 times in your twenty-year career
Someone is come up to you
Real or not
And suggested you blow up you're not doing a good job you're in a bad line of work
You're attracting the wrong crowd and now I vote
I listen to the show
I really hope
It's time to go blow up
If you're a cop or you're just playing a prank
I think you would probably run away if I was just
Zirkops
It happened 30 times but be that as it may
Beds
All of them
At this point in the episode Alex brings on
Is Big CIA whistleblower
Tosh Plumlee
Tosh Plumlee .0 right
I don't care
I don't really care
But
Answered
When does Tasha
8 fraction.
All they do is blow up
Asians with the help of minor radio personalities
In his interview though there's one thing I wanted to play for you cuz I think it's really interest
I think it's a very very
If you listen to this closely
I think
Veritas
Plumlee
Pointing a finger at Alex
I don't know if that's the case of assholes doing this
No I think he's subtly
Trying to be like
Giving
Hints to the audio
For something like this
I would say that I don't think I've heard top Plumlee on the show in a long
Time
Heather maybe like
There might be a thing where he's I got to want to come on your show anymore I don't know I'm not entirely sure I don't
I don't have the statistic
Text back that up on 2 weeks ago and
I just met the sheriff something like that
But there are things that
He's staying in this clip
That are
Like
I think I'll pick up on
Wow you're so incredible
Illusionary Warfare training
Well that's what it is
If you can control their Communications if you want a war
Are you going to Pickaway
We've had Mockingbird that's an old CIA project qualify something here on CIA
There are people that are
We have
I'm talking about a Shadow Warriors
Autumn Shadow Warriors on organizations and things like that
Exactly what the hell we're getting right
The big foundations
Run
But have
Security clearance
The clandestine dirty
Program
And so what time is the local police the FBI or the CIA don't know
Foundations that are even above
The program
Here in the United States
Right on the head Alex okay
Organization
So
3 things
They were said within that clip
Criticism
That are in the Auntie Alex Jones online
Community
The first
Is that idea
Of
Communications people are probably the most
Suspicious is the biggest mouth
Piece of the Patriot community
He is the communications
Aspect
Of that entire operation and Alex
His own words
Implicate him and big like
Himself
So the second thing
Is the idea that Alex Jones
Desensitizes people
To the situation
Fat people the powers-that-be
Sensitized so they accept their
We have this powerful globalist
Who have their fingers in every pie that they control all 7 factions of the CIA
The secret 85
Conspiracy
That exist
Iron
Clyde pedophile blackmail
That want to kill your children and drink their blood and all their stuff and all they're going to do
Trying to f*** with you
Like making you depressed through the water
The chemicals in the water
India is going to lie to you all the time there's going to be fake terrorist that are going to run you over with
With a car You're Not Safe in public
This idea is
Against them except by giving me my
But like the idea that his role in the whole game plan
Desensitizing people to
Be able to
Can't fight back
To direct
I'm through protesting
The writing letters to your Congress people
Voting
All those sorts of things
Like those are
Legitimate things
You can do can push for reform
Those things you're not
Like we are not
Alex Jones's rule according to a lot of his critics
Rennline
Is Vicki
Is there too
To train you to think you don't have anything you can do
Craned
Listener
Alex Jones its bills in his audience even as I was talking
Support him
The third thing
Half minute clip of Taj Plumlee
That is also one of the big
Fingers that gets pointed it out
Is that he is a
GateKeeper
And the key is in place
So there is a flow of information the correct way
I don't necessarily believe this
Because that implies that the globalists are real and that but that criticism that comes to him
From these internet commenters
Is that the global still real
And Alex is a limited hangout you controlled opposition with
Stratton order to make sure the
You stay
Suckling off his teeth
As opposed to the real truth tellers in the world
Out
But there is it
I would say he likes me is amazing that there's three of the
Biggest criticisms
Text within one minute and a half
Of them talking I know you are but what am I
Like you're not like what they're doing is just accusing the opposition of what it is
Whatever it is they think they're due
Either they're silly
It's a little different than the general
Coming from Tosh Plumlee .0
No.
Yeah
It is a little bit different
I give it
I give it a little bit more of a pause to be like why is he
He saying those things
Alex
Pictures of course
I'm rubber you're glue
Stuff like that
There's probably an intention behind it and it's not just
Deflecting
She didn't have to do that right he has no
Skin in the game
Necessarily
You hit the nail right on the head Alex and then take something
Completely different
Here's a little bit of a commercial that I really enjoyed
Alex that does for his product
DNA Force
Great don't know add pivot to speak out on this but man this is a great commercial
Chester biopqq
Is 12 to 14,000
From
It's
Forced hardcore
Just to buy a Pikachu
Has equivalent vitamin C delivery in the body
Read the science
A blueberry
You can't text
BBQ1 pill
Pounds of blueberries
Blueberries
Thanks Fast Track
For something since we made our own formula
All blueberry
For something like this
Biglots.com
I thought a cop herbal product for $50
Do you know what's the best infomercial
As Seen On TV products
This is the perfect time to be like
Have you ever been eating 300 lb
Blueberries
Mouth is blue and there's a show like Abby roll from
From Wonka
Flipping how many times have the situation
I was looking into this I don't care about the blueberry situation
Find myself
All the time
Do you mean the band The blueberries
Canterbury
The difference
Between Alex
Whose product other products
Is indeed
Snow the nutrition information
What you find is
Alex Jones
The bottle
Proprietary blend
And then whatever
The proprietary blend all blend the ingredients
He doesn't give you an actual idea
Percentage product on like some other that
Another company
I'll give you all the extra how much
Did he say it cost $14,000 a kilo or whatever
And that could be enough to
Goat 6 years
Or something like that
Hold on once
Percent of your daily allotted vitamin
I'm seeing this right
How many pounds of blueberries
Pounds of blueberries it's absorbed the same but different
Nothing
So in the next
Alex Jones has another weirdo cast a guy by the name of
Hate this guy get off this blueberries to measure everything in pounds of blueberries
How much in a bowl of soup
Cereal
How many pound
Songs of blueberries
Honey Bunches of Oats
Blueberries blue-berries blueberries
Blueberry
Joel skousen comes on
I don't want talk about his history or anything like that cuz
Take him down
I'm going to take him down a little bit later in a much more thorough but
If it's clipped
He basically just rewrites what happened with the shooting of LaVoy finicum
Gibson
A real generous take
I wonder why
Very mild-mannered grandfather
A Mormon
To already well-spoken grandfatherly type
Why are Mormons
Good man
Religious man
She's the one that got shot I'm in the sky
He was not about what happened when he got out of
Shut up
One of the witnesses
I'm talking to Bundy's bodyguard said that he rushed
Yeah walking forward to them
Basically bearing is Chester them with his hands
Application for the police
So
Beyond let's let's pretend he wasn't.
Which is not true
Admittedly
Bundy's bodyguards
He was angry and you rushed the cops
With no information at all
I don't think that's
Let's Pretend he wasn't armed
Situation is right
Now let's imagine the situation
Kitchenware
Joel skousen
Songs words
But he he was fed up and he said shoot me any police bearing his chest
And they told him to stop walking and he kept walking towards them
David there's no way I was Jones would ever give
Any kind of a path
I think
I don't think that's
Who were there
Reported what happened
Cool
The other one was in his pocket reaching for
That's true
I think if you're a grandfatherly type well-spoken
Guy
Pull a pistol on the cob
Grandfatherly
White people
Winchester
I know my grandfather was the kind of guy who would take
Government money
Do not grow things online
And then get $100,000 a year from a charity to have a bunch of foster kids
Children
It's crazy
And this is where Alex Jones
I wanted to leave this episode
Because it's been a little bit heavy on me
Poking bathroom holes in his historical beliefs
Right
And I wanted to leave with a good example of how he covers news
Little clips
From time to time with him
ESAT News what you should have said was
Lure of the day
Headlines
Laura Vitale
Griffin Griffin through the headlines
Enjoy
Destabilize Europe
Are zombie clear also give the exact same headlines
Get into the actual stories of earlier
He just pees on repeat
Record-holding athlete
50% of refugees
The strategy of repetition with no analysis
No discussion of whether or not these things I'm saying or these things are
Just repetition to you believe it
Into your head
Be afraid
Putting acid in the water attract bears
Babies
Absolutely
Disassemble
A conquering Europe
By the state
Flights
Cousin
No I'm out of humiliation
Global superlative donaldtrump.com
Out of control people on the left are like Lana Donna m
Bad example
I looked up what Lena Dunham said and I should
Yeah
Call and worship
Rolling over on our backs
Papi
Just goes on and on and on and on and on and on
Nice
Rugby
Fake glasses
He delivered that line right there as if it's an old-time catchphrase
Call and response on his farewell tour
TV audience
They are they keep it illegal
Where is the Avenue
Hamburger
Statistics on reject
Kings of these essays that I'm sure are
Just part of
I don't know
Vista
Like a formality
Just write something
If you write an essay that would scare you 300 on the written sat
Will give you a
If you could avoid saying I wanted done kill somebody
Then you get a gun
As a carcinogen because studies came out the show The Kitchen
Category
Potential carcinogen
Plantation attack
Advani has run out of stories
All the papers
Fluoride
Wanted to just remind everybody
One more time today
Special
That was lame saw that coming
Yeah of course it was
Still happened
Who is trying to keep us
What's from getting good at
Blueberry
Rosicrucian cult
Dude it's like I know a little bit about the rosicrucians
Things that I think
I think that in terms of what we talked about
Christianity or the lack thereof
I think that I have been too focused on straight-up gnosticism
I think it's some of those ideas about living on through
Are your children
Might come from rosicrucian
Cuz they're big into reincarnation and Perfection of the
The soul through repetition
And stuff like that
So I think I think that might be
Subscribe not only to
About history he might also have like rosicrucian Christian
As well the rosicrucians
Then quite frankly Alex is dumb
Those two are not mutually exclusive Alex is dumb so it becomes dumb
We're in the interesting becomes
Stupid
But that's the best sentence I've ever written
That's the show that's that's his January was that January 27th
Yep beautiful also just to give you a little bit of context this is after he has decided to join team Trump this is after
Rest in peace LaVoy finicum
It is sad that anybody had to die but at the same time
I feel bad for the 15
Kids
No wasn't it I am on Monday
He was the one who adopted all of those
From the government according to the site I saw earlier today
Out of context drop
Which is just as fun afterward that it was it would have been before
Okay I thought you was being sarcastic
Said he turns into the
No course I'm psychic I can't control it
Control it though
Where is the show
Amazing opener Nate barroso
Like our show
The first 10 minutes of this podcast
I don't like their show but
Let's be polite in Cicero
Saturday February 20th
At the tell me if you can't www.the playground theater.com
Woodley's last fight
Knowledge underscore
You can look it up on the iTunes we live there absolutely
Beyond that I don't know you know what
The perfect
Have the perfect
I think we should call Madra
So you can get one too that would be
Has a garbage day
Trash Dip Joe Walsh
Things are way too close
Rio Rio app
Drake
The f****** worse
M in order of draft
Yours as well
They can all live in that bundle of
Go fuc yourself
Alex
I love your work