Alexandra Thurston color
About Alex Jones in some sort of
That would make
You listen to
About an episode
As we usually do to our lives I was going to transition today
My next turn
Super-awesome
Some folks
Great news I don't know if you guys have a great time
How to make it sound
Nice
But I also think
Extra theater playground letting us do that
I like I like the way they let us run the show which it seems like
When we started the show everybody just left
There was the sound guy and then there was nobody else there stuff
I have no idea there were more employees
There was no rules forgot to make one of the big points that I wanted
To the episode that will Air tomorrow
Probably but also that
The want the point that I wanted to make about alley
What's John's in that episode
Especially
Almost everything else
Is that he never takes the time to get
Stories
You know what I'm saying and that's one of the most dangerous things
By the people in media and
Especially people in
Persuasive media
Right he knows in this case he knows he has
Like two days or so
To get a story out before the facts
Anyway
Is looking good
Keep that in mind that is a really dangerous thing
Closet
And then listen to us
I don't do that but anyway I would also like
To say thank you
GoNoodle
I'm a policy wonk
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket
I don't want
John Cena
Thank you very much
Is a little bit apart
Lance
To the native
Nighttime
Find an episode to do for the live show
12 or 13 episodes
Michelle it was like 40 hours
To take some time to go over some of the stuff
You doing
And second
Of 2013
This is something that I found
Is that
Every April Fool's Day
I thought that might be some fun
Really it wasn't the kind of fun I was looking for like most April Fool's Day
Exactly and so on this 1st April 1st
The 23rd
Alex Jones
Tells a story
Through most of the show
It's one of the best
Experian
This story
Is not
It's about a vacation that he had taken recently and autobiographical
This is the Halloween story all over
Perversion
Exciting I love it the first one
And we come back I'll briefly tell the story
Union
Resort outside Austin
I went to that
Company at my house
I just was in the hot tub
One guy was from Portland Oregon engineer
Businessman
Smoke shops
Yes how do you do that
Alright Google storage
All three of them
How to solve America's problems
Because they're all listeners they know that cyprus's problems are our problem
Because if
The globalist
And then one of them no no
I didn't hear a different guy I know too much
It's a different guy
I heard him
Different guy
Different
For a secret in this situation
Well you'd be thrilled
But it's not a secret globalist in so much as it's one of the people he's hanging out with
In the in the hot tub
Chorus and he's like
How long was he there
Details salon
Okay
Nevermind
That's fine story
There's some red
But he was going out to break at this point we didn't have time to
To fully flesh out the story
So now he comes back from break
Any of the
Text to give the story
A couple more layers immediately after break
I told the guys in the hot tub
I was in a hot tub
Like I like that Alex admits this is unbelievable to the best of my knowledge he does not have them onto
Cramping
I don't know how we bring together
Antivert
Call
Working in our utility Contracting was talking about the power plant
Call Powerball draw successful
Successful in business
One guy has a payroll the quarter million dollars a month the other guy
Thousand dollars in taxes
Unnecessary details
Wait till this is midday
Sing a later night like everybody's drinking
Beautiful gorgeous
Alex
As far away from them as he can possibly get that was ridiculous nurse
And
Imaginary globe
Baseball cap on
The suicide Nets
Extermination
Globalism
Pics of change everything
Wait wasn't even old white male
Everything
He said you've lost
We want to build productivity
Enjoying the free market
Socialist countries
Falls apart
Matter we control things now
We control the narrative
Oh my gosh
Obviously
Alright so now the story is it's all about white genocide
Narratives are being
Confirm to buy this weirdo stranger
Who overhears him talking to a couple people at a hot tub and he's like
Wonderful
I think
Written well by Kate Chopin
The great author there
The story out of the park
No
Exactly what the internal monologue of this government scientist globe
Authoritarian
I mean if you see a man
Wearing
What will you be wearing that
That makes him look like
I don't know
Could have been
You're in luck
Cuz you're asking about likes
Some details
About 10 minutes later he tells the story
He isn't his Workshop in this story
Little bit third telling of it
There are no Heroes
My mom
Outside Austin Texas
Could everybody
That's a nice hotel
And there's a
Hot hot sauce
Crony capitalism
Discussion
Evil Obama
Anneliese Lee bad minorities
How old are you
Heartfelt
Are you having this conversation
Sitting there
Using viral
We thought it was joke
20 minutes
Points finger at is Wiz
The most ridiculous
They have real
There's a little more spliff
Do he admires his father
I think there's a little more to the clipboard is like this Authority
Old man was like you stood there for 20 minutes point to get Alex
20 minutes because
Does he say anything or is
Apparently I accuse you
Just like
I think he's insinuating authoritarian
Cuz he was around Alec
Like there's something about Alex
His toughness that rubs off on other
Okay
There's a little more to the clip here let's see the rest of the story holes
Those words
Strong winds around me
But it was just watching
And he was laughing
Smart
People
Obamacare raise taxes on
Who was the white guy
All this doesn't make sense like Noah
No one babes like this
All of it where's your first hole in this
How can we punch up the store
I would have
Like a page
Page one rewrite just from scraps start over again
Condense the three guys here's what I would do to get rid of
It's unbelievable if you hanging out
Wyoming
Go for it
That's an okay you got to have a driving force
No because it goes to grocery stores and people turn into demons when they look at him
Stephen King
It's like that there's always going to be the guy
Right right there is a unreliable narrator situation in anytime
A story about his own
I we know lives Fight Club
I think that's what's really going on here everyone else wants to
To fight with him part of his psychosis
We're having a lot of fun we're laughing because obviously not true story
Flowers vacation
Now we should be serious about
No you should be serious
This
Event in Alex Jones Is Life
Had some serious.
Nightmares
After I talk to that guy Saturday night I woke up I don't really use a nightmare
Oh no
I woke up just
Sweat
But they're so horrible and so weak and so evil
And so dangerous and so pathetic
Because they hate goodness
They hate success
That doesn't track
Viral scientist
Also not true but
Big deal yeah I mean if he wouldn't be a nobody if that is
True
It doesn't track logically
To be like
These people are so evil and they wanted
Destroy ubiq
Cuz they're nobody
How to destroy the world
Text Billy
Well
But that's just a pathetic
George W bush rhetoric
Like they hate our freedom that's like that
I hate George W bush
I think he's a monster tried to pitch this war on us
Then he uses the same rhetoric
Against his imaginary enemy the global
Bizarre
Bright very bizarre
Both enemies
Ultimately the same thing and that's brown
Well
We both hate
Agreement
The whole day
Set story for now
Yeah but
April 1st
We do fine
It's not good
It's mostly this story
But at the end of it
We get a visit
From one
Shattuck okay
Make it pushing the Sandy Hook was fake
Narrative
Alex
Are in the hot tub I can tell you all of it
Tearing up
Fake fake mustache
Britannic
Alright
Everybody in Alex
Is life
Is living a concert Make-a-Wish for Ally
Everybody always
Listen in all of his stories
Give him something
Finger talk about the baby kids
Told every single day that Alex
Needs to be the best day
I think there's another theory
But if you use the logic of people like Steve pieczenik
You could say that everyone Alex runs into his princess
Dugood tray that
That's very classic
Kind of
Boyhood
12 year long
Wingfield
Everybody f****** with Alex Jones I couldn't I couldn't handle watching it
Cuz I know the consequences are this
Very good prank but unfortunately
Explaining
Pretty early on why you believe
Sandy Hook
The false flag
Also DACA what is your take on
Black actors
What's your take on this
Xanax
Sandy Hook
Call erupt
Call The Hunger Game movies
Society
Siri
That's where it comes from
Sandy Hook that's a big part of their either Sandy Hook Theory
And because Susan Collins
This from
Call her
Right you could it's suspicious that you says
No comment
She doesn't have anything why would she comment other than to an official Outlet possibly
You make a great point
Seacomm how f****** soft is this s***
What else does Susan Collins have today
You could make the argument that like a you know
I don't know
Doesn't movie The Faculty
Usher Usher Raymond
Usher did it
Usher wasn't bald
Musician
It's cool
Right
This is this is this is a disaster
Nobody shall have
The Japanese
A person
Millions of dollars
Albert like
It bums me out cuz Alex
Is wrong about so much
And I never knew that the like sorted Genesis of
This seriously it's coming from Steve
And 100 is one of his big resources on this
Look Susan Collins from there she wrote
That's not
That's not any
It's always being plication then
The government hired
Her to write the Sandy Hook massacre probably
Fluor predictive programming through the Jungle Games book
Susan, we don't even know how to fall asleep I get the dog scenario
We need a script writer
Because week
The Sandy Hook massacre
We need Harrelson
How would you even begin to write
The Sandy Hook Beach
Would you just look back at all of the other school shootings that we've had
Better Health
Right
The Hunger Games is nothing like so I can you do
I feel like we
Shouldn't have to say that
Terms of a
All those sorts of things though
The similarities
Kids died
I guess that's the big one
School
Alright then he goes on to talk about crisis actors and that's a load of bull.
Crisis actors all this
You look into all that those argue
Those are for that macaroni
Not macaroni
Swiss
My friend
I wish they had something better but they don't
Same thing that we talked about over and over again
Telling stories before there is a story
In order to get ahead of
Like right right it just
Making stuff up
Making out
Implications
Insinuations that are irresponsible and that's
Caught on
I crazy
Alex
Maybe that's the connection
Conspiracy
Yeah
Susan Collins
Alex Jones didn't start Sandy Hook shooting like that
But
Publicized
One of his big
Big guy pieces of logic is
Hunger Games
Ridiculous
Anyway
Do We Go From Here onto April 2nd
Is that
JK Rowling what are you talkin about what are the highest-grossing
Come on come on come on
Alright April 2nd
Headspace on the April 2nd
Things off with a little bit of vodka
About the UN
Little in the grass their helmets get big
When they're finally done making you hate the police
Yeah 77
It sounds great
Sure does
Preceded it
Q76
Q78
Get rid of the entire military
I feel like one of the other on either side has
Similarly good you're asking stupid questions
Every other one is like
Using the toilet
Next
Mention this before I didn't realize it was such a huge part of Alex Jones
Beliefs about the
Is a duck
That was put out
Amor
The United States program for General
Complete disarmament
Peaceful world
Are released into
September of 1960
Weapons
Taken
Away not weapons taken away from everybody but the escalation of arm
The reason for that is there in the middle of the f****** cold war
I don't
Primarily what is about is
Reducing the risk of nuclear war
It doesn't really have to do
With disarming population
As it does with the United States
And the f****** Soviet Union getting together
And negotiating to not use nukes
And to make sure that other countries don't
Operation
The nuclear weapon
So this is just something that was written
By the states
Submitted
The UN wishlist
It's conceivably submitted to the UN but one of the things that you can do is you can go
To the UN
Website
You know what they have
They have minutes
Of every assembly that they have
So I went back to the
The 16th General Assembly
From 1961
And look through it
Is there anything here
Every single Un General Session
Every every single one
Even some of the stuff it seems Petty as hell
Like they're just
Making Proclamation
That's largely what they do they have General Assembly
They generally don't end up saying like
What he's doing is that they say
It is our feeling
That what we the people should pursue
Is
Do you like me not using nuclear weapons at like that
So much like the cloward and Piven
And I've discussed by professors
Jose
General Assembly
The laziness of human
That literally every single you and General Session
You can go and read
And there are still
Conspiracy theory
16th assembly pulled up and the 17th
He was a good one was great if I was going to rent all of the UN General Assembly
Start with 70
The sex was amazing
Of course in the top five
Is number one but that's really just a
The Legacy Thing lyrics
You know the general assembly documents they have the entire minute
It's just stuff like this
Admission of the Republic of Rwanda to membership
The United Nation
They're things that are proposed
And then they discuss them
And they're all listed in here
And most of them
Some of it is about money
A lot of it is about
Disposition
Dispensation
Money
Steamship status
Stuff about
Kneading
Fill positions and stuff like that it's the minutes of a boring meeting
Order 72
But there's also stuff on there about like nuclear disarmament
What Alex talks about this rule 7277
He's not
Steven passed as
United
States
And it's not
Something it was even put to the
The floor in the UN General Assembly
So it's nothing it's just something that someone wrote
I'm kind of inspired inspired by this level of
He doesn't take the context of documents
Exciting into account
The fact that he still sites that one
Dumbass thing about chemtrails
Articles
It means like well that was also something that the virus scientist admitted to him
In the hot tub
Nefariously
20 minutes
Now this is a whole new wrinkle on Alec
Text that I want
To be in a hot tub
And just happy
Say random
It's close enough for jazz
Now I just am a
Every story of his
Hamburger hot
Didn't he wears a chain
I feel like he wears a chain when it gets in
Probably never never were any other time she'll press
If you wanted to make some other critiques of the unob game
For them cuz the UN does have a lot of impotent
Enforcement
Human rights
And a lot of the employees of the UN have been caught doing some
Pretty bad s***
I'd be all for it
What is there like
Focuses on the international
As far as
Correctness
Vioc view Olympic Committee
Okay still top three
On International
Sprint number
Globalist
Global
Number 12
AT&T
Weird weird
Sprint
Not a fan
But the UN does
IPods
But this isn't about you and this
Made
Facetious
Argument
About
Killing kids up till three years of age or something like that
Be more of a thought experiment than anything else it was
Serious proposal
You're alone in that opinion
But
Whoever made this facetious argument
The way he says it it means the other thing ever
Caught a lot of people
Right there is
Problem for his future
Sometimes
I just like to imagine I'm with the New World Order
Disney list all the things that he did for Trump what I'm thinking like
He's showing some signs like going to be on the f******
Dream
Favorite
But here we go
The Wanted
As they poison as they destroyed my future
Look at Obama and he's for me he likes me
Kill the babies
Eighteen-month-old walk-around
That's not the shots
The government
Magazine
Pizza
Move stuff
Magazine back at this point
At this point he's selling a magazine
Spreads
I don't know what
So
You mean he was right on time and getting into the prison
Gets back to the UN
I should get all the get all of the Infowars magazine
I know you see Miss America up there saying I love the UN and
Percival starving
Helped
Ohmwrecker
No killing
And if you wanted to look at it
It's barbecue
Roast chicken over fire
They were there with machine-gun shut up
When I had
And then they tried to get out of the campsite
Come up
The operations
So Alex thinks
Rolando was a false flag
Right
I like to read to you from this article about
If you Google if you type in the exact words
He says nothing
Comes up do not
Even if something did come up don't trust
What's the first link on that
Conversation
Helena
She was in Rwanda
Un peacekeeping soldiers were there
Here is a quote for
Indicates what one of the bigger issue
Do you want respond
We could not believe that the United Nation
Just going to let us die
We're always here in the radio how they were there to help us
When the killers were looking at in the eye and say we were going to die what did the UN do
That's really the issue
Man that's really more the issue
Of the response there was
There was not a there was not enough resources there wasn't enough
To even the motivation necessarily to resolve the issue
They've bungled
If you go back and listen
The interviews with Romeo Dallaire
The guy who was
We are the head of the troops there
It's some of the most heartbreak
Wingstop to hear him talk about
What he wanted to do and what he wasn't able
To do that sort of stuff
Terrifying
To hear
Alex wants to make the argument metaphorically that the UN
Killing of I think was 800,000
Some people.
But it's If he if you want
To make that argument
It is true in the sense that they didn't do what they could have done
But it's not true
But they were BBQ
Children
Right
That's now
Can Alex get me
Me in touch with that virus
Question number one
I don't know you question number two
He said there a way to devise a virus
The only kills wife
Question number three
All of them
He did say that he gave the other guys robbed email address but probably not the authoritarian I would imagine
No I feel like they
It goes on
Pichu
How to not be a
The part of a radical Islamic terrorist
There's a dude
As the
Right-wingers
It's so funny
Spyglass
So sick
I think it might be a real laugh
And he also admitted
Right-wingers
Hey tomorrow
You said must remember this
This time Park part of a bigger thing that he's talking about that he's like it's so silly they're going to try
And save it right-wingers are working with Al-Qaeda
Which is ironic cuz now he's a
Entire argument is that the left
Is working with Al-Qaeda
Andar
What
What fantasy
And pretend to be terrorists
Well that's what he thinks like with Oklahoma City
He thinks that that
Is that Alex likes
To say he was just a good guy
He was a good guy
Is it normal
Jive
Who they had
Go be a part of white suit
Supremacist
Violin amp
Organization
And make you look bad
He didn't know was real he thought it was a drill
Alex Alex
Explain that
Together this drill
What could this drill sir I think
Purpose of the drill would be in fiery to catch other people who want to bomb something
I think that's what he think
He never really spells it out
Alex doesn't really get
That part of the narrative.
It's bad
It's the only way
Wiggle his way out of white
White terrorism
He makes it that far
It was a setup and he wasn't even a white supremacist
I know he was at those those weird militia meetings and stuff I know that you know people who testified
They saw him there but that
Did the military had to make it look like the bad guy
It's so stupid
He talks about how right-wingers will do anything
To prove that they hate Al-Qaeda
It doesn't make sense
Well then
You could totally use
Okay two lives in there go
Yeah yeah
Alex tells of what
Spoiler alert
Very dumb
We must be totally divided into racial and religious
Districts
The Hunger Games
Floating fortresses
Getting a lot of work for the government
At 120,000 feet with microwaves
Years ago I saw him bragging about it
So Alexander Haig
Is the former Secretary of State
The blind but it is actually
Do you know if you look into it
Alexander Haig was involved in government
He decided to get a bunch of people together and start a business called
Skyspace
Is it what they were doing
Is they work
Create
Giant balloons
Telecommunication
To just over Giant
Satellites out
Space
Lower
They would provide internet coverage
Three entire cities
Great idea
They would provide like a relay point for phones
Scientists
Together and
Get this done
They didn't work
Yeah
It didn't work out
So
Remove
I know cuz if
Giant
Look the reason that it hasn't been done I want to verify this blimp story
Do the blimp Story part of it is real in the sense
What's that like
We're trying to make a
But it was for internet
It was way ahead of its time
It's okay for this Alex
Blimps those are the good old days
This was that this is back when I was
2014 article in Newsweek
Developed
Had promised
What blimp at 65000 FT above the city I could have served all of the 1990s level internet traffic from the
7 below
A blimp could stay up for 5 years
But as with other scheme
Time killed Skype
We ended up life
Sing the technology
Did someone else and walked away Alex Hayes
Nothing
Has come of it
Microwave
Microwave fry
They were trying to find ways to service population
Alright
New investment opportunity
Knowledge fight blimp
Internet service
Okay well I think we're going to run into a problem
Sky say something
Not the way to make money
Blimp startup
Looks dark not talk any more of it or less
Steeler ideas
Our brilliant ideas
This next clip
A call from a guy
Miami talk about Heather Waters
Poison
Then
This caller
Heather really into
Testing idea for a new segment
Alex's show
Flip talk
Hormones in the water
Eco science
Monsters
I agree with you but I do think there are still a lot of men in the country and I know they're out there listening right now and I want to speak
Just a moment
People to call in
Just A short segment of your show when you do have collars
Call Linda and we want to hear from the man in this country
I'm calling right now man I'm one of them
I'm making videos on YouTube I'm speaking to people
Telling you like I'm fighting hard man I'm fighting up here I'm fighting with you guys and you guys down there need to know you got Brothers in the trench up to
Here in Canada
Time
We're together and we're I'm here to fight with you man
Revolution in
Insurrection
Possibly
Of the men
I move that the idea
So ridiculous
You're out
The strengths to open up in
Irene
Maybe the
Test of manhood
Ability
Push ups
I'm speaking real man though it is
Alex Jones talks about a couple of
Alex talks about a couple of real man
Rap
Real man
Krakatoa
Battles and wars and stabbings and shootings
German
Nails
Andrew Jackson
Why do you hate
And you'll be thrilled to learn
It's so did Davy Crockett
He's known as the man of the Wild Frontier and all that
He's known for all that s*** but in addition
Into that
Served
House
The key was a politician for a bit
He did Andrew Jackson
Absolutely not because
Particular
Somatic
American
Is there anything more
Andrew Jackson
Then Hayden
You might have a decent point they're super passionately against
The Indian Removal Act of 1830 Andrew Jackson
I was trying to pass
To be like
Pretty serious
And beyond that you had a lot of ideas about how Andrew Jackson was dealing with finances
And the bank
Do memes of like that
Yeah it's okay
About that Becky is
Very
Seriously got into rows with Andrew Jackson
Is emulating their only like 8 years apart
Or something like that
Born pretty close to each other in the only like
Time that they really come together is
In the Tennessee militia and
The two of them serve
Together
But then Alex
Just jacking off more
Because he loves Andrew Jackson for whatever reason
Graphics
Descriptions of violin
Crockett apparently also died at the Alamo
Like our friend Colonel Travis
Default hero
For Alex
When throw into whatever argument
Anthony wants to have
You know
David love Trump
Whatever you're making the shut up
So
At this point
On April 2nd
I was jump start talking about people
Handguns
Across Mountain
Right
Nike more easily American dudes
Battle
Blob
Priest River Family reunions this weekend
The point is finger and go you're right we're taking over
Who are you
I'm a government Professor scientist
Smile
Oh my God
You're a population reduction issue Genesis
What you got
Don't interrupt this at all
This nonsense
What where did she
Wait wait
I make it my business
You make it your business to lie about people
Brutally sanity probably don't exist the moment that he said
Straight up pointing
Started pointing myself
It is really hard to hold it for this long
The longtime to ridiculous amount of time
Like I do and I apply
Yeah
I'm starting to go numb
So the stories change now Alex Alex tells him.
I play bridge you know why he throws that in though it's to combine it with his narratives about his dad
Confirmed it by confronting his authoritarian Cyrus scientist
Oh no
Zagara's
I shouldn't have stood up pointed in revealed
I don't think there's first of all I mean that none of this is
There's no way he told the story three times in the first day
Send it
Little little bit difference
I like it
Long time to rip off that book
Yeah so we're one more clip Jordan here in April 2nd
Little little
Little tight episode here little little hour long
For the people
Alex Jones
He's basically
Sort of doing his own version of that song that don't impress me much
Shania Twain song
So you got a
Yeah.
Car bed
That don't impress
I like your leader
That donut brother me
Vagos also
I didn't pull the clip of that cuz I lyrics
The whole
No no just maybe
Converse
I don't know the time frame
By worldly
Play things
I see somebody
Defeating
I get butterflies I get tears in my eyes and
Expecting crying
Want to
Because all this personal ladies and gentlemen
Do take it personal with McKenna prisonplanet.tv
What the f***
Literally
Physics
That one's Next Level cuz it involves fake crying
Future
Walgreens
Secure unless you buy prison Plantation
What's even worse than that cuz he's like I take it real personally cuz of my children
Sweet sweet darling
So take it personally with me
I would like to take a profession
On the level of like you know how I find words that I speaking of blanket like that it
Level
Disgraceful
That's next-level stuff
That would make me feel all good
April 1st and 2nd
Alex Jones
Has
Authoritarian
We found out that Steve pieces of the Sandy Hook narrative is
The Hunger Games
Alex Jones
Buys a lot about the UN and very
Specific ways
Any right ring
Right-wing terrorism
Made it to know that offers you like
You want to be a right-wing terrorist.
Do not take me to check Bob
I also I guess we learned that we're all going to die
Well yeah but we all do that
Anybody's ever watched
Steampunk anime
Alex Jones news
Think about David
It's been fun
So what's going to happen if tomorrow the as it comes out just come out on Tuesday
And then on Wednesday we will put out the lies episode
And get this
There's more to the story
Of the live at the
Then just
What we covered
On the live episode we could only pay half hour of our or so
The Narrative goes on
There's a fuller picture
They will explore on Thursday night
Come out on Friday
Part 2
Of whatever it is covered
Thanks schedule for the week really appreciate everybody listening
Website.com
Underscore
We are up
You do all those things
Aa.com
We're still we're still hovering around 70% of the way to our monthly goal
Cover up game
We will bet if we get there
Take
From what we made at the
I'm not mad at him
Nobody's here to pay you
Right it's just an empty building
They're at the box office
Albany
Balti Wok
Jordan
I will tell you
You today
You inspired
Okay
Because
Andrew Jackson
I agree
Holding
Tell Alex I love your work