Alex
Birthstone colors
Welcome back to another site and then I forgot to turn it on
F*** you George will be edited out
Let it breathe
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about
Wine
Is what we are doing absolutely first wines we drink on the show
The first one was the expedition
That sounds appropriate for them
Why the Bogle in honor of Bogota
This is my guess where I know a lot about Alex
I'm guys welcome aboard how are you doing that's good
I feel like I'm going to
Steal some more of your mystery Oreos eventually
But the mystery Oreos guys
They're okay
I feel obligated to do a review but they're okay
Play Flavor where you're like
Oh this is great for to sepsis
Too many like I never want to
Cat with a disaster
I don't understand all the words
Excited about it
Transition is amazing
I'm a policy wonk
We appreciate it so much
Very much film
Also I'd like to give a shout out
I also like to give a shout out to
David appreciate it
Someone sodomizing
Weaver's
If you like to come policy walk yourself you can go to our website knowledge fight.com
Cookie support
Yeah I mean I feel like we got some buttons going out to people who has I requested them
Send me your email address
Send it to you
My girlfriend's mad that they still exist so let's just send them on out also because we have like
Some donations in policy walk stacked up we have not made progress
The last time we hung out
Odds of the progress toward
The end of the month goal
I don't know what did you just say
Do I was announcing the goal
Terms of the month
Trying to raise 100 extra dollars per month
Getting the Alex Jones documentary
Documentary
Those people who I just gave a shout-out to we're already factored into the last
75% of the Declarations
Every single
What I'm doing
No
I told you a little bit about this
For the show
I just don't I don't
Think there's value in talking much
About Alex Jones
In the prison
Anymore
I think that he is entirely
I think that's all he's doing
Times for something
And desperately trying to
Abstract people
From and discredit
The investigation that Robert Mueller ism
And I'm not entirely literally every other Republican
I'm not entirely sure why he's
He's doing that
I mean obviously the team sports
Being investigated
There's some of that
But I don't I don't feel like that's a satisfying answer as to why but I can't speculate as to why
I mean we've we've uncovered him admitting that he's spoken to Russian intelligence
Barely meme
Absolutely I think that's
Very very likely
Give me a number of times he's done crack
I wrote an article about this
On the website
They might not understand
The frustration
2 in terms of Alex Jones
Present
On the 23rd of January earlier this week
Alex Jones got on air
One of the most embarrassing things that
I've ever seen in my life
Considering that I watch
He married Dennis Rodman
When she ended up doing
Was
To give you some
Text Georgia going to keep up
With all these stupid
Idiot
I'll tear the world Chris Jericho what's going on
So
There is talk
On all week
Conservative
And conspiracy boards
About a mysterious notorious memo
That has been written
To release and they will release it is absolutely fine
For them to release it and they will release it at any moment because
Cuz the Bombshells with fiery terrified
If you read that memo your eyes
Would explode it's like at the end of Raiders of the Lost
Absolutely all of the Nazis eyes and brains
Very
Such an important
For so long and they still haven't released
Play up how important it is without ever actually releasing it experts
It's not an actual intelligence
Product or anything like that literally nothing
Which is described it on the plug
Nothing at the same time until it's revealed what you can't do
Text message of the Seeker
Christmas idea like that
The moment they revealed that
Everybody who is on the fence web
Consideration of the stuff we were talking about before the trends that Alex
Experiencing
He's fake intelligence sources
Zach not being as cool as qanon
I'm falling for the antifa Soros document
Researcher found on Fortune the embarrassed
He lives a weird world of having to get out
In front of the story that is already always
Already out in front of
He's been left behind by the
Conspiracy world
Notorious GI
GOP memo that run around
So Alex
Gets on
The 23rd and this
He lays it out
Got a lot of sources obviously in Congress
Nope.
In the federal law enforcement
I got forces cross
Bored
I have basically reverse-engineered what is in the bombshell
Congressional memo
My sources
Without them
Secret
Play the little game of is this
By the way
Put it in a sealed envelope inside of a lockbox
And when the memo is revealed
So shall they grab that
Pull it out and you will know by Rivers engine
Sources are still reviewing
Secret information just because you play a game where you like
No
Top secret
Okay no
You can't say it but is it okay let's
Just play 20 Questions
You don't have to say yes or no
You know how in the house weigh
Truth or Dare they have open testimony in the house or in the Senate intelligence committee
It's only ask a question about something that is classified
Play I could not
Confirm or tonight I can't comment on that
Starts to show up
Figure it out with him
In the document
Are you going
What are the hour
A little bit later in the show
Samaritan
It's not bees I give Alex a BTU for what hand
Little bit later
Alex decides to go full Hog on
Okay folks I've got to go off air right now
Drudgereport.com
Our leftist throw fish
I got to go off air
Asean
Arabic film
Who's advising
He just said hey here why don't you just have
There's another memo there writing about this memo
But here it is
I got to go off
This is the classified memo
Sources
Whoever's telling
So there's a lot of problems
Having is the foreign intelligence service Court memorandum and opinion
Approved
2016 sex
7702 certify
He's been public
Online
Sent at least May 11th
When it was covered at nauseam
It's beesource
Of all of Trey Gowdy and all of that but people are in Congress
Section 702
Yeah cuz it does bring up some issues that
French
Disgusted on the show
This is not
Something secret and classified classified
It is not what the notorious memo that the GOP is been talking about
Playing up
Because it's
Existed for a long
Problem and it's an even bigger problem at Alex's thing that William Benny
Technical head of the NSA one of his major sources and frequent guest
Sent it to him saying it was
F****** idiot
Which is entirely paw
He's in on it
Actively creating propaganda without
Which
He is f****** with Ally
Because that wouldn't be hilarious possible but if he
F*** you because because he's on the hook for this
Alex
Because Alex
Document
If you're playing games you want to f*** with Alex
Cuz it's classified classified what's going to happen to him
Okay first off
There's nothing there's no legal Ramen
Suffocation
Classified
And then we will follow
Like it's not like
Taken seriously by other media sources
That he's no longer
Adrian veidt
Just so we can be clear Alex a little bit later.
Here is here's the situation
No consequences
Even if you think
That Alex
Dramatic
Him for lying to him
Escape say that
Alex has to continue to believe whatever bulshit
Behind the scenes
Play cookout
In the future when he makes it over
Clear
That this is the memo that everyone's talking about
So then he does this a little bit later in
Which is
Pretty fun
It's not that
Why were trying to post it they grab control the computer and turn it off and fry it right in front of us
Used computers
Already published it
Already got published we haven't told you yet
Your fool
Hillary Clinton all you
Daniel computer
I think it Daniel probably is looking at 4 and it was absolutely cannot believe though course not
Disgust for 7 months there's no global
Pectin in Friday's computer because he's trying to post
I think he
Means
That that computer just melt
I'm I'm going I'm not going to literally
From top to bottom melted as if it was poured into lava
Kate Daniels
That's what's going on
Of course this is the inevitable
Constitutional crisis
Play compared
I love Sunday supplement for me
Very expensive operation
Products.com
Imo's
So whatever he does alarm clock
Love and Rodger
Got to give it to him
The issue is distraction
We have
You have to get in on what
School on the internet in the conspiracy communities
And he has to do one better
And so he
It's embarrassing
Wait so is anybody else
Hold this bowl
What
The internet
Like I'm
But with this
Their ass but Alex no
Because everyone on the internet like this isn't going to play
Quickly but
Doesn't give a s***
It's a weight
To try and get more ears on it commercial
This narrative
Follow to the next day
On the next day on the 24th I believe yet
24th
He's talking about the Secret Service Test
Birthday text
So he just jumps to that because that's what I'm talkin about
That's what I see world is up in arms
Listen to the show today
But I got blown up
Those texts got released and they're nothing
He's just
Not worth our time
Definition
Because
That is kind of
Quintessential decline of the US media
In the first place
Is that
Once you start
We started having a media that chased
After the internet
It was
It was over
Because the internet has
The shortest.
History
Once the media star
Chasing the internet
They destroy their
Right
This is the same way
How big of a story
That's forever us
That's a feather in his
Cap forever
He has to pretend that everybody else
He has to pretend that he does though
Because he has to pretend he's
The king
Of that world
Ready or not
He's not be the internet is much better at this
Creative
And he's like
It's a problem
And I don't really care
I Don't Have You
Anyways keep
There's not much
We can do
About the
I really don't think so
I think the date
Look I'm not going to toot my own horn
But I think I can do pretty decent job
Investigating a lot of
I can't emotionally handle doing
Is chasing
Bulshit
Reds
In the immediate that Alex
Throws out
On my part
I don't care about the
I'm not
Interested I'm a check back from
From time to time
But whatever everyone's talkin about whatever the newest meme
But Alex Jones
I probably
We'll have very minimal awareness of it
I'm going
Back in time
I don't
I'm only focusing
Because I think that is
Yeah
I don't either
That's her way of coping with your
Disgusting
It's not draft go
Rather than combating
Hit head-on no it's not it's
I can't handle watching
You showing the price
It's a bummer
It's a desperate man raving about
Yeah and it's not
Like I told you before the show I think
Think it's beneath us
Quite frankly
If you
Started editing
Out
The Alex Jones Park
Just left in Rodger Stone
Gradle
I think I'd be fine with it for good
Maybe maybe maybe for a little while
It was like
Nixon was crazy
Jordan
Listening tattoo my way of telling you some
No no
I found
Some really old
Oh no
How old
We're talkin 2008
No s*** so we're going to a back in the past
Today we'll be going over March 18th
Calpers
It's be what we can learn
Do you know what
Excites me the most
Officially Marty
I honestly
Expected around of a
Applause
Trivial
Where do they cover 2008
I mean we're going to be able to cover Obama's election
Cast from the past
We'll be able to get in
We're just going to
Absolutely dismantle 2000
Trove
From 2028
We'll be going back ten years in the past and 10 years into the future
About aliens
Let's go
Every single app
Prepackaged
Guess what
James O'Keefe
First project
James O'Keefe was just interested
This
Audio package
A couple of James O'Keefe prank calls
To Planned Parenthood which we will listen to now
What's your position
What would I underweight abortion is that apply to minorities to
Typically wanted to underwriting abortion for a minority person
Okay
Definitely way too many blocky for a while so I'm just trying to do my part
That's what I'm trying to do
That's a first
That was real
Yeah it's the sort of thing where you get the scent by listening
To them
Whenever he proposes that this idea of like
I'd like to
To give money
Before
People
The way they interpret that is
There are a lot of people that we don't have access to health care in minority communities
And then like any charity that helps
Anybody who doesn't help on their own
Are also minorities who can't afford it
More about the people making them
Then the people received
Because the positions that they
Advocate
Really out of line
So
We're do listen to him talk like a white supremacist and not be like
Oh yeah you're a white
He's playing a character
You sound very sincere
Call Autumn
What about abortion for the underprivileged
Wonderful
Appreciate
Abortion help
Minority group but that be possible at the black community for example
Abortion couldn't kebede
Before
Currently on if you wanted to designate that you wanted your gift
She's being very clear about what
Accepting this as
Do you have a full of racism
At this point
The call could have ended
Because for what he wants to get out of it
Right
Will accept your but however
Another like 35 seconds unnecessary and probably just
Great because I really faced trouble with
I want my kids being disadvantaged Dino again
I just had a baby I want to put in his name
Can I put it in the name of my son
Yeah he's trying to get into into colleges and I'll be applying
British really big
What are you doing
Alright
Complete nonsense
It's just it doesn't prove
A goddamn thing
College
Trouble
Multiple with affirmative
So that means
Everywhere he goes
He gets affirmative action.
This baby
People like Alex and Alex
James O'Keefe is using affirmative action as
Is a racist
Floyd
To prank
Planned Parenthood
It's false
Align with their beliefs it's just
About that as opposed to being like
Whatever version of their complaints about
Him on the phone is like this is just letting out what
Michael complaints
How does that but it's
It's very much like
Okay
You're going to make a racist donation that's
Still a donation to Planned Parenthood
And like all the donations in Mike Pence's name is just like
The first point is generally their business is making money for Planned Parenthood
They're low-level functionaries who work there
Also there they're just like
They heard him say I want to make a donation
Navigate to Leslie whatever it is you're saying
Is great I don't care if you give me the card number you even heard of the first one that's like the ladies like whatever
Find believe whatever you want about us
Killing minority
Sprite
Your racism went so far you're doing good for black
You're at you're doing good
As a prank
I think it was
We got to that point
F****** piece of s***
Go all the way to otherwise you don't have receipts
To quote the great Insane Clown Posse
Let's go all the way
Anyway
Great quote
Thank U next clip Alex Jones her to talk a little bit
About O'Keeffe
Stunt of a recording called the 500
Because
Consent to
Now it's believed that the person who went into
The Clinic's pretending
Can you be pregnant and recording
I don't know she did time but you did get to
Some trouble about like a harassment
Recording people without their
Consignment
This doesn't look good
They are shooting group randomly called seven different out of a list of hundreds
Chevron
Planned Parenthood they all said the same thing
If you believe that he only called seven
You're insane
Giggling snickering
Oh absolutely
Liberal
Sprouts
Barack Obama criticizes
No know they'll be lots of
They know who they work for
Add more huge transmission today Stay With Me
Okay
Little lizard
I think he's out horny
Killing black
Well he's getting into it
You know like
You can see flickers of the neck
2050 at Planned Parenthood
Even hear that guy
There's the myth
Quoting of people
Acting like
It's it's
Like to take this document
From 10 years ago
Oit present
Why
I just like
The fact that nobody is bombing
I guess I got that Snow Buddies
Spray painting
And all of that was a very was a much more
Shooting at Lenox
The tea party was not a great organization
Station hours
Wow they were Proto night
Discussing the tapes a little bit more and I
Don't think he does a good
They randomly called
Planned Parenthood
Laughing smacking of lips
Right there
The smacking of lips is literally what he says about those people on the planet
A direct
Verbatim
Example
It doesn't accurately depict either
Instance
It's just a weird hang-up he has about people
But smacking the lips somehow like indicates to him Eva
Weird it's
Consistent
I do think
The second one's word Okie
I'm not going to lie it I think it's pretty good imagery because whenever you hear smacking your lips you think of every animal
Behavior a child an annoying child
That's what I think
Weird
Prismatic
There's too many blacks I want this for black so absolutely
And the people that run these I've been around them I've met him I protested them
They are literally some type of
Weird
Zombie
They are just the sickest
Cast of Wicked
Cult-like people you can imagine
Don't believe me just go down and go into one of these places and talk to him
One has to experience the Matrix before they
You can really be told about it is just better to experience it
You know his call his listeners
Go down there
Talk to them
Yell at them
The Matrix when you're
Hostile to The Matrix I like the idea that the
People who are going to work everyday
Not V
Insane people standing outside of the building every day screaming and holding sign
If you're going to choose which one was the cult
Would it be the person getting
Payday lifx
Bright
Is that like
You know
The only real relevant conversation here is
Does society
Overwhelmingly and buying large approve of abortion
As a medical procedure
Yeah we've had that conversation
Should be over to all of this other side
Traffic is
Just
It's the same thing
Just distraction over here to try in
Chipaway
Woman's right to reproduction
Did help
Under the name of racism
Or something else okay so if your argument is
Planned Parenthood
Is yes cuz I can be a
And then they'll be like
Yeah it will kill minority
Dispel all that
Claims that all black leaders are globalist
Which
I don't know one black leader if you could have just stop there
Ben Austin Texas
Blackbeard Dallas where I grew up I don't know one black leader in the country about that leader
Six out there
The mainline pimps of the New World Order
You have there is already a dichotomy that is on sustained
Because he's
Is controlled by the global
Good ones are dead
The only good ones
Take a look back through history and see a lot of very good black leaders who have been killed
Walmart liquor
Specifically for being good black leader
Does not mean
Necessarily that all of the black leaders that you are 12
Now
But you said you understand what the
Intention of that argument
It's to disenfranchise
And take legitimacy
Empower away from any black
But Al Sharpton
That's just
Also James David Manning
How the new world order
Every major groups people under control
About the Judas goats
They'll give fiery speeches about devil yd all day and then
Stop their chests and talk about how
Whites are absolutely Wicked people
When an average the average white person to guilty in a chicken neck
Limp-wristed person running around with a guilt complex
Rolling out red carpets for black people in my
Some experience
But also we can tell already in 2008
Narratives
Want you to make me feel bad for all the bad things that everybody I've ever known has done.
The point of saying I don't want to be made to feel bad saying that all white people already unnecessary
Really feel bad
And he's pointing the finger at them
Time for that
Position at least
It in this Ram
Exactly
Which is the
To take his
To be so correct that he
His denial then has to spiral further down into
Insanity
I think it's negative progress
Speaking of which
Navigate to that clip
To Planned Parenthood
Singer thing against the different it's a different part of it we've already discussed
Rosanna KKK
We've already discussed the idea that
You started Clinic
Specifically in black neighborhoods
She didn't the early ones
Women
Which may be the largest issue Clinic
Especially in the early times
Disproportionately in low-income neighborhood
Because those were the populations they were serving
Because they needed help
Cuz rich people
Have always been able to
What if you make it illegal
Rich people will still have
Neighborhood
Do it the way that they
Clear the idea that like making it illegal doesn't
An abortion
Kilwins
Yeah
From her that's maybe why they
Maybe they hide like maybe that's a smart idea
Find the idea that
Planned Parenthood
It is
In order to
You kind of
Counteract
The fact that their hatred of it is more massage
Criticism
Planned Parenthood on
Kind of
Angle
Is massage
Yeah
Women shouldn't be allowed to
Men should be allowed to chew
Right like that's what it really is
22 imagine it is
It is
Like one of you think
Planned Parenthood is racist
You're still a massage
You don't get don't get a pass off
That the murder of babies cuz
By the way
And the racism
Specific
Exterminate the black community cuz that's what they pretend
Planned Parenthood is doing
Supersedes
My misogyny this is more important. Of your eye before you criticize the speck in mind
Understand like
Why would you need to escalate
If your argument is there murdering babies
Why do you need to need that because some people
Stupid and are tricked by the races
Some narratives regarding
Yeah but
Not racist
Isaiah
Anyway I want to get to this clip
Because we're coming up on
Maybe my favorite
One of my favorite clips of all time
It's not that but it is
Yeah Planned Parenthood predominantly in the minority areas its mission
And these are
The official writings and letters of Margaret Sanger and Foundation minutes
Black person is a weed
Be exterminated
An
Let's make those letters all these robber barons she was getting millions of dollars and I was given a billions back then she was being on the show
Foundations and how far we've got it higher blackfront doctors because
The blacks only trust other blacks
So that part is we've already talked about that
How to get black doctors
Wasn't because
We can trick them probably because
What that was part of it but the excuse or the reason
Something that she gives in the actual letter is that people are more likely
People of their own social
Idea
Opening up
To a white doctor might be more difficult than a black person opening up to
Remember
This was like in the night
20 this is not like
Furthermore
I don't
I don't either
Person should trust a white person ever
Okay
Different directions
I should have known
Native American
White person
I wanted to take out of that
Black people being
He's quoting Margaret
Okay so this isn't
Is it
Is it in the minutes
Wealthy there's a quote that
Attributed to her from 19
They went around it
It says human weeds
Black soldiers and Jews are a menace to the race
Eddy Grant
Snopes
Finding out what
The truth of this was
Their breakdown
Was it just the word
No 4:00
!
Prove difficult as many primary iteration
The earliest versions We were able to locate I didn't appear until sometime between 2008 and 2009
Right when we're talkin about
Primarily on blogs and message boards
All of these initial iteration site
Does pregnancy centers website
A cache of which can be viewed here and they linked to it
Statements by Margaret Sanger the founder of Planned Parenthood
Generation of the quotes
Suggested bracketed paraphrasing
Singers words have been
Been somewhat creatively interpreted
So
Did you write him in French
From the website
Is this quote
Immigrants are human weeds
Black soldiers and Jews are a menace to the race
Eugenic sterilization is an urgent need we must prevent
Application of this bad stock
Eminem quotes
Margaret Sanger April 93 birth control reviews
Control review is available online
And they look through that quote doesn't exist in any way we're the citation
Of course not
Referencing something I was quoted on message
Switchboards
GE said he's pretending that he did deep research
Into this and it
It's not
You just believe in the house
Even then if it is it if it is in the minutes
Stay lyrics
Right
This was in the minutes Margaret Sanger
And it was
Was written down
In two thousand and
I was running
Planned Parent
Inside the 60
Looking through
Margaret Sanger inspiration for existing
Notes and I saw that'll be like
That's it out
Right
So somehow
That's the posing gun that somebody had a
Copy of these men
And pass them down
Hand-to-hand
To get to 2,000
Yeah that's really saying this is an oral history
Avulsion
It sounds
It sounds Wild
Not be
Super on
Unfair
Margaret Sanger was
Into eugenics
She didn't seem to be a racial eugenics
She seems to be a practical
Well yeah unfortunately prevailing theory in the 20
Good and it's certainly something that we hopefully all should have moved past at this point
In the twenties was inextricably
Erase regardless of
Whatever it was likely likely
The argument that Alex makes about
Like having
Eugenics
Racial
It just doesn't stand up
Here's the thing about that
Alright
No matter
How good a person you are
Immediately after the election
There's probably a point where you were like
What if we did just get rid of dump
Technically
It's a dangerous precedent
And you immediately go well that's a bad idea but it
The same time the thought is there
Skip this next clip
It's not as interesting as I thought when I was cutting clips
Play Jewish
I'm just trying to cause trouble
There we go
Cuz you said it before in the past I was just trying to trace that like
That's what we believe for you
Oh yeah you.
Betty White the reason I'm skipping it is cuz I need to get to the next clip
This
Makes me
This makes me so happy Jordan
This
Truity
Despite everything I know about him
Horrible
Part of me
I want it I want there to be a way he can be safe
You're rooting for the Redemption
It's impossible 2008
It might have been possible
And I know it from this clip
Put your mic sound charms
Wait for this moment
Kris Kristofferson
I wonder why
First
Spoiler alert
But also
When he just said
Best part right here
That is
Exactly the point the song where many times I've drunk
Waylon Jennings
Where's the beef
Find a place
Find your apps
Coming up
Interview
About 40 minutes
Chapman today for a full hour to financials
Call man
Can't wait to hear you play the whole Highwaymen song so awesome
100 awesome reality
He was a radio DJ just did that
Classic
I find that okay just talkin over it a little bit
Even if even if you
Easily through in the
Also by the way Planned Parenthood is full of racist mods
Anyways
Like he's what I love when you're doing a rillo by morning
The songs about the rodeo Amarillo
Santa
San Antonio San Antonio
That's the stuff man where you see those flickers there's like
Bats
Fun
And it's even more surreal
He was genuinely having a worst thing that ever happened to him is he got popular
God we should go so thrilled
Does Waylon Jennings vs the best part
NuWave
To interview Alex
Don't even bother with asking him questions
Don't bother with trying to remember when you were
Protective
Well now
I think he's dead
Tumi
He will always be
I can't get over stuff like that
Reruns of
The Dukes of Hazzard
Hazard nose
How to get a sample of what what I'm talking about at the beginning of the show
What I'm talking about the present when he's just on this
Attraction b******* go back to the past find stuff he's lying about we can have fun and then I can hear stuff like that
Huge piece of s*** but that's Charming
That's Charming
The reality of him just talking about like
Blacks are the real racist group black people
I can't get enough of it I love it I love it so much
Johnny Cash's verse
The universe divide
I'll find a place well Alex
Or maybe
Single drop trailer
Listen to you and that song and the way you feel about that song and then listen
To Alex in the way he feels about that song similar
You guys are the Batman in
And the Joker kind of like
You're the you're the same Spectrum
I am the I am the darker brother
A poem
Pretty funny.
Spoiler alert
Love getting up there and say
Anyway
Jon Bon Jovi
You would have made that song great
My burial
I also as a guy name
Football
Something else which we will talk about the end
The guy named Jeffrey
Who just wants to talk about GMOs a whole bunch
Interview with dr.
Jean Adele or something I'm not sure the radio show
I don't I don't really care to all that much
Because
In the same way that Alex singing the entire song of Highwayman
Was endearing and delightful
Vixen
No
It's amazing
Okay in 2008 Alex Jones was still in a play
Where he would invite
White people onto his show with Judd
Doctor Dell
Adele
Whatever
Deidre
Keep smack
In this first clip into vaccine
Westside with him
Should have let Alex to a more intellectual study of the
We know from history that Alex Jones
This ignores everything
Literal real doctor
Supposed to
Is chiropractor
The point there really isn't they aren't.
Sodus Point Alex is making the argument that sign Marisol is
Chemical that
Painting
In vaccines
A little bit
I don't care what the chemical the argues for an hour
Because I care about that first
You better show me evidence
Health officials admit vaccines may have hurt Georgia girl
Federal Blue Ribbon
Panel this is just a February
25th is just last month
Found Emerald her favor this is a blue-ribbon panel
Does not imply the vax
Young child if indeed this is not a court of law by the way
He's making reference to something we've gone over this
You have to pray
That one case
Millions and millions and millions and millions
That's very unusual mitochondrial DNA
In combination with
Something having to do with vaccine
Not for Marisol really carefully
May have played a role in
Nobody
Smallpox often face of yours where is it
You don't take that technology
Because there is so
It's not absolutely perfect to drive across if you love it and you willing to take a 2500
Killing yourself is here
Americans grow up and understand
Let me stop you.
They're actually in and if you'd like
I'm actually about 50 I'm here in front of me
So he goes on to say like you
My favorite part
My favorite part was just a robot
Just the first thing you said was
You have to
To keep reading Alex immediately like
I mean
But to say it
Spring-trap
So good and Alex Jones starts yelling about like
There's so much
ISM in the world
Nyr
Numbers going up so much
Tell me he's manipulative Lee using thread autism numbers
Reflect reality necessarily be
Because
It's great but I'm not sure
Do you know if you want to talk about Alexa
Evolve time in our history we didn't understand
Various parts of
The Spectrum understand how
Diagnosed properly
Autistic
Work
Presenting
Chisholm
Hysteria
Interesting how many different
Diseases
Have
Disappeared almost
It's
It's the same thing that you can make these stupid arguments about like I'm sure what you would do
Idea of like the feminization of society
Before
How many people were trained before
But either killed themselves or never were, or or never comfortable living in public
Be captured by statistics
Part of life
That's the way he manipulative Lee uses these
26in what have you
Anyway
At this point mr. and mrs.
I'm afraid your child has
Has been diagnosed with
Douchebag
Mr. and mrs. Jones
Alex Jones
Because
Doctor
Adele
I keep hearing
A delightful name
But it's not
I look into one of them wasn't
It's dinner time
Anywhere Alex at this point tries to go in
To like
Here's here's a story I can tell
This'll prove my point
I was in a
More or less
What is doing.
Because it's increased
Did the Tooth Fairy do I increase autism
And what's going on to wait
By the way
There's a lady there at the pool
Autistic son
And I walked over and I say when did this happen how he was 18 months old and let me guess
Let me see how you know do you know me
After that and then
Let me guess the hospital
Real quick will get you
Respond
Is the story
Details to present day
This is one of his favorite stories
This is like this is one of those Road hacks
Right right
Same power 420
Man wanted why is it I get the shots in the hospital
Listening
Reasoning fallacy
That are given to kids are
Is nothing can happen in
The trial that is in a week or two after a shot or we
It seems like there's a relation
Insurance
Seems like
We need to find out but we're just waiting and spinning our Wheels not getting to the bottom of autism
To put down
Theory that kind of came
And it kind of went so let's move on why is it so cold
Why is it that women have certain up testicle problem
Tomorrow is
Clip Alex tries to bring up fluoride today
This is a really interesting response
I love the way that
The doctor is just like
Kind of what
We will
Aspire to do TVs laughing
Alex
Come on he's treating me like a child which is a child
Stinging do you like
Grow up grow up
Once he laid that out
You're like
Alex what do you got
Right
Fluoride
Let's take sodium fluoride
I just said you there in the breast
The
From the aluminum and
Of course fertilizer manufacturer that's what they call fluoride
But they didn't put in the water
And you said I never heard that
How to make sure you get email all the mainstream documentation and
FDA investigators also
CC
Don't give babies fluoride water
Right because they're getting plenty of it
Getting plenty of it as it is you got to be very careful not to saying that they used weight
Material
Fluoride
I wouldn't be surprised but the same token I can
Can take water from your toilet
I can reduce
Clearwater
You might say hey I'm drinking
Do you drink a water it system process
Factor to Sarasota
To make fluoride
And there are
Little white spots
On kids Front Teeth
Comes up
Play come from fluoride Big Harbor
Situation where they graduate
Did the report about increase
Navigate to Main Line University
From China to Japan
To England where it causes massive increases in that type of cancer and boys
Massive increases you got to be careful with that
In terms of applying
Cause and effect cuz it might seem so but
Amion
I doubt it
When you start doing stuff
But suppose I have a drugs and I'm putting it on the market
And I do eight studies in a row to find
Side effects
Killing people then the 8th and the 9th study finds
We could we could study right
Find out hey this is a great drug and doesn't cause side
What do you think is going to get published
Careful in that you look at in the
The entire body of the literature
The membership is 650 who still believe
And they do their studies
I would not say the controversy with 99.99% of sign
Believe one thing
Do we want to go
Because we love the underdog I guess they want to go with a polo 1%
The Meg
He's pushing at the other big governments and banks are doing
Toxic waste Nebraska
They say every sign disagrees with man-made global warming
When that's actually not the truth it's the opposite
Cycle
I am so you're saying everybody you know they all know that
Tell me the last time
But you saw in the history of cyanide cuz I know the few examples here
You saw that
.1% of scientists turn out to be right
And if they turned out to be right by the way
Approved
.1%
Bi-Rite
Wow
Al-khazneh
It was the last
I'm not sure but he moved the goalposts talking about fluoride
Is pushing
All right we have a logical conversation
Keep moving everything
Okay that's a whole new conversation what the f***
Okay
Ever now
Alex
Changing the conversation
Let's talk about how dumb you are here
The problem is you want me to
He described you as you want me to come over here cuz I got you
You're actually Stupid Alex that's why you're losing a million-dollar operation
Yeah you can't do stuff
Over and over again by a real doctor
You should have done if he was smart what you should have done is be like
Get out get out
Go go
You should have like we lost we lost
Connection with the s*** out of
Do curb stomp into the alley
The reality is like
He should have taken some of this to Heart like
Locate these are really good point
About why my reasoning is flawed
I'm going to try and do better in the future
If I were him I would leave the show feeling like s***
I would leave being like
I blew it
Nope
Countless study after study
It is always
Hey whenever
People are shown to be wrong
They just double the f***
Make it Angry
Do you want to believe in your own
Comped
Compton
Vigilance to not
Get eaten up by your own b*******
Self-criticism
We are constantly evaluating
Batman figure Joker of the doctor in Alec
What have you
This one's good
Because
Like this is really just him trying to
Layout like
Simplistic logical concept
60 - 4
And auntie I mean I'm sure you know you're a medical doctor procedures University
That a lot of our modern Sciences
We're dominated by eugenicist
Papa Joe
Thirtysomething
For sterilization here
And that then they went underground with crypto eugenics
Underwear that
But I I kind of I kind of
Don't think it's helpful to take our path
Mistaken condemned the future
I agree with you these things have been horrible black marks on the history of science
Listen you can say
America is a horrible horrible country
Because of all the horrible things we did look at our mistakes
Violence and blah blah blah blah blah on our history
So I think
Very very careful in your races issues
The baby out with the bathwater cuz I'm not saying a whole country is bad
These mad scientist
Literally I mean
Watching Project
He was there when it was Eugenics I read books
I'm saying the vast majority of the captain
You know what I mean
50 years ago almost everybody at the highest levels of Science in this country and England in Germany
What's a raving racer
Just everybody knows
50 years ago most people were
America and I would say we
We haven't we had and still have a problem with all this
Year of doing the
Finally found
True heroes
I'm an ass man
He's everything I've ever wanted
Going to take a step back cuz I don't know enough about him and might be some like really terrible s*** that he's gone or
For dark hair
I have no idea I'm not willing
Totally about ramp
Don't bring this in
Spring reality
You know how how long
How hard
I have wanted
A true hero on our Infowars podcast
Beautiful
Is patient
Kind
Enjoying himself and his
Constantly slapping Alex down are you sure
Suck it
Just heard the man I want my father to
About Jesus that's all that's a lot
But I mean in that last week there we saw him explain to Alex
What is a composition
Individualism
It's not really willing to act
That is not willing to do any of this work is that willing to
Deal with the world reasonably and I love
Love the idea of this guy
Just coming in
I'm out
Multiple commercial breaks
It was like it was like if your bombing if your bombing you still want to try and go out
Laugh like you
To try and go out on a, gotcha
Never Comes
Doing his introduction
You made it
You made it seem like let's see if he shows up I'm going to get them
I don't want to treat it like I don't like
Arguments as though there's a winner and a
Like you and I are
It's not about trying to win but I feel I feel I don't feel great
I knew I like to I like to learn I love being wrong
Lego
Just like you were saying
When the icon I feel like a loser an argument about whether the return to innocence was a good song.
He's talking about his Wendy iconoclast
Is right
Science what he
He didn't get to finish
Was science goes
Batshit
And
Love it for everything everything
Think about
Also is that
When the iconoclast
Is right
It's because they have
Proof
Exactly
Obligation
These things
Do you have the album
Listen to be like
I'm wrong
This guy proved
Right
The difference
So that's why I don't like
Azul winter loose thing
I like whenever I'm wrong cuz then I get to learn
Like that's crazy
It change
Just the way that I feel about
Chris gethard model of life
How many of our conversations have ended with me saying you know what
You're right and I've changed my opinion on the show a bunch on the Shelf
In public I will admit my failure
I'll see you in hell about how I should love Kanye
You should love
The doctor
And now this guy named Jeffrey
Smith comes on
Basically all he's doing is talking about the evils of GM
Fair enough
Two stomachs
Disagree
The GMOs are as dangerous as people like Alex make them out to be
The GMO company
Monsanto's of the world
Problems and the idea GMO then the problem is
Does unilateral mean
Sprite and patent
They're not so much
Scientific problems
If this guy comes on and he has a laundry list of these
Specific examples
A people
Investigating
GMOs
They got screwed over and what have you
I don't believe it
Even have the time
Teresa
One of them stuck out to me
Because it's an argument that Alex will continue
This is another example of the
Genesis
Of one of his
Against GMOs
I've done it was dr. Jean Adele f****** with him while wearing a fake booty
A fake voice and glasses
No it's not
Is Jeffrey Smith
You list out this
Here you give the specific example of someone
Fujiyama Lobby
Alright
Another example
Irina ermakova
I interviewed her at the EU Parliament
We gave a presentation there
He had the documents piece of paper
One day and a piece of paper was burnt under desk kind of has a warning
Some of her samples at
Open stolen
Told by her
Her director into no longer do research on genetically engineered Foods
Viciously in a public Review-Journal that have lights
Telling her that she was going to be bothering an article about her research
And it turns out
They just wanted to set her up
So what was her crime
For her crime was discovering that rats were fed
They were fed genetically engineered soybean
History of spring tide in more than
50%
Compare to The Offspring
The rats that were fed
Regular soy Italy died at about 10%
He also founded the signs of the office
Spring when the mothers were fed GM
So I was much smaller they couldn't reproduce
Her crime was simply
Eating rats genetically engineered store that weed everyday
And discovering
Deaf and problems in the office
So
This has now been
Absorb
By Alex Jones
The Peace of his narrative about what the globalist
Want to do to us
And uses it to say
Studies have shown
The GMO
Yu-Gi-Oh die
Much sooner and are unable to reproduce
Smaller
Then
Normal rats
And that's what
You which I say
He says
The Regeneration
I are unable to
Produce that doesn't make sense
Nor is it
Reasonable
And I looked
Into this a little bit
Simply not how
It's not possible
For that to be a legitimate
Conclusion of your article
But there are so many other variables
That you have abs
Absolutely not
Like if you do a regression analysis of
A study
And then any other studies
You would find out that ate hers is an anomaly
Well actually there a bunch
The critic
You know science
Together
Petit Coeur study looked into it
Because she refused to
She just went around spouting the The Binding
Arena ermakova macova
Natural biotin
Technology where they tried to get to
The bottom of a number for clay
I got a eight.
Dennis office
You know how popular natural biotechnology is
You can't of
Void every
Everytime I go to Walgreens
Trying to buy cigarettes
Natural biotechnology
Everywhere
It is the most
Famous
Magazine
There's no magazine
More noticeable
Franklin
It's f****** Ennis
Escapable
How popular natural
Dewgong
Yeah boy
I just want
Morris Day
That the thing I read most
More than any
Book more than
Like have you ever read Google News
On every option
Natural biotechnology
There's always an article
Play some candy crush
Your
I'd like the guardian reference
Technology
The Atlantic Politico
Who knows
Okay
As far as I can go
Biscotti
What was the level of morta
Georgia
They asked her
What was the level of mortality of the pup
You found in the
Control and test
In the first three repeats of the experiments up till five times higher mortality was observed
The newly-born pop
Whose mothers that received the GM soy flour supplementation
Compared with pops
From rats receiving Protein Isolate
Traditional side laboratory Chow
Which are the control group
Pops from Rhapsody
Inside a GMC diet died mostly during the three weeks following
Blah blah blah she goes on
I'll give I get a couple of
Looking over this
Here was the assessment
Pup mortality is usually reported at Day Zero or day
Causes of deaths are not report
Provided
Show that 8.1% of Pops died in the
The control group
The typical mean pup survival
Observe for wistar rats
Is greater than 90
Plus or minus
2 at day one
+ 99.54
10 + -1
8 day 21
The abnormally High
Instapot mortality in the
Controls
Poor animal stewardship
Possibly arising from poor animal husbandry
No Valentine Tif
The conclusions can be based on a study with
Poor performance
Control group
Table one also reports 10% mortality on
Conventional soy
No conclusions could be drawn
From a study
In which the convention
Control mortalities
Fire
The normally Observer with DAR rat
Okay that's the first problem
The first criticism of the study
Is
You killed
Right right whatever the case is whatever the condition
You had
Dance Ali higher death rate
Line of York
Control group is unacceptable for science
That's based on
Every other control group
And you have
You're the one who's wrong
Before we begin the claims issues making
Of the gm01
Being lower weight
Your mother's fed GM soy
Supplement
From Rats of the
The positive control
Group or from the conventional soy flour
You found that 33% of Pops in the rats
Controls
So the critic
Sad
Individual animals and illiterate then averaged desmeon for females and mean for males
To account for gender
Fable 3 does not
Is not separate
The two
Table three
Stupid does not segregated by gender
Percent larger than females at this age
More importantly
Under carefully controlled conditions.
Is approximately
38 Grand plus or minus
Will vary by no more than plus or minus ten percent
The data in table three are presented in an unconventional manner
Determine the exact mean
And standard are derivation amongst
Table three states
53% of control pops
Are below 30 G
Which is abnormally small
A two-week-old with star wrap top
More than 90% of wrap-ups fed conventional soil more than 20% below normal
GM story 9% below normal weight
Approach
And isolate said pop 78
Fair someone
Do you know otherwise variance in data in table three and the high percentage of low weight animals are clear indicators of malnutrition
Environmental condition
No conclusion can be made about abnormal development
Unless they can
Controls conform to International observe Norm
Do you know why
There's no greater
Own
Then the science Zone
Because it's
Equivocal
Like any
Anytime you see a spa
Patin
Pacific Journal where so many people are like
Okay here's why you're wrong
It's always the most
Thorough specific examination
Line by line of why everything you did was wrong but there's no way around
You even
Brian come back
You're just going to be like
Yo William
Saw the song that date like you've got
Okay this is why your process was wrong
You should probably didn't follow
Different variables that could be affecting the outcome
So in Japan
People got together
The study in 2000
Seven witches
Yeah and
Atlas 2007-2 Alex
Should know this get this in the scholarship at the time that you going on Alex Jones Show
And touting this as an example of groundbreaking
Who studies
He doesn't know about this
Vape
Didn't
Just do a short-term
Study like she dead
Didn't entire year they follow follow the guidelines
Control groups and standardization entire finding
Read
That dumb lady is dumb
Gross necropsy findings
Hematological in Serie A biochemical parameters Oregon
No meaningful difference
Between rats fed the GM and non-GMO
These results indicate that long-term intake of
Genetically modified
At a rate of 30% in a diet
Has no apparent adverse effects
So
So he can
I mean I mean the
Non-use of that now
Cuz it's not like
He's a loner unique
You know like his guests is doing what he owes assholes
He's gay
Is someone whose business it is to know about Guillermo issue
His guess is coming on
To discuss this issue with somebody whose business it is to lie about
More the point
But that's like a
You're running
Look
You're the difference is I'm I'm responding
Ending to what I asked
Expect
Alright
Expecting an ID
Idealistic Viewpoint that will never
Passing these Liars are always going to
What we need to do
Kill all the dumb people Eugenics forever
The argument that I'm making is that even dating back to
The 2008
It's very clear that
The guest that he has on
With exception of dr. Dina Dell
He's got
Are still propaganda
Yeah there's still people who coming on with an agenda that doesn't match
Reality
Because
One of the most important things I think with going back into the past
I already told you
Someone just asked Jordan friends outside of the podcast
We'll see we'll see if we go get a drink after the show
At this point in history
Alex Jones
As far as I can
Intel isn't selling youngevity
You haven't gotten into the game.
He plays now with
I didn't hear a diamond gusset commercial on this episode but we'll see I will keep you posted
You started selling
Some supplemental
But he's not selling them
Advertising
For them
How to say like what is he
He selling it
Yukon men with
Come on.
Are shockingly all for his
Documentaries
Loose change
And stuff like that
Commercials
Dollars for a postcard
Soap
Commercials that he plays cuz these aren't episodes with the commercials cut out
Most of them are kind of like
This is local radio
You know I bikes
We seen his contract in present-day andweknow like
Breakdown of time
He gets four
Right. I think it's possible that back then he didn't
Have
Time commercials that are on there are four
Gcn affiliate
Has a soap
Person who is an Advertiser
He's big but he's not huge
So anyway the reason I brought it for supplement thingy
Is he says something on this episode that is particularly weird
Considering what we know about
Alois colon and body cleanse
I don't make an extraordinary climate just cleans out your guts and is a detoxifier
Asbury Park
Did that make you
Sprout wings and fly Rattler forever
The other supplement pictures I don't be associated with that
Okay this is just
The good stuff it's just it's associated with his future self
I'm confused
Boy means like we're not making any wild claims
DNA
Keep your DNA
Together in order to make you live longer
Fair enough
I have
Specifically because that's the end of your DNA that as you age they
Continue.
But at the same time
He's also right
It's just it's just ironic
Nobody
So at the end of the episode
A bunch about the economy
How things are bad
Now we know from history
Did get pretty bad
This is 2008
Come on
If you know it's standard operating procedure for
Alex Jones
Anycast
To say
The house is on fire
Yeah but
In this case I accidentally were right
Chapman is on
I don't care about what
You saying because
No it's difficult
To parse out like
Mark
We're in March okay
So this is
Pretty much immediately after the massive
Stimulus FAQ
Gun threat
I don't really care because something more important
In the middle
Sinbad and all that
Alex husband
Alex
Okay Steve thanks for the call when I come back in the final segment Bob Chapman
And we're going to take
Final call but now
I want to rent in Anderson on
Okay every you can on Expert we have on
Manager Alta top guy
Have the New York Business School
The head of Shadow stats your Nobel Prize winners all of them
Are saying Metals Metals metals
Silver gold
Palladium Platinum
If you got more money than just give for a few Colonial into some of the mining stocks I'm not going to advise him
If you want more rest like Bob was saying maybe he'll give us some advice and what's in the
Forecaster
I just support the network that for 12 years
I have been home by a little gold company Ted Anderson little girls company
Decade
R210 real fast you got offers again
That you shut the price of this s*** gold at 1000 gold
Between 1005 and 1013 today
They're trying to suppress it it's not working
And I know I just a little bit more so little bit more gold from you you know I don't have a lot of money but I bought a little here little there
Bill job
Tell folks about the offer you've got today
Of course Alex right now we have the British sovereign coin it's a real gold coin
The great coin
So that's a disgraceful at pivot
But like
Is nowhere near as professionalism
Well I don't know it snow
Because of what we know about Alex
His business model and how he behaves now
We know that what he does
He tries to create an emotional response in people through some narratives and then payments to an ad
Is it like this is what'll make you feel better
Having a whole segment Bob Chapman talking about the economy
You know there's trouble
And all that invented
Call Alex
Is vouching for all the Tidy Up
Yep all that is why we have somebody who sells gold
I had also owns
Then don't talk about that much
FB
Important in
Here's a bigger
Does
Alex hoard gold
City by the little here little there
Doesn't get a discount he's not buying for Midas
Cuz I've done a bunch of research into their markups
Some stuff like that people
Like if
Constantly taking
The court in Suffolk there's a reason
Beyond
What actually ended up getting
The bullion license
Stripped
Record the number of times
Super Bowl
We're suing him for over pricing
Yeah go to the Ripoff Report complaints filed
The Better Business Bureau is a bunch of
Complaints
Surf cam
I'm not joking it's a damn
The BBB is actually a scam look into the Bebe is a
Midas resources
Look into it I agree with you on that I'm just saying that
Separate from the
From the GPS
Situation
Is also
I'm working on a large
Peace about
Resources and what have you
That I found
Court documents
That are pretty
Bandy business model
Which is
Hey hey hey f***
I'm sorry one more click.
Happening with ketchup
10 more people to Bob and there's and we're talkin about the same
Reply
Walking Liberty halves
And they stopped making those
A lot of this by running out the prices exploding
Getting meter spot
He's got great deals on gold silver
686 2237
I love doing this I love loving something I believe in
Good deal do you hurt the New World Order folks when you move out of
Dollar dollar right there
They don't take them in
Yan in Brazil they don't take him yet the alligator town yet everywhere 800
686 237
2237 right now
2237 don't wait
1 800
It's only going up
Thank you Ted
Vinyl siding with Bob Chapman the international forecaster.com
Thanks for thanks for having me on Alex
Guy who I own
Thank you so much for bringing me on
Contractually
Like you have
To do all the time
This kind of brings us full circle
To the beginning
And that is
10 years ago
And today Alex Jones
Both iteration
Incredibly desper
He's a desperate man right now
Provide cover
Distraction for
Regarding the investigation
With Mueller
You go back to 2018
And he's not a star back then he's not big time
Probably this point broadcasting out of a very small Studio
He's not the the glamourpuss that he is now
He doesn't get the supplement stuff until like 2013
Yeah it's so at this point
All he is all he's got
Is a gold show
He's desperate
To appease Ted Anderson
Yeah I mean I don't know
I would say he's probably more desperate
Now I think he was just desperate in both cases and which one is more
Equus now
As opposed to being a aggressive
Apologist
Fair
You like okay
Here's a here's a question that you just
Raise up in my
Raise up Boblo
So he is
We we know he
He's desperately obfuscating
And lying
From the Mueller
But I think
It's not even
That that's primarily motivated
Okay I think there's a
Some chance
To some extent
But what he's distracting from
How unimportant
Compared to the internet
Ego-driven
He's from the fact that he's not as in Port
Qanon or read it borderforce
Or something like that
Yeah that that could be part of it
But
I don't know anymore in the general
Of like
Alex doesn't actually
Like Alex can't have any kind of a
Insider information on that
As We Know
The truth
William
He said that that was the memo
Let me know the only reason
Isn't that he is
Working so hard
It is just because
He's in the tub
Like really it right
No I don't
The part of it I think I think
And that's a part of it
As part of it
The part of it
I think that he recognizes
Conscious level weather
He's willing to admit it or not
That most of his traffic
Bixbi could experience
The beginning
16 was due to box
Yeah he's worried about what
He's also worried about what might be
The uncovered
Connection
She had that might be
Implied
Because of it probably even a fourth
I think it's probably something that we don't
Probably something
From site
A little bit
And
I don't know we can speculate we're not Alex
I don't have fake swords
But I know that it will come to Bear eventually
Reply.
We stand outside of Alex Jones
Studio
Alright
Boombox
Overheads
Right
Highwayman
I think that would lure him out
I think it would be possible
Maybe
Then we just have a good old-fashioned sing-along
Like let's do it let's not even fight
Are going to have a sing-along
With Alex Jones
If you
Stab him
If you all were at
Bar
Like a rodeo
Akbar
We didn't get in
Politics or anything like that
There's a decent
We could get along
Is exploding
You guys if you guys ever got close
Just touched fingers the would like it will be a hundred percent energy
Explosion right
First of all
I wouldn't touch
Second
What do you think you feel
I think he feels bad
Like I would
I want to I want to walk my
But I don't think we get along now
10 years ago
Long as we have
Your hair was sometimes when you
If we applied those same rules
Race politics religion
Everything but Highwayman probably have a pretty good time
But
We do I have
Website
Can go to
Brother
Michelle
Something about and I've posted
Far less massive thing about how depressed the world is equally important
And kept their lives in Portland
Research
Knowledge
Book
We just got a lovely review from a in Austin
Australian fans
I believe
Thank you so much
Yeah I got to assume makes us feel better we like feeling good
You can listen to us
You can leave a review there as well if you're like
Also if you're listening live and watching on Twitch there's an after-party over on far outstrip
That far out rhymes
Believe Nikki Gibson hamburger be doing some s***
Super fun but
In the meantime Dan I think
Turn like
Who's who's getting
There's no
There's no doubt
Read my mind about this
Trey Gowdy
Go f******
Fuc yourself
Alexandra Thurston color