Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
They're like a hook
Is there a reason you would listen to to Yahoo's talk about Alex Jones
That we are stuck
No there's not that
That's all I can do that
And it's turning out that now at 3:11
Does it
Peanut in it
Hexohm
Still going wrong
It's great song
Amber
If you like couple of there so it's not going to do it I don't want to wreck my brain trying to come up with 311 songs are okay
Jordan soy before I believe we made the Declaration that I'm just sticking in the past
March 23rd 2008
Before we do
From Today Show
Okay this is going to be a weird
Radio show that you're not going
You want to miss
Alright
Selling it up top
But I'm learning very interesting
Is that
In 2008
Alex Jones radio show
It would not like a regular radio she was not a production
You didn't have a lot going for him and so like nowadays whenever he wants a day off or something like
Now maybe do a half-day
Tekken couldn't do that
He doesn't have that he doesn't have
No so what he would do
If you would replay interviews from a couple days previous
And make it
Like its lie
Yeah because I was listening to
No
Cuz I was listening to like the 20th or something like that March 20th
Dr. Dina Dell comes back
And I'm like
Call Jack Brown
Broadcast which is even crazier
I'm listening to remember a bit of this
And there's a couple days where it's
Just a no-man's-land of nothing
That's that's
Butt stuff
So
I think it's the whole thing the whole thing is just rebroadcast
Together interviews from previous days
Diabolical
Yeah I think that's what a lot of radio shows do though a lot of them will announce like I'm going to be off for a few days
The best robot ever
No he does not
What's going on
I'm a policy wonk
Thanks so much for joining up with the show
Also like to give a shout out
I'm a policy wonk
Don't get mad and tell your brother
Appreciate it so much
If you like to come if you want
Mark I want
Can we Commission
Do we know where Gina Del is now
Yeah I think he's retired and it's Dean is the first name yet
I don't know can we commissioned him we can email him
Email him
To call in and record him
Giving
Steve pieczenik
That's what I want I want I want every
Character on Alex Jones Show to record
Those exact
Just go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
23rd of March
Easter
I think it's
I think they are the special going on I know because he doesn't have enough selling product
Stay in my salesman
Which actually gives the show an entirely different feeling
Rick the fact that he's not throwing to commercial all the f****** time
It feels totally different
I can't you're so excited
I am and I'm not
Exciting to me that this is something new in the sense that we haven't had to deal with that for like 4 months
The I know everything about Alex Jones you know nothing about it holds
True it's kind of boring for me
Listening to him being like I know what he's doing
Now it's like
This is crazy
Kind of crazy but
Is it just him
Like he doesn't have co-host she doesn't have Rob do hanging around in the studio
David
I think David Knight might be around at this point but just doing the Nightly News
News back then as well
I know Paul Joseph Watson
Is around because he referenced having him right article
But I don't know if you've gotten him to be on-air Talent yet
Infowars.com is still around
A planet.com
Happy most of the commercials like I said on the last episode of our essential he was all for his documentaries
They're all just like
He plays the sound bite of
George h.w. Bush
Well
You'll see immediately Easter
And also I should say
Way worse on this Sunday show
Because he's broadcasting out of a
Studio
Has much better sound
Where is this broadcasting from
This is the KLBJ Studios
Austin Texas after three days he will emerge from
I guess so
Welcome ladies and gentlemen welcome and thank you for inviting us it is discharge
When we worship
Fertility
Set my Playboy symbol
Rabbit
Rabbits
How many cycles
Each year their breeding like rabbits
That's why
Pixel rabbit
Has the symbol for his Playboy
Empire
And so
In the last 60 years our children have been trying to not be Christian
Ion
I am bid for hundreds of years
Has been called Easter the occult symbolism
Hidden in plain view the Eastern My Worship
Ishtar the mother
Goddess
Fertility the eggs
The rabbit
And it is a huge fertility ritual
We just had the beginning of
Bring
A couple days ago and then we shall liberate
Lehigh occult
The holy that was object
Nicole branch
Just all over the world
From the Aztecs
Shot to the Babylonians
Of course to The Druids now going
Nobody's doing
He's just
Repeating zeitgeist
I want to hear him explain more
Did we get that you know
Banging like rabbits
Because rabbits
Have sex a lot famously like throw the baby out with
Time somebody threw a baby out with the bathwater
Play has bunnies
But I'm almost certain that's why
That's not correct at all that is not correct
Hugh Hefner was thinking he was like okay
First of all it's not a call
Boogeyman
Easter in Latin is known as
Aramaic word
Hebrew name pesach
Which is you know
That's over by also the Easter doesn't come
From Ishtar it just sound similar
Wake up.
This is something it's been a whole bunch
The the name Easter traces
Most likely
Absolutely
It's something that's very
Commonly thought again
Goddess of fertility
In the same way if it like Greek goddesses would have
Multiple purposes
She also is a goddess who is a lion
I guess not a bunny or eggs at all that's all just made up s*** that's not true
In the least
Associated strongly
Is it give you a history he's wrong about it
Fantastic
1 animals associated with
Is a f****** owl
You know that
Consistent
Animal
Is Tarzan
Bucking why
It's not a bunny rabbit
What is a lion
The bunny rabbit of the catwalk make a decent point
Do dogs butts
Be the most accepted theory about the name
Is it it's derived from the name of an Old English goddess mentioned
About a Old English month
Aveo stereo
Fairmont goes back to
The the goddess
Ostara
Which is actually a whole lot more
The issue is like okay
Alex
What he wants to say
Is
There's Pagan ship
Behind Holiday
You just say that
But if you want to play this game
I know all of this but you guys are actually
Christian he comes off like a
The kid in high school
This is one of these guys in high school was like all you mainstream people are posers
Write your dick
Sometimes when screen is great
Strong
Lot of bitterness in that little story
A little bit
He's wrong and continues to be wrong
And the kids have fun with the eggs
They do
The whole point is is that I don't worship Ishtar because I'm conscious of it
And I realized what it is
What's a globalist
Enjoy
Tricking you
They enjoy manipulating
They enjoy having things hidden in
In Plainview
But that's part of their
Aluminess religions they get
CorePower
Out of things
Things being in Plainview and you still not
That's all part of
The basic crazing
Look up
The term Easter
I did
Encyclopedia
The route from
Charlie the goddess
Fertility and in springtime
All over the world
Different cultures they differ
Would engage in different
Sacrifices
Sometimes it goes
Sometimes a ram
Sometimes a bowl
Sometimes a horse
But there's a normal blood pressure
If you talk to her then there was obviously
We're going to get you a child
It is true that it does
Beam lights throughout cultures there are
You know like in Greek
Mythology is Demeter and Persephone
Beside the coming of spring being the Persephone is let out of a couple months
To hang out with her mom
Right
Throughout
Old-timey cultures
And the ideas of a goddess
Brian spring
Cool that
Grows and everybody like if there's a God for everything sooner or later going to be like it happens every year
The climate or whatever
And then you get really bad at Smith's
Okay
Thermostat stuck right what it what do you want
Daniel in the Lion's Den
I don't know David murdered his best friend
That's a very modern man
Android line with our culture
Daniel and his buddies
Meshack
No it's Meshach Taylor
Shadrach Meshach in
Can a betta fish really caught up in Meshach Taylor being one of them
You can f****** the guy going down into Hades egos
To grab the girl but then there's six of the Creator pomegranate seed
Cuz it doesn't make any goddamn sense
Sprite
Some help
What's the note you took
Okay if you want to look out if I wrote down
Pomegranate and Hell
Sure
Business
And
I wish I wish
He read anything
Because like
He could
Haven't we wouldn't have a show.
I knew that we were going to go back to 2018 start looking to go to have a better argument to make
If you did
Do not like the base of the argument
I mean it's not that Pete likes
Aluminess
Globalist
Occultist
To trick your kids into something
But the argument
But you could educate your audience
Hagan and druidic origins of a lot of holidays
You could actually teach them something if you wanted to wouldn't be a bad idea that the starting point of Education Alexandra blowing it
Blowing
News story
On the show
Security companies
King with the airlines
To make you fit a taser bracelet
Around your wrist
Everyone who gets on the plane will be fitted with a taser bracelet
And Zapped
If they have their way I'd love to thank you
To be fitted with your taser bracelet
Training you to be a Slave
Trailers
It's about the federal docs on that about humiliation about
If we do anything and everything
This is all part of a
Dog training basically pavlovian training
The train you how to be a slight but where to play this clip
Coming up after the break
Where are there advertising the fact
You'll all be fitted with your with your
Zappers
Everyone will have their own they say oh by the way
In the real working outside the airports
Externalizing
I don't have the audio because it's not really worth it and Alex
Resizing for on a show now
Just like
Globalist in your life
You're shocked memes
Around where you hide your
I don't play the I don't have the audio of
Keep it cuz it's kind of boring and Alex talks over
What it sounds to me like is a
I like a tech
Business that has an idea and they're sort of
It's not it's not like the government is
Planning this
10 years later
Wianno stock prices
Finish this up
Alright but I feel like I was
Has to have an automatic kills
Wait for the police
Go see somebody might run from
Sorrel
Killswitch in our car
Or she's going to watch the government
Historically
Most dangerous
Thing we have to
Lookout Ford doesn't matter
Automatically
Cars
We'll all be fit with our Kaiser bracelets or necklace
You can't make this up
Are you laughing say something I did a few will
Doublethink shift
Say okay I'm for
I thought you been pre-programmed
When high-tech mind control the television
League shop
The culture and then is Amplified by the culture
Troll
The peer pressure
Monkey Nexus Overdrive
Is that what we term I just climbed there but that's basically what it it
Nonna's
Go to popularly known as and then whatever was he and then he's like
The hundredth monkey Nexus Overdrive
Even the coin term he just came up with this stupid
How many reasons is that
Absolutely
It's clunky
Too wordy
I kind of agree with him that the idea of all cars having
Killswitch is
Not good
Necessarily
But I also see the practical application of it
I mean
I don't know that one's murky
No I mean it's an interesting idea because
Car chases
Like my cousin
Hit by a
Running away car
Chased by the cops
And no never caught the guy
Time an old person behind the wheel run through a crowd
There are
Terrorist attacks that used cars now as a cheap to be happening in Europe every now and again
So you're is a practical application
The only problem is now you're talkin
Sing about a remote kill switch
And as we know about any kind of remote
Technology
It's going to get hacked
Somebody who knows how to use it better than you do
It's entirely possible
Negative
This point already
Kind of stupid
But at the same time
He's also very
Bluebird about how smart
Write the noise
It's not bad
You know it's annoying but it's not it's not
Alex Jones
To get out right now is the Muslims put kill switches
Then we're talking Alex
Is it like
Three things so far
It'll come up
We've got Ishtar being Easter which is not whatever
You want to get into your esoteric babbling about weird internet memes and s*** like that
Fine
Good fun
Good on you there is a segment of the population is because of Ishtar
I'm I'm susceptible
Like I watch videos on YouTube
And I wouldn't want someone
Just because it's not true to not put it out there I love it I'm fine with that
Then we have
The government is going to put shock bracelets on you in order to fly and then we have
Kill switches
Cars
Are like their paranoia narrative
But at the same time
The way he presenting them and the position he's in in 2008
Is the kind of guy who I'm cool with exist
Because
The absence of that
Voice is worse
But you know the government's
Our organizations tend to overstep their bounds
Their hundred percent of the time pushing
B powered
Just naturally does
It so having someone who is
About like
He's kind of a value to it
I agree
Because the absence of that voice
Allow
Something to be unchecked
To some extent
I think I think they're smarter voices that do it but possibly not more popular
Are granted his positions rrl alarmist and paranoid
And not based in reality
I'm not saying he's right
But what I'm saying is the this point it's
At least
Let me make it worse as yet
Episode goes along but like
He's not as offenses
Izzy is it like
6 years later
Right
I mean yeah he's he sounds more like
The guy on the corner with with the sign saying beds
Apocalipsis
Yeah
Yeah I like that I like that available to me like if I'm walking down the street
Thinking about whether or not the
Bright like to be reminded that it is
Regards
We know from the last episodes it's like being mean there is still bigotry going on he's still
That's still part of him
So you just didn't know he also hated it
I'm conflicted about the position he's in in 2008
In terms of like
If you could get rid of the racism would he be a valuable voice
In public discourse
I know
I'm not sure
There's a better argument for it then then there is now that's
For damn sure
Anyway I don't know that that's just a thought that I
I've had
I don't know what to do with
Anyway
That's all we're having is
Is Alex Jones better or worse
Now way worse
But I think it's worse for him to
Anyway
Listen to this next clip
And that way he brings those sort of narrative
Together
Alright
Welcome ladies and gentlemen it discharges remember
Do they start favorite song
Purple green and
Pink
Easter eggs
And hopping around
Fell asleep 50 years ago and I just now woke up on a cryo freezing
Turned on the news and they were proposing it we all walk around
Weren't shock bracelet
I feel more relaxed in the entire public be fitted with
Photoshop price
Oh yeah
Definitely Al-Qaeda because
Cuz I don't want to wear mine
What's good
Cement blocks keymaster good
Everything
Is fine
My friends
Alex loves doing radio
Keith
So much happier 10 years ago
Edit do something to me okay I'll be
Just lay all my cards on the table
Are you want this Alex
To come back
Identify with
You take away the racism and stuff like that and that's the life I f****** want it for a long
Long time
Just being able to talk on a talk show like I have your own f****** radio show and really love it
Like I can feel it
I can
Feel his enjoyment of this radio show
And it bums me out the path we know the next decade takes in his life
Story of capitalism
We need to have
A FurReal
Crisp
Was Carol situation going on
Yeah the ghost of decay
Jakari Jax
Sandhill go see what it was like whenever he knew a black
Those were the days
Larry Elder might still talk
I will take him to the DC office
This now and he'll realize how boring Jerome corsi is
Of course you get a f****** hotel room
It'll be hard
What is an Alex
Could get back together with his first wife
I don't know if that's a good
I'm going to go
He'll get back together with one of his 150 high school sweetheart that could be
And maybe maybe I'm willing to
Except that there is a part of me saying like he is
He is a
Terrible voice
In the media landscape
Because
Identify with
Having your own Radio Show in Lake Highway
Siding that looks like
Ethernet cable
It's possible
Time like
I don't know I'm coming out of my mouth I realize I can't I can't
Kinda like a
I can't
He's still basically saying
All government is evil you should be afraid of everything which is really the Bedrock
What makes my problem
So do f*** that you're saying right now like with Alex because he enjoys having
Radio show like that's a very different thing that I like his voice being available to anybody
It's it's really difficult
To walk because a certain amount of paranoia is used
Too much paranoia is dangerous
Having a paranoid voice around
Is
It is good to check some of the underlying assumption
That we have
You know you're saying he's not the Overton window
Not know
No
More towards paranoia but not all the way
Know what I'm saying is back then
There is a there is a purpose and
Society videos fulfilling to some degree which is being
Like you said that crazy voice
That guy who yells stuff and like maybe one time out of 50 is right
But they put because of how crazy it is it causes you to take a step back
Re-examine your
He's not that now
But going back and listening to this like
Same guy doing
Something very different back then
I guess maybe it sort of
Growing Pains or shock
Of jumping back in time that I've experienced in this
I think that's just because the bar is set so low
He needs to be arrested killed now
Are you just going to get people to believe dumb stuff
X-rays of relatively benign character underlying racism
More fears of various
If you look at what was going on on like Fox News in 2008 it's really not that different
It's no different than libertarian or conservative
Just stocking trade
I don't know I'm having a very
It's not something that we want to
Yada yada yada over
No absolutely not I don't think it's good
That means in terms of what we talked about
Alex
Far worse than that.
I can trade stuff now
Sandy Hook and all that stuff
Not 2000 like Timothy McVeigh
Yet I haven't really heard him talk about it much
Very complicated it might just be because of e doesn't
But listenership
That makes up his race is horrible
These shows
I don't see how
He ever got
Popular
From what I've listened so far does yellow stuff every now and again but it's not like
Like his voice right now he's got that little upturned at the end of it is
It's interesting to think of the trajectory of like
This being 10 years ago and we know that he go the only goes up
Right gets to like this
I mean is it a plateau now
He's going to crash
Very Hearts what are the things that forced in my mind is it like that growth is not organic
Play can we listen to that
Bill 15-minute interview we had with all of his narrative
Why you got to be careful
Statistics you got to read other studies
Conjunction with the studies that you're trying to
And I don't understand how anybody listening
To his show
Think like
His own positions are being undermined on his show
Yeah but never underestimate the
Absolute hatred that a lot of Americans have for anybody who knows fancy learning
Yeah that's true
Anti-intellectualism does go a long way
Alex Jones junior varsity
Narrative of the show
It's about your blood
I don't want our blood
Department of Homeland Security
I want to spend some time on
You all of your children
35 or younger you've been putting an illegal International database
All of now
Your conditioning
36 years old
I know that I'm going to read the actual document
This is real
Blood they say go to the health department for a blood test
Did you ever ask why
Why the hospital can do a blood test
Your blood publicly went to
Federal database
International
Okay for DNA testing
DNA background
They claim they own their child's blood they make DNA patent
Who's out of it
New proteins and things
But now
It goes to Homeland Security in the National Crime database
Wood murderer
Bank robbers everything else
Celebrities too much paranoia paranoia
One of the reasons that your ospital doesn't
It's kind of expensive to have that kind of
Issues and the ACLU in particular is working and has worked
Towards
In terms of blood from your baby and you get screen for all sorts of diseases
Because some of them
Are things that can be dealt with very easily immediately
Will be under on reversible later
So it's very important
The genetic condition
To do that sort of thing
But the issue has become the
The information
From
Store
Depending on the state
Furlong
Periods of time
Okay that's great
The test can be done in
In terms of
Incredibly valuable
Correlations in order to track.
Dreams for other Jeanette
Conditions
Things like that
No lot of the time that information
Yeah it's on identifier
Has all the identifiers taken
What's your name is
Connected to it
Or anything like that very weird
Terms of consent and privacy
And the ACLU is working
And has been for years
Trying to like
Allow people to
I have the right
In terms of invasive
And that sort of thing which is
How much more
Well there's there's the story of the the black woman
Blood and genetics
Material that was cultured again
Again for like
60 years or something like that and it's one of the most important
Samples
Medical research history
But I've never told her about it
We only found out that
It happens
Like recently in the pack
And it was all done like
Hey we just stole your stuff and now it's
Copyrighted in Patanol that said I'm not sure if
Driver but they just stole her information and used it
Willy-nilly
But I don't want to
From
And the B wait what I don't want to minimize it but like what was she going to do with it
You know what I mean
I don't I don't think
It's great to be
Blind
Depressed but at the same time
You right to be blindly paranoid about
Yeah because there are
Credible medical advances that were probably made by users woman
Yeah but I like Isaac
I think it's a licensing fee
Right
Feeling use your blood
Bellingham Herald
I would say give him a license
They can have my blood out
Alright I'm not using it
We're going to be like 15 damn timers
Maybe great awesome podcast
Loving Network
I was reading up on this propaganda
There's an article in Newsweek
From 24
How's read you here sooner than average with serious Shadow dies
Has worked as a filmmaker 4 / 2
10 years
He's traveled throughout Europe in the Americas producing sports videos news packages and documentary shorts
Ressentiment
He was diagnosed with a rare genetic
Condition commonly referred to as
KU where the body cannot properly break down
Throughout his life he's taking medicine involved special low protein
Diet restrictions
Enjoy the healthy life
Recently though he stumbled across the
This video that showed people with undiagnosed
UK you
Well you heard stories about what would happen if you never treated his condition
I never seen pictures of it I've never encountered it myself
So it wasn't quite Realty
You says
I want to watch that video he Trails off choconut deposit
Until the Heartbreak pass
It just captured me
I have the sudden realization that I would have become mentally retarded
I would have
The tution had it not been for
Newborns
And that story is true for
Thousands
Thousands of
People every year with PKU but with all sorts
Two conditions
Curate their life
It would be nicer to it like I said
Things are treatable
And manageable
Initially
But later will not be you can't go back
Write this screening stuff is absolutely essential
Yeah but it's preventative medicine
He hates vaccines
Going to see the doctor you should
Just buy like bulshit pills like
He despises any kind of
Actual
Solution
By every account newborn screening is one of my day
Biggest medical success story
That's what I would say
23andMe
That company were you send a swab in and they tell you your genetic history
Here
23andMe consumer genetics company will genotype your DNA and provide you with a 3 related reports in a raw data
Previously 23andMe reports
Ratios for certain Medical
In November 2013 the FDA prohibited the company from
Continuing to sell Health Report
Isaiah. Could not be analytically or clinically validated
In reality a health
Report may just be the most in
Enticing carrot 23andMe was able to dream up
In order to get your DNA in it
It's computers
As noted by the authors of an article in the New England Journal of Medicine
Quote 23andMe has suggested that it's longer-range goal is
List of collective massive biobag of genetic
Information
They can be used and sold for medical research
It could also lead to patentable Discovery
This characterization is not denied by
23andMe
This characterization is not
Denied by 23andMe
Accelerated genetics
Discovery
F****** amazing
The real money then isn't selling you a health analysis using selling your data for biomedical
It's not much difference
How Google Yahoo and Facebook give us email and social networking for free
Only to sell all the information they gather to anyone wishing to market products to us
23andMe is already conducted research
Funded by the NIH
And collaborated with academic and Industry partners
The company offers customers who buy Personal genetic reports
The option to participate in this wider research program
Currently 23andMe stores data from more than 700,000
Genotype customers more than 80% have not only opted into the research program
But it also actively answer survey question
Here's here's where comes down
The way it does
The way information becomes really valuable is when we can start
Look at genetic information and also understand phenotypic
Big Data
Explain the company representative
Research looks something like this
After first isolating all the customers who have stated on a survey that they have a particular allergy
Erasers
Might run a query to see if these customers share some genetic mutation
It would further analysis find out where those variants are located
Quote
Those are the things we want to explore 23andMe
But we can only do that if you answer question
Predict your participation in biomedical research then really has two parts
Consenting to use your genetic data and providing your personal information to
The value of the data
So
If you look at that just from a consumer model that's a 23andMe
That's what
These bio Bank
The information that comes from the babies
Are going into
Same sort of thing they're tricking people
Chances are
They were just sending out
Random generator
Right I don't know I don't know that they can't do that anymore is because
We can't
We don't know if we can confirm this so you could be lying I think it was random they probably would be sued
Because that would be the sort of thing
Because that's what you would have to do it come up
That would come up
An audit
Or something like that
If the FDA is telling them not to
To do it anymore they probably looked
Into what they're doing
I would assume
Because the idea that
You can't back this up
They would have an opportunity
That would be a conversation
Yeah
That's what I'm saying so
That's because it's like a random ass thing
Same thing is like
Giving a horoscope
Pretty much either of us can prove it
Next point
Neither of us can prove any
Fair enough
Keeping in telling your genetic information
You're giving up all of that in
Information to them keeping a keeping it and selling it to you
Towards
Breakthroughs in science
They can be
Used to possibly
Isolate where these allergies come from a table to make it so people don't have to suffer with those allergies
Is anymore allergic to liquid
I know somebody was allergic to Sun
You know like there are really crippling allergies and if there were some sort of breakthrough that could be made
I think there's a lot of people whose lives could be greatly benefited from it probably
Now that's a super good offices
Able to be sold to
Do anybody though
It's in their f****** small print people are paying to use their service so
I don't think these people have any leg to stand on
I was looking for it I can't really find any abuses
Like I can't find instances of abuses of this genetic information flus
You think that's because of the whatever
Is if I was going to use a database
To genetically engineer a
Strain of the flu
That could kill 90% of the population
Call 23andMe
This flu season did not kill.
I'm positive test run
Could be killed
Dry run
I know Alex has
Again the Cradle of something that's like there is a privacy issue
Little more responsible bodies like
I've been aware of an active
Yes
He's paranoid
Ignore the more important and
Socially
And medically important
That seems to be sort of a runner
Yeah
Yeah I mean I don't have too much what would they do with like Ikea
Information
Copyright your jeans like I own your body
Or something like that
Think so
Courtney
I don't know I don't know exactly what the fear is he
He's never really super specific on it
Let's go to the textbook
Cuz it's what you might down
Another delightful mama
In 2008
Alex Jones
Out in the west Texas town
The police demanding drug test me I refused so they tasered me five times
Basalt
It's so much fun oh please
Feed me more
Wild America Wild and Free
Face scanning cameras everywhere everything to do track
My town
But I wasn't allowed to own a gun in America anymore
And I wasn't allowed to
To fight either
The kids aren't allowed
Now they're banning
Running
During recess again everything
Risen
Great
So that was Marty Robbins El Paso musical comedians
Who are
Jealous right now
Improv Musical
Yeah
Still
Kaiser things the wrong song over another Zone
It's nice that he takes time out of every episode 2 mi of Empire
He wasn't doing entire country song every episode
Who is the life
I think everyone knows that because of the penultimate episode of Breaking Bad
Teachers at 2
Great song
El Paso Marty Robbins
AutoZone
Mischaracterization stories
Which is fun
I gave that woman
I've been a little bit
Too generous to Alex throughout
The show perhaps already
Get to now Wyatt
You still there
You still bad in 2008
You're right go ahead
Without going up to Kenneth my dad
I'm we sold out for helicopter
Just flying
Like it's real close to ground
Backup
Call on the highway
Highway 76
Big lot of cops
Operation
That's good
Giving you safe
But if you say you don't like what they were doing that they don't exist but you say you appreciated one of the police state they do exist
Saladworks
You got to learn how to work or do you have a
As long as
Around mine
They're winning
And they're on top of
They are
Is that
The analogy is Somaya
Business is falling apart
Oh that I might competition
Deep trouble
You want to answer
Certainly.
What
Hey we went up
What's a candidate there were four helicopters in the police operation
Go to town Alex tell me what was going on
Give me a conspiracy theory and I was just like
Nope
No cuz I have excuses for me
Alex is using it in service of a bigger
Conspiracy theory at Matt is that like you're not supposed to worry about that stuff
First second but those believers
If you believe
Probably just there doing
I'm sort of a routine
Is waiting
Other
Hilarious
The next clip
Just like
You're an idiot if you believe anything is
Nautica
Conspiracy
And that's a really dangerous mentality for him
I like I sounded Young
The caller sounded Young
We went up to Canada with
Is Dad all right
High School
Can you speak
Two people
You should not
You shouldn't reinforced the worst parts
Of there
Their mentality
I think he's doing
Wizkid man
Because of stuff like that
I get my but my car and I drive down to the studios of Newsradio 590 KLBJ
Can we check into the satellites
FM dial
Communities across this country
Travel cast on the internet for way worldwide we're not giving up
We're not going down without a fight
The New World Order scientific dictatorship
The robber baron
Valium Cisco
Ladies and gentlemen
Afraid they try to dumb you down
Turn you into a bunch of nerd and understand the world really works but you're starting to wake up
Feel the freedom again
And you're starting to wake up
Big brother doesn't like that
Play pop in there
That's right
We're back live
High School football speech
I have ever heard my tire life
They're moving over today Weird Al coach Taylor get out of the way closed hearts
Cantler's
So f****** into this
I love it I love it
There isn't like
You know when someone likes what they're doing and it's infection
Minute-and-a-half how much he loves his job
Nobility
Shuffle
Stuff is soaked like it's all not true
Man the passion is
Oh yeah
RadioShack
I do not like
The others
I don't like the other stuff about like
Those moments
I think what I'm getting at is
I want I just don't want to be a nerd
I want to rap
I want to admit wrapping up the show but I want to wrap up my feelings from earlier I think
We have empathy with human empathy
To our detriment
Where I say it like
Alex is much better than
Probably comes
A place where I can
Feel him
Being
Yeah
I can feel him
Even if you thinks all this stupid government
Paranoia fear
All this stuff even if he thinks all of that's real
His place in life is right
This is where he belongs
That's a really good point
The worst thing that ever happened to him is whatever artificial
Success he had
At some point after this
Because he's lost his way
He lost his soul entirely
It probably has
Much less to do with Trump than we think
Play cuz it's probably
Before that
Even like his stuff from like
2014 he wasn't on the Trump bandwagon
He's still like not as happy as he is there or when he's listening to Highwayman
New plan to
To fix
Alex Jones
I don't think it can be done but I think I know where you're going but I don't think
We get him
To coach
A little league hockey
A little
He'll fall in love with Anna realize that that's not the woman
For him to get a cutout of George do exactly
Conspiracy theory
Alex gets really blow Hardy about history and religion and
Even use the same
Quad Squad together
So I can make
Judgment about a culture
Metrobank
Degenerate
And the Aztec culture was.
And very satanic I'm not to go down there
Thousands of
Skulls
Walls
Hellraiser
Like hell
Majestic Power Trip
Priests whacked out of their mind on drugs
Meet
For the pub
The General Public
Sacrifices
Is that a couple sacrifices every day even the smaller
Nope
Call centers around villages
Nope all around
Central City
Where they got their orders
And they would kick the dead bodies of the people
Play chakra
Everyday
Sundown in the people would get select
Makeup
In fact you got the look
Sub priest-class with hanging up
Father feet
Cut-ups
Does price
And cellulite Lester. I don't think
Until the main
Meet
It was out of the children
So I
Apologist on the subjective
Just let me know
Just worshipped Ishtar bunny
I want to know.
Just be ignorant
Just March
Google
Human sacrifice
Ester cultures is actually really fascinating
First of all that happen monthly there is a like 80
Gmod calendar that the Aztecs operated under and they'd have different
Sacrifices of a dude
Pacific Theaters
Sacrifice
Is actually really into
Christine as well
Generally speaking with the Aztecs believe
Was
That their gods who came
Before sacrifice
Themselves that
Humans might live
That was a foundational aspect of Aztec
Believes
Christianity sacrifices we would live without sin
It's not uncommon in religious
Traditions Christians are just less hardcore
They weren't always
That's true
That's a good point but
The people who were being sacked
Generally speaking were very willing
Fencing at because they understood their role
In the the drama the cosmo
Drama that was being
Anthropologie
Just to study they find it
Three almost unbelievable the people were forced into
The sacrifice
Most of the time
They couldn't really have been
Because so much went along with being attacked
Sacrifice like you had to leave
Procession
Beaches
Have people sing songs
Go and talk to people
Like there was a really ritualistic
Part of being the sacrifice
Right into this idea first of all they were doing it multiple times a day is
Absurd
Except
In an instant
Like christening Duty
Temples 2
Then it would be like
They're very reports on it but like
People who
You really study to come away from
Spaniard propaganda
Spanish who came in in Concord
They needed
To justify a lot of their atrocities the way they did
By their actions a lot of time with you like they killed 80,000 people trying to
Krishna Temple
Which is a lot of people
Festival Foods
You know it's spread out a little bit
Organize
Right
The infrastructure
For being able to kill thousand
The people in one
Enough
A few days
That's right
That's a lot
It's a well-oiled machine
How many how many how many
Our
I've never asked the question how many sacrifices can you do per hour but now I want to know
Propaganda argument that's just what I'm
I'm choosing to call it
Cuz a lot of people have suggested that it is
Was it over the the Great Pyramid of temperature
In 1487 when it was built that they sacrifice 80400 people in 4 days
U14 sacrifices of minutes
For the 4 days
Which is
Generally speaking
Pretty unbelievable
The real number is
From people who have like
Critically is
Baby 10001
And then I old Aztecs to talk to missionaries told of a much lower figure
Probably about 4,000
Which is still a lot
But it's part of their religious cosmology
I don't know enough to fully break a lot of his stuff down but from looking into it
The role of sacrifice of human
In their culture was
Fascinator
Play doubt Wars
Between different Aztec cities
Where do the goal of the war
Was not to kill each other
It was to injure someone bring them back
To be sacrificed
And the people who were on both sides
That was their rule were they to be injured
It was like playing out a drama through Warfare
Where you were actually trained in Warfare at like
Target practice
Yeah but then also you know you know sacrifice
I'm head with a rock you're probably going back in
Taking to the top
It's it's fascinating stuff
I looked into it and I realized that
Is not the inspiration 24 Flag Day
Know the false cognate
Other cultures are fascinating and looking at them through solely the prism of our own culture is
It's a definite way to end up hating other cultures
Things are worse than you
Saudi cannibalism affect
What's cannibalism
I like the way that he described because he was like
You get sacrificed and then they kick you all day
And then do the cricket down the steps
You repeatedly all day
Call Daddy
I don't think they would hand out the me like what he was describing is that beat
Because of the kicker
You'll get really
Hinder human
You down the temple stairs
That's what that's
He said all day though
Sacrifices all day
Whatever
The issue isn't like
Early
Anthropologists thought that because of the
Ecology and the
Where the Aztec cities were located that they wouldn't have had a ready source
The protein
Emmet Sullivan
Sacrificing people was away too
Create a source of protein
Later Studies have shown that that
Yeah because there were plenty of plenty of
Sources
Protein
Lizard
Weasels
Salamanders fowl
There's all sorts of birds
Amazing other other crops
They could feed their carbohydrate needs
Theory of human being
Protein
Is not not accurate
Don't get me wrong
Some people take it eat
People
Sometimes you're going to get eaten
But
If it was bit like this big societal need and everyone was clamoring for human flashing would have you
It doesn't make sense that they would then
Take a lot of the organs that would be the best eaten and sacrifice those to the Gods
You know what I mean like
Illinois
What's the new rumor Crystal Lake
Okay
I'm fine and they sacrifice the choices cut
The tastiest giblet
From here on
Alex
Freedom
I would say
Holidays
What starts off on one topic
And jumps to this is another reason why I think
Loves doing radio known being able to tell him what
To do this make any goddamn sense
In this clip
Use ghost
One topic
Max the max
Mexico it's a show
It's real simple Christianity was
Oppressed dominated
Attacked several hundred years
Never cries
Then a Roman Emperor decided to adopted
Wouldn't go away
And so they hid
Everything
Basically in plain view in all of the Saints
Holidays
When they celebrated
Christ's birthday
You know that's
Middle of the winter the dark
The winner
Just a way of
Like looking at
Probable reality from the other side
You could say that those
Pagan symbols and Pagan figures already existed in Constantine took over in the
Early
So like 3:30 maybe was that when he became a Flipagram
Christianity you took the pre-existing things and relabeled them
In Christian
Populace is together
You're trying to run
Empire
Isn't on there because it's like
A massive
Government is telling you what religion
To to follow you should be on the Pagan side
Me what God to worship
When it starts in
Getting wider app
After that
Celebrate going
Cheyenne
To the winner out of the
Fall I mean they have all the
They're all on
Kia cult day
It's all over Europe
All of them
Again riding to Asia
You looking at this backwards
They hide them
In Plainview
Fertility symbol
Symbol for tin star
The Babylonian goddess of
Infertility
Was worship all over
River names
Every culture has
Freak
Christianity stop
Churches with big balls
That is the male phallus
The Martian Monument theater
Is a giant mailman
Cat scale
Women's breasts
Dick
The doorways into them I'm not going to go any further
This is mainstream Architects by pussies
Temple priestesses
Are the Washington Monument or of the text
For the goddess
On top of
Of the Texas Capitol
They're very point-blank
The match because predating
Christianity
A Judaism
Under solemn
The son of King David
Do you know what that is extra
Most powerful in a cult black magic
That is the most powerful symbol
If you read the old test
The genie
The demon back in the bottle
And so he
Tapped
Total control over devils
Real or not
So the Star of David is
Black magic
Shalimar
Nothing you've been told is what it really is so
They openly call Eastern boys yours you run around talking
King about
Jesus
Play walking around animals
It's three months off from
He was actually Chris
Does down for a long time to get them to like why does the sun look red when you look at it it's Josh.
It's dust it's a lens effect it looks shut up Alex
Ramblin from topic to topic
Whatever it is just what you think of that moment that you're wrong about it
Jesus being crucified
It's just another guy named Jesus
Crucified
They Crucified a lot of people that he's referring to from the histories of like juicy fifth
The other historians from back then
Is not the Jesus
That
Christianity
It was a it was not a singular name
Well they're talking about it
Jezebel
From what I understand
Religious studies professor
Not not my dad
Historical Jesus
Conflated
The one that Alex is referencing
Who got
And there was a rabbi
Slightly different time periods don't quite match up perfectly
Do all the sayings are attributed
Historic history and especially
You know what I hear especially Paul
Paul is pretty
Particularly guilty of this because he
Was the one who wrote all those goddamn letters
Corinth
That Bass
His his work
Probably had a lot to do with
Complacent
So I don't know
But whatever else is talking about isn't accurate is a prince and the Pauper
That is already what do you mean why would you have a hippie rabbi
Why would that come about
No way would that happen then
Through a lot of them
Who is walking around Navy met this other guy named Jesus they looked a lot alike
Twins
They were twins
Jesus had a secret twin
Okay
Switch clothes
And live out their lives
And it turns out
This is a real morality
Okay
If he didn't have his robe
He would have just been
Criminal
And that's what he became
Okay and the Jesus
If he
He would have been Jesus
This makes perfect
That makes total sense
Finally got
To the bottom of the G
All you need to do is add an explanation for why
I was going to switch to a King Ralph butt
Goddess worship
Just be aware of it I'm not saying you're going to hell if you put out
And the occultist
They openly laugh about it
Say look at all these
It's out here
Practitioners of
Dragnet
Where the Tom Hank
And Dan Aykroyd
Notice
The local preachers actually devil worshiper
That's how it
It works
The cops the drug dealer
The big mega church pastor
He's the hyper
Locally generally
And that's just how it works
Dragon fruit
Are you saying that you have a big
Church what is that
Oh that's a big dick
You're all in there and it
That means
Jose
Patriarchal
Religion
Hooked askew
About oppressing
It's kind of a weird esoteric
Anna Anna
Goddess worship
Remixon
Domicile
Otherwise rhetoric Secret
Wherever you find a war memorial at a capital or anywhere else
Look around you
The 5000 dead
Cavalry Battalion of whatever
From Civil War
Stop
And look around you
You you will see within 100 yd
Up on top
Pillar BB
And she'll have her hand
Towards the Sun
We're in or vice versa
You're driving along and you see a goddess on top of the
Impeller
Are you sure
Capital r
UCO University
Go in
Within about a
100 in front of
Also
I bought a courtyard courtroom
Still have like
Lady Liberty
You know there's a goddess
In the courtroom because he demands in just
That's nonsense in the world
Football field
Square footage
Think about it
So dumb
Places that there are memorials a probably graveyard
Some sort of Big Mama
The idea that there would be some sort of
That's right in line
It's not
It does not ring of like some esoteric order
But that's alright
Generally straight
It will be a shocker
They will put a
Memorial in front of her
She needs blood
Answer the practitioners
They had to be secretive about
Are mystery cults
And there's a star called
The rest of it
Shoved are there
You load your coach
Colts
Remember even ABC News admits that the bushes worship
Eulogio
Goddess
At
Robert
And this is just what I did
To your question
You haven't
What would that have been the answer of a question
I remember what the caller asked
What can I put on eggs
The beginning of the eclipse you said you're not going to hell if you put out eggs
What question
Could it be answered with
Worship the goddess
That sounds right
Do you know about the Greek goddess eulogia
No
You couldn't cuz she doesn't exist
Well that's what happened
Neither do wmds
Must be
The code is created by
Creative mythology around themselves
They first started
Yeah it's very dumb
Look into the beginning of the skull and bones and More You Realize like it
It's a lot of dudes
Into another frat and then they started
Something really weird
It's gaudy
What is it
Anytime weird repressed White
Lego
Your Amway for racist lyrics
Baker Alec breaking into Bohemian Grove
Repressed old white dude
Getting weird with a
A showpiece play in the middle of the Woods
I don't know I'm not sure exactly what kind of identify with
You probably get bored
That that's sort of pageantry probably I can spices
No maybe go do some stuff in the woods for a little bit
Probably much less mysterious than we
Are our brains like to make it up to bone
All of that stuff like about
Jacking off
10 coffins and stuff not true
Or if it is it's just a weird dude jerking off
And more likely than the reality is
F****** dudes back in like the 1800
Couldn't get into other prestigious
Frats and orders
Was it Yale
I think probably cares
Weird and their problems
Is it a like
Do something
That's stuff they watch they read a little bit
Not the Good Ship
Anyways
Anyway
Is it snowing
Because this this show is not like
He just talked about it start
Can't beat that drum
I'm too hard but you said something towards the end of the show and this is how we exit
And I have a lot to say about it
Is it
There's a lot of problem
Just like our government
Serbs
On the starting spot Back Bay
Gus Robert
Search
You know the history
Report on that
I want explain this again you very very slowly
Are criminal government
Created Al-Qaeda they use them to attack
Servicenow
That is enough for criminal media
Corporate controlled media
They them come out
That Iran is funding Al-Qaeda
And that Iran was behind 9/11
That Iran is attacking Iraq with Al-Qaeda
Group War with
CIA and I'll tied up
Now I'm not saying they're good all governments are evil
The point is Al-Qaeda
Is run by our Criminal
That insurance
It's all documented my film
Prisonplanet.com
Centurions the show
It's only with 9/11 was an inside job
It's not
Also
Right but his films are also not
Accurate
I want to say is first that mentality of like all governments are bad is really I think
Motivating Alex stuff
He's really an anti-government guy
And it's weird that now
Pro
Trumpian governor
Really sums him up in terms
Except inasmuch as that Libertarians want almost
No government
Buy highest
Highest Authority in the land of the local
Absolutely
That's just the true facts Al-Qaeda being used to start things off
And I in Serbia
Recently booked
It's called
The trigger hunting the Assassin who brought the world to war
Franz Ferdinand
The reality is in the nineties there was an Islamic faction from out of Cu
The country called
In Bosnia
Presenting this is really f***** up
I'm just going to read to you a passage here from this book that I read reasoning
Is from Bosnia we're highly secretive during the war but while I was researching the book I made a breakthrough by tracking down one of the
Before in Muslim Fighters
A few miles from my hometown
Shahid but was just two years older than me boards Birmingham to parents originally from Pakistan
Working as a reporter I'd first seen him in a yemeni court in 1999 after he had been arrested
Can charge the terrorist activities committed an FM
His brummie accent being memorably out-of-place
The far edge of Arabia
That would be it would be more than a decade before I was able to sit down and talk to him about Bosnia a cake shake
Cake shops Irving Arabic tea
The pastries in a Birmingham suburb with a
A particularly strong
Islamic
Quote the thing you have to remember is that when I was growing up in Britain
Nationality
This is a time when the streets around my home would have walls painted with ATL
Huge letters
Packy Lee
And all through my teenage years people like me were being abused in the streets getting beaten up
Having dog set on us that sort of thing
Back then just leaving your front door to get you in trouble
When I'm at school all I wanted to do is serve as a filter
I wanted to be a royal Marine right
It was a time of the Falklands War
The best all over the talion in the papers
I went to recruitment office and asked to join the Royal Marines
You know what they told me
They said we cannot have you because you're a fat pack
So do you know what I did for the next year
I ran around the streets near my home in boots with a rucksack for the brick
I went back to the recruitment office 12 months later and asked to join the Royal Marines
And again this time you know what they said
Well you're not a fat Paki anymore but you're still a pack
In the early nineties I started to attend boss
For some of the first radical clerics were beginning to preach
It was around this time in the war in Bosnia began
You watched video cuz that's showing Bosnian Muslims victims of the war
It's very confusing to begin with
Stevie's Muslims
Blue eyes and blonde hair
It was not like anything I've seen before traumatic
Overwhelming
Just to learn the people were suffering like this just because their mother
He joined an aid Convoy arranged through his local lost that sent out to coaches
From Britain
Supplies
Intended for Bob
With a plan to bring back Refuge
Chaos is the vehicle got no further than Zagreb in Croatia
I was unable to cross
The border into the war zone
Quote there were these guys
To wear eyewear Metro organized
You said you were going to do one thing and you end up doing another
We fell out it was useless
So after some prayer I joined up with a guy from London
Driving to baz
I never been out of Birmingham
And there I was all of a sudden towards
We gave out the food
There were lines and lines of people and they took it all
And that's where it came into my head
The media likes to say a Muslim like
Meiomi fights because we're some kind of crazed psychotic
It was not like that
I went to Bosnia to bring humanitarian help
What other humanitarian help could I give up
Protecting them
These people cannot protect themselves and that's how I could help
I would fight
My mate with the van went crazy
It's not like it is in the films he said are you for real how are you going to fight you don't know anyone here and you don't have any weapon
He went on and on trying to talk me out of it but I made up my mind
I wrote a letter to my wife what you took with him
And then he was often
Is van in the morning
The sun still Rising
Next to the road
The town called track
The mujahideen forces
So you most mostly restraining in training.
I don't want to say I was here or anyting but the times I took Park
Attacks with a really heavy
Yeah guys on either side of me getting hit
That sort of thing
I saw myself as a traditional
I was a fighter sure but I was fighting to help
The oppressor
To protect them against
It was a noble a
I want that I would do again
These guys are takepart and suicide attacks they're not true mujahideen
They're killing innocent people that makes no sense at all
From any point of view
It makes no sense from a religious point
As it's not part of my religion
And it makes no sense from a military point of view
The Strategic perspective
How are you going to win the hearts and minds of people to kill people who are not involved
Bosnia's role in the evolution of modern Jihad has largely been overlooked
Example of what
From the anger of young people is ignored
Western politicians
Who stood by when the worst atrocity
Lease of the Bosnian War
Replace ethnic cleansing
Death camps genocide
Inadvertently provided Islamic militant
And cry they would later use to just
Stuff I act of Terror
Yeah there's there's another there's another path
I really short one that I think really
It sums up some
Stuff that I just want to grab here real quick
This is a quote from another guy
He was traveling with the author
Temperature
Jim Butcher
Interpreter
He's describing what they ended up experiencing cuz he lived through the
He was a Serbian Muslim
Who were
Difficulties
In terms of
The croat the Muslim
There's a lot of
Complication in terms of what
Caused
After the worst
Parts of the Bosnian War
Yeah but
This guy was a Bosnian Muslim
And those times
This this quote I really stuck with me
Is it all this s*** comes along in the 90
Suddenly it matters if you are Muslim Erick Rowan
That stuff has been parked
4 years for decades
Those people who said
These people have always hated each other
We're just being lazy
In my own life I saw people from different communities works together live together getting married even
There's nothing
It was just that a
You the extremist
The elite
The greedy so nationalism is a way to grab what they want
So
Everything
Yeah if you want to go to Germany in 1930s
When you go back and you hear those stories of like
We live
Perfectly well next to all of our Jewish neighbors it up one day it was like
No Jews allowed
And so many people just will go along with
Nationalism
Yeah everything I've read
About that
Particular conflict
Always goes back to that's
Situation
And then
After the after the war
End
Switch
You know
Is ending is a
Is up four.
Everybody tried to just four
Forget you know like
Oh that wasn't made that wasn't part of me I never hated you guys
Because you have to try and live together again like that's why
He's writing
He's writing a travelogue
Follow the footsteps of Gabriella
Received from a small town to Sarajevo
The car lot
And I'm Muslim
Along the way everybody is kind of
Like
Almost it seems like there's almost
Confusion
About what ended up having
Because it
It's very difficult to look at
In the face the reality of what
Caught up in
And the importance of that I believe
Because first of all Alex's
Inline
About Al-Qaeda being
Used to start
War
Hi in Serbian
In the night
Sprite
Courtyard that's that's absolutely
Nonsense
But beyond that
Z
The greater truth
What happened there
Are so applicable to Modern
Time
Good lesson
For Alex to learn
Especially seeing that the guy who
He
Really is in favor of
It 2018
Is presiding over one of the worst
Census of race
Scapegoat
Seem
Maybe in our lifetime
For sure
The idea of
The
The ramping up of ice
Deportation
The the attempt
Pinpointing every single Hispanic voter
Disapprove the voting rolls
The idea of
Posting
Publicizing
Immigrants
Crime
Those sorts
Two things are all
The steps
That you will find
If you look
Deeper into
The history
Ism's
Did end up taking
Can place
Like what happened
In 1930s Germany
Like what happened in the lead-up to the war in Serbia
These sorts of things
That you're talking about when people just
Break with my Jewish neighbor and now I'm not
They don't happen mysteriously like
It's not like you wake up one day and you hate your neighbor
Teach you to hate your neighbor
Those are the steps
People take two
Get you to hate your neighbor
And it's fascinating to me
Very depressing
Well if the story tells the story of
Terrorism in miniature
Like the guy was
Attempting to do good
Start doing everything you could to try and
Help people who
The Western governments just
Watch.
Like that's a whole another foreign policy
You can have like what's the correct way to do all this example of
The more realistic story of the beginnings of radicalization often
It's for him and
The world I guess
He didn't end up going down some sort of I'm going to bomb people
But you understand how easily
I can get flipped
The wrong influence
The wrong
A person in your ear
Could be the difference between someone who goes
Trying to give humanitarian Aid who decides to
Suffice
Back to the oppressed
The guy who
Straps
It's not but that's not the but that's not the initial inside
I mean the inciting factor is
Complete
Oppression
Before
You know what if you want to talk about horrible s*** that
The government is done
Killing one-and-a-half million civilians in Iraq and Afghanistan and everywhere
We f****** drone bomb
Great murdered
Like we're we're not the good guys
And the same thing is true there with
Terrorism
We send a drone bomb to get a terrorist in wind up killing 20 people around
And you know what you're one of those kids who survived
And you look in Hugo
Great you kill the terrorists
You also killed my family
Who's who's bad
Your beauty killed my family
I would absolutely see why people
Become suicide bombers
To become terrorists
Because
F****** you kill my family
You don't like
I'm I totally get
Via
Blue understand
If you want to go if you want to go with me
Who perpetrated 9/11
If you want to go through there that goes back yeah that's it
I understand that I understand I understand
Wondering
The direction you're going to go with
Rationalizing
90s okay
The reasoning behind it is America's actions protecting Israel and doing all of those
Seduce
Terrorism happen
And you find that it
Oftentimes just
Play constant tit for
Protec going back
And back and back
It's not like 911 happen because they hated are free
Sprite and it's not like any of this stuff happen
Because
Muslims are crazy
I think
It may be bored
Eloquent way
To put what you're saying is
The results that you see always have
Macaws
Pause is
Is generally
Trauma
It's
Directed
In the same way that senior like
Your town blown up by a drone
Or whatever would
Create
It would definitely make you susceptible to somebody saying that you can
Do something
Causation
That we have in society
And I mean we can go back in
4th and conser
Bicker and argue about like
You know hey
Well
Have
Drones at Village
If there wasn't that terrorist we were looking
Then you can play out like what was that terrorist beginning
Ohey
Had some other atrocity
Befall him because we were fighting ex-wife
You go back to the root of it but
I genuinely think
That
I don't know I think I'm more productive
Empath would be to record
Nize that
We are the ones
Things
Much more
Effectively
Stopping
None of this to happen
Ultimately the if you go back in
Time if there was one thing that
Change about
It would be immediately afterwards
If we Act
Billy said as a country like
We forgive you
Like for real
You know what
Fine we're going to build it back up the exact same way that would really hurt the country did Arts
Would have
Gone insane but that's the only way
Really to stop that Circle of violence
Perhaps really what it is
I'm not entirely sure but you might be right
Eventually somebody is going to drop
And I think the only way to stop
Everybody from dying is
The government to go like
That's at
I don't know
Conversation that's full of all sorts of theories and who knows
Check us out we have our website knowledge fight.com
Knowledge underscore fights on Twitter USA
We are on
Facebook you can go to iTunes you can leave a
Show your friends
Show your
Just
Sunrise
6 times a day to not wait no.
I want to
Because of
F*** myself yourself
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color