Alexandra Thurston color
Fix it around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
You dance
We are drinking
Goats on
Goats do roam
Tonight which is a very interesting
Podcast is about how I know a lot about Alex Jones
Get going I would like
To start things off
I'm giving people shoutouts to our new donors
Nicely done thank you
Who has joined up with the show we really appreciate it
Thank you so much right
I don't know if it's pronounced rice I've never actually
Rhys Zealander rice
Now that's a celebrity I don't know all of these
Celebrity
Bump it up became a foreign policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
A mother and tell her you're brilliant
Thank you so much
Guess what
What we're in a situation where I need to give a little bit of an update
Oh no beginning of January I made it announced
If we bumped up the donation
$100
Within the month
Hundred dollars of recurring.
Sponsorship
As it were
That we would begin
Doing
This film
And that we would put out the episode starting
In
February
36 hour livestream
Pazzo the report that we have now it's going to be our last episode
What we hate dad
Continue can we get into the larger philosophical issue
Point
Is this going to be our last episode in January and we've made it 85%
And here's where I'm at
There's no damn way
That we can make that kind of progress and then BB like
Deadwood $15 short to do
As much as I love you and thank you so much for chances are
Disappoint The Listener
Even though responsibility to those who gave that fifth
Team dollars to do a f****** good job that's what I believe in
To donate
And with the understanding that people will continue to donate
Hey man
We would take those episodes off
For me to say like suck you off
Doing that anyway
And we have to figure out exactly what the structure is going to be
And because we didn't
We might end up putting the first one out in the middle of February but it will be
Sing it all the way to play by our own rules
So are coming and I appreciate it
In recognition of the fact
Edmonds Alex Jones episode
Now I've got a whole bunch
The endgame I've got to be breaking down
You're going to have to work very hard and
Well
None
0%
And I realized it like you know before
That deep water
I realize that I need a break
Need a break from Alex Jones
So here's a clip of what we're going to be covering today
Really easy
Did you get ready
Did you hear what that man
I don't need it up late again
Really easy to blow up a planet for example
First people on earth
We are
Okay
So you know pre-show
Jordan said Turn My Headphones
Camelot and I want it I want it all over the place
Finger on the pulse of Project Camelot
Mark Richards
Who doesn't keep a pulse on project question
Literally find stuff that's like there'll be weird
Interviews like
I don't I don't
But
I saw one
There's a gentleman
By the name of Courtney Brown
He comes on the show and they talk about
The war in heaven
Yeah
So Jordan
Glitter 11s
Let's start off as the interview starts out with Kerry Cassidy or friend
The show
Hi everyone I'm Kerry Cassidy from Project Camelot on I'm here tonight with Courtney Brown
And we're going to be talking about his team's remote viewing
Afraid from the Bible called war in heaven
And this should be a really fascinating show I'm going to bring Courtney on the screen here with
And Courtney say hello to everyone
Hi everyone I'm glad to be here thanks for having me here
You're welcome
So Jordan
You are the cutest
Did she just say
Remote viewing
Oh yeah
You're not with the phrase
Awardhacker
Yes
So these guys are going to be remote viewing
Like like they're going to
Are office
They're going to do with the
Think about remote
I do not know everything about it but I do know that it's not real
I did I should have
I know that much
A little bit more as the episode goes along
You get to go to some of the specifics of it and what have you
And
I can't stress enough you have
No I
Idea where this is going
This is going to be one of the more f***** up episodes
That we've ever gone over
Unintentionally
Kerry Cassidy
Has no idea either what she's doing
Okay
I don't want to I don't want to give away too much too early
So let's get into this next clip where
Courtney Brown
Give us a explanation
What he does
What I like to do in this case I do think
A lot of people will know who you are but give yourself a brief introduction
And then we'll just launched into the
Remote viewing
And
Perhaps introduce the the various the viewers that were involved
Also
You going to make reference to people who are the remote viewers one of them is named disease
One of them but it's a normal name and then other one is named princess
Right don't be distracted by him referencing
Princess
If you won't promise to remote viewing smoke-filled room
What does that mean
It's an old John Fox
Call Joe
The lazy dog jumps over the sleeping fox or whatever but I'm typing test to firefight
Fossil
Sloppy joe
Okay sure I'm Courtney Brown as you know and I'm TV director of
Farsight Institute
And The perseid Institute is a nonprofit and we are
The largest biggest
Venue
Public
Fully
Fully open public projects
For remote viewing in
Anywhere
And so what we do is we use remote viewing which is a mental procedure that was developed
Originally by the
United States intelligence Services US Army
Military to use for Espionage purposes 10
We're civilians named leaves
Procedures have driven original military procedures
And
When using for exploration
Scientific
Huge number of projects that we done on our end available on our website for site.
ARS igat like seeing far
Beauregard
And most of everything that we have up there is for free something about ticket sold at movies
Warren Avenue
Well I went I went too far
Confined
Stuff like
Sounds like this guy has done
I mean
If what he was doing was real he's doing the Lord's work
Is he working really hard to Hitler's mind Becca when he was giving speeches
He's figured out what happened with the JFK assassination Martin Luther King
Roswell Area 51
Explosion
The Giza Pyramids
The mysteries of multiple
University
He's figured out climate change
Atlantis
Also he's done that real problems we got fake problems
Figured out
Can you give me an idea of a
Of course I watched a bunch
Shazam movie
Videos that are free and they're the most ridiculous
But you've ever ate someone standing at a dry erase board usually in front of a green screen
To the green screen
Some cool image behind it
Send lots of sandwich
Trust Atlanta
Government
CIA approved technique
Another interview
Complaining that the CIA the government weren't using the remote viewing technology correctly
Exactly
Civilian funds but
Imagine what I do
Groundbreaking
Revolutionary Technologies
Inside the Mind
Hitler
Snow White
So what he's referring to is the thing called project Stargate
Sometimes referred to as operation Stargate
Kurt Russell
I see umbrella name of a series of secret project
Back from the 70s and 80s
That the government was doing
To look into remote viewing
Psychics that crazy at the reason they were doing that is because there were rumors flying around that Russia was doing it
I may need it to
Keep up
The Russian
Have a remote viewing leg up
Figure out
Psychic
Sprite Davis
The project ended up being
Continued
In the 90s
Because of like
Yes
Absurd
Keep doing this
Government aspect that you talking about
The Men Who Stare at Goats was made about
It wasn't right right
The other the other piece of it is like people have tried
Constantly
Play U2
Empirical evidence
That
Remote viewing is pasa
And every time they do so
Incredibly vague
Suggestions of life
Like I see it
Stuff like that and then if you want to believe it you'll go ahead be like oh that's
That's proof enough for me
But it's the thinnest
Whatever it's all right.
In control
Seeing somebody with the letter m
If you know that kinda
And then you just fill in the blanks I am painting a picture
Intentionally
People are just making it up
They're they're goofy they're Goofy
They're just standing in front of a dry erase board making s*** up doing it basically improv game
That's what I'm saying
Brown wants to tell you something else
He wants to tell you about the rigorous
Training
The his remote viewer is go through
Typically the training for people to do training at farside
The training just the beginning training
Takes 9 months and that's
Twice a week all day
For nine months without a break
So you're talkin about
Between 16 and 20 hours of work
Every week
Renee
Streaming
About you screaming about crazy in like out that's nonsense
You would know
There was a place in Columbia Missouri where I spent a large
Which portion of my life called the school of metaphysics
Non accredited school
And you have to do
Diaper
Because a friend of mine got duped by them
Hundred tons of money
Trying to come up the rank Scientology Style
And they would have similar things you have Visa
Were you need to like go through all go over all this stuff
Classical technique of breaking
People's will but it's not bad it's not an aggressive technique
Sleep deprivation and playing loud music
Cooking dogs on you
What is a way of like
Letting your guard down
In a slightly friendly
Or supposed Academic Way in order to rebuild you in the mold that they want you to be
Basecamp
Bootcamp
Pictures like that just like that
The first time that I heard this
Lake Winnie
Describe
Salat immediately was selecting that the people who come out of that training
Crazy enough to a god threw it in the first place
Your organization will never be infiltrated with naysayers
You'll never have people who are involved her like that maybe I'm not actually doing anything.
Me for 2018
Infiltrate
ZZ farsight Academy
2 + 2
I originally thought it was called Fireside knows like
Brown is one of their professors
Professors
All of their classes are just
Fat lip got kicked out of the University that offers battery
We learn more
Will the universe exist
And then they start appearing in our time goes by Jack which is a predicted news bill that comes out once a month
When they do that
But they make
Is they end up in this time Chronicle or whatever the name that he literally just
But I can just look at the website
Cross project
I watched a couple of
Does this as well
What is supposed to be is the vix
You have to get you get you really get into it in the fifth
Like you got to get through the first four where there's 200 tablets
Sigma characters
Episode 5
What I was describing lost
You at the farsight
Academy
Computer whatever
They have a
TV show that they put out on YouTube
Where they tell you what next
Next month's news is going to be
What are the predictions of basically there's going to be trouble in a State Building or something like that
Supposed to be in November and then so at what they end up
Medusa weather like
It's going to happen next
Month
Yeah that is what it is
Is a do like okay
And then when they put out the next month's video
The beginning is this guy Courtney Brown
Having a discussion of the predictions they made the last month I thought The Interpreter
It's crazy
There's so much you can go watch if you want to
I'm going to main line that so I watched one and like I said that prediction
House building
Before informal thing
It was supposed to be prediction
November
And so when Courtney Brown the next month
Is giving an explanation he's like
So I easily figured out what this was
Because they'd had such a great drawing
And the lady who is doing the prediction
I'm so he's his music she was predicting
Milo yiannopoulos
Is trouble on one of those University of California campuses
Exactly
October 31st and we were looking at November cover the news it was reported in the
News November 1st
So that's why we cover fee
Too many rules
Aldi's
Anyway he has a psychic new show
Settles with the wrong
It wasn't going to happen
We're doing the statistical analysis for that now it's been extremely successful since we started in May of 19
For 2016
And
Grandpa almost a year about or about a year of that then I start working on our Mysteries projects which are
Big projects that turned into movies
Projects such as the Great Pyramid of Giza
Atlantis that are available for free
I turned into the Disney movie Atlantis
I'm a guy who loves watch
And I will say
That this video that I watched
Of him and his remote
Is one of the worst things ever watch that Atlantis
Oh by the way there is no right
Call Parisa is regular movies through Vimeo and Amazon and DVDs and things like that
Heaven is one of those that just came out and it's a three-hour
Believable
Very believable
No it's
Just conceptually it's so amazing that you think
Impossible but it is very possible
We were able to pursue what this is all about
Also it's
Scott 12
I was going to pay that
Coming soon
On the website it says the Amazon link will be updated when they're available
Did anybody
Nick Cage
Will do that movie for twenty bucks
Tuna sandwich
Guaranteed
Left Behind of course
To watch this thing
Yeah probably seems like you would do just about any
You might be asking yourself at this
Even though you know we can't watch it
Who's still wondering what is this Lauren hasn't about
What's going on with completely forgotten about that why is he
Can you describe
So to speak how they were given the Target and
What I am not sure what the objective was why you chose that particular
In many cultures many religions
There are the talk is written in ancient texts
About this big battle that happened along the gods and things like that
And you get that
She get that in the ramayana and hinder text you get that
And has alien check
Bring back the
Kitchen is alien
And he's roundly criticized for not being able to translate the length
Translate Sumerian
To the question of why are why does this war in God
Beam seem to run
Consistently throughout
So many cultures
I would give much
Simpler explanation
Then.
What he's going to give here in a minute
And that is that
You know
Cultures needed an explanation for phenomenon that they couldn't understand
Science
God nature that's
And then they had
To come up with a reason why
Things happen obviously it's because he's God
Aren't working in
That is consistent throughout all cultures the reason that there's
Trouble is because dumb God
Petty differences with other gods
And we are Pawns
Get killed in in the mix
As they play out their struggle
That's why
Could you have
Explain
Salmon you have to explain natural disasters
You have to explain those sorts of things
They're actually right
Everybody is always known the
The gods have been fighting and we have to
To figure out a way to stop them
Providing so what we're going to do
Way to go back in time to before the gods were fighting
We need to drive
All right over there
We're going to also
Hitler
The god start fighting
Assuming it's Hitler's fault
Did something crazy
You know what's crazy about worship
Here's the weirdest
The Greek pantheon
Just such a weird thing I'll tell you why
Did you remote view that Hitler has okay
Cena from his
Let's get back to the war in heaven stuff
Yes
You decide about the war the war
And in the judeo-christian tradition you have to have it both in the Old Testament
In the New Testament the big mention of courses
In Revelation
Answer the Book of Revelation chapter 12
There was a war in heaven
And Michael and his angels fought and the dragon and his angels fought
All of these different cultures
Different religions different prophets different everything
Separated by hundreds sometimes thousands of years
Go after religious studies
Professor
So the real question was
Let's go remove your project
Where are we
That word does that phrase in chapter 12:7 in Revelation
What is this so that would
Start Pugh
So the time to kill was
Whatever the perceptions were the original prophet
Who is receiving this
Saying that he later called the Warren heaven and wrote the Book of Revelations about
And
We wanted to find out what time for what
Whispers
Until we got it
So they got it
Play I want to go back and figure out what was going on with John of Patmos
They're going to start
A remote viewing
Inquiry which I love
Because that makes
Sounds like there's a big bureaucracy
Percy of like
Like there was a pitch meeting where these two low-level guys are like hold on
We're going to see what happened
With the war on have
Brewski
Just just throwing that one out there and they're like okay well we're going to take that whether or not I'll have in it
It's Friday
Really need to talk
Actor John of Patmos
Whether or not
Right
What
We're going to go
Find out
What's your deal
What's which got your crawl
You going to get into John of Patmos here in a minute
Before he does
He's going
To explain
Some of the results
Look what they found
Do they have fidget
Citgo results
Do they eat the Whiteboard
Is a physical
He does he makes the claim here the beginning
I'm here that the fewer the remote
Communicate with
Each other
It all came up
And I don't care that he saying
Cuz I don't necessarily believe it
And further
Play out one of my big critique
At the end of this here real quick
There's no communication between them
All got the same thing
Huge space battle between basically two planets
And basically to
Different species all there was a couple of the species evolve
He was really like a Star Wars that thing
They got the Falling Rocks the lava rocks coming down everybody got the same thing these two opposing
Spaceships and everything
Aggressor species that look the reptilian
More humanoid
Very similar
Different but similar
They were battling it out then the humans
Humanoid
Reese's blizzard
Underdog
They were the ones
Getting the bed they were getting species was the Italian
And they were nuking the place
They were they were nuking the place they were
They wanted to control the resources they wanted to control the planet
It looks like that other the other planet
Is a
The Last Resort just put a Zork
Chespirito
Shawna Baum towards the bigger planet that they reptilians came from
And destroy the entire planet
It was a
You know it was a Doomsday
Type of a situation
I'm sorry I cheated
I'm wondering is
Became clear I guess partway through the sessions I think
It leads to the viewers that I were talking about Mars
Yeah they're pretty crazy
Oh yeah
Is forthcoming
Me most about this
He is just f******
Like we just he just f****** identifies with the humanoids because
Cuz they look like
The humanoid
Committed before the plan right
This is an expensive Alex Jones excusing all white terrorism
Jerry Springer crazy how this overlaps a little bit
But
I want to point out here
Is all just basically
This is the stuff right out of Zacharias
Books about
The planet
Also Ender's Game if I remember correctly
This idea
Talk beforehand about what they're going to
You're saying this
Charming
Because I would Gamble
Everything I own
That the people who go through his rigorous 9-month
Process
Basically having their they're brainwashed
To some extent to become one of these remote viewers
I think they're probably in ink
Credibly
Hi in
Who go through that who are
Really interested
I think that they might self-select
In some ways for people who already know this mythology
The scientific sample isn't
In this case
Are you saying that
I think they were published in
Now I can't remember the name
Forsyth
Know that it read
Rimmed
Natural biotechnology
Technology
I love
Don't do this again
There's a giant battle my friend and she's going to later called Martin
Is the one that got marduke
Also possibly known as
D'amato's old-timey religions ulma
Play this is 100% out of 6
Is it two or three of his books and
This is just exactly
What position believe
Repurpose nonsense from mythology
Nocap
Do some explanation
Of all religions
Let me have on Earth
Where do they come from
Revelation was pretty weird
What happened
And Courtney knows allegory for the fall of the Roman Empire
You're a fool
It's our first Target was
Original profit
His perceptions when he
What is Rhema when he was receiving this so-called War Of Heaven what was happening to him
What was he looking at evening when he was getting that
Second target was
The actual Prophet himself at the time that
Not his perception for the time that he was receiving this vision
What was going on with him at that time that was a second so we can see like
How is he getting his eyes and imagine
And it turned out to be an alien abductions I think so I suggest
Is John of Patmos for talking about the author of the book of Revelation
Kia
He basically
Extraterrestrial
Around him and it was one in particular big guy
His head
And he was doing the best he could do was not in control of himself is not the best you could to try to sort it out
And when you got it when the whole experience was over he wrote a book
Revelation that's how we got it
And it really is that's how I got into all these other cultures apparently these humans to know about this
So then
We wouldn't be able to process it
Okay
Processing if we didn't know that
Also
Bucked up
Clearwater
Coded into Revelation or something. Then
Tension
That's my topical referee
Prince for the month
Haha so I don't know man
This stuff to Annex
Spent
Like it's funny
Because we're not idiots
I love you
Oh man this is this
Fun
Storytelling
If you just think it is
But like
How am I going to
Refute
The John of Patmos
How could you
Stroke
Alien abduction
I love the way that he hit that I love the way that I hit that turn
Is it like because it starts with with your you don't like
Closing his eyes and
Imagining
Getting a vision
So what you're saying is he like
Sort of rhetorically knocks down the obvious
Not all
It does it's not even his dad
Azhag Jesus
Okay William James
He's going to he's going to slide of had me know
And stuff
Not even if there's a whole long
Alpha
The amazing Randi
Set out to
Debunk people who are making
Pseudoscience
Difficult
Yeah yeah yeah
To get into like
Yeah yeah
The amazing Randi
Planted
Do people with Envy
The rank
But he knew
They went through
Completely tricked all of these researchers
And then they had a big conference about like
We are
Just using
Singtrix Wii U cheats
It's all gone
All of this.
Are about doing was involved in that as well it's another reason
Be very
Skeptical about these ideas
Without any
There's always been
Yeah amazing
Magicians and then they're like
Okay guys
You're dumb
Outlook
You've made me a lot
Also the
Randy Foundation
I believe that's the name of it they give out Awards
Not a great day
He sounds like a riddle a really horny
Give out Awards
People who are
Get this award
But ironically
No
It's Pegasus
The Flying Pig
It's given out
For people who are the exact opposite
Unwrap around there with Alex Johnson
But Alex was not present
During the space.
And we need to learn more about it
Why would I find out a little bit more about this
So
This morn heaven
What is a war between two
One was Donnelly living on Mars
And the other was living there were playing
Living on this other planet
People call Mal deck
About the asteroid belt that was totally destroyed in the war
And that's the word Nick depressed really
Apparently wanted us to know about him so they see that information
Into our
Collective consciousness
Force-feeding the information and then they write about it in their Jackson
Long behold lyrics
Become slowly aware of it
What do you mean the aliens
Symbol
WhatsApp
So simple
You find
The profit
That you know is going to write a book that magic
The Council of nicaea it's going to make it in
To the Bible
We're not putting
The Bible that's funny.
YouTube on what the one where Jesus
Raptors
Right or the
The Book of Enoch
Where they're like
Probably actually we you know ahead of time
It's going to get into the
The main book
What you do
Deserve
Cool special
No that's what he saying you saying they got a
Where do they
Not though
We're going to get to it
It's not really an abduction it's an abduction like
Scenario
Where he's standing on a lien comes over
Stop
He's going to explain a little bit more later but
Before he does
Text clip where I Courtney Brown
Bakes
I weird
It's fine
Weird point
About the remote
I really want to mention it for me it's really important
These are millennials
Hazelnut
People that came out of the military that were getting ready to retire or die or whatever
So
Having young people
Do these things and having a level of training
It is
This huge level
Just
It's revolutionary
And it's really important for the future of humanity
What did you just say
I love him
You're going to go on such a rollercoaster
Come on listen to him talk about
I'm just happy that's what is millennials
Likenesses this is way better than a New York Times article where is like
Millennials are killing the wine industry this was writing an article that's like
Millennials are resurrecting the crazy industry
There's two reasons why
He's more interested
Millennials
Why you saying
The things I say
One of the reasons that he's making the point of millennials
He wouldn't
Cuz they don't have a lot
Life experience
Young people are much more impressionable
Specifically if you're trying to start a cult
You probably going to start with
Didn't start with elderly
You casting aspersions on
People who are in the military
Have this is going to
Play out
Because you know who
Kerry Cassidy sources
Does General ER
X-Men
But still respect of the real
It's right so him bringing this up
It's kind of something that I don't
Send Carrie it's real
He's going to push back
Kerry pushback Willits
This is going to be bananas
It is interesting because
Project Camelot
Famous interview this with boriska
Who is a young boy from Russia who had total
Past life recall of his life as a soldier on Mars
Create floor here on Earth after that
The planet was I guess decimated so the surface of Mars and
As he describes
I guess some journalist
Heard about it and I'm in the community and then
At least this is how the story goes
Then started
To notice
Of course now
We can't get ahold of her ass. Because he's probably working for the Russian government but none the less this
Parallel information
Another thing that he came across was they were
They actually we're trying to turn Jupiter into a second sun
It's something he said
That makes sense
Sure
Whatever
I like the way she said generally speaking
Stars can become bigger Stars
I don't know about
Planets becoming centaurs
The stars all the time
I mean like horse
I don't know what
I don't I don't know enough
About the world as a whole
Give me the gallon
I don't know enough but I do know that
Dasani
Planet I know that
The Sun is
Not a planet
Jupiter a planet
Turmeric into a star
I don't know man
Class called
Astrology
I don't think this is the name of it cuz I think
Comedians B
It's exactly that
Allergy free
I had to take it in college
It was
I still don't know what the
A professor's name was
But it sounded like
Professor Messer
That's all I remember about it
It was a wild time
I don't know a lot but I know that Jupiter
Is not going to become
Confident
University
Another
9i used
To tell this friend
End of mine who I had from the neighborhood East tell him that I was an alien
That you have perfect recall from your past life
Another place where you around
I wasn't it was a it was a humanoid
Into the
Basic tenants of
Communism
Trying to tell stories to my friend of the plant that I came from or everything with equal
Everyone was
Taking care of it up your friend animal
Mostly make it up later I grew out of it and I like Ike
I should probably stop doing this
Probably never told your friend
Never got a chance
Sorry
Know what I'm saying about all that
Is that probably what happened with Mariska
As opposed to he's not working for the Russian government real world
Explanation for that now please go ahead
He is working for the Russians
Into the
He was the only one who saw
People would not shut up about
Hillary's emails
That's why they talk to you
Robert David Steele
Stefan molyneux
George Papadopoulos
Make your point
No I just love the way that you said That's How The Story Goes
Like when describing vraska's origin story of like
Well he started out as the
The small boy
To his mother and then a journalist
Or That's How The Story Goes like
The part that she's
Skeptical
Brightright
Uno's weather
There was a giant space battle on Mars
Probably fighting alongside Randy Cramer
Space Randy Cramer
Send that I have to
Is easier Reptoid or is he human
Will get into a rapper
Episode unfortunately
Yeah it sounds almost I keep forgetting which side is the good one
Because there are no good
So In that clip you start to see
We carry be like well
These are the things that I have figured out that she's starting to grow a little bit
Possibly resentful
Hey boils over a little bit in the
Text clip where we got our
Easy to blow up a planet
There are lots of places on the planet where you have
Literally hundreds
High powered nuclear weapons
Stored in one spot
YouTube
Enemies
Nuclear weapon
Nuclear capability this is this clip is a little bit longer but I
Secure them bickering
It might be a good mic down.
It's Cady as hell
Is it happened the same way with l.ron Hubbard
They have these
Everything's cool
It's Abby 50
B-2 bomber
Cesar bunker-busting nuclear weapon
Right
That just makes perfect sense
Species you maybe Reptoid
Made of course why wouldn't you build a bunker bus
Is that you have a bunker-buster missile type thing that goes and blows up
Stockade of nuclear weapon
Let's keep Oliver nuclear weapons
Gunshot it into one of those places and detonated it
You really like me
Ignite all of them
They all go up at 1
Really easy to blow up
Earth is an 8000 Miles
All of liquid Molten
Lava
Just liquid
I just got an 8 Mi thin crust
On top of it like a grape seed
Balloon
To this I would like to remind him of volcanoes
Yep Oklahoma
Player
Earth is a lot like
A grape seed
Yep
Alright
So if you took
One of those repositories
Hundreds of nuclear weapons and shot one weapon into it and detonated it
Defendant
You destroy the entire planet
That's not what we scientifically know
And and we also don't know
You know I think there was a lot of way
Using to destroy planets in fact I have some information from one of my
Witnesses about that and if it does involve other things such as shooting a neutron star
Through the Wormhole
It is not hard to blow up a planet and this is one way you could be done using current technology that we have
Okay but that's also what you know as a surface human that's not necessarily what black projects
Secret space
Program are aware of and utilizing even to this day
Is that most people would say blank a planet you can't do that
It's just for Bridges reaching for the idea to explain the people it's not that hard to blow up
Has this ever been you
Planet
I don't know how to do this I think my hands keep slipping
Turn off oven
So easy
Fresh
I don't know about this
Shooting a neutron star through.
It's less important what makes ice
Collapse
A wormhole of itself
It's less important what makes sense and what doesn't
Is more important is this
Friction that we're seeing
We've never seen Gavin
Be like look
I am Morley
Venue
You're saying things that don't go in line with the Project Camelot line
And I got a
Polite but also shuttle
You down on some stop
Because everything we've ever
Oh yeah let's
Panera
Why not
Cereals Auto
More stealing for the bra
Coronavirus fights
Phuc yea Spider-Man
Ian Holm
Onboard
What did you just say about f***
Mars bunker-busting bomb to blow up a nuclear
Moron
Everyone knows
The f****** neutron star in a wormhole
From when we were fighting it
Vietnam
Courtney
What you don't understand is I
Other crazy people before you and they've assured me that they're crazy s*** is real
If therefore I can
Can't go along with your crazy s*** they are having a dominant struggle about crazyshit
Well I mean
Of course the old saying is there's more than one way to
I'm just saying this
How you could do it
If you were to do
That sort of mentality of
I got to push back a little bit Lisa
Who carries Cassidy accidentally asked
Most Salient question
Of all time
Iveta Courtney
He does not enjoy having ass out
Was there any detail you know because there's this thing called actionable intelligence
And sometimes I wonder if these remote viewing
Avoid
Even on purpose giving us
What what might be termed axonal
Actionable intelligence things that could be checked out really that are very very hard
Now you say there are some in some of these
Things that were involved here
Got to some degree have shown up in our cultures
And so in a certain sense.
Information that's validated
Simply because it's been around for so long that something of that nature might have happened
But
Do you understand my question is here
Not really
Okay so the question is
That these remote viewing sessions are giving you actionable intelligence
I'm not sure what I would be mean by actionable intelligence
Means that you can follow.
Define heart.
Animal project
A base tan
Definition of intelligence
No no it's not
No it is not
Ma'am
Oh
Carrie asked
The one
Question that you are not allowed to ask on Friday
Jack Campbell. Which is it
The question
I noticed from looking at a lot of remote viewing stop that it seems like it's almost
Intentionally vague
And unverifiable
Quick question
From me Kerry Cassidy
Is any of this real
Our entire operation is
Call Leon real thing
So
It's been forever look
Place that she is spent
Entire life of
Which is the Skeptics
Place exactly
Batesville
Right
She wants
Don't believe you
Believe in you
What you know that your heart
Filled with
Martian history
Still pure paranoia narrative you have about the world being some sort of
Describe it that's what she wants
To perpetuate
She's going out of her way because this guy is like
I think she
I don't know
It's very weird
But anyway she asked another question
Just suggest another question that's actually really Saline
They
The human
The humanoid
Separate but equal
Pitiable
Humans on Mars
Mal Duke
Whatever
Malbec
Answer that
That was the end of this war
There was a mass genocide
So
If she has a question about
I like how would that be
The war
Necessarily
Don't
Courtney has a good amp
Was the nuclear decimation on the surface of Mars
A result in
You know
Payback
The destruction of the planet when it blew up
That apparently was the end of the war
There's also the engine
Good games tomorrow
This may not be answerable I'm I'm just
Why is if they know if you have a fleet of
Army or whatever it is I'm not Army but
You know above your head and it is attacking you and
Their home planet is blown up
He doesn't automatically therefore follow that the police suddenly band is there war and
You're correct and certain are correct in that everybody just didn't stop
You know for all intents and purposes you can imagine that
After that
People are just trying to sign find someplace to go
I mean Marty really wasn't a very habitable
Easily habitable place after that either
Well that's
Bro remember we talked about
Exactly cuz you just said I see
And we also know that there are many different races of reptilian
You certainly
It's Raining Men Planet doesn't miss. Didn't do a way with them you know that for a fact because we have monuments
Reptilians
You know
John Oliver
Isis was tasked
According to one of my Witnesses
Which is throwing a lot of the evidence in the Middle East of just that the reptilian domination of humans
So
So that we bring Isis into the fold
Isis
Places in her position
Create
Tudus
Destroy
Proof of rep
Alien domination of Earth
So if I understand correctly
Isis
Not gdubs is
Nope
Reptilians fault
Perhaps humanoids
Committing a mass genocide
More fun
As an explanation
Fanciful
It said
It's really still just
Trying to ignore the real
We just got the last episode
Destruction
You've laid on people
Population
I love that carries
Wargaming
Carrie's doing a carries doing our job
What is this is a little disappointing
I know that Carrie Campbell
But she's been holding back all the time I'm only brings this out whenever she likes
But I'm done with this
The whole bunch of ships out there still
That's why you blew up
I might also that answers your question is too like what about Mars why can't you live on it
Do the Fallout of the Fallout
Is August
His is answer of
Well you know Mars
Really a great place to live anyways yeah
Dad you might as well
F*** off
Into a different plan
Get up on a soapbox
He's reptilians
And so the question becomes
Did
And this is just
And for people to
Into possibilities as to what this could mean so it's not just an idle thing
Guero somewhere in the far distance
Earthlings were attacked on Mars and that was how it
Ended up looking like it does and basically they went to Earth after that
Did follow we know they fall
And we know they're here now and we also know that
They have been here in the past because we have the carvings
Sturbridge show
In various societies which include stop America all over Sumer
Egypt Iraq Iran you know serious pederasty
So what I'm saying is
May we look forward to another battle with reptilian sometime in our future
Let me say this
Indy Reads a lot of interesting questions of which I don't have
Okay
Fair enough
Callahan
All of my other guests
Perfect human
Allowed to be translated to my
Will you don't have
Is you don't know about the secret space program
Music
Well obviously remote
All of your other information
Is silly
And if you believe the rest
Believe he has
Extra human abilities
It suited his team what are you doing Carrie this is
No regular surface
Psychic
Just because your other fake gas to rid fake documents doesn't mean that they have some sort of grasp on true that this site
It doesn't matter
This is been there it's like since we started doing project
Camelot episode
What is cuz I've always wanted to know what the
Carrie to go over
To the other side something like this guy
Through the
Xperia Z Theory window
But now she's gone all the way to the other side of
Skeptical
Conspiracy theory
She's too deep
Mantooth gone native
Next clip
Courtney
Brown
Hey just dumb
Jesse Ventura
Set of harassing people
There's a hole
Lorde
Under Area 51
This is about the Dulce base
Kind of stuff
Disconnected tunnels underneath like a bunch of
Military installations Area 51 Dulce base
Send apps at all come
I didn't put it all comes from
Dude
Who killed himself
It's a very tragic
Big story if you look into the reality of adulthood
It's
Not real
Very very sad
That this guy threw his fake remote viewing
Perpetuate
How how that brain virus meme
Kind of work
Like with John Pat
John
He was on
No I'm talking about the guy from
Uncle Johnny
No
There's no way that he could ever have imagined
Is that his
Dumb allegory was going to last
2000 years
No
Like this guy
Invented the
There's no way he would have expected
Affected his he was just trying to make a living you just trying to make a living going right to UFO convention
Selling fake little scraps of metal AB
That's all he was doing
Viruses
So many people
Once we wrap up this episode
And even more fascinating aspect
Like
The nature of this.
Does he take off his
Surface even Mexican reveal that he was a reptilian the whole time
The deeper you go the larger the collection of bills people are
Chill about reptilians by
Military Witnesses in people that work in Black
I don't know that though man I can just say what we have done
Area 51 and we did find what we can described as reptilians are there
They were not particularly friendly
Committed
I mean yeah
If you believe that
That's
Swiss cheese
Ridiculous
I'm telling you so here's where we get to
Starting to not believe it I think what I've described is like
Point of no return
For the two of them at
Staffing Partners
And then they can take the information that we have at the Warren Heaven which is at
Information from any other one single source
So I think this is going to eventually change
The tone of all of these discussions we don't need
Speculate so much
And guess we can say okay Lee spino this much
And based on this much
We can start asking
People that do no more governmental sources things like that or more information
You're not going to get this information out of the military
The military works for the government
They don't run the gout
You have to
The military
Disagree on whether they run the government or not and whether our president is actually
Present because there was a military coup
So I'm not going to go there at the moment
That's not true
Sisyphus interview
But I do appreciate you know what you're you're talking about and I certainly agree that this
I do think that
The viewing
You are it adds to assertive a Litany of information that I certainly have gotten from Witnesses
He did work for the military
Uber
That's so on
Oh s***
That's so fucken
Comfortable
In a Land of liars
Yeah it's really interesting 12 Liars butt up against
Really
Cuz it does go down to like
Who's asserting Domino
I'm trying to
Assert
Ipassive lazy version
Dominance
Over each other
She's going to win every time
Fox news interview
All I like this is whatever Fox News brought out whatever
Silly liberal voice that would go on there
Yeah represent liberals
I like it as a strategy
She's going to get it
40 minutes
So the interview was fine and then
Took a turn somewhere and I'm not entirely sure why
I think it was when he said
It's the military
When he was talking about the millennial
Videos working for him I think that was the truck
No because he in the ain't talkin about the millennials
Disparage the idea of all right
Spell against the Pendragon
Carrie's rap
Sochi
I think that guy was
Play the military
At this point
You start asking questions
From the message
Cuz there's a live stream going
What I thought was
Particularly
Last question someone wants to know if you have information on what Ed dames
Call Patel shot
Ridiculous idea I've ever heard in my life
I don't even talk about it
Alright
Okay well it's been great again to talk to you
Do you know about it
So
Remote viewer
Flames
I'll just list awesome
Movie caught stealing fertilizer from us companies
He said that the existence of Satan will be proven by science
Monsanto covers both of them
He said that Bill Clinton would be killed in April 1998 on a golf course by lightning
He claimed to know he was replaced by a change
They claim to know the exact location of Amelia Earhart
Explain Madagascar a cylindrical object
Containing deadly fungus spores released by an alien intelligence
Heading towards Earth and 9th
That was the satellite Act
Beat fungus that
Would spread to the Americas
A motto
Killshot
Yes
This was a late 90s
He predicted a series of powerful deadly solar flares
Determine the killshot would impact the Earth
And wipe out civilization
Queen 2011
So it didn't
And
Wait what
Didn't happen it's one of those things that really is used as an invalidation
Remote
These claims were like
Didn't come
Druid
Still seen as like a legitimate
Part of the remote viewing
Community
EXO
This person bring that up is a hey go f*** yourself
Courtney Brown
He's through that
That was an answer back in the day I'm
I'm sure that the two of them
Tongue
They were
Contemporary
So the largest remote viewing facility on Earth
If you don't know Ed
No
Lay down
Libertyville to the end of the Project Camelot episode
But it doesn't bring us to the end of our epoch
Oh no
So I've been withholding a certain piece of
Information from
Wait
Did Carrie go on
No
This is all still in Project Camelot world
So I went to the farsight website
I want to farsight. Org
I mentioned some of the things that he was
Involved
Courtney Brown is involved in
Remote viewing you know you have the Hitler thing
You have Martin Luther King give Area 51
These are listed on his website as the
The project
Climate change
Giza Pyramids
Reptilians
There's one thing that you do
Left
On his website
It is a very big
To discuss it
I had to go back
And find an episode
From 1990
Yeah alright
In November of 1996
Courtney Brown
Went on
Buy with Art Bell
Coasttocoastam
To talk about the
Hale-Bopp
Yes here is the
Obviously there's something to this object is 4 times approximately 4 time
Let me be clear you talk about the
Trailing Hale-Bopp
This is based on
Fraudulent image
Do they have come out
In the day of
This episode in November of 9
Trailing Hale-Bopp
We're going to get to it
Size of the planet Earth
And it's headed our way
I don't know how your clerk awake is but I'll start right now
Wherever they're going to organize ourselves
Galaxy out there there is sending all the Galactic Federation the council
And I prepared.
Anastasia Galactic Council or some higher order watching very interested
Are there watching a hologram on the phone
Like watching election returns or something they are all seated around a table in the Subspace
Looking at something
Like that
Very sweet about that event which may be happening
Going in a Direction
Which is not
Direction which is not evolutionary but only time
I will tell and I
Time is of the essence
And many things are happening
Is accurate description of the subject
Well I'm not sure I want to hear coming from more accurate after coming
I'm on page 11 and I want to make sure I cover the most important stops on
Okay I won't remember anything else
Check really important
Immediately
Something spinning
People on the ground here
Batman looking up
I mean ideas Restaurant originated looking up in the sky looking at some structure
And there was also something going on in Subspace communicator
Fundamental
There's a message being sent
Someone who is listening but not hearing
It is essential that
Description of persons wake up and listen now help will be there when he died
Somebody a message
Interpretation of its Collective
The message is being sent to us
When listening but not understanding this message coming from this object
Yes and it's also been coordinated by the larger Galactic Council
When was the
I don't know that
But I do know
Wedding March
We're going to need to cross-reference this
He just described the
The plot of the
The fifth
He didn't describe it as remote
Viewer.
Let me take a look here
Holyshit
So he predicted this plot of The Fifth Element
Call
Don't f****** know
Gary Oldman is no longer my favorite actor
You're missing the forest for the
The trees
Courtney Brown
Is the reason
No
You got
He's the reason that the idea went around that
Spaceship was following
The Hale-Bopp Comet
I thought he said it was an odd
Check the size of Earth
It's a huge spaceship let's go to the next clip
Who is a large object out there
It apparently is
Tunnels in it
Illogical artificial and natural in a sentence that has
Rock
As well as
Mantua
Humongous it's absolutely large
And it apparently moving in an artificial in artificial man it's not moving like a normal Celestial body mean
Under control
A vehicle
Four times the size of the planet Earth
Is a big eating thing one thing one thing about the eighties that when they decide to put on a show
Plano theater
Laemmle Theater better than anything on Broadway for me
You understand what I'm getting at here
Courtney Brown he's been right the whole time about everything
Courtney Brown
The guy that we've been going over
On this episode of project
Now
What episode of Project Camelot
No s*** in 1996
He went on Art Bell
And basically
Through his remote viewing b*******
Created the idea of
The spaceship was
Was following the Hale-Bopp Comet
Was picked up by the Heaven's Gate cult
And led to the deaths
What
Yeah
He was the one who killed the Heaven's Gate people
You know why you know why it happened you know why it happened
It's not all his fault although he's playing with fire when he plays games
Like that the entire idea of Heaven's Gate with
Level
And if there's going to be like we're learning lessons
Skier and there's messages from
Space that we need to listen to the way he's presenting it on this episode of Art Bell
It just so happened
Typically Falls in line
With the teachings that Marsha
Applewhite was
Put putting forward to his flock
This idea that like what he says in this episode
Everhart Peltier
He's like oh did you like
This space
Item
Space object
What the messages
We are hearing them
But there's an individual who needs to listen
How could Marshall Applewhite not
End up like
This is
So clear that he got all this
From this episode of Art Bell
Really
Nobody knows
When did
Well I was sleep
Do you want cuz it was right around when the hell by,
March 24th
26 + 90
Cuz they didn't ship
The idea
That you needed
To like the idea of Hale-Bopp being
Part of it and the I'd of the object
Floating behind Hale-Bopp
And the suicide stuff
Was it not a part of their cult for the
Proceeding 20 years
No she Heaven's Gate existed for a really long time
Before
Becoming a suicidal doomsdayco
Call
Company
For a while
Tire Source or something like that was the name of the company like great at it you understand
Like
Good the reason that I I'm
I'm bringing all this up
There's literally no way
Way to get around the idea
That
To be your crazy dude who was a cult leader
And his teachings matched up
Entirely with what this guy
Went around and spit
On Art Bell show there's an obvious one to one
That he listens
To this episode of Art Bell
And that's where
He started the
Come up with the ideas
That lead
To the
I mean people
No it's not this is everybody
Just before he made reference to it on that podcast about heaven
It's really good people should listen to it
Even as I was listening to
Did this episode of
The Project Camelot
Pieces together
Courtney Brown
Was the guy in that episode of Art Bell
From 1996
Who created the entire mythology
Around the idea of it
Wood spaceship
Coming
Behind
Bananas
Just made this up
Yeah like there's no other recorded
Situation
Before this other than of course
I know of
Well other than the guy who wrote The Fifth Element who have a remote
Fraudulent pictures that were
Serta doctor it up
Courtney Brown
Set Art Bell
Some pictures
Forgotten
From a anonymous
Astrophysics
Telescope
Turned out they were doctor
Pictures from
The University of
Quiet
Absolutely prove it
Uses to say
Pictures work
He's caught up
Elaborate
That ended up
Being really
Really f****** day
Crazy now granted
We can take a step back and we can really realize that
The situation
If you look into what was going on in the heavens
Navigate called
Word dangerous
I already
No matter what there is there is a chance
There's a chance they were going to end up committing suicide
Obviously at one hundred percent
Sent fed into it
But also Cults generally don't and
Until there's a satisfying narrative for the leader to play out
Like
The only reason they'd Jonestown ended the way it did
Is because
We got to pull it
Where is
The story he would have probably rather lived out with them at suicide would have been slightly different
Unless forced
And rushed that it was
You know what I'm saying with Jeff couch
This episode
Of of coast to coast
100% gave Marshall Applewhite
The
Narrative
And gave the idea of like
Oh s*** this entirely
Different 20 years we've been saying that aliens are going to bring us to the neck
Next Level we have the story
This is a professor
There's a professor who's going on this show he has a doctorate
He's no slouch
What's
Political science
But we have one more one more year from back in 1999
They're really drive home
And like this is the stuff I was listening to earlier
I got nauseous
I need to listen to many people will not be around
Many people beings
Interested
7 is is underway with regard to the Subspace,
For the entire decoding process
What does that mean
Structure infrastructure were looking at up in space
It's got some information it's kind of information
We have to keep our plan our Escape
They have to deal with
So what's the Subspace realm of life
It's open to interpretation
To the point where a cult leader
Who was
Very frequently and now
Of the heaven
You know everybody is art really that's not
Who we are there's a sub-level our souls
Red Rabbit
I don't know how to put a button on
But like
When we talk about
The Project Camelot stuff
It's super fun cuz it
It's f****** stupid
But at the same time
The episodes about Mark Richards in the Raptors
And stuff like that
He's a murderer
He's a f****** murderer
Why don't you understand
Episode did super fun about Courtney Brown coming on and talking about how he has figured out
The war in heaven
Then we can laugh and have a lot of fun with that you look at his past
He's response
Not responsible but he had his hand
The death of
39 people in the end of the Heaven's Gate cult
I guess that stuff
Do you understand
And I get it
My problem is
Is a micro version of
Religion
Like my problem is it's a micro version of the worship of guns in this
Country Vet
Like what
But that's why I'm not
I'm struggling
Yo I'm struggling
Any kind of discount
Kind of emotion
No connection to this
Because it's
Relatively speaking
In the grand scheme of all of the reason
These people murder a s*** ton of pea
Objectively Hilaire
Well I guess if you're if you're in the Heaven's Gate Club
If you're in the habit
My favorite okay
So I had I had the bottle
Exited out his crate
We would debate things now
And I have limited sympathy
Heaven's Gate
People I'm not I'm not I'm not interested
Playing
That's not the conversation I'm having
The conversation that I'm trying to bring
Is
They are very serious concert
For people who play these sorts
Crazy games
You know what I'm saying
There are
There's a real world
Fantasy game
That
Kerry Cassidy is playing
On Project Camelot
If you scrape beneath the surface a little bit with a bunch of the people that she has on
You fine
Their involvement
In very dangerous
Whether it be a murder
Perpetrated on Coast to Coast AM
Said into
A ritual mass suicide
So so if we take from that Annex
Extrapolated
Jerusalem isn't that big a deal
I didn't say that
Jerusalem
You heard it here first
Not that big a deal
You lot like Courtney Brown
Jesus was the Courtney Brown
Of the Bible that's what I'm going to say
Alright
By AP the answer
The other point that I wanted to make you can have stuff like this
In your past
You know people
Know about it
And
It doesn't matter
No it doesn't
His behavior in 1996
Should legitimately disqualified
From anybody listening
To him ever again
He has a website
An Institute
People in
Training in remote viewing
Which cost them a lot of money
For the training
I don't know I didn't
Get an exact figure on it
But then he also sells his
Bulshit
Channel 2 movies
Do people buy it
Cuz people are into this f****** ding dong world
And I look
I'm not coming down on people being interested
In
These sorts of topic
Like some stuff like that
I'm coming down on the idea of
Of Canard
Using it
So easily
And there being no
Like most of
The people who watch Project Camelot probably don't know
This part of Cameron Courtney Brown pissed
They probably don't know March Mark Richards was
The Pendragon
They don't know these
Well the Millennials didn't grow up
Right and everyone
This guy has a doctorate he probably knows some stuff
I've heard of remote viewing before it's probably real
And therefore he gets to
The play out his cycle again
Right and whatever comes of a lot of this remote viewing stuff
You could end up
I mean you just got to be careful cuz you're making
Stuff up
And some crazy person might hear that stuff that you're making up
And run with it
And that's exactly
Amazon
Does the crazy stuff he makes up
People run with
End up harassing
Shooting up puppy
Two again one of the things that
I feel like
Justifies our and of course I have to have so
Some sort of
Things that justifies
The way that way
We attacked
Alex Jones
And project
Is because
These guys are the weakest link
Con artist
Exactly
You know like
Alex Jones is the weakest link of the
Conservative propaganda
He's so clearly and obviously
Force Unleashed BlogTalkRadio probably whatever all the sudden now
You have the tools to see through all of the other day
Conservative propagate
Yeah because
You can tell they're using the same
Exactly
Just left obvious
Camelot
Of the game
What is
And anytime you hear stuff
Like this
People consider for a moment that they might have
Incredibly checkered past
Staff hoaxes.
15 Yukon truck
Also shoutout to dr. poodle Papa in the chat room
Not super early in the episode
And then I'll bring it up
Podcasts
Heaven's Gate podcast
Recommended
With the caveat
That via the host
David is a two-bit Jazz weirdo
Yeah I listen to it it was it was
Compelling audio Lee
Orally the story and the research and it is amazing really interesting but
Buried if
Cat got out
It wasn't bad it was just it was like
You listen to NPR for more than an hour you start to lose your
Tarak Mehta
We made our point
Be careful all religions are wrong
When you hear things
Careful
Especially nowadays but like that
So I will I will
Themselves
Is this week
Art Bell
Now that's every
Are you sure
So now Tarbell
Coast to Coast AM with George Noory
The obvious person
Twitter
Facebook
We are on
Well
I think
Marshall Applewhite you can go f*** yourself
Yeah I guess so
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color