Alexandra Thurston color
Little bit about Alex Jones
Disaster right now
You could have just flipped it to me this is off to a very combative
Is there a headphone information
Hey Mambo
Alex Jones
Before we get today
2 couple dollars to the show
First of all
We appreciate it so much
Now very much
All of our policy wonks and donors are special
In our hearts
But special
At the last minute
Do bump us over our January gold
The business and get this endgame documentary put together
California
Someone sodomites
Thank you so much Andy from California
We appreciated
Right it just gets better
See forget where it goes like we had one big blowout
Last dance contest
From on
They're not taking away our endgame sets for Less reference
Okay just because I came in at the end let's not lose
And Tessa
Yeah we got episode
Brett that scene
In Brokeback Mountain
It turns out that Alex Jones in the past
In the present
I just can't quit him
Alright
So we're back to the front.
I'm still digging through listen to these months
But I'm realizing
It's going to be much more difficult to make a bow out of that
Because like I said he repeats a lot
Their lot episodes that are like I'll just as last week's episode
The time it would take for us
To keep up with the show doing it like that would be
No time
And we are
Here is
Is episodes
Stupid
Georgia Lottery
What is this Alex
Ramona's cell phone computer at home
I believe it's the 2nd of February
28 drunk
Here is a picture of Alex Jones at his desk
I conveniently not hiding at all the highball ThyssenKrupp
This man is boozing pretty good during this episode
Is a very exciting what is this
What are you talkin about
Alex just go straight out and say
That's
Screamed
Indication that he's feeling
At the moment the pretense of this I believe is that he was going to record
Video while I was drunk
Get home
I don't know if Rob do anything
Very close attention
You can hear the cameraman last
And that indicates to me that I think
Partially Alex is trying to do a comedy piece
A little bit
In a second
Let's start
Well is there an endless preamble
No
It does
It does seem to go on forever it's a it's a 20-minute video that could have been for
Something like that
Look there are parts
That are fun
Not the way he wants them to be more and more
Like I revealed one of my cards
This is embarrassing
Like to the point where whoever recorded this and post it
They're doing Alex Jones a very serious disservice
If it were me I'd be like
Didn't really built anything
It wasn't nothing I just
I'd like recorded it and then was like the internet
This game winner
Send the internet with you
We've had a meeting about it
So I believe what's going on here is that Alex wanted to make a video about the memo release on Friday
And
It was shattering
World-changing information it was predicted
And that is that as soon as it's out it's nothing
Until it comes out there is political
How are you
You can gain from it
Insider source
Claimed it something else was the memo now the memos out and it's like he claimed to have already had them
Invalidates
So much of Alex Jones
It's like she Cannery about sources anyway Special Report
Sort of talks about the memo and then quickly skips on to another topic
Gentleman Batman
Fisa memo
Blueprints
Activities
Fisa warrant
Warren
Seriously
That's what everybody said about the memo so far right
About trying to overthrow the will of the text
Pears
Is because you like taxes
I don't know why
Process
Text Sharon
What are pundits on MSN
Calling
Violence
Trump
True
Don't touch
Were there a little bit
Cuz he realizes Rodger Stone Nixon
Alex Alex
Prosperity only Nixon could go to China
And bring back prosperity
Alex Jones would've been all over Nixon
There's absolutely no doubt about that
Anybody who has a authoritarianism
All over
That's what we're learning I think
Is that there was nobody who ever run for president for President
In Our Lifetime has been on air
A cruel authoritarian
Right right right right
Folksy accent behind so you're like so you can erode civil liberties that's
That's alright kooky little cat
Really anymore at all
To lay the groundwork
He's going to get into this clip from MSNBC
Where
Hyundai
Commentary
Here for
Video
Sonic.com
MSNBC called Revelations from
Illustrates
Again
They take that compressor election
Break down the borders bringing their world government
It's just like a girl
Darso
So long
Slate
You're mixing metaphors
Clearly
We have
They just want a picture
Clerk
Marshalls
You could stop at Starbucks
He's about to take a big
American Recovery
This is unfortunately kind of rights that a gate the sky misspoke
Multiple people have been indicted
Guilt the gates
He's fighting
Glenn and a Papadopoulos
I didn't know the Papadopoulos it's like guilty conviction
Do you want to be like there was a fight
BFDI
Able to vote that guy is technically correct
Play semantics games to make a little bit of hay on that because you know they didn't have full trial
Clothes or anything like that
You know his
MSNBC
Islam
I mean I've talked myself into
He's not right
Indications and like I guess it hasn't gone through yet
It looks like that
It's probably gone
Yeah that would make three
You should absolutely do that
Who knows what's going to happen with that pick situation
What are these
I don't know man
Wild wild stuff
It is
To know that this is the government we deserve what America has come into it like look
Idiot
Here you go
Idiots run the Asylum now and we're all like
F***
They're not good at that but you know you know what
What super telling to me is that like
Pretty much
On board with Trump
For the most part
If it wasn't
Except for Shep Smith
Has become
Heroic for being like
Hold on reality
You know what I'm saying is if it wasn't
Ratings advantageous
That wouldn't be probably where they go
Curious version of
Support
For this
Crumbly Administration is Alex Jones
And when you look line denial then when you look at it like that he's a guy who's
Perfectly happy to get wasted and recorded 20-minute video of you
This is great
That should tell you something running distraction for you is wasted
Pizza
Magic State of Affairs if that's your propaganda
New Yorker without
Into whether or not he was on record like
Comedy
But one that's going to get us all killed it's
Well we got to go some way might as well be comical
Might as well be hilarious clip Alex
Get back to
It's not a lie that you have been convicted
That was going to be the one thing I gave him credit for
Already been convicted
Trump is clearly on by Putin
Christopher Walken
I know he's not clearly
You can't keep a hold of it it it it's a slippery impression
PV football player
We have
That's not true
Clearly this man is
Futuristic Clueless
Literally possums coming out his ass
Literally
Okay
Picture
Still going
Monkey
Popcorn
They come back from break
So you start to quit.
That was the moment
His impression just slid squarely into
Clown
I don't give a
He's f****** wasted
When he started doing that about halfway through his like
Cut it right here
Put it on the internet this
To f****** go right
Raise the bar still further
And we got
The pivot man from the
It the clown by reference to the Nigerian state
He got tricked by that
He's so obsessed with it
It has to be it has to be about himself
Everything is about him
I think that there's no other way to look at it
Like
I lost my
My shirt
Disease
They said President Obama
New new pet
Turn
By the night
You think that's what made him go crazy he's a Nigerian scammer
Okay
You're not going to get this Nigerian
But
You're a great scammer to
Game recognize game
We're trying to get into the supplement Market on your way
For a long time I've been trying to figure out is like
Good luck you will Forza very little
I've been trying to figure out those various like sort of pivot Points
If you look through history of Alex Jones
The terms as like
Find something weird
A I am that might have been one of them
Lexia prop is one of them at some point 3813e started selling supplements
That's clearly another one but you look back further you got tricked by the Nigerian
Actually I think you just watch the movie Coming to America and he was like oh that's like being tricked by the Nigerian scammers
Also to the chat room I know that the clowns name Pennywise but Alex always calls him It the clown
A daughter of who his naming conventions Iceland
So if Preston was that you're wrong
Clearly the Russian Salinas electro-pop top officials
We have
Now we'll give this present
Permission
Rosenstein
Chords
Gingivitis
Who's this guy
American call me if you want
What was unemployment
Rosenstein
BFDI
Wait was he
I don't know this character is
Very difficult to pin down although I do know
From the literal end of this episode
I know what the character is
Does Alex Jones
Seaside Park
I'm not Alex Jones I'm black
Rod Rosenstein Hillary operative blah blah blah that's
It's really funny to me that about all of these like
Economic benchmarks that
Trampas
Achieving all of it if you look at
Continuation
You recorded this
That's when the Dow Jones
No like 626 points
Oh there it is the mark of the beast
So when Alex is like talking about the market doing really well there's a reason to believe that
Means possible who knows what's going to happen
The biggest fall since
2008 or whatever since brexit
Yeah so I don't know all those arguments or to fall flat
Who cares
That's an interesting point this is it this is an important point
I don't care
About the stock market
I don't want to hear about the stock market ever it doesn't matter
It doesn't matter
It's not it doesn't change the stock market has gone up for
For how long in a row
Has anybody's Act
Virtual wages
Some people
Billionaires Walmart
Tricks
You're being
Strict Walmart work
Use the thousand dollars that gave you
For my union and then f****** get real job
I know
Would come down at Asner
And we need to get off the f****** gold standard
Alex lays out the exact kind of danger that were in
Care about the stalker
I understand and uses
Oh this is proof that we're still doing good
It's just as frustrating to me is whatever they talked about it instead all this is proof
We're doing bad or whatever the
It's the fact that
By god dammit
Fair enough
I don't know what to address in that ramps on the lettuce
I would like to doesn't mean
Just a pivot away from your
I don't have anything to add
Hillary operative
Israeli Talent
Because that
Indicates
Piano
I think a lot of people in this world
Everyone who is a trump operative
Right
And that that's how everything works
Person who leads democratic
You know X Y or Z
Figure I got Obama operative independent agent
Everybody is always working under me
And that means that there's clear
Divisions in sides and it's like an army
So if you have somebody who goes against
Then they are not operating in their own best interest or or what they feel like they larger interest if it's there
Reason
Treason
Rosa
Pretty much
Mueller is a republican itself
A Republican
It seems like it that's why Alex Jones is the perfect person to be the
LakePoint man for this propaganda
Because he doesn't give a s*** about
Democrats or Republicans
Kind actually does
But he's able to say any Republican I don't like
They're just globalist
Democrats are there's a couple of good Republicans
No good Democrat
Lump in the Republican with a Democrat
About the danger
Let's do it
Take tolls
Donuts
Alexa
Blueberry loquacious made man
This is
How did you still try to make this work
This is right around when I was like
This is embarrassing
Holyshit
S***
Like this is something that I would be like
There's a video making millions of dollars B propaganda
Someone's Secret
I think of me rambling
Terrible Mafia pressure
Dude
Hush money time
Now that Alex
Is the perfect man is because
You can't embarrass
You don't win
Well I think it would be embarrassing what eventually when he goes to rehab
Help
Hiccup someone my maker
Crazy to live
Anyway
Like I said
During that clip that was when I was like
Impression Trails out
That sort of thing I was like this is this
Is really unfortunate situation
This is where I was like
Holyshit
This is a mic.
Why are you doing that
I feel like I said he was drunk
Cuz I wasn't really paying attention to the table
Glass cook number 10
I'm tired
MSNBC
Lightning suck if you want
Future American
Tavares msnbc's Union
Going to take you make you all along we gotta run your life
American flag
America first
Excuse me
Holyshit glimpse of like the real Alex Jones
Angry angry I see myself you're a little more eloquent
Get funky
Knox
Character
That's the real you know I think
To some extent by the
Excuse me if you realize it
Pasteboard czars dafuq
Who gives a s*** no to be fairy didn't put her in that
Is anything wrong
V
Christian point of view would not be fine with any
Regardless
What's the talk about like the arosia no values and stuff like that
Look no further
Like think about that think about how you talked about how good the globalist
Erode the family and religion and all that stuff
Look at what he's doing
Looking with looking to have
I don't know like three wives
You know
They want you to have multiple children
And they want you to get divorced multiple times
Let me tell you something about interest
You charge
Okay
The s*** okay the other than global
Maintaining a kind of faithfulness to your spouse
Globalist hate that
So then you definitely don't want that
They want
They want to make sure that everybody's treated don't want a president who doesn't
Give people fairness
They want people to be on the up-and-up
They want somebody who cares about them and their issues somebody breaks the f****** first rule of Jesus's
Follow me in the f******
It's easier for a rich man to get through the f****** eye of a needle anyways
Christian president
He's the one
From the top do that again but in a mafia
So this f****** guy also has a weird stereotypical Jew
It's going to slide into a little bit.
That comes with the play
He's too drunk to keep his oppression scrape there is no doubt about that but in the talks about the economics
About Brooklyn hold on hold on
Trump is so great about
Recognized
Is being recorded on the
Literal day that the stock market crashed
It hasn't years
Frightening
Billions
Travolta
Again there at the end is it
You remember that video that went around a David Hasselhoff trying to eat a cheeseburger
Propaganda version of that to me
This is where Alex Jones daughters
Should show him this video if you like
You need help
F****** help
You're a major public figure you can't do this stuff
This is this
Underlies and and hurt
Your credibility
Another word for the Baywatch remake
They were never going to put you up because
S***-faced on air
Absolutely
You need to lose 40 lb
To take more supermodel
No doubt about that
Is more or less just sacraments of the 20 minutes
Cuz he's I like to give you a full picture of rain
Text keep pivots from this economic nonsense
Into screaming about his perceived victimhood
You son of a b****
Vista impression starting to sound familiar
Conspiracies and propaganda
Real real quick at least no one else
Call Toys R Us
But unclear
Connection with the Kremlin
You did say on your show that you have
Intelligent
But also he's misrepresenting this Wall Street Journal article
Come down
What they're suggesting
I'm not sure actually a hundred percent
Having suggested videos for things like Alex
Two more credible content
That explains what he's lying
So you can watch the sidebar there be like
What this is really about
That sort of thing
That's effective
But it's not censorship it's more like
People actually trying to take a proactive stance
Against your b*******
Relics
Ethan
Silencing
Free Speech it's just letting people know
This person is f****** lying to
That's that's next week
There's nothing to do with the argument has nothing to do with free speech
Or the 1st Amendment
Sing like that the argument is
Why aren't you letting me live in the world
Brightright
And its people into believing my s*** for this long
If you are one of the Alex Jones listeners you don't want a video coming up that says
You believe is right
While they're watching Alex Jones
What they would say
Think is a
Literal example of why Alex
Is right on the side
And you just have like
These fact-checking sites
Fact-checking videos
Some stuff like that whatever
Or the new bad guy
Cousin Alex Jones has had them trying to take out
Snopes and PolitiFact
And stuff like that
All you're mad about is if they actually document
That's all that's going on
Alex Jones Show
Bring it down
See this video over here to the right of me
That thing's bulshit alright
MSNBC or whatever the f*** it is over there
It does introduce possibility for us to get a job
If someone needs to make those videos
Anyway
Or if somebody would just like
Two dedicated trolls 2
Put videos right next to his on a suggested video for them for YouTube I got to figure
Yeah that's
Alex Jones YouTube coming for you
Stop the jobs coming back
That's how you dirty shut the freak speak dog
We're getting into Lennie from Of Mice and Men
So proceed victimhood clip
Legitimately lost
The character doesn't make sense anymore we started
Welfare with the anymore
He started in a mafia thing switch to Pennywise
Almost
A vested interest in mocking people who sound Jewish
Next
That's not true
You got to go in there and say we're going to kill him on TV
America almost
Chinese money
Washington Post
Hugo bully America
Show me picture of
Socialism
Google Play
So
What you got
This is actually a new College course that auntie
Teaching
Professorship at the U of U of I C
And
EDD
I wish I had said that
U of I Champaign
It is just
Re listening to that clip
Over and over and over again
And if you can figure out
How his brain went from a to
Alphanumeric over there if you just
PEMDAS
Exercise for a college course exegesis
Trying to figure out from the tech
It would be more riddling event decoding the Dead
What in the
That sounds terrible
At least it is impression you can laugh at it but all the page pool boy
I almost wanted to put up like
On the wall like
Pictures of his idea tie string from what it like a serial killer
Your killer just being like
How did we get
From here to hear what is going on here connected and why is he sounding like bulldog
Dogs Go To Heaven
Spoiler alert none of it makes sense
So none of it's real
How dare you
You know what he's talking about there with the Chinese funding
Answers
No
A little while back the story came out I believe it was in Politico about
These things called Confucius and
Institutes
That have been started to be
Popping up in
Right there's a number of them that have I think it's like 100 universities in the United States currently have
Confucius
Institute at them
Actually a little bit of a murky
Territory
And that they are our bodies that are sanctioned on campuses
And what they do is they help with
Teaching about Chinese culture and language
Which is a great service to LA
Universities that don't have the resources
For those sorts
The classes particularly
The language stop
Does all the funding eventually shaved back into a place
Swear they
Influence
A little bit extra
22R tides
To like a propaganda wing of the Chinese government Taiwan is a part of
China Tibet is
Performance
I don't feel great about either but they're not like
Funding the university it's at these universities have allowed them to operate
Little piece of the University
Right not like they've taken over the University or the Communist Chinese or even funding the University
Is that there are these cultural centers
That are all
Connected which again
Automatically problem with my issue has nothing to do with the government
It is
It is just like if you were reading a block or so
Something like that
You should have sponsored content
Clearly label
Right
So if you're getting a
That's awesome but there should also be
Sponsored content
From people who want to make sure you only know their picture
Even as innocuous as Justine
Language
May seem their opportunities for you to eat
Confused
Lance Stephenson
Back in Mandarin
I think that that's something that probably merits a much larger conversation
But it's not with Alex Jones is presented
All of the universities are funded by the communist Chinese
That's not true at all
Most of them
Major universities don't have
Kind of smaller colleges
Is there a bit embarrassed
Universities that I remember in this articles
Specifically reference through like
See
University of Iowa
George Washing
St.Louis
There aren't
There are
I think it's mostly in smaller State schools and smaller
Famously George
What you doing
Right there's a lot of
Lexus
Erschools cuz they already have Chinese culture Department
And they already have Chinese
To offer those courses
Where is the
Assertive stick
Advertising
Right right
Attached of carrot is
Right because of that I'm against it but I kind of understand why
Exist
I think we need to have another not profit
If it was
Independence
Source of funding going around saying
Here we need more people to teach
Chinese language in Kyle
That's great
If it is
Gerbils
Chinese propaganda is he still alive
That bad
Yeah and it's bad
I've seen is that sort of
The point of our podcast
In good
Since being favored of the
Confucius Institute
I see the bigger picture of them
And I know that it's not
Really for me to decide whether they're good or bad I don't have enough information
The people should be talking about it and I think that
Sponsored content and like I said
Has just recently come out in terms of reporting on it in Politico
I think that the conversation will grow over time
As more information is found out about
These places Alex Jones
F****** stupid
Is Nex-Tech
Is even worse
How do you tell if a chicken
Just like Mom Bismarck said
First of all that's not the quote
It is until he said you suck
It's kind of a tell whenever you're like God loves America and Americans children's
The drunks you fox
Your
Two of those
Like the third
This mentality though
To justify their
Ignorance
I want to talk about more is that this idea
Things that he doesn't like or that he disagrees with
Anime
Cuz we only have to go back about a week
CNN fake news has been arrested after allegedly
Threatened to kill the Network's employees
Michigan management arrest
For allegedly threatening to carry out a mass shooting at CNN's Atlanta headquarters
A series of possible phone calls earlier this month
Operators
In 22 separate phone calls on January 9th
Contempt in which he allegedly called the networks fake news
And threaten CNN employees of violence
CBS affiliate w
GCL TV reported
Quote I'm coming
The gun you all down
He reportedly said
Quote I'm smarter than you more powerful than you I have more guns than you more manpower
Your cast is about to
Gunned down in a matter of hours
I'm coming to Georgia right now to the CNN headquarters to f***
Gun every single last one of
So you got arrested
Famous quotes
That could be improved by adding you fux
Okay
Ich bin ein Berliner you fox
I understand
You fux
I'm not a crook
That would just do presidential quote so we could go we go all over the place
You just put your lips together and blow you f***
Sophie
It's one thing
To be concerned
With
To do a better job which I think we both agree with
Yellow heartedly
But it's another thing to be like these people are the f****** anime
Does even as much as we hate Alex Jones
In this show
Major problem
But no-one should f******
No maybe you scream about it but
Character
Let's political politically
Bright
You know like that that mentality leads
It's just stuff like that guy going
The shoot up
Aspiring
Alex Alex exemplifies the enemy and that is not
Person it is
The
Bring
Railing against railing against
Is the people who take advantage
Of this
Fly in the human
Mines
Processing
Yeah that's really we're going
Send we'd like to
Like there should be a bug patch
First human
Download a patch processing system to get them past all of this s***
Free virus software
We're talking about just has too many pop-ups on their browser
Click on weird side ads
Navigate to Mozilla or whatever
Everything is going so slow
But if the same time like
I would never call
Alex Jones's listeners or Alex
Anime
Because
That brain virus
They were describing and talking about
In the case of Alex
I think it's too far gone
Personally
But anyone who believes believes
Stuff
They have the potential to get over it over and over again the people
Are much more malleable than we think
You believe this stuff you're stuck there
They are motivated to work are they can change
Quite easily
I believe that
Even if these people are f******
Alex
Is f****** stupid
And he's advocating for stupidity I still
Don't
Harbor Lights
You're the anime you need to work harder
That's what I would say you need to look more into the things you believe
Right because they're f******
Kingdom
If I come dumb
Maybe some of this is me projecting how much research I've been doing
Easily pick a part of their narratives about like why he believes there's a new world order to begin with
That sort of stuff is he
Stupid
Anybody who actually reads the
Site
Wouldn't
Believe him
Yeah but didn't exist at the same time I also think that
What we're fighting
Alex
Is not
Jet
Stupidity
So much as it is his brain operates
A nonlinear
If you
If you followed along with his
Laundry list
Really is just laundry
If you follow along with that you see that what is really going on is if you were to go up to him with all of this
Look into this further
Here's another reference
He's just going to bounce on
Say OK Google
Look into that
He's going to bounce on the next
A focusing on anything
Long enough
To get to that point
Santino's
So he's like a perfect storm of
Dumb enough to be you
Virus
Mentally incapable of focusing long enough well
Kind of antenna
National because
I think on some level he knows that his evidence
Does Quincy
And the tactic of jumping around from one topic to the next is his way of never really having
Stand behind one of them
Because if
He did believe like let's say Oklahoma City was really legitimately fake
Yeah he could dedicate his
Tire life
The proving that
If he believes he has proof
Then that would be
Major
That would be very big
If you would do that
Instead of jumping around to XYZ
ABCDEFG f****** nonsense.
Distraction narrative
If he has the goal he sets out
To do
You know I'm saying so like
Leave the distraction to jumping around
From thread
The thread
It's his way of never having to
Come to Jesus
And recognize the fact
Get the things that
You saying
I mean it's at the same time
It's a question of
Pathology versus responsibility
Like-like to me
I don't feel like he is
Capable of that because of a pathology
Because it is a
It is like alcoholism play the part of his
But it is it is more with the way that his brain Acts
Functions because when you say you know
You could dedicate your whole life
The proving that
The OKC
Saying what he would say to you
So why would I I've got other things too also
Rolex
The work is done
It wasn't even hard
It was even hard to look into this and disprove just a service
A long time ago
Let's move on
Because the next
Sport Clips that I have
I have no idea what's going on in them
Alright baby just have various titles
This is what he's talking about
Where's the nearby
What is ahead
Technician
Information
Classified info
I'm going to get there fake Warren
But they denied they did it prove
Nelson riddle episode Concerta
Security
That is
Time
Brachytherapy after my weiner out there
That's a very serious question
Is there an FBI
I think it's probably a fairly
Majestic Way for him to end this
You suck cuz I'm a girl auntie
TV and I don't have any f****** credentials to be here
That's kind of what are you getting
That was a Great Bernese
Thank you thank you
You know I don't know
MSNBC anchor probably
Pretty decent point that all just people who a railing on abuses of fisa court
It's still all voted 4702 to barre3 past
A little while ago
Nonsensical
With the
Wikileaks ignore all the crimes they committed like
How to tighten that up
Emails but what you actually said is people ignore the crimes WikiLeaks
Just an interesting much more interesting conversation
Right
Beyond all of the dumb s*** that he said which was
Staggering
Even
In such a short. Of time
There are a couple of very good points there insofar as
You want to
Say like
They had to go to it every 90 days
New information
At the same time part of what Snowden released
Prove that the fisa court is essentially a rubber stamp
Whenever is Snowden released information
They'd only turn down like three out of the
Thousands upon thousands of warrants
The day
That's a good point
I would respect that I don't think that the fisa court is
When you're saying that
Dear
Do you need to be very careful because just the idea that they turn down
3 out of 1,000 or whatever
Doesn't mean that the other 997 let's say it's
Does Princeton
Word
Cases where it was legitimate
The idea of it being a rubber stamp
Court is
The perception that you can have
But that doesn't meet you have no idea what those other cases where neither does Alex
That's a fair point all of those cases that
The warrants got issues
Could have been things where they were very Meredith
Any evidence was there to look into some of the cases that were rubber stamp
Can do now that like what released
And you find it
A lot of those fights that warrants a lot of the spices
Fight the warrants came after the FBI
Legitimately setup entrapment
Okay somebody who they felt might be a candidate for
And then they listened in on their conversation
Trying to roll them up
To get to someone higher
Is pretty f***** up
Collar
That's what they were trying to do they were trying to show that the terrorism enforcement was working
Terrorist they created terrorist
I'm going to bed first of all I did
Disagree with
I disagree with that wholeheartedly
But if I were someone who was
Trying to figure out
How to penetrate
Higher Networks
I don't know what other strategy I would
You don't I'm saying I'm not saying it's right and I'm against
Time I understand
Thinking that leads
Intuit
Right
Do you want me to you
The
I get what you're saying I get what you're trying to say there and I think you're misunderstanding what it was they are doing
As opposed to
Like the idea that you have
Hey what you do is you find somebody low-level
Monitor that isn't inclined
You turned him into a terrorist
And then they end up
Communicating with someone
Who is more legit
That is
Bad tactic
It's very unreliable one and you're not going to get good information out of that but I never cared
That's far less evil than what they were doing which was
Closing the loop
Like the higher ticket I was going to talk to
Was also an FBI
Like they were just in traffic
Like legitimately
Committing crimes
To make it look like they were catching
People committing cry
And that's what a lot of is not a lot of
Some of the fisa warrant
So many of those by two warrants have been just
Sweet we can do that
Lego
Problematic
Problematic problematic
Little murkier than that
I think they were probably like I'm not sitting here saying like let's trust Authority implicitly or anything like that but I
I think the picture is a little more complicated than
Then your position and Alex
No means am I trying to say that it is uncomplicated
My point though is I would rather we were on a healthy
Healthy suspicion of
Secretive
Tribunal Court
That can justify warrantless version is much more healthy
Skepticism
Well I also I also kind of agree with him as far as Democrats having a fetish for the FBI in the CIA
Like we should not
Belike we should undermine faith in our public system I'm saying that our public system
Workforce has already been laid
Great
Jesus
No there is
There is absolutely but murdered
Okay I'm going to trust Muller
Because he probably helped murder Fred Hampton
Look I agree with you there tremendous abuses that have been carried out by the intelligence community
Believe the answer to that is some sort of oversight
Some sort of reform within the process
As opposed to outright.
Just dropped an outright demonization of the people
Who took just because you have the examples and I'm not saying it's just one there are many but like Fred
That doesn't mean that there isn't other a very important work and it's done by people
Within those organization
I don't know
I think reform
I think civilian oversight
To some extent
Is Meredith
Could be away some of that could be implemented
But I don't know how you doing
Solution-based
I agree
That is where you and I agree
I'm guessing Alex
This point of view on how to solve those abuses is not the sea
No he wants from the chat room Vietnam
It looks like
Galaxy
Train that Amtrak Collision being false flag
You can
That's an interesting thing
Why is Mueller has to know
That
Vietnam lasted
How many years longer
Just because Nixon wanted to
Win re-election
Write like
You can't be
Be the FBI director not know that
Right
So he lost many years of his life to Vietnam
And yet is still a republican on down the road
That
Yeah I don't know I don't unpack it looks
The bottom
Probably this
You think he'll take care of the country Integra future or this stuff suits
I want to know what the
Rosenstein work for Hillary
Present route
I don't know
President Roosevelt believe
Stupid praetorian guard kind of thing you're saying about Mueller
Couple months back
All this
I don't know man
Information
Comes out
Itself look
Kind of embarrassing cuz
The investigation.
Predicated on the Steele dossier at all
Seems like
There were other things
The triggered it
From
Things that Carter page public Papadopoulos
Email like they might
It had more to do with the beginnings of it
And then
The Steele dossier got involved I'm not sure though
I think a lot of this will play out in coming months
It seems as though even with what they
Even with what's been called like that
Redacting herb you know
Cutting out a lot of the omitting a lot of information they would have provided more contacts
It still seems like it justifies them spying on Trump campaign pretty solid
What do you mean
It goes through a lot of different things in your leg
This would only be unreasonable if you already sis
Expected
A conspiracy to take down
Like oh yeah yeah yeah
Right right
If you become president
No matter what side you're on your life
Oh yeah you should probably about
Probably a good idea but if you're already convinced that Trump is
Under conspiracy
What's the the sort of track has been laid by the axis of the world and what have you
Here's another ramble I don't know what this is about I have no idea
He's drunk
America's wedding
We had America Underwater
Guys were rolling back bubble coming out
Super Facebook
Noodle promo family
Euro promote churches
This is embarrassing
Hold on
Disagree
That was
Beautiful instance of character work cuz there was a journey
Tremendous it was
I mean there is pesos
I have not seen better acting out of Alex
Franklin
I've seen a lot of professional place
Not as good at acting
Will get respect
Anti family stuff here towards the end of the
Episode
Next live show we're just going to open
With a transcript
Of this class staged readings Tire thing we're going to have some but we're going to hire a professional
Probably he's gettable
Be great Alex
If we do do a show in Austin
That be great title is just Alex's too drunk to pay attention
I wonder what that mean
At this point
44% of the country doesn't trust the FBI
We don't trust
Hillary Clinton
Daffy Duck
Another place where he and I agree
I mean
Crazy
Know the facts
Titanoboa decision at all
I would rather watch this than Rosencrantz and
Interjet
I hate to say like people should go watch something
Does Don but Chula Vista
It does add a bit to it like a video of
He's doing like weird faces at the camera and stuff he's f******
Tanked what is this
He's playing the game that he plays a lot that I think is one of his greatest skills and that is the hinge word game
The guy says
Define the word to him
Much like I do with transmission
But Alex
You will rant
And it doesn't work
Speaking of fueling rants
A little bit
Antifa
Penis game
Didn't need to be people in the street
Alex Jones live
Overthrow
Embarrassing
I want to talk about what he's talking about this is just realize
How playing this would make me super uncomfortable
It's me
I don't want
I don't want to kick
Kick him when he's down
Saturday morning today when were recording this
I imagine he woke up hungover
What did I do
2000 views
Oh well no way let's pretend that didn't
Here is why this is
Have you ever read the comic book
No or seen the TV show
No
No dork
Go ahead
The reason that my mind is because if I understand the mythology correct
The legion
The demon write Professor Xavier
Sun okay
Charles Xavier son
The most powerful
Bux-mont
What hold on
All of his powers though or whatever come from multiple personalities in his brain
So anytime he wants to do with thing he has to use the guy who's I get why it's boring
But my point is
If you got this guy drunk enough to where all the sudden all of those personalities are just
Randomly whatever they want to like that's what Alex
There is no out
No there still are not looking for Alex we're looking for whatever part of Alex's brain to shown up on any website
The core
Legion has even taken over by Lee
Form ideas of trump being involved with Russia
Because
Discontinued
Texas
American troops on our supporters
Fuel station
Newk's
It's cuz he wants to give them free energy
Little boy
Haven't you ever even seen this clip before
If you watch
Yeah he might
Show the clip that he's reviewing I'm sure Paul Joseph Watson wrote the article or something
Making some s*** up
No I mean I don't know
ICBM
Depleted uranium
Mom them two are the borders of Russia but we are
Now that's a good idea
I don't know man I just think he's he's
At this point
Comedy
He's trying to get in there with his exasperation loving it
Bada-bing bada-boom a I was gone
Vegas is the most enjoyable Bob Hope that I've ever
So at that point the end
This guy realizes that the clip ends
Here is that and then Alex trying to desperately trying to figure out something else
Discover
While still in character
Is Alex
Member of a s******* country and everyone else's
Remember when that was a thing people for a brief second we're like
Is Trump racist
That was six years ago
Duh
Person killed President Kill Everybody
The sjws
You just looked out for a second
Some cells and f******
S*** and call the guy c*********
I think he's getting defensive
Quoting the president
Is true
You're rushing it
Remember
Don't talk about
Family health chart
You don't get that
What's the weather
He said let's go back here cuz he's trying to throw back to the cliff that the clip is over
Something else to talk about
It's like Robert De Niro doing
Rich Little doing an impression of Robert De Niro
It's very bad
Infowars.com
Call developing new Hillary emails
Delete
Deepstate Desperado yeah right
He's reading
Infowars headlines
Attractive to him to cover go to court mandate
I want those
I want those notes
Michael Moore
Stomach
I don't even I don't even care about it like Infowars reportaj
It's so bad that I don't even
I didn't want to look into what the truth of that article is
I would love to just be like
CareFirst
Spin in Forza put it on it all I care
About is
How Alex Johnson
Tutu reference
The most important open mike eagle
Open mic
Lyrica
I looked up
What Lena Dunham said and I shouldn't have is how I operate on most
I looked at what Michael Moore said and I shouldn't have
Most Alex Jones
Headlines
Sometimes they're good opportunities for education
S*** about
Especially
Don't care
Let's get to this this is the last
Hard yes
So I don't know I couldn't find a place to cut this clip
I couldn't figure out a segment or anything like that so we'll go in the middle
He starts by talking about it
Representative
This is really more about the impression
Joy Reid
Trump using the word
Oh my God.
Stop
Church in America
His commitment sadly
Call Trophy
Nationalism
Scout
Oh yeah
Launches back to the
The other Bernie
Joy-ann Reid put out was
I made her point
Correct all the all the
Tropes
Speech were very
Civil rights
Era
His behavior does
Consistently the rhetoric is very
Why are we still talking about right
To me is like
Okay but what's fun is
Paul Joseph Watson wrote this article on Alex Jones is covering it
On this drunk Rambles
And if therefore
Pretending it can't handle the word family
That's not really
Well I remember
I remember reading something about
Liberals were triggered that Trump said the word America like 85 right
The point is
Is this is a dumb thing to do mission of the forest for the trees
You're pretending
The complaint is that someone said family
Isn't saying
All of these trips that he's hearkening to our from era that is no longer here
Anymore
Families don't exist anymore
What I
Like the thing that I
Constantly think about
With all of the
Constant
Like borracho
Here's the new
Sing like obviously it's racist
Like the whole Russia investigation like that's not going to wind up with Trump being indicted
Jail or even most likely impeached unless we genuinely retake both houses
Of Congress
Hopefully we'll be able to
The whole problem I have with all of it
Is that we already have enough
He should already be gone
Worse
Airport
New news
Really f***** me over because it's like
It's like it supersedes the old news
No no
Profiting off the presidency
You're missing the point
You're missing the greater point that is what
This Administration
Has been able to do
Is a large-scale presidential version
What Alex does with his narrative
You know there's all this terrible stuff and then they never gets proven then we moved onto the next time there's never a consequence
Get into the next storyline
The next
That's almost
Spiritually why they're perfect match
In the chat room
Fatso
Cedar Rapids
He's got to take
Jonesboro
Like everywhere else
Small Point Bernie Sanders
ProTech
You still updating
Sodus Point
Look into your heart
Not taking care of yourself is a bad thing
That I had to boost the audio cuz he's basically whisper
Yeah there's like a
This is real this is the sizzle reel this is
You know the truth
Google account
Hubertus
Fingernails
How to spell peculiar
Strip club
Yep I got it
I got a buddy
Just want to say
White people music
Literally
Buckley
Press upload
Good forget it on the internet
Get it up
We can attach the door is going to move some pills
Who cares
All right now that
8 or 24
Who is sulfur
Can you imagine him
Onstage
Holbrook type situation
This is why I got a new plan for us
Infowars the musical
Alright
That's right
You are a holding your spit take
On purpose
Action template
We gave lin-manuel Miranda
Look.
Alright
We write the best music there's ever been
And we close it with Alex Jones he's on his knees
Soft spot light jumped on him everybody is f******
Because nobody knows what's going on
Beautiful birds
Sexy man
That's his last words
Right
Portal 2 the musical
No I've moved past that
Music
The issue for me is
I want to come back to
Like
The Comedy of it and
The character
It's 2
Consistent cuz at the end he's like doing this Bernie Sanders
This is great
Images
I remember either I thought you said that he's a good man
Nevermind
Nevermind he's a bad man
Exactly right
I guess the character work is more consistent than I was imagine
F****** s*** man
The end result of this
Not really any real
To discuss politics
Because much as it is
Alex
You need to get help
And we just drank a bottle of wine while recording this
You are the problem and here's what it comes down to
Good Deed the recklessness with which he is
Demonizing people calling
Media personalities Vienna
You f******
C********* f****** nonsense
F*** f*** s***
That that sort of stuff
Discount
Doing that I would feel bad about
We do not have nearly the amount of love
He influences people
The fact that he sees fit
To just get
Really drunk
And ramble about nothing
In ways that are
Specifically dangerous
Other civilian
Yeah I don't I don't think
I think
Alcoholism is not
Defined by the amount you drink
Or the regularity that
The consequences
Cuz of your drain
If you look at it through that prism
The times that we've heard Alex
Drunk on the show
I think they're
I think they were very serious
Consequences
The key doesn't
Other
Have to feel it
And
I think if you had any amp
You would recognize
Is the damage that he
He's doing to people
Because of his
And I would
Encourage him
And I would allow this to go on the internet
This is embarrassing
I say that is Alex Jones is sworn enemy
This is disgusting and embarrass
This is a disgrace
It is Alex
Agreed to let them put this up
He's a f****** idiot
You must have
He must have told them
He must have pretty probably did when he was drunk he probably was wasted inside but it up and there's no one there
Alex come on
It's like having a boy King
Yeah
Well you're always
He's living at the behest of the whims of a child
Yeah
In a in a real job
For putting out garbage
Spray fired if you said
This is embarrassing
UB murder
20 minutes
I should impression but you can just cut bait you don't have to put it out
This is sad
We stay in that impression
Most closest
Most people could not stay in a bad character for that long
He slid through three or four characters
At least he was
Credit for that
Pittsburgh
If you guys want to more the show where it knowledge fight.com
Follow us on Twitter
Fight World on Facebook
We found on the iTunes
Abstract as it said by Alex Jones doing
I don't know them
Where do we go from here
Well usually we
You know
Call someone
Selves
I guess I would say I mean I don't go to the fair one
To do but I would say
Alex's Mafia
That guy is
What is kinda
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color