Alex
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
Drones unit is Dan Dan little robotic there from me until
Is this late
On a school night
Well dear Friday
Possibly getting furloughed from the government so that
Tomorrow that's a good point
Ignore other letters
People
A larger amount of people than we have any right to expect
Right at 10:30 on Thursday
Alex Jones
Biscuits
Taste pretty good biscuits
I've never eaten a hibiscus flower
Local flower today I want to I don't know what I want to do
Start with something
I really did I really had something
F*** you know what you know what I
I got so distracted by the Hibiscus I have a terrible time that I
Successful stand-up comedy making in the tens of dollars
That was worth Kodak to
So Jordan today we're going to be going over the February 8th 2018 episode of the Alex
Thursday
Of this week
And I will say this
Please give me a lot of fun
Until it's not
Intros now I'm dreading what's going to happen
That's why we're having some
By the time the booze kicks in will be alright
Where we're going here than Adipex
A lot of unpacking to bummer
What's a bummer when it's a lot of like trying to get to the bottom of what he's even trying to say
Out of context drop from
Today's episode
Sounds believable
People you don't have to scream we're not lying. Generally when someone yells at you about what they're doing or not doing
It's best to take Ty with a very large Salt Lake
Look
I don't know about body language Stillwell
I've got questions about that so today there's a lot to go over and then the shows
Dog sheds very stupid
Going to have to point out that like I just don't have Clips around them cuz
Boys gotta prioritize
Full day quite frankly Alex with a shout-out to
We got to the bottom of some stuff about Alex Jones is
New website fortified supply.com
And actually we should put a pin in that just cuz it's going to come up on the show
But I probably put in a sick
16 hour day
Ammo
14 right now so let's
I've been working on a ton of Alex Jones between that that right up the endgame documentary
That will be putting out in the very near future this episode has or worth just
Mentioning in passing
But at the same time like
Who gives a s*** I just been Googling
How to make a citizen's arrest all day don't think I qualify for
Standing to sue in either it's like I don't know I don't even know the legal process of what to do
Very confused
That sounds like standing so here's the first
Nice transition Donald
Drop if your name come up
With this idea that he's going to he's going to have this military parade, and I just hilarious
With it no I love it but here's one of the problems that I didn't foresee
Alex Jones you got the idea
Some might say
North Korean regime
Just a little spoiler alert the last time America had a full-on military parade 1943
Kings of military
Pageantry on like Veterans Day holidays
But the last one was a 1991 we pulled out of the Gulf War
To give some context it's been
What
27 years also
That's not the time to
I'm sorry where did he go
We're going to pretend this was a w mission accomplished
But
Interrupt
Was going to call for a military parade
I really hate Trump
Because last year pushed
Did you get a letter to Trump
He's gone
Sheriff Joe
Arpaio you're nasty
They are you hate that kind of access
That
If I had a perfect world
We would remove Joe Arpaio Street tomorrow
He would just have no feet
Yeah
There be no wheelchairs anywhere near him no prosthetics
He was just a man
With no fee
Just want to Wally
I feel I feel like a nice down here. Probably be generous
Results for amps for a long time until
Sure is a good way to
To get information out of people because it's been proven that it's a terrible idea
The information you know
So I like the idea of the drudges for a fact
Responsible for this military parade I don't
I don't care to unpack that I don't care if it's true cuz
If it is
That's f***** up images.
Why does drudge look bad on
Realistically the only like
I don't know I ate stuff to WarGames things when people are kind of
Crazy but like
I don't really see
A reasonable motive for having them like a huge field
Dial French
You know what
You win some you lose some
Nationalism
Want to talk about how like Russia has Victory Day
Is there celebrate
USSR
Probably important
The end of WWII
Heavy f****** lost 11 million yeah it's insane
Compared to other countries all other casualties combined I think is the statistic
Russians is probably accurate the all others combined
Counting Japan
China in which case
Anyways militaristic Victory Day Parade
Totally on in line with like yeah that's the piece of history that makes sense
To celebrate in that way
But I think one of the chief complaints the people are making when I looked into it and read some articles
Are the people are complaining about
Putin's Victory Day celebration
The last few years
It's been getting very Soviet
Really
A lot of Soviet imagery is creeping back up in terms of like Soviet
Uniforms being worn by some of the soldiers a little bit of Stalin revisionism
That's not good stuff going on in Pittsburgh
Is there a solid history joke
And f*** you I'm not saying it's not I just
Went over my head
Whenever Sally would kill one of his buddies
If you wasn't if this buddy was in a picture with him removed from the picture
It's like one of those creeps who takes out the eyes
Do you know what else is about
Removing Joe Arpaio
Noel one day
But for now it's about making
Fun of Alex Jones
Brazen attempt
Make money
And so at 8
But I'm going to
Play you this next clip
Commercial
That's very exciting
Listen to Live there's no commercials
The voice-over talent is not out
It is 1
Owen Shroyer enjoy
Every year we spend hundreds of dollars on chocolate
Jewelry
And sappy cards for Valentine's Day
It's time to get a gift
With the Infowars life
Isn't hers pack
Now at 40% off favorite products
Super male vitality and super female Vitality that help boost vitality and energy for Less
You've already taken care of Valentine
Make sure you and your significant other
What are you just f****** take at the polar pillow already
You guys already taken care of Valentine's Day now let us help you with Valentine's night
Unless Florence has a citizen
I can't imagine any point in a relationship where you like
Look we had a great Valentine's Day I love you I'm attracted to you I am very excited for this
Let's both take droplets
Alright
Because the business
Because obviously if you're going to run a Valentine's Day
You put the mail in
Female vitality
Into chocolate
Like that's like one of those no no no we haven't we have historical evidence
Male Vitality pairs with Asperger's
You can actually have it with Suites
Do you like the better about it
Okay
So in between
Race-baiting
They're also like guys
You want Infowars
To teach you how to
That's what you get, Sutra
It's just
It's just to put Recon a Kundalini kind of stuff
The how of it it's
The Y
Dutchbros like you halfway expect the commercial to fill
And with like
Hey
You need to lay some pipe
Plumber like it like that. Kind of birth
Commercial for like
Fly
I don't know Funky Cold Medina
What's what's
I don't know good
We should call Tone Loke
He's a great couple episodes of Newsradio
I don't want to talk very clearly want a regular Cold Medina
I just want to remember
Surf Ninjas
The greatest movie of all time
I'm trying to think of another star can't
Leslie Nielsen
He wasn't one of the principles of the main villain man
Four on the call sheet and then I'm probably that kid
Subway Surf Ninja
Confused
Alex has a distinct
Full complaint you want
To make about the last
College campuses across
This country
First started
Alright
Are you cool
Yeah show me start this over
I'm going to take that as an ambassador for the left
Yes
We're proud to have banned the end I don't think you guys still somehow
And we don't stop you
Non-band anyting
No anyway let's start this from the top
College campuses
This country
It's crazy how days are really quick
Bears like mentioning
Like first of all they didn't say what the college a lot of people through that around
Is there hey now but like at the same time
He's saying it
I understand that comes from this weird libertarian
In place
Of Lights marriage
Specific rights activist and you're not racist you just like I don't want to restrict
That sort of stuff
But it's very weird it's obviously race it's it's very weird for someone to be like
I am against
Efforts to get white people
To not say the n-word so much
It's very weird furthermore
You lead up to that one
If you're coming out the gate with the left band the n-word as a bad thing
Where to go get your already wrong in a month
Quite frankly like Michael Richards
Can't have a career
He's still a f****** millionaire
Work was he doing after Seinfeld
Wellington weather
F****** the same thing anyway I'm going to start it from the top and honor of Alex Jones
It is the left
College campus
This country
That was fast
All God's Children
Black white yellow
Red and brown
Where's the trans where's the
So I looked into this and actually what it's about is a college
College college a a student group that got together
And there's a mural a painted mural off wall of the building
Yeah that has a Martin Luther King speech on it and they were arguing they should
Replace it with the new mural
To say f*** you in the Martin Luther King right to reflect the fact that the civil rights movement has come along way races still in
Incredibly important at a big piece of it
What is expanded
From there into all sorts
Moline group
And disenfranchised population
Answer it was more like an update more than anything else
And if you look into it this colleges had that this mural of Martin Luther King sense like
Something like that
But before that it had another mural was Woodrow Wilson
So it was it was good but liberal band
Who founded the university and it was something
Good and then it's time when we don't know if
I'm at 9 now they like
Having a conversation about Martin Luther King
Conservatism
And
Oftentimes probably the least defensive like
Maybe like
Maybe the most justifiable
Fear of change
Like there's a lot of parking back to
A bygone time of picket fences
Kids it's a good idea
Because if you are if you were just like Innovation for Innovation let's change everything then
You you may wind up throwing away what should
He built upon instead of
What should be
Alex
The n-word should not be built upon
It should be back
Place to start an argument
Right I'm getting I'm getting from the chatroom the trans isn't the race and yes of course not
That for now
Because
It's going to get way worse
Also
Through in terms of what Alex is saying
Is because
The trans Community is a part of the modern civil rights
Picture
As opposed to
I guess
Still was in the sixties but it wasn't nearly as big of a
Like it didn't even at even at the time
Most
You know if you want to go anywhere though
January
Trans people gay people all of that s***
Punishable by you know whatever it is you on
Do you know
There was that there was no except me the Civil Rights Movement should expand
Everybody who's not straight
Because that's everybody who's being oppressed
And
Everybody's not straighten Bridge
And then we prioritize
Black women the most
Okay I don't know why I don't know why it is
Civil rights
Jordan
Prioritize your voice
It makes sense in the context of what Alex
Just he's
Next clip
YouTube
Throughout the first like 15 minutes or so the show
He's rambling about
Gentleman Square
Cuz there's a military parade coming up and there's a liberal professor
Went out inside
He's going to stand in front of the tank
It's a little green Sandy Maybe
But it's pissed off about this he's developed a theory where in
Liberals
Did the Chinese in the tank
That makes
And the ball.
Are the guy
Sure
It makes sense of you
Just let him explain
Coffee on my head
Violence is good against the right-wing
That's referencing was a troll
Who got on CNN
Communist Chinese
Free speech
Conservative Trump supporters
So I want to say one thing really quick cuz this is part of the
Things Clips couldn't quite make it and turn on timing
E-Z-Go
Can write like five times on the Shelf
Borders I want like it's totally fine to fart into a mic
Wait what there's a video of this guy maybe guy in his 50s
O'Reilly in there talking
Millie Weaver
I think it's my life
It's as funny
Little girl flipping off Owen Shroyer
That's something that you shouldn't even mention if you're out
Excuses let that one go because that's objectively
It's adolescent as hell but man
So funny
Himself walked in here and farted into one of our mics
All would be forgotten for the 30 seconds that we would laugh and we would hate on him again
F****** hilarious version of Infowars
Rally in the alley
You would call it a classic if you're if you're in Thibodaux
Alright
Anyway
AK-47s in Austin and won't let me
A woman
Who was killed by illegal aliens
We go to a vigil
Children and pushing
Look on calls for killing cops and cops
Old is weatherman Style
On CNN MSNBC
Earlier
Fascist
So again I think that liberal Professor that he played I have no idea who this guy is introverted
Before
Let's really think that
I think that he might be a little early
But I think he's a little more dramatic than
Maybe is
Required
I mean that is one of the most
Line-by-line examples of I know you are but what am I
What am I I think we've heard in a long time
Think of it
Just go just go f******
Word-for-word what it is he is saying don't let that the left has done
And then just go to Charlottesville
Well there's that that is exactly what the Nazis.
Supremacist have been interviewed on CNN or New York Times
Or the how many times are we going to listen to what
White supremacist have to
To say and then it's the same and then he's like
Will they let leftist on here saying that white supremacy is bad
Please
There's an even greater irony that you're not quite capturing
That is anytime the truck people on the Patriots want to get together antiques
And the only example he comes up with
Explicitly white supremacist rally like I watched a video of Owen Shroyer trying to get into that right
Rally and the rally is not
It's not a vigil for Katie steinle the girl who was accidentally killed by a stray bullet that ricocheted off the
The grounded misfired
Yes undocumented immigrants
Yes all those facts are
Actually have Eric's
Absolutely but the rally wasn't a vigil for her as much as it was
Collection and sounding off
A gathering of people who are really mad about immigrant
And it was it was an anti-immigration
Anti
Who knows
Bruno's the depths of what the
What was really
In the heart of it
But that's what it was threatened with anymore
Anybody is threatening everybody at open carry rally
It's the exact same thing
You can't have it both ways but
Again
F****** stupid pointless Trust
To bring up the Apocrypha
So
Now this is fun
Alex Jones gets into symbology a little bit
So enjoy this very weird
Very
Pseudo-spiritual
What kind of
Okay
Pentacle
Powerful powerful symbol
Is about the upside down and deciphering the energy
Dark energy
Destruction
People
Go in
Warming her hands to the fire of evil
Sponsored
Sponsor of Hazard sub company that helps fund the operation
Shopping cart
So it's made a very crucial error in that last bit there and that's what launched my investigation
Are not in Earnest today
Supply exactly is the first time I've heard him since he unveiled the 425 Supply on
Summerfest 2017
That's what got my brain
Thinking again
Is very damn
And that is
Giggling roundabout
A problem for him
I recommend all of you listening
Go to knowledge flight.com I have an extensive write-up
Patience screenshots of Alex Jones
And legal documents he is operating
What I believe and I
Queer although I don't want to say this
You know as an accusation because
If I'm wrong in some weird technicality
For slander or something like that very much appears that
He is operating
Fortified Supply as an illegal
Elia for his company
Class A misdemeanor in Texas
If he is doing this as a
You could face up to a year in prison
At least that's
Redwood be awesome
But he said on the show like him admitting
This Is Us
That is our website
Getting alcapone on tax evasion charge
For all the crimes that we have
Seen him commit borderline Christ versus like ride
I mean if I were just like
Talkin about
Any other human
I still think that about Alex
I also hate them
So
Prosecute to the full extent of the law I guess this kind of selective and philosophically problematic for us
We do run a business
Even more
Exactly
How much power do the does the left get from
The Pentagon
Spell Jewel
5 joule
It's a national forest
You think of what a reasonable number would be
Salata Jewels jewels
Do you think there any scientist to like try to start a cover band called run the jewels but Jou
Yeah
Probably they did
No
That's what that's a hot Halloween costume
Alright
No
Clearly what he just said was that the reason that he set up the Fortified Supply situation
Probably the reason that we're in
Nation where we are with him
Lack of
Registration in the light
Is to get around Google
Block
Google is not allowing his
Advertisements because
Of course
Well I don't know but I don't don't have it on with the Infowars
You can put it up
Through Google and it won't give them the alerts I don't know if
The
It's a little bit complicated in terms of how you file a doing business as a Leah
Yeah and that sort of thing is having this conversation right now
Will be a little bit difficult for me to explain all of that
And then six hours from now will get into end-game
If you have a business
Is like a LLC or any other sort of business a corporation or anything like that
You file your corporation
Like if I started the corporation OB
Knowledge fight LLC or whatever
Now if I wanted to start another show called
Freezing point
Good's whatever
I don't know
Art pencil drawing
Drawings
Cell
Is freezing point good
Or whatever with the company that I've started
Without creating a business as name with the secretary of state
The clerk of the counties that you're doing business in
And wherever you have an office
So
I would need
To do that
Exactly the same
Now
In doing that in filing that paperwork I don't know if it would trigger Google or anything like that
That is a way to get around the Google block
So that part of it is not explained by the explanation he gives there
But that is the case
I'm saying that that's what he's implying
Well but at the last time he talked about it in December you imply that the reason was to get around map agreements minimum advertised
Prices
Right by sign with his suppliers so his story is even change
In terms of what his motivation for doing this
So I don't know it's it's one of the most suspicious things
I think I've encountered in terms of
He's done a lot of special yeah
But this one's really big and I I really hope you will pay attention and get the word out about this but
She may have a money laundering website
Well that's where it comes into like
Where in where in the round rampant speculation
At that point it does have the potential to
That's one of the big reasons why it said off pretty serious red flags when I started looking in
Into the nature of it and that is the potential for
Taking in dark money under the table
The money-laundering capability
Or just
Hiding acid
That sort of thing could be done very easily with
And a non-existent business
But you're running that has no
Tax identification that has no
To your normal LLC
And to me that's either sloppiness or a really desperate move and I don't know which it is and it might be a third option
I don't know I mean
How many
Someone has to find out though how much money has been run through your your boys like
It's not necessarily A desperation move it could be just
A mass
Revenue stream label it as a desperation thing is
Because the history that Alex Jones has of being on the up-and-up with
Episode of paperwork
Because you do over and over again
Like
The various business names that are used
Prison Planet Infowars
The Jones report even filed 14 that's not even really a thing
Anymore there's a while back
Do you have all that history of knowing what to do and doing the right thing
And I think now it might just be
I don't know
Either laziness
And or just
Lack of oversight sloppiness could be desperation
You know whatever it is he try to avoid
And he's he's got somebody who is going to really throw a lot of money torrent
The avarice I'm not entirely sure the capabilities of it but it's possible that
Through this sort of thing
We could hide money from
He does owe a massive amount in Southold
Sports Authority thing where you trying to create a workaround I don't know
Maybe his wife has standing
She text wife
She actually does to some extent I don't zactly I don't think with this but
With some of her other business
I believe she is listed as a
But you might have
Like
She might have liked relinquish that in the divorce
Situation all over again
When I was looking over these records
Like the searching for various
No Alex Jones related record
County Clerk's Office
Tons of stuff
Can find like I found his marriage license
From his first marriage
Text to Kelly
They found that marriage license
Public
Alright from 2,000
He's married again
I couldn't no married
I don't know if that means if they're not legally married or what or maybe they got a license somewhere else I don't live
I think you still have to have the license
And where you have it
I don't know how it works but I don't even believe
Common law common law marriage
Anyway it is next class says that you're okay with marriage
On this but just because it's something I've been really looking into bit and extensively today
But the bottom line is something
Something is up with Alex's businesses
Someone
Smarter
With more access than us
Really needs to look at that
Borax
Exactly
More
Call only sponsored post
Chances are he was married in international
National Waters
Admiralty admiralty comeback to admiralty law
Alex
Of this show
He was pretty
Staunchly in favor of the military parade
You know why
Because at this point in the day Grandpa would come out and say that hey
Well I will support the military parade
If Trump brings everyone home from Afghan
Beyond the word
Nice
So Alex now is a little bit that's a little bit like the liberal professor
With
Like
Your little grandson
Grandpa's principles supposedly is for
And so Alex I think is real
Much like the Ghost of Christmas Past is reminded of the principles he once had
Bootlicker for
Aspiring authoritarian
Music
Should I got to get wishy-washy about this
You Force bases around the world
Cut the
But
Also known
What is a military parade
Did you hear what the name of his new product is
Icarus
Creator of the labyrinth
Play The Minotaur
Dungeons &
Extend past just dungeon dragon
I've heard that it's not appealing for a pill
Let me give the image in my mind of Icarus
That's the thing that comes chiefly to mind and of course
Icarus son of Daedalus
The Dallas created waxwing
In order to to fly
Is Alex's next product
Waxwing
Valentine's Day
Only sponsored post is killing
Tonight
The point is is a terribly named product
Very terrible very terrible
So I want to make a run down of before we get into the rest of the episode of some of the
Narratives that we will be missing
Just because
Nice little what got cut segment
Yeah Borderlands
Discuss the Victory Day celebration that stuff
Joseph McCarthy was right we aren't that on this episode and it's based on Russian
Files
That have come out
Russian files McCarthy
Alex gets really defensive because the Dow Jones went down another thousand points today
Sure
That's fun
He gets really mad about Elon Musk shooting that car into space
I mean
That's a legitimate grievance all because at the Staunton bulshit what have you
Gil Scott-Heron whatever whatever elonmusk did that
Elon Musk sent a f****** car into space
Butt acne
Not as good but Alex
His take on it is like
This is a ritual
This is evocative of that movie
He and I robbed you created like a little Special Report where they at
They point out that there's references to heavy metal
And as they're discussing that
The car
I turned
Beyond the Blackboard
Which is a reference to
Alex
Reference
Aren't those really dumb
That's that's
You stupid just one thing to say on the parade and I wrote about this today but
I am off
Thanks for this parade
And I don't want anywhere you say everything I would I just want everybody to watch this parade
Because
In America we will all be like
This is
Dentist
Sad at the lake parade that they had with all the empty bleachers
Imagine imagine being really terrible
Pomp and Circumstance
Some of the people who are just like I don't support him but sport threat
You get you get those little girl singers in the American flag
Stuff I got screwed
And so let's leave
This one guy
Matter
I looked into it it's nonsense
This guy testified
Not under oath and a without a transcript
Great that Hillary in the uranium
Sirius Fox News The Daily Caller and all that s***
Rose's doing s*** all up in the
Adam Schiff
The other that is Senator was they there
Said they talked to the Department of Justice
Like this guy is not credible
So it's man from the Iraq War
Also not trustworthy
Or the serial killer Kuklinski
Is a reserving judgment on this guy who gave testimony
The granted it's not under oath has no penalty for lying
Doesn't really matter who said it but 99% of success is just showing up a hell yeah
Hell yeah
It looks like a bud best donkey
He's just that put into the chat room I'm getting paid right now looks like the furlough is happening
Cheers cheers to that
What are we talkin about
I don't know that's what I'm taking it anyway
Because
This is fun
Alex Jones does not know anything about Bitcoin
True
Consistently been like I don't want to
Because
He thinks
The secretive
People behind
Globalist
Is there something like that get a lot of weird ideas about what's going on with Bitcoin cuz he's never really looked into a door
Standard process of mining
4 Bitcoin or anything like that
I would say you should just leave it alone
I think you shouldn't touch it
On the show he had a Bitcoin expert on the show who was
Expert pizzagate weirdo Named Dave Seaman
Expert rebranded himself
February 4th
But be that as it may guy named Rodger
On
Where does East
Something about Rodger ver
Is David Dum is very dumb ber
He comes on to talk about Bitcoin
And his own saying it's called Bitcoin cash
Dammit
Right
Version of this dump
Because you got to make your own thing ma'am
I don't respect that
But entrepreneurs
One thing that you should know about this dude is that he renounced his citizenship
While back and now lives in Japan
That's one thing you need to know
And that's why the Skype doesn't work until I can play almost any of this interview
Beginning back
Go to break fix up some Skype issues
And they come back with some
Calls
And these calls
Are not good
And Alex
Because he knows nothing about Bitcoin
Handle any of it
This is very complex
Systems
Flying
Summit blind
California you're only here worldwide with Rodger ver
Alex big fan
Just want to say hi
And it's a scam
Chinese damn coin that this guy Rodger has been arrest
Supersonic aircraft
He's trying to push his own agenda and actually take down
Bitcoin
He was arrested for stealing it closer
I'm his
Bkash
Just a fork of the original
Bitcoin
I hope to say one day in reference to misal explosives on the internet
That is operative
You did 11 months in prison for 11 months
Zout is illegal fireworks
I have a little bit of a little
Play songs like cartoon bombs out of it
And a big skull on the front
Office quit but it goes on much longer of him
Just being like everybody else
Marion and I was against the gun lobby
The police
It's all victim s**** all
But Alex
I love that hit this Bitcoin expert is like
Yes
I did sell explosives on the internet
You can trust me with this fake currency that I've invented right and the other part that I love is Alex's
I do not know that Google my guest
So how does it go from there
It should be basic knowledge of this guy before
If you do
Any reading of your gas price
What is it the third sentence on his did 11 months in the Pokey foretelling bombs
So Alex doesn't know what to do at this point cuz he don't know anything about a Bitcoin
This caller is made a point that
You know Rodger isn't really
Disputing that no one is prepared to deal with Alex's take on it
Rodriguez
I don't know what to believe
Okay
No he just said it
What do you mean
Both of them agreed
And I think that's more in reference to the like you being a scammer operation being
Damn right I don't know I don't know what to do
You both sound White
Alex Box up and takes us.
Call
Oh no
Greenwood Indiana
First I want to say it
Well-known
Community that Rodger ver is a stammer and this is his way to scam
And I do have a question for him
Everyone that Craig Wright is
Nakamoto the creator of Bitcoin
But it can be easily proven
I've cut out his Rodger versus response to this cuz it's like cuz I've never said that in public
Got nothing to say
More interesting
What Alex out of his death
He has no idea what
Do this degenesis block mean
He has no idea what a Bitcoin even is
Hello Rodger ver is
This response is really funny
Which means
Proving that he minded the first Bitcoin
You cannot do that but Rodger continue telling people
That this guy is Satoshi Nakamoto
Wichita
Cybertron
Will you release the core
Are you Megatron
So
Book the radio version stamp amount
Yes
Nah dude
You said words
How about you guys both seem to understand what you're talkin about it most of the shower I'm not in for it so
Megatron Megatron
Rodger ver
I am not Megatron
Beautiful
There's a certain Joy coming from
That's great that we could have this time
Goddamn
Are you about to take the
I'm not it's just what we're about to get into is
Bike
A very weird
Last hour and a half of his
It's very weird he's in a very strange
Play send it
Tire leak
Clear like what's going on is in his head but it's something that's unhealthy
I'm not entirely sure what it is
We'll discuss it
But one more thing that I want to bring up is that Alex Jones is very dismissive
Charges
Ex-Wives of
Oh no I don't know I don't know I didn't want to hear him talk about this
Record
Just wanted everyone to know that I'm the show Alex Assange
Oh well you do not know I get you
The Alex would say that
Cambia tu
I get what you're saying
I just misunderstood you for a second
Business plan
Is incredibly bizarre
Totally bizarre
But still
Not terrible
The last
16 minutes of this episode
Are going to be
Just know that right now enjoy this while you can know
16 minutes of Alex Audio 48 minutes
7/2 hour Walmart
First of all the beginning of it makes me laugh a lot
And then the second
No the second part just makes me understand how I
It's Jones that interfaces of the world super fascinating
I mean it just reinforces stuff that
Play we've been saying for
For a f****** year
Yeah
Thinks he's bragging but he's actually revealing
He's dumb
I'm going to split this one have
But enjoy the beginning
How much brakes
The show
By the time I'm 3 hours ahead
Not really tired
I'm more relaxed
Remember the topic I was going to cover and don't feel the same outrage
The real quick that's the first
Part of that
Alex is straight-up admitting that like Five by the middle of the show I was kind of lazy I'm in a Groove
I was feeling relaxed
And I just can't fake the anger that I can the beginning of the show
I want to scream about these topics but by the time
I didn't interview his Bitcoin guy I was
I'm sleepy
I have this I wanted to talk about it look I'm mad about it don't get me wrong
I'm f****** mad about it
I just can't get it up
I can't fake it
That's what he say that's a hundred percent
He's a great actor is performative you saying all of this is like
Oscillating
Michelle which I strongly disagree with
I find that most of the time when he's Faking It the hardest hits in the third hour
That's because he doesn't
That's
Crying that's when the spirit gets good to him right so anyway
The rest of this
Nelly
So much fun
So I know what the media's response is going to be
About me
When I cover these topics it's that
Get that
No this is
None of this is going to make sense and that's fine
Italo
Only time this show is the only time you can say that
Are you speaking in tremendous vagaries and it's not really going to come together for a while but you'll get it
You'll get it eventually
Absolutely
Programs understand
The book
Weather alert
I have
Totally different person
You lied
Children books when I was about 7 years old
Started reading
Adult books
That's not good not the way to go about it
Years old is probably first grade
Maybe Ron about her second grade
There's no way
Vivian 95% of humans have
Even
Higher than that 98% humans
Genetic learning
Erase memory erase memory know I don't add
Four ways to learn like the cognitive development that it's required to even really understand.
You know
Complex dialogue complex narrative
It's almost impossible at age 7
Was just about to start reading Brian Jax's Redwolf
Right by the Lesser works of
Know you know why you don't stay in The Dubliners is a huge
Difficult thing to read
He will never understand Dublin The Dubliners is a hit with the elementary set
The problem is
You cancel actually elementary kids might understand Finnegans Wake alot better than some of the English Majors I knew
But that's more about them
The problem is that like you can physically read anything
You just can't understand
You can't understand that
Back the textural deepness has of Fame can understand
Subjects you can understand
Rhetoric
Those sorts of things
And you really can't
Until
No
Something like for a lot of this complicated probably into your teens
Oh I mean
A lot of people still don't understand the first
Sentence of Pride and Prejudice
I know I do is going
Because my dad loved.
My dad would buy me any books I want
A school rap
Book the occult
Vietnam
Time Life
Looks
Lake magazine
Are they is like the village serialized books
I think I saw a like an infomercial for those
Earliest commercial of it I don't know I don't know what they are
You kind of do even though you don't
My books
Project other super science projects
And I would
But there was just my dad's a big book
20 volume set World War
Idea
Shares rise and fall of the Third Reich
Tabulator so bad
I just get around
This gets to the heart of the matter and that is that Alex Jones read all these things that he cites
Before he had cognition
Understanding
And they created a framework in it
His brain when he was 7
10 years old but isn't mature
If he is telling the truth no I believe that he
Through those books or the process of reading
Be honest like
Technotronic era is
It's a difficult book to read
It's engageable as a thirty-year-old or if you're in college
It's about it's about right
Your ten-year-old even reading that
It's going to take you
Couple months probably cuz every
What does this mean or you won't
Right I mean if you like
End
I mean if you are reading WWII books at 8 years old
If you're reading books about World War at 8 years old
I think it's entirely reasonable for an eight-year-old to be like
Hitler was a strong dude
Oh yeah
And that time.
Play Kenny framework of the world
Sing like that
He's a great character
He's the monster though
You know like when you're when you go back and read that
In reality you go oh look at all of this other stuff
That'll hurt f****** monster is
And if you are from that very young age
Inclined to believe that the strongest
Or the the most
Ruthless
Is then
You get your Alex Jones
If you're reading
Like all of these WWII
Please read 200 books
I mean you know presenting that is being over the course of his life right but it is you
I don't think he's right under the book
But if you if you're if you're like reading a Lion's Share of that bulk of it when you're
Younger
Then
Right
I just I just don't think
That you're going to be able to critically analyze
The Viewpoint of the writer
I think that's
There's a decent chance
He might have read some like
Even possibly
Row
Nazi
Well
Or at least
Dubiously
1/3
Book being the best of the best evidence for his
Inability to
Again if this is true
Which
I have a healthy
Suspicion about
You can you can see from his vocabulary
That he is unable to comprehend
If he had read Calvin and Hobbes when he was a child
He would have a better vocabulary than if you would read
World War
I'm not certain I understand
Built into it it's a great great, guy recommended for hands
I also
Plagued him throughout his life
He functions in the world
With that childhood cognition
Adult
Everybody
He exists as this really Furious
I like you don't understand the book
Because I can go to all of them
And I have I mean I haven't read everything that he claims
Do many of the things that you
Cited
Specifically
I need don't say what he's saying right like a lot of times he pretends that they're prescriptive
Like they're saying this to happen
Or something like that
When they're just descriptive
They're just explaining the
Situation or they're explaining
The world as it is
And not offering a solution
And because he's a child in his brain
He's like
What they're secretly saying is
I mean
Hellscape we should
This is a reasonable thing if you are capable of growing out of it like it's like
Like that
Shittyboyz
When I was when I was like 13 I read that
And I thought it was a shity book
And then I reread it and you know later on in life
And I understood the depth
And the point of views that are are built into it
It's a shity book but it's still 88
Much more meaningful now that I'm capable of understanding
What that guy was f***
Talking about because I don't I didn't really understand the mindset of chill
There's a lot of stuff that you
Right right
That's one of the interesting things about as your perception
You'll find that the book itself
Absofuckinglutly yeah the only thing
Steppenwolf the best book of all time
Even in my life
Are you okay
Just thinking about
The other book I was going to do an audiobook up
Automatic LS3 lean is
Boyfriend wants to look into it
So terrible but next clip
Alex
Makes a weird Claim about Hollywood
That's a good enough
People
And none of them live in Hollywood and I don't want to be anywhere near it and they try
Everything they do is a hit
Christian conservative Patriot
That's what America wants
That's very cool
Convenient
That's convenient
You know for somebody who loves to give example
No course not cuz it's a nonsense thing
Hollywood Patriots hoodie talks about there's always
Is Jay Leno
Tim Allen
He brings up
A large group of secret
Conservatives in Hollywood
I don't really care about that cuz I don't care
Cuz there's a lot of very powerful conservatives who are out and doesn't really seem to be that much of a stigma
Rock already revelar
Revelation
But even just on a on a very specific level
It doesn't change how I feel
Think about the Rock
I don't think
Anyone cares
Unless
You are let's say
White supremacist
Right
I don't believe that this this this Mythic
Secret society of conservatives in Hollywood exist
I'll believe that Alex has talked to them
But it's so fun it's this game against the play where is
I have this secret knowledge of these secret conservative and guess what they're the most successful
Left Behind series is bigger than Harry Potter
I'm still want this f****** wizard b******* you know that the Lord has said that you should
Witches
Totally absurd
How many he does actually have
One Pivot Point
Hinge
To his a Hollywood ramblings
In this episode that I
Agree with him on and
I'm not going to
Dispute
And that is the one guy is a piece of s***
Not going to reveal who that person is
Because it's more fun it's going to be who it should
This clip is going to lay out who it is
Galax forever to get to
Free beer things I've ever heard
I don't know what Alex is talking about in this clip and we're going to have to analyze this a bit but the
Conclusion I will be taking
Extensive
The conclusion of who doesn't like
I agree
Check your pregnant miscarriage and have it done at your place with your people
But everybody can say that
Decision
16 years ago
I'm not normally a vengeful person number for the undecided
So hold on
Hold on
What was 16 years ago. I think he's accusing someone of kicking
His wife down the revealing that he kicked his wife downstairs I don't know what's going on
It's one of the most terrifying
W2002
When I first heard this I was like
Well I mean it was right after work
Right is a tough time for everybody
I thought could easily end up getting threatening towards somebody at the end of the clip and I thought like
2002 is probably right around when he might have still been working with linklaters
That's possible
Spoiler alert it's not like later
The f****** thing
Is he literally talking about someone kicking his wife down the stairs and causing a miscarriage to try and frame him
What the
F*** is he talking about
His Burrows was Juanita we don't want you to scroll down scroll back a tiny bit so you can do that again
Because that's so weird
Decision
16 years ago
I'm not normally a vengeful person I'm a forward I decided just now
Walking Track
We'll see how you do when I drag your ass out the light
Because you're never going to get away with what you've done
Engaged
I think
Piece of crap
What is worshipped in Hollywood
Because he's a degenerate
Filthy scumbag
And I think it's time
We have
People on
Tarantino
Oh yeah
So I guess that
You did a note just came out
The audio is revealed of him being like
That girl votes
Nothing yeah
Monster
Surprised by that either
We didn't know
Yeah that sounds right
For us
And people who work
In the business you know what I mean like for us
No...
Yep yep yeah it's about that
Like we have no idea what people personal lives are monstrous
People
In character
You know who are actually awesome right you can take a long list of like
Professional wrestlers wear the classic heels
Who Behind the Scenes were the sweetest people in the world you know
Their whole public perception Persona is like
I cheat and brutalize people and beat them to beat them down
The opposite is true is like traveling around doing doing enough shows with Queen
Comics
Total end your life
You're a f****** monster in real the time the time
It's so there's there is that like
That
Sensitive like
You don't really know from the outside
That's how I felt about Quentin Tarantino for a long time
I'd heard something
Really been thrilled with him
Suck it
I like some of his movies
I think some of them are sophistic garbage
I think Alex's
Film criticism is even
Knock knock who's there it's it's
It's within the realm of okay
We agree with Alex bring the troops
I'm more concerned about the idea that Quentin Tarantino
Kicked his wife
Alex's wife
And if that's the case
I want no way more about that
Yeah
Nothing about it
Say 60
Years ago
If you weren't
Referencing
A specific time
Your wife was kicked on the stairs you know I think
Most likely
I mean if it's
McKay's the Quentin Tarantino kicked Alex
Which
Ladies and gentlemen
You heard it here first by the way I told you earlier in the show I found their marriage license they were married in
5 years after 16 years ago
Was common law married admiralty law
But if that's the case then
I feel very sad for Alex
Text wife
Yeah that's all I need to know more about it
Realistic realistic
Occam's razor
He was riffing on globalist and what they want to do to you
And then he was like
Oh wait I was wrong
I need probably referencing 16 years ago human Quentin Tarantino like onto a fight
They got into an argument
Tarantino has roots in Austin and
Texas
Or Alex was with
Party for Mike Judge
Or my judge yeah yeah there's no doubt that like Alex is an ant
Another a****** mixes in with an a******
And then they have a fight and no one
That's probably the most collateral damage of
The cake downstairs that's probably just
It's probably not
I don't know
Got it no wife at 16 years
And this is why I want to be friends with Alex
Even though I want to destroy him
I want us to be like a jocular enemies
So I can have it
Right so I can hit him up on Twitter be like Alex you were getting weird what the f*** were you talkin about
I like all know that was just me and Mike were pretty liquored up
You want to know
The day Alex without the trappings or we can wait till next week
And see what comes out next week is going to start taking it out you know what quite frankly if you just
Text Quentin Tarantino down on the Merritt
I'm all for it I'm not really going to fight
Baby
As long as you're not lying and exaggerating for no reason
I'm cool
That Alex
Assumes that
Many of his critics have a dog in the fight right
Oh you guys are going to defend Quentin Tarantino
Well I get watch you both
Light each other of fire I like you loves the idea of
Uniformity of what he's supposed to
Yeah
Be super mad about feminism
But there's a large portion of feminism that's trans-exclusionary
Kinda be into that
Or whatever you know that there are different segments
All of the groups that he's against it's not unipolar right like this even look at our podcast
We're not unipolar
No you and I have different
Like philosophical principle beliefs
Like if Alex was just like knowledge fight is one thing that's against milk
Realistically me and Jordan both
Hate you but
But there's
Nuanced there's differences
Best thing about people with black-and-white worldviews is that they will always
Project that onto everybody
Definitely so if you have a dichotomy you all you will always projected that everyone
Else has a dichotomy as well break
F*** that guy f*** you
Whatever reason with whatever it is I'm criticizing cert
Things about
F*** you on the merits
Unfortunately that works both ways two-edged sword
Who gives a who gives a s***
Kill Bill but I'm not going to like Inglorious
I mean
Now is not the time to get into divorcing the art from the artists
People who are way worse
Hookah hookah
Not art. Are we what we must do now we have one
Segment left
To do of the Goodwin
We're done with the good
We're getting we're going to get into the blitz but before we do
I must take
Quick intermission I apologize cuz this is a late night show
But you got to pee
And I got to be focused
For the rest of this about minutes
I apologize the reality is we have
Wanted to keep my keep my
Focus on point
Like Alex Jones
You didn't want to bring up the the fake energy to be like
Sometimes when the body is
Doing things
You end up rushing through something lose track of the
Which is disgusting things
Contact us
Should be discussed
And I don't want to do that
So
Or you could say you had to
I had to pay
Jordan
The last
Hour or so
Alex Jones Show
Turns into I started with that clip or he's like most
My anger and everything I weird cuz it was like run out of gas
But Bitcoin guessed it not go well
And he's like
I sometimes
Yes
I did go to jail for selling explosive
Fair enough
Isaac I can't fake it sometimes
This late in the show blah blah
Read lots of books.
Come to me and say I haven't
I got a little defensive about that right
Not bragging but his
Historians are stupid
Compare to me don't stop all that I'm at the king best not miss
If you remember when he was getting into that he was talking about like if this is the key
But you never got to it have the keys which in my notes I wrote keys to?
What do they have
Keys to what I told you
This isn't going to make sense and don't worry about it
I know
Here's where we where we get to it
We got a long long clip
Pausing throughout
That is really no edit points throughout these are
Boy this is this is a lot of trouble
Let's jump this is where
Is this clip starts with Alex Jones
Paul Revere
It's weird it's very weird
Know what that's a release aliens
Comparison
Has Paul Revere
Historically is far more celebrated than the female counterpart
Cuz I'm a piece of s*** damn it I hate my
I called you out on it but I don't know
I think it's a valid
Criticism and I apologize
I do too
Well you are supposed to say the trees somewhere that's what he was looking for
Historical diatribe Forest talkabouttd
That's not how that goes
Give me evidentiary information out
Nope
Instead of just being Paul Revere
And
I was there and I saw him landing and they were on their horses
He said the arms arms
Redcoats Atlantic
Why can't I just say that
Well
A lot of reasons
Because
What I say
Mercedes upfront at the North
They don't want you to
So I just want to be clear
I am keeping everything in
Including Alex saying people who are going to cover this
Are going to take it out of context rehnquist it I promise you Alex
I hate you
And I respect you enough not to do that
To begin
Here is what he has said
Instead of giving specific
Historical evidence
Diatribe
Bibleman
Well that's actually kind of
I mean
That's exactly what
That is like a self-assessment
Verifiable
Which he's going to
Continue to do but in a very ugly ugly
Is very ugly
I can't stress this enough
We'll have some fun with it I put this is so ugly
It's in the white papers attend attacks now they're staying at the news
In the fifties and sixties
They're going to adopt in the water
More manageable
Do science of Obama
Holdren 1974
Alex is not read this whole book
I have read most of it and I've read the relevant passages
Do you talkin about
In great detail at read this
Surrounding
Text to the
Contextual
Pieces of it
This is a textbook
About ecoscience
They don't act
Putting anything in the water they don't talk about that advocates for
Eugenics
Not really
Not not in any extreme way especially
You know
1874 Style
Eugenics wasn't really even all that popular in 1944
He's describing the 50s and 60s
If you going to talk about
The deal it was a little bit different than our understanding of
Still
Much much different than Larry inversion
And like
Strictly
Scientific
Neither is great but there's a thin line there's a there's a conversation to be had but it's important to note again
That Hitler's Eugenics was begun and American
There's a lot of that I've read most of beholder
Eco Science Tech
Thousand something pages long and
I f****** love it I think it's great
It taught me a lot about geology taught me a lot about water distribution
Patterns
Okay there's a lot of really great
It's not a white paper in some way it was
About ecological science
And the parts that Albert was written on was base
Alex is taking so much of this.
Will get into much greater detail about this in the endgame
Documentary
He brings that up
We'll get into it
Completely lying about that
This idea of
Depopulation
Is based on
Cool bunch of
Kissinger road back in the 70s
The difference between
Prescriptive
Descriptive language
There's this
Kissinger
Right you know
Criticize Kissinger
On his own merits you don't need to put him in a weird
Situation
Beyond what the b******* like I don't want to be defending George Soros
See the f****** billionaire
Nazi collaborator
In the same way
But the advocate
Eighty percent of the population
Killed
Absolutely not true breeding of things that he wrote Alex is still reading on AC
Braids for 7 year olds
Which is weird because you might actually be able to make a good argument for Kissinger
Being a Nazi collaborator
Like that's probably driver them Soros
The Kissinger had his hands in
Yeah
Clearly Utah
It's sold
Angelone
Kona the big island in Hawaii beautiful Island
Coronavirus video
I grew up in Hawaii
I looked on a wahoo
City of Honolulu
Spent a lot of time on the island
What's a good time
How you doing
The Big Island
This entire episode has been you waiting
To say that no actually when I was
But it's fun because this is an example of Alex like he started the clip about being a
I get into like
Talk about like
Historical evidence and all the minutiae and Paul Revere
Yelling the British are coming
And now he's getting into the weeds but it's not historical evidence or any factual truth
It's just him a rambling
It's just him saying things
Wait
What the f*** we just go to alii Lani high school elementary school also how old
30 I'm 33 did we go to elementary school together
It's getting weird go back to the cliff
M a Pacifica
20th century and the 21st century
I flew here
Largest ocean of 70
Check percent of our land mass covered by saltwater 1%
Freshwater not a 2% below ground
It's rambling on science and you just listing off numbers and s*** like that but like also
I don't know what Red Hill Elementary
I'm sorry
Fighting Illini
Illini is Illinois
Anyway
He said that
The service
8 / 71
The larger the larger point of this knife block numbers disconnect
Acted fact essential truth
Annie School
That yes
You can memorize facts
That does not matter anyway here's my Juno comprehended
The meaning
Do you understand
When
In your life
It's most important scholastically
To Rattle off
That's most important
Thin small area
3rd Rock out from the standard yellow sun
Unbelievable
Compendium
Here's the bottom line
Biological
Cultural
Systemic
Societies and cultures impossible
From Texas regulations
Biologicals
Propaganda
To the
Medicalized
Start out with these words
This is going to be triggered by various words
Becomes Vexy
Becomes feminism
You know whatever it's all just like that
Shout out to John Lithgow
3rd Rock
Isaac
Refuse
Standard
Standard yellow standard yellow sun
Maybe Christopher
F****** sense
The most common type of star
What color is the sun on Krypton
The red
Red Sun of Krypton
Is it a is it a read the whole thing with the Krypton is not
I think I'm not a Superman guy I don't like overpowered anyways
I think
Comic book
You're right. The bigger point is that you rattling off
All of these reasons why having a family is right
Super Bowl
He is Old Town Buffet of
Bulshit examples
He's giving our literal like
Counterexample
Break for having children
It doesn't work
Some of the examples
Along the way
RV
And clearly trying to spell
And some of the other ones are like
Nope
Yeah okay I got confirmation
I can move on now
With your life
I don't
I'm going to scroll this back cuz I don't think you heard the context they're back at work
To the
Don't believe it
You're not
Why would I join
The SEC has 178 words are not supposed to sound radio
Carla
I what
Did you let Alex once interviewed
Bet
Beck
Tell me tell me that you have
He didn't he didn't interview
One of his reporters went to a book signing and try to get
You did not spray Matt the correct what he says
So there's 07 words
Not supposed to say the n word
True
And then now Nazis are bad
There there
Apparently
Frustratingly not bad
Most people
Really cool with you
Really all it is
TV broadcast
Who always
The word
Which
What created
Twenty-something Years Ago by people in the community
Suicide big problem
Might as well just take a break there
I mean
No
If therefore
For their life
Definitely has nothing
It was used against
The gay community
Your fault
I mean look if you want to
I'm in the list
As long as
Words
Gated communities
Have been
Co-opted
This Liars
Exactly
Whose fault is that
Yeah
Probably
Very open-minded people like Alex
Riesbeck's in d.c.
Facebook
So Alex is claiming here is the vice president
Vice president
The Facebook
Called him
You recorded the call
And the guy said he's going to explain
T words
You can say
Baby but what band you if you say that
Keyword
I don't believe it for a second
I have not
Nigh on a year now
And it has been a delight
A lot of people post
That word but yeah I've seen a lot of people post
That was definitely there
Categorical nonsense
Do you know what you know what is RuPaul uses that word on her Facebook page like
Right that's a different conversation
Do not have standing
No
Is that like
I have a standing position
That whatever Alex
Footage of something
And he doesn't produce it I don't believe
He does this all the time
He said he had hours of footage of Megyn Kelly sucking up to him
And all of this is proof that she's a liar
Emily soon as the interview came out and it wasn't that damaging
Never going to happen never really saw that footage
Never needed to talk about
He has
Hecox
Hours and hours of footage of antifa beating up with rally
And all the Deep laser these
Wildly innocuous videos of someone
Maybe pushing a Mike out of their face
You're like
Hey girl you didn't need to hit that Mike but you did
Certainly not in the salt
Certainly not extreme
Please like we got hours and hours of this photo
Never produce
Vice president of Facebook
Hold him
He recorded the call
It's not
True it's not absolutely not true
Until proven otherwise
That is
Indicative of one of my
Largest
Issues
With so much of media attention
Is that
I have checked proven
Consistent Liars
It's not that
They shouldn't exist or that they like
Like once you become our
What you becoming untrustworthy source
You should not be consulted
Devalue people in the mainstream
Paul Ryan
Everybody should just be like no
You're not trustworthy or Peter.
Oh absolutely
Does anyone think
Who's that guy was on 30 Rock
Like I was real phone on 30 Rock that news anchor lied about
She's boring is it now
I'm not
Because he does not
Credibility is still intact as far as I know
There's so many times
Keep seeing
People who have been
Documented lying to us and they're still allowed to go on at like if you're up
King liar that we proved to have lied multiple times
Let me know what you'd listen to you
Yeah believe it comes down to
Two-Face
If you are a good
Liar
Like someone who has lied in good faith
Like you accidentally reported a story that wasn't
Truth like you're in anchor and there's a story that comes up and you reported
Turns out it's not true
And then there's a correction that released it all then
Add Face line
Yeah that is
Hint that that is really what it comes down to
Yeah you know I'm saying like that and that's what Alex does that's what cernovich does that's what all these assholes
It's bad to say it comes down to this
Conti and idea
Of the only thing that's good in life is a Goodwill
And they have a bad will you wish
They wish bad
Anytime
If an oil
Lobbyist show up on a
Can show to talk about
Climate change
It's like no
You're not allowed here
Right because you are a liar it's been proven
You're done
There's no both sides
Science Guy
Turns out he's
He works for an organization
Tons of money from Exxon
Google search search
To be fair
Had to find the organization he works for it I mean like
What it really comes down to attending this is something we talked about
Vaguely
All the time
I think it's really spiritually what we're talking
About
And that is that like
Lot of people are going to lie to you or lie to you accidentally
And it's your Civic
Responsibility
To understand what
Your hearing
Right but we unfortunately live in an era now or theirs
Is enough people with bad wheel in bad faith
Who are operating running around pretending
Because the Internet is is Dutch that you can create a real good official-looking website
Yeah or you can be someone who has enough
Juice on Twitter or something like that and you can get invited on CNN or
It's no longer a place where you can trust the public discourse has
Routing and reality
You have to do you have to look
I don't have to check
I don't think that that is a phenomena
I think the
Now
And it's got a farther reach
But if you go back through history like
Liars about
Meijer's abounded but generally speaking
I think
Things were a little
Before disagree
Maybe
Back then there were other problem
Dogs with like
You know we'll just never tell
Cover
Something very important
Or you have your like
We won't allow the like when lvj refuse to
Because of political reason
What was the quote like
We can't put this out because it would undermine people's face
In the government so much
That it would be destruct
Like all of these different lines or Nixon
The Vietnam War going
F******
Negotiating secret anti
In order to make sure that he could be re-elected
Thousands upon thousands of people died
Justin Nixon could get
Re-elected
Michelle lately
I haven't heard from him in a really long time I wonder if he's dead
Morbid thought
I know but he still
Metro
He certainly doesn't seem
Healthy even
Is this
Timer of life
Is Abe Vigoda dead
If there is a fish if there's the fish of a knowledge fight it's f****** Larry Nichols
We should call it
Not now
It's never too late
Now call
Shout
We've had four beers Now's the Time to call Larry Nichols
They should listen you can stay on
But there's one
And I training
Facebook and Twitter judge in 2017
But you can't say that
The n-word is still
What is
Secure
Here's the problem that I have
What do you mean why did they choose that
I don't care to me is less interesting than the flaw and Alex's logic is like
Why not
If you if you are like no it's a free speech issue
Quote the n-word exact
Yeah exactly what is your f****** problem
You say
Right
You know
Doesn't give a s*** about them your audience isn't going to be offended by that they think they're weird
Yeah but he's going to get a lot of press from saying that
There was an article in rightwingwatch but it only covered
A slight
Portion of the day
We'll get to it but
No I mean it's the old John Mulaney joke
Writing for an award show
And they're like
Okay
You can't
Say
Midget
It's
The n word
He's like
Well
One word we're saying
And the other word were not right so it's not as bad
You know like that kind of thing
And it's not
Like I'm not endorsing hair and work
These words are acceptable or good label
Let me throw this out
Yeah all of them aren't good
It's not good maybe don't think about it
I really really like
I don't
Understand where it
Comes into like
This is this is this become such a problem for me and it's not just because I'm a
Supporter
Trans rights
That that that that's secondary to
Does the idea of like
This is a free
Speech issue
Why can't I say things
He called
I was like
You know like
If you if I didn't know you
I just screamed at you on the street right probably generally don't like being called a s*******
Cancel for saying that
Yes
Take any of those identifiers out of it
And it's all just
So much just so much of these conversations can be boiled down to
Don't be a dick
You know
According to
They're song
All right.
Just like beer
A f****** courteous human being
Hearing what people say
I know Alex
You are hearing it
Inward and don't drop a hard-r on that you know that you're funding
And all of it isn't going to
To dry up
If you drop it in bham
On the show you know that
Right you know that your funding doesn't
Depend on that
You really gave a s*** you just
Be throwing the N word around like
And that to me memes
That your principal is flawed
Your idea is stupid
But
Keep digging
Because
It's trans
Men that want to be with a man and
Once they get you
Daily Caller
This is an article about
Radio thing where there's
Offended
I don't really
I don't I don't I don't think that's necessarily the appropriate response
But also I
I think it's student radio especially in college
Is a q territory in terms of SEC laws
I don't know don't have a dog
Don't care
That he just said that I think is one of the most
Important things
Tackle in regards videos
In regards to the most important
The idea of
Trans people
Want to be
Iron Man trailer
The case
That gay people
Want to be gay
And it is not it is not a
What connotation of like
I am choosing this
Because I desire it
And not because this is
Part of my identity this is worth who I am
I want to be straight
I have no desire towards that that is just part of
Did your orientation
Sidered
I mean
I was waiting I was waiting for that
Cast
Cigarettes
Yep stupid foot
Down right there boy
Great
Goodbye goodbye
Yeah no totally totally the idea of your desires in your orientation
Beating the equivalent Earth are very
Very different because I mean
You shown study
The idea of trying
Change
Your orientation
Road
Peril the road the
Never really does anything but more shame
Usually more internal anguish
Any idea
If you want to take this
Cuz I was going to eventually
I don't think he doesn't
This episode but he always does
Do that
The dumb
I think actually do
I'm going to hold off on this
Cuz I think he gets into the biological stuff later
To me it is
It is
The fundamental
Issue with
With
That kind of
Acceptance of
Difference
Ideas
Exes
You are like me
So if you are not acting like me
Then you are
Desiring something that I find to be morally
Objective
Or quails
Yeah and so it is not something that you can accept as
You are not like
And so
You are you
It's a very it's a
Projection
That I use is such at the heart of all of this
Prejudice in all of this
Hey where's all this stupid
It's like it's like it's like saying
You know what
These black people
Just don't want to be white
They want to be black
Instead of it being something that is
Part of a
Who You Are
Brave
Desire yourself out of
Something that you are
Which I think is b*******
Totally
And there's there's a secondary aspect to this that Alex
Really the core of what he's talking about is it
The ability
If men and women
He's going to dig into
That a little bit
And one of the things that is never charged me about that argument
Is that like
Look at the reality is that no one is ever really shot
Down
Language
They're expanding
The reality of
Piano
Back in the day
When America was great
I know right
In the fifth
Don't even like it
Straight people in the queer
Bright
Right I don't scrape I'm going to let you continue being satirical I get it but
You had you had Tata me back
A bunch of people
Fit into that dichotomy
And they were limited
But
Major provision
Give us yet
Right and eventually those people
Forced to conversation
The language of God expanded
Do larger portion population that are heterosexual
Cisgender
Designation
I don't hurt them at all
All it does is
Expand
What
People
Application
There was
Heterosexual
The negative
Everybody else
And it was it was not
Straight Talk
The back then there were people who were like a plow
Really
What these people think I am is a queer
I'm bisexual
For I am
You know there's there's a
Seahorse
And as time went on
The language expanded
Into Alex's arguments about this idea of like a closes off language
You think exactly the opposite
I think all it does is expand line
And expands
Our understanding
How people
Experience life
Amazing beautiful thing does not
Shutdown
Language
It expensive
Yeah
It's a tragedy that
Like
That he has a
Feeling
You know so much
The tragedy is that like
He believes the thing joke
Counter to
What the people on the other side
That he's against
Are actually saying
And actually believe
Eminently reasonable
You have
To take an illogical and stupid
Approached
Divested
Yes
Who knows what that
But
Find some more f******
Fortified braces Supply
California
So real quick what he's talkin about there they arrest you in California there's a law
The book
And it's about
Consistent
Misgender know people
It's just a it's more about harassment in the workplace
Is not about like
Hey you accidentally call someone by the wrong pronoun you're going to the clink
Or anything like that
Absolute nonsense
And you study eugenics
Hitler Hitler
This is what this is
Rampant misrepresentation of all this
A lot of his will be covered in the endgame
Documentary
Although there is a connection between the early Eugenics movement was not
Westerly racist eugenics
They became a
Humanist movie
And that is
Not at all involved in
Gender issues
But because
Prefixes
Does the sands
Alex gets very confusing really everything
That's what
That's
We got to walk everywhere. Got to walk everywhere
Brothers
Pro-government
Human development through chemicals to biological to culture
Brainwashing
No it's not
Like this triggers me
To no extent
But
I don't show anger really much at all right
I've noticed
Assholes
When they're talking
In the middle of their sentences to say okay
They do that
Okay
In the middle of things
As if they like my god do I say that now I'm terrified I would have terrified of all of my tip
I would have punched you by now.
Like I know I'm an ass-whole
Is like a rhetorical thing
The people who have
Nothing
In the middle of sentences in order to be like
Bucking board board
Yeah you are what I'm talking about
I make it a point here and if you're not okay
It's just
It's one of the weakest things in the world
The one of the best
Examples of a we talked about this
Press conference
Alive show
The
The Larry Sinclair press conference
Like trying to explain away his crimes.
Now that I made that connection like Sarah
Huckabee Sanders
Does that
Condescension
Yeah the rhetorical condescension
After we did that last year
Larry Sinclair
Is big.
From
Sarahah
He wasn't alive
Someone in Minnesota
Who sells gold Jesse Ventura
No Ted Anderson
Chinese based in Minnesota
Chance
Anderson
And
Reverend
Holyshit
Berkeley
Cuz we got a fine
I don't think you'd ever talk to us
Probably bored
He's a rich man
Next episode
That's great news sources it's like that
Rice table
It's not true that they're just showing like
Whatever flashes up on the document
Pedia article or
Some bike
Eventually he's going to get into the Tavistock ride either homepage
It doesn't prove anything
That has to be what transitional
Discuss human evolution
Is the shelter
What you want who you want to be how long do what you want to do
It is a very human thing
To be a man and say I want to be a woman
I wish I wish that was all he
Human
Touche I want to be something I want to build something
Beavers make dams
F******
Pants
Like just a let
Ants rats
Make a rap
King
That's true bundle of rats
Yeah
This is sad like this is
This is like
It's so
It's touched
Funnel Vision
About
Liquidation
Did the totality of Human Experience
Animal
Even like gophers make
Old
There's a lot of
There's a lot of animals that
Now that I'm thinking about it change their environment Franks
Pretty much a lot of
Yeah
Where they want to be 50 different
This woman loves her blender
Weird whatever
Sure
Alex Jones's game enter exercise
Criticize
Understand
Zoological
Ramirez
Ago
40 Years of human animal hybrids
Human human hybrids
Human human hybrid called chilled
Artificial
Artificially made or what is it or does it at rides
You're done right
And that's why
This is a critical area
Mexican women
Once a thief
This is the total
It's not a choice
Sushi
Force directed
Here's where my issue comes in with Alex
Is rhetoric
About like I don't
Alright
Budgie specifically to talk about
I don't need them
Not granted
Very similar to chimeras
It's destroying human race
You can't you can't you can't you can't use this rhetoric you can't use this rhetoric
And this
Analogy
You can't use the
This level of analogy game
I came just be like
Now I'm not comparing them to f****** comparing.
It's not okay
I think the thing that triggered me about
Hold on
It's not that
Well to be fair again we have
Exhaust
To be fair
Killing it in the chat tonight
Vfw's tailpipe it made me so angry
It house veteran of Foreign Wars
Reading disease
How dare you
0 disease is spread
Buy f****** your car
Not taking vaccine
Or by not using a condom
If any
That's what I heard
It's alright
There could be some out there
Putlocker
It bums me out and I know what's
Succumb
And so I don't want to I don't want to get
We're at we're at like
Two and a half hours
And I promise you that
About to get
Really bad
You're back
Interstitial hold music
And forgot to plug my phone back in
So there wasn't much going for the people in the chat room I apologize
Appreciate it so much
Eclipse last
Second clip is I promise you Jordan
Yes literally punchline
Unfortunately
We got this
We went to we went to commercial
Without saying
Manufactured nonsense
Like the transphobia is strong
It's very strong
Like Anakin Skywalker
Sports
We've pointed out a number of things that are low
It gets a bit uglier
In this
Back from commercial
So this will be a little bit more difficult to deal with
But
Live there is a
Blitzkrieg
Wife Against The Human Condition
Artificial constructs
Control
Forbes
Reverse engineering
And then for extermination
That is the admission to the Goblet Elon Musk
Not true
Elon Musk just tweeted
About some guy
You're the last
How to do that
She's a dishy common between kind of know each other in
Probably don't like each other
Again Whitey's on the
Who demands Humanity be exterminated
Do it
The whole trans movement has nothing to do with
Homosexual man
It has nothing to do with
Trans people
Sexual
The very debate about
Someone's chromosomes and biological
Easy Legal
Only works
So now when he was a gay lad was a gay day
Appropriate
From homosexual
Just like no one will say
Caucus
Now that's true no one will say Hawkins
Alex seems to have like a
What I would describe as a warped understanding of
Like words
Appropriate language I don't think
But I don't think that's a
George's Tire
Or heterosexual
Sexual he talks about that like me like
Oh I'm going to say homosexual like
Right right but I don't like I don't like
Any
Gay is bad
Kind of way
It's not enough
Call Juju
You know like you are a Jew but you can also say you in a way that is like
From Zoe Sunny Always Sunny episodes
I mean like if somebody's bit before it does come down into
You know like
90 different
Trans movement
Yeah I was not about
Constricting language
It's about talking people
Which is the second part of what he said
The trans move it is not about gay people and I was like
Yes
You nailed it bro that's a different thing and then he said the trans movement is not about trans people
You do not understand the transmitter
Language
It just comes down
I think
This same libertarian died
Idea about like
I hate the Civil Rights Act
Because I can't say no blacks
Somaya stabbed
Or something like that
Can't say I don't want to run that business
Look at the language of like
Desegregation
D integration
We were against
Integration
They use the same language of like I don't hate the people but I don't like the affected
Has on business right or something like that
Couching these beliefs of like
I love the people they're fine they're great they should be able to do whatever they want but
It can never be said enough
How unfair
Popular
Martin Luther King jr. was totally
People
Hated have killed him
Yeah exactly
Words like the revision of your history is always going to be here oh he was the best
At the time
Even people
In the civil rights movement or like
You're moving too fast
Yeah like it always going to be the thing
Realistically I think that we have
Probably a more evolved
Populous
Right now then
You did back then
Like if you look at the numbers
In terms of the people who were active
Civil Rights Movement
Are people who were on board with
A lot of progressive causes now
I think we probably
Probably have a better
Bulk better percentage of
Which is
Which Occurrence at work I meant that everyone over the age of 4
45 should be killed immediately
What
Feel like it's all right number what it was so I'm not going to speak on it
It's for the show but I can't remember where the Warriors
Thing to do
I want to change
Modelo beer
Wants to
Do that vanilla beans
Model
You can't
Name
Hold on
Is Negril the scientific name for black people
Negroni
That if
If you want t.i.
The scientific name
Homosapien Sapien Negril has I don't know what it would be in Latin
Here's what I think it would be
Folks
Sure
People
Middle School
Wellness
But that's what children
Do
They think
That Niger sound
The adult
Confused
Because they're trying to
Geography geography and they know all the countries
The children are the ones who are like
I have it looks like the n word
Cuz I remember I was a kid
Until Alex is like
He's projecting that
Don't
All of this
Is
Child
Thoughts
Alex
Dial
A great everything in his brain
Is not evolve
Fascinating
How this is
We are lying
This episode
You saying
It all goes back to
Is the keys to
Right that they have
The key is I love him his b******* about reading
When he was younger and not understanding
He still doesn't actually know how to read
I agree
Psychologist
I want to reduce world population
Sure
Who doesn't
Again he's confusing the Tavistock entail
Tavistock
The plan for transnation Transworld
And once you say
Two children
In the fifth grade
Starting first grade
You're a girl you can be a boy
Boys be a girl
You can't say boy or girl for someone else
I'm out I don't even care
This is
Let's move on I mean the reality is like
If people are giving this sort of
Influence to children
It's not
Hey boy
It's more like
Hey you makes it sound like you're walking home from school and there's a guy in a trench coat any opens up
The penis is like you want you want one of these slugworth
None yeah it's nonsense I know a number of people
Who
Come up Tran
Human-like that's how I said
Their experience
Very different
Write to this idea of
The idea that people made it okay which is
Perhaps
The best
Rebuttal to
Alex Jones
Argument
About length
The two of us
We both want
Very much
Be as inclusive
We want our language to be
Azan
Inclusivism
And we still fuk up
Because both of us come from such ingrained backgrounds
That a lot of our instinctively that we're not
Like we're not constantly evaluating that whenever we're doing a show like
We don't have
We're just talkin
That is that is not
To say that we are not
Conscious of it or aware of
It is something we're constantly trying to learn
More about
Well it's a pencil and so if you do say something like that I don't like the way I said
Come up transfer it is not because you are
Just how it came out of
Exactly
It's what it's like
I'm trying to
To accommodate with my language
As well as I can
And I'm not going to be good at it framing sentence
Alright
Friends
And bikes.
No one cares if
If you fuk up cuz it comes
It comes down to the difference between good faith
In Bedford
People only really get mad
If you have
It's comes down to the exact same thing we're talking about earlier with the
Jay
Here's stolen it's always sunny
Are we sure are we keeping
That's good
And there's a there's a market differ
Prince between
The way you're using the
The exact same language
And Alex
He's a seven-year-old he doesn't understand
It could be very easy for
I just I do
In function
It's very easy
Mindset
Be difficult
It would be a very simple action right but it would take
Unlearning a lot of things
I grew up in
Such a
Repressive and
Colt
So it is
It is something that I am still
Like I'm 30 years old
And I have spent
20 of it trying not to be the a****** that my family has raised me to be
Not great at it
Hadn't have been raised
You'd still be struggling
Like it's just a
It's a product of Art
X
It's a product of our evolving
Understanding
It's
Evolution of empathy
It's something where
We are
We're realizing
Experience is much deeper and
Much
More
Wire married
Venom
Yeah
The good old days back when America was great
We thought it was much more
Unipolar or bipolar back then
And I realize that it's
Thousand
I grew up in a town with Five Guys
Like that was that was it
Burgers
Pretty much Five Guys Burgers and Fries
Publix
No I grew up in a very very small town and
The
Experience was
Very limited
Denso
Even even now after
You know escaping that
It's still like I'm still learning new things that I am f****** up
Not because I
Existed in place where those things
Even exist
And God like it's one of those we
Weird curses
Cuz you know those like
May you be like that cursive like may you live in interesting life span
Packers like may you have to learn the whole
It's kind of a curse but of it like it's a
A good purse
It's always going to be on
4 bulb
Always going to be learning
Let's read
If we're humans are malleable we're not
Like
Not like you have to
To be stuck in your ways
If it's
The reality was that like
There were
This movement
Is really trying
And reproduction
There was some
Actual evidence of that in the
References Al excited
Pretty freaked out about
I would like I feel like we got it we got it we trans identities awesome
I agree
Need to discuss
The ending of reproduction whatever you like
Anyway let's that's
Let's do it
This whole trans movement is about
Outline
It's about outlawing male and female
Chromosome
Absolute
He's mixing up sex and gender
Come out like Jordan Peterson
Biologically were born as this
Irrelevant
And now Google Executives just come out in lawsuits and they did that there
What do you say
Child dragon
Maybe it's a dragon
Female
Different from a dragon
At which is
Is not a word
Well anyways
If you would like to learn
And Dragonette
Read Anne McCaffrey
Peterson in the Bronx
Some of his shed
But
This is
I don't care what
People might
Weather like
Hold on a second
Are you saying that billionaires are f****** assholes who should say
I'm on boy
Not should
Do desert
I've been too weird like
Reroute
Said weird s***
I don't care
This year I'm just over this
Just so happens that this one might have
Right
I'm an expensive building
I have yellow scales
Everyone does.
You have expensive building
Building
Ayane Golden Dragon
They are making you cry
Chromosomes
And then the sky's the limit
And then there's
Psychological warfare technician
Suicide of improved in the world
Well
Who is
Psycho
Warfare
I know one dude we know a guy who's a psychic Warfare guy there's one guy who Steven too much
Beautiful Liar for Alex to allow on his paper while is really into
Psych ward knocking to use Aztec Warfare on out
Well
I'm going to give you 5 stars
Steve pieczenik
Warfare guys go home and call your mother
Go Get Your Shine
Tell me more fun
That's also
The very
F****** idea
Cymbeline
The trans community
Is
It's backwards backwards there's no more
Have. Been done
Very clearly
There's no
Like
More perfect
Indictment of the APA
Then trans suicide
And the way Alex was doing it in the way he's about to
Definition
Orchid veterans Farmers gay man in the
No
I have been captured
And there's dangerous underworld
The people that want abused
Almost every quote trans person
You know it's
That's terrible
That's so terrible
It's kind of amazing
Sing to me
That's
For the most part
We took his
He's monstrosity
And his language
So many
Them
Every time he brings up
The trans community
It is
Unwieldy
You know why every know why every time when we have ever heard him
Him talk about transfer
Houston
The most offensive thing
Yeah because you can
The Vanguard now in terms of like
It's not
Like socially
Totally unacceptable to say these things
Right exactly that's why I said the n-word
If he's excited feels like it's okay to say tranny but not the end
Example
Static document
If something that like
15 years
Even
The Alex 15 years from now will be
When Alex Jones said that word
Yeah
If you really want to get into the reality
Of the transit
Experience
Which
I don't think I'm
Fully
Aware of
And and looked into
To some extent
High incidence of
Escorting and profit
And that is
Not
About
Probably it's it's it is not
Well it's it's there's no probably about it
It's probably
Totally
More about
Runaway
Kids
Almost 100%
About
Don't accept
There's a much higher
Homelessness
Youth
Which is one of the reasons why we support the charity we support absolutely
The issue comes down to like
Homeless
Israeli ramp
And that just
Parcel
With that experience if you want to talk about the totality of the Tramp
It's not a joke
That's an embarrassing
Costings
Aventa lump in
The highway
Suicide
Puzzle
You're all prostitutes
You fucken bunch of people everyday and then you grow yourself
That to me is one of the
Like
That's a terrible
Easy line to
To draw
Between how
The people who don't belong
Dominance
Social
Stratus
Exist with a higher suicide rate than the
Isn't it such a simple
It's such a simple line to draw
Of like
Oh
Are you constantly excluded
Surprise your suicide rate is
Like it's that simple
Even like the
The train speed
Does it just go back
To another
Do you like go back to feudal times
The death rate
Suicide proper was higher than
It turns out that historic pushed to the side
Treated like the
The other
End up with
All of the bad stuff
Right
And and
The people who do have all the
Look at that
What's wrong with them exactly
Right f****** stupid
Emmett even like we're not
Just think
He waffles back and forth
In his language
Thank you really only
Villard
People who were born male
Who are actually in
Other side
Are men
Right
Anyway
It's not important
I just wanted to point that out cuz it seems absent
The conversation community
You're at home correct
Totally lost
What's about Lexa
Western
It's all just like
Where you got that from
I think his understanding of
Community probably a lot of it might come
From Torrance
Well I here's here's my
Analysis
And it's pretty simple
When it comes
Two guys like Alex
It is
Ultimately like a
Fear of
Is this lady I'm
I'm trying to have sex
So if it's a woman
Identifies as a man
And lives her life that way
He's not trying to have sex with
If it's a man identified so far
Yeah exactly
The man who identifies a
Does a woman
Then he is
Terrified
Is the possibility that he'll choose out of it entirely and now just
Becomes a train
Exactly comes transaction about about sexuality becomes a thing where it's like
I can't I can't
Barter with
You are not even
It's a purchase in my landscape it's the modern gay panic
Of like oh no what if I actually want to f***
The modern it's very classic
Horribly
Was that one for
Nip Tuck
Show
Watch one episode about it I watch one episode
It is very terrifying
And in the web
Doesn't wanna discuss that
Because they're using these people just like Hollywood
He defends Roman Polanski
Because
Pig
Barriers of family
Because
Now
People would have been
In Illinois just a few weeks ago said I
Certifies child
Not at all
Really simple
Only thing the courts
Possibly debating is
Do we put them in prison
For life or a hospital for life
You can be dry to be in
Prison is it's going to be a thing
Kills himself the first day in prison
I don't know about that
Yeah whatever it's not like it's not like
It's not like quartz or debating
Huh
This guy thinks he's
Is it trout
No one is having that conversation except Alex
The only person who's having that conversation
Just say you're a little boy it's okay
Semantical games
You are one hundred percent for homosexual
F*** you
Homo genius
You write f*** you right terms of
The definition
He's wrong terms of the
Interpretation of like
No one's mad about the word homosexual
Your projector
Sing this on to yourself because
Cuz if the safe thing to complain about
It's fake
But it's safe for you to complain about that I have your f****** dumbass listeners
In The Sticks
Don't have any idea of what the real conversation
You'll never have someone on your show Alex
Who actually ever
Grasp of the issues
They'll just be more Russian propaganda
But it becomes this whole idea to make people victims
Including I want to put Drano in my eyes I'm blind
You are blinded to Stafford way off
It's not abuse
Music
Blind because they identify
As a purple penguin
HK416
Purple Penguin
Science fiction book
Who would come up
Something like this
Trans is good lower population actually
Oh it's so good
Your mother or father a boy or girl
Because
You're okay I'm out
Are you done yet
To anything
Anyting
Dragon
Adult dragon
Using these poor people as a victim
F*** you
Communities abusers
Or heterosexual and homosexual
The whole thing there's the last 16 minutes of audio that we played over whatever
Time to talk
Was
Hey
Drastically
Transphobic rant
I wear any pretend
That I like the people
But they're going to destroy the species
They're f******
Stupid and everyone is just enabling abusing them
Listen
God loves gape
But he hates
Re-ride loves
God
And this with a smile on your face
Cuz I have one more clip
After all of this
That is
Justice vintage
I'm glad closes
At least that's actually closes talking about Donald Trump
No no
He's like
He's like a dog
Like one of those dogs that
What's that
Bernard
Nope that's already closed
This
Navigate to that close
Vintage
Go fuc
Yourself Alex Jones
Been around the block
And
I could have sex with most beautiful women Hollywood
Forget it you know why
Every time they didn't have a soul
I couldn't get attracted to him
Because it was all fake
Let me tell you something
These people have no souls they're not happy it was it was bad stuff
Great
Great so f****** you is bad stuff
No apparently it's in the hot cuz they would have been thrilled to do that
So f****** it would be good stuff
Wait so the reason they didn't f*** him was because they don't have dolls
Yet know that's why he wouldn't f*** them
What so I'm Alex Jones your Angelina Jolie
Hey
Pretty good you want to have sex
No I don't want to have sex with you offering
Where do I get a note
I have your glove life maybe we should have a larger
Exactly
I would say that judging someone is
Having no souls Bangla judging
Tired
So probably indicates more about you than other people you're judging
What a piece of s***
And again
Hours ago but
There is a great
Article everyone needs to put that out if they can
And if you're going to book or Twitter and you can push this out to more people it is in Port
Is that more people understand that Alex Jones is
Probably committing a crime
F******
Did some real invest
Secretive
Journalism
Incredible
And I am hiccup
Oh boy
Let me scare you karaoke style. Hiccup until
I have to tell somebody to go
Mysterio
I think Alex Jones
We are on Twitter at the knowledge underscore fight run
On Facebook
You can go to knowledge fight.com
Also just an honor of our good friend John
Policy wonk John would like to end the show by playing a little
Clip for him I don't know what level he is
The
He's a technical
Designation
Here at the end of the show
Amanat Ali Aprilia someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
Thank you so much John for all your help and everything you're a great dude
Michelle but I was saying knowing very little about
Call throw
Can f*** themselves
I mean obviously it should be
It seems
Implied
Let's make it larger
Pearson
Go f*** himself
I know much about him but the more I learn about him the more I think
Vicki needs to go
Go f*** himself
Holding
Alex