Alexandra Thurston color
To this podcast
And I don't know anything about Alex
I bid you hello
Our intro is
And then
Getting out of the pre the free B yeah it's impossible
Hi
The names of the people I need to give a shout out to cuz I forgot to do that pre-show
What kind of signal could I give you the high sign
Coming back to stretch out a little bit is giving
I really appreciate it
Don't get mad and tell your brother
We appreciate it very much
Oh yeah
What is it like
Do you think
Canada
Miles Davis
It's called
Kilometers Davis
Debauchery
And I love it
Self-conscious
Off the top
Cuz I pick the name of Shannon
But the spelling makes it
It's shanin but either way
Whatever however you pronounce it I apologize but I don't know for sure but we do appreciate you
Thank you so much
Congratulations
From now on and this isn't something that I think
Think is a rule that we should
Should have but instead of signing your name or your name down
Send an audio clip
Let's completely phonetic
Who knows you can do so by going to dollartree.com
Sports
Has donated
Created a situation where
Now
Do a full-length documentary commentary track of
Alex Jones
Terrible documentary endgame
I would we will be doing
Releasing
Shortly
You were working this weekend at a club so we were not able to get together and I'll make it happen this weekend but next weekend
Will be recording it
I believe releasing it over the course
Of the next week so we look at a we look at a calendar that'll be the night
Keep that looks like the 19th will be wine
The documentary starts dropping
Oh okay
So that means that will be will be spending all of daylight
One day most likely how long how long is
These days not that long ago
So
Fiesta
Sometimes I feel so stupid because I'm like
Wait
Are the days getting shorter or longer right
Summer solstice when I get shorter or longer
Equinox what is the summer solstice
I don't know
Have to go in galivants around with
And celebrate
I don't know
Celebrate around summer solstice
Does the passage of time
Transitioning
Great transitions even better than you know
So what time
Get that people donate on the time traveler level
Time travel
Behind Project Camelot time travel
My favorite this one's very weird
We got it we got a request for time travel episode just the other day
We had one from Fox
October that we forgot to do
This one
Put on it about it cuz I went back and I told you I needed to do a little bit more research and
Custom stuff
Just forgot because Alex got drunk
Episode
The present is such a hot mess that's like what are we going to do
That's such a perfect
Issue with our shows like
We were going to do something but then Alex got drunk so there we go
I was going to do this than Alex.
That's always
I cannot believe
What song was so big man
Terrible
This time travel episode
Jessie
We really appreciate that
Sporting the show and what you requested
To their birthday
Which is March 3rd
Of any year
Birthday about that
A couple March 3rd
And I found
Almost nothing to
Be excited about right
Can I listen to March 2015
And I
Highest high weird
Very high-level weirdness on Alex's party
Phantom excited to break down some of it
Here is a clip
Text drop
For you to enjoy from this
I don't know if I can answer that question
Also slightly take issue with the idea that science fiction
I think every part of that sentence is wrong
Mary Wild
I would describe it as
Tragically Wild
Okay fine
Nazi
Know it cuz he know
It's just a dream
The man we know that
That's true
Possibly
Just give you a little break down on what's
What's going to happen on this year March 3rd 2015 was the day that Benjamin Netanyahu
Did that
Angry about that actually hits the nail
Right on the head
In the middle of the power play
Election
The flexing of power coming over here in consolidation
Obama was not into that
Rich
Weird feelings about
Yeah we all have however I think Alex
She's probably on the wrong side
You know what I don't know what side he's on
That's right
He loves right wing
We're going to get into something that's really interesting that is like different versions of anti-semitism
They're going to come up because
There is like ethnic anti-Semitism in political anti-semitism
Kind of not always related
There's the version of like
I hate
The Jewish
People
And that comes out through like blood libel
And then you have political anti
Semitism which comes
In the form of life
Being opposed to Zionism
Weird
Division
Between those two
And I'm not sure I can fully explain all of it to you but
Alex is kind of guilty
If there is a way to be Alex will find it
Alex is
At 8
Some ways his most admirable dinosaurs
Jurassic Park
Life
Episode twice
And a half now probably cutting the clips and everything
Understand where Alex is coming from
I don't understand what you saying
Because he's been put into a really uncomfortable position
Because he doesn't like like you said he's supports right-wing type stuff
To be really involved in Israel they packed Library very strong
You just he doesn't know where to land on it
A bunch of ambivalence
Jewish people
You can't love is
If you hate
Muslims
You kind of have to like
Israel if you love the right wing
For some reason
They hate Muslim people and
Palestinians like I don't know what anybody is doing
The Sovereign to you can't really be thrilled with the prime minister of a foreign country
Coming in and speaking to Congress
Against the wishes of the president
He's a man without a country and you see it sort of coming up already here in the
Broadcast
In the third day of March 2015 Benjamin Netanyahu
He'll just basically completed
Some of the
Spoiler alert
Breakdown the
At all really
Israel will not be
Like we won't be the victims of genocide all aggression
Ever again
Do me quotes
Guess you with that
But the sentiment I agree with
The problem with that quote is
Really it kind of is a
It's almost in netanyahu's words
The opposite
Of what he's intending it to mean which is
We won't be the victims of a genocide
And the only way to ensure that
Is to genocide everybody else
Right right there is there's a feeling of
You're not you're not saying everything
I'm here
Pharrell
So don't look forward
Because regardless
In the face of genocide aggression are over
Refused
Chariot
Pelosi on the floor
We've got video of all of this ring to be healing up
Problems with some
Diverse country
Alicia
Not biased
To secure
Economic foothold and to secure the US
Israel
So we're already seeing
There's a conspiracy in his mind
Israel is using after they back in order to reinforce
Our support of them
No using the
The the word
That doesn't make any goddamn
He doesn't have anywhere to go you can't be against this me can't before it
He's got to play The Middle
Pandora play the middle he's got to be really weird about it how complicated is B is real situation
Even Alex doesn't have an opinion
Yeah that's
That's how complicated it is pretty complicated
Many thoughts and opinions and I have
0 solution
Is all of them are like
I mean
Genocide I think that's the start
That's a damn good solution
Let's solution
Orlistat
Transitional bowl today
Be a lot easier
You know this is going to play out it's going to keep going
Here in this next clip is where Alex
Certificates on a reasonable
Playground
Interpret
The political
Loses it real quick
Obama said he wasn't going to watch it
Pelosi freaks out and
Netanyahu's facing re-election
And by the Democrats
Socialist
Anti-israel to the Core
Sure
Different
Israel
The whole thing's very very hard to figure out some of the barrel
At the bottom of the whole situation
If you go to a leftist event
Karl Marx
Real quick
Is because he at the beginning of this episode of Play-Doh Mark Dice report
Where he went out on the street and ask people if they see
Supportive
He was supported Obama
Christening Karl Marx is his successor as president
Beavers like
Most of the people
Pretty bad so amazing Heather
Basic competency requires to
To do a man-on-the-street interview
It's still Beyond
Time let's not forget
I believe that Frederick Douglass was still alive
So I mean if you want to play that game
Karl Marx
Whatever I mean
They're promoting
And handing out and shelling
Who's doing that
The right
Their literal Nazis
You should read some of these stories that are coming out about like
What's going on on College
Increase 300-volt r300 percent
And the last
6 months
Jessica
Have you heard that
The story up from the one college where they had
They had a right-wing rally
All set to go
Free speech
Yeah and then
Because they were
Concerned there was also at the same time
A movement
Raaa
An event
To support
Right
So they were like okay
Well we got to let these knots
Please talk
So we're going to cancel the support for black
People movement
More America
Nothing is more American than
Well we got to let the Nazis talk what I mean that's just point
Baked into that idea of free speech being too
Protect unappealing
Maybe fetishize that a little bit
Then the very same group
We'll run around claiming that brown bags are racist
And having a fiesta party
Tabo
Enchiladas
The Mexican
Obsession
24/7 on
So
No
How he got
Any of those thoughts
UK
To talk about Jews a lot in this episode
Master like talk about all of his other narratives and then sort of goodbye them but not
How much it's
This is one of the most
Like
Ambivalent
Alex I've ever heard
To go to Florida in any direction
Going to piss off somebody but at the same time we talk about this all the time the idea of like
Didn't with the sombrero parties that he's talking about
Using someone else's culture as a costume
I would like to also point out this is a really fun thing
Cemetery in Louisa row
British.
Material needed a series called weird weekend
Where he would go and hang out with
Fringe
People for a weekend
You wouldn't like the Westboro
Church for weekend is pretty horrifying
Reminder you about whites
Supremacist
Metzger's
Something Metzger
It's not but he's a big leader in the white supremacist
Movement
And what have you and go give speeches at
Neo-Nazi rallies
Happening is it turns out that
He likes to go to Mexico
And get really
Can waste it
Bluey goes along with this
F****** white supremacist
Nazi
To Mexico
Because he's weird
Coked-out lawyer guy who represents him
Banging around with a Mexico
Prostitute
So they go down to Mexico
And of course it's just
This Metzger going around with a sombrero drinking tequila
Mexico have ever seen in my life
1st and White 2
Supremacist
And somehow I don't
Understand that bore after you told me that
I recommend a documentary so highly
Just a
Aesthetic look
Hateful man
Those are all on YouTube
Yeah that's true
Throws Works. Highlights
Alright has great style where he's like really unassuming
Kind of people to open up in ways that they probably should
Very compelling
Hangs out with
A couple skinheads
These Jewish
Really rather not answer
Get the f*** out of my garage
If I camera wasn't here I would beat your ass
Suicide really
I prefer not to
No
Alex talks about
Define whistle
Jewish based conspiracies
But somehow it's not okay for other one
That's very weird
He has to be loves it whenever anybody pisses off
He doesn't know what it is
Is he supposed to say
Yep
Totally
That's going to come into play a little bit later to that specific feeling that he has about
Democrat
It's like it's like an old west movie where some a****** is like
Firing a gun at his feet like
The here
Only way I can describe this is
Starting
Talk about something then
Super off tracking
But you have no idea where he's going
And it's acceptable
In leftist ideology
Jewish conspiracy of colonial
No there's not
That's not acceptable
That's the spirit
Do you understand what he's getting out there
No
I don't know hundred percent either but I believe the Woody saying is there is
Flipaclip play Let's see if he gives us more context
Exclusion
Not good
And then
A Jewish conspiracy
Basically
Shawarma guys
An insert with that something that juice
I want juice work to be
Position
Show me nobody
Achievers education
All I know is evil inherently
I'm constantly fighting with each other like every other group
And runs the gamut from
That's not the whole thing
Or or some of the others
I'm just sick of the stereotype
And then the globalist above that the very same problems that you socialism
As their control system
Who are definitely not you
Again
Scapegoat
Problems
I do I am
Very uncomfortable
I'm deeply troubled by what he saying
It's still weird for him to be like
Weather left says
Conspiracies
And the right isn't allowed to
Industry
Because my profile position
And I'm against they are over
All Jews are the same thing
But I'm against stereotype
It's almost like he's saying
I mean
What are you saying is like
The left has their conspiracies right as theirs
Most of them are true
Behind my sexual things true
What books does Harry gets off the hookah is like different
Different I'm not being able to make when I use all the
Describe the globalist
And I can't really prove it exists most of the globalist that I do talk about
Wind up being Jewish like the Rothschilds
Ed Oliver
Completely lie about the other history we're going to get into a little busier
Everybody knows nothing about Jewish history
Especially like Alex's
Dangerous edible leaves
But he has about the Rothschilds that like
I mean
We could do
2 hours on it cuz it's a disaster
What we just listen to is a little bit
Desi Alex
Tread lightly you're heading towards something
About complaint the people
Tired of being attacked for being anti-Semitic
And then he launches into something directly antisymmetric
Throughout my life
Who will blame
For all of their problems
Don't want to
That's what it comes down to
And this comes from somebody who's Ben Savage
Israel
George Soros is a Jew
The guy
Ron's organization
196 million
With the US government
I can find
Didn't know eviden
Notoriously developed
Marine Corps
I'm largely responsible for the dissemination of
The protocols of the Elders of Zion
Personally responsible for Distributing hundreds of thousands of copies
Anti-semitic fraud
The Ford Foundation analysis
Came out in the church
Committee that it was that guy
Government-run and
Got these documents Anthony Sutton
Written a number of books about likes
Skull and bones
And what have you
I tried to find any connection to
To him and
Church committee
The Ford Foundation
And that
I came up with no
We just made that one up whole committee was about invest
Navigating the CIA and the FBI
Intelligence operation
And of course whether or not to buy
Absolutely
I don't I don't know
I would withhold judgment on this one
But my gut tells me he's just pulling at straws
Because
I like
Frankly
I kind of kind of at the end of this episode
All I need to know how I feel about Alex
And his stance is just
Play the little clip of himself
Jew
And you're like Soros
Is it
It's really fascinating to me
To hear him go from like
I'm so f****** sick
I'm tired of everybody saying that I made
Everybody just lies about me
All these leftist Jewish organizations lie about being called me racist
George Soros is a completely lying about George Soros
Directed way
And again
I don't want to be defending
But I
When there are these sort of accusation
Spurious
Fraudulent accusations
Being levelled against him
Specifically
Because he's doing
Resume
George soros's just want our
Bizarre
Financial
December 10th
Right let's get it and I Alex
You cannot just sit there and point
Complex
Rothschild family
I did
So
Well
This is
This is deeply
Deeply troubling
Not true killed The Rock
Child tour
Where's Matt
Then that where he's going for here
I guess I don't know
The Rothschilds
Funded Hitler
If you look into the actual history of it in March 1938 within days of
Angeles
Personnel
Alice's
From Alphonse residence
Plunderers took 3444 items
And from Louise mansion
Louis
Bluey
Additional 919
+ 190
Everything was meticulously inventory with the most
Important Works earmarked for Hitler's plan fewer Museum in Austria
The town of his birth
Lesser pieces were directed to the Viennese Museum
And others mainly porcelains were fenced
State-owned auction
Open house at Dorothy
Dorothy
Has the war preceded The Collection was transferred from several locations outside Vienna and I-90
Open hidden in the
Altos a salt mines near Salzburg safe for my lights on
The following year the America
42nd division
Hey baba by they were able to
Mix it around
The restaurant business Empire with pants down
Generate
Until March 13th
Came in
Two salads banking
A fraction of its real worth
Well are the Rothschilds
Was in prison for a year and only released after substantial Ranch
It was paid by his fans
After Louis was released
In March 1939 the Nazis place
Form of SMS
Under compulsory Administration
Nazi officers
Senior staff
Free museums also empty the Rothschild family estate of all their value
So basically what ended up having
Is that the family had almost all of their wealth
Stolen by the
A lot of them were already out of
The country by vendor least the one
Areas
Became occupied by knobs
Directions work
And they were f****** multi-millionaires back then
So one of the one of the great myths about the Rothschild has if they have like somebody took money week
Because they had millions of dollars
100 years ago
So they're not nearly like
Sure family probably still has
In the billions of dollars
Family is spread through
All sorts of marriages and
Kids and generations
The power that the family wields is
Almost
Yeah
Now in researching this claim
This is before you go any further
This is such
An awful thing for Alex
To do because
Every example
He's giving
Bar
Jews
Participating in the Jewish
Exactly my point
It's just like if it is
So close to him saying like
Well they had a common
Cause of their own Jen
The most
Powerful Jews were the ones who are really perpetrating
The genocide that way I don't have to because a white person
Eastlake their own suicide black families do
Don't stick together so that's why they're poor
Layman disenfranchised populations
4 things
Society has foisted upon them
Especially
Male dominated Society has foisted upon them
For the crime of being other
Now
While I was researching this claim about the roster
Something very in
That is a 1995 article from the New York
Let me redo the
Dutcher Bank
Admits it helped Hitler
Confronting a dark
Got your bank the expiration of Jewish businesses and helped Hitler consolidate
Control over Germany's Neighbors
Between 1933 and 1945 according to a history of the bank
To be published in March
So
The Dutch bank
Came out and said
So this guy I mean like go back to
Siemens
Made
One of the newest members of the board Oscar
Wasserman was forced to resign in 1933
Start to be long string of such recognized
But George
Thompson
Successor to Mr Wasserman a prosthetic letter to the chairman of the bank's supervisory board
I fear we are embarking on it
Explicit well plan
Passports the annihilation of all Jews
Germany
Mr. Sampson lambasted the
The passivity and
Complete lack of solidarity
Other countries Elite
Most of them had not yet
Become members of the Nazi party
Refused the bank personnel
The party before 1933
Many opportunist
Opportunist
Did so after Hitler assume power
At the end of the war in 1945 44 the bank's 84 Branch officers were partying
All them a joint after night
In the end mr. James wrote
The guy was right in the history of this stuff
Bankers unlock generals were largely
Powerless to decisively influence of course
History but through their passivity they also contributed to the whores
Now why is it important
I would like to
Nice of them
Just save it
Bankers
Have no influence
Isn't that interesting the bank history
Change
You know just
Having all of the money that they make
See with the Rothschilds situation
If you didn't
Play ball they were just going to take out the Nazis were just going to take over your bank
Like it's not
I'm not saying anyone off the hook
But in terms of being able to
What was going on
I don't think the bank
Cuz really had that much
Much control their past
Very clearly said in there
And they should be deeply ashamed that they didn't do anything
But
I find it hard to believe
That
The
Thanks
At that time
Would not have been able to wield
Enough financial power
Curb
A lot of
Maybe I don't know I don't know but I don't know that either of us knows entirely but
Banks divesting themselves
From oil
Yeah
Climate change is
Immediately
Yeah but that that
Totally different than the idea of climate change being a
An army
That has
Authoritarian
On power in the
No I armies armies
Actively complicit climate change
And a gas company
Are not they don't have foot
Soldiers that will
Dudley take over your back
In the same way that the Nazis did
I understand what you're saying and I agree with the points
It's not like they kept all their money in
I mean maybe they just had a big ass bolt and full of gold
Yeah but
He's going to go to branches
Each individual branch and be like hey
We're going to take 50 bucks from all of these like I don't know what the
Possibly
Possibly they would
Yeah that's true
Fascist
Takeover State and everything
I'm not again I want to be totally clear that I'm not letting
Any
Off the hook
I think every
Bank executives
It's probably guilty of
295 article is admitting
Helped Hitler in the Holocaust
Pulled roughly 300 million in debt
To Dutch a back
Leslie that
Without comment
Well anyway
Complaints about how
Coronavirus real
I know Israel Traverse different political parties different ideas
I have a love-hate relationship
She better get a hundred percent behind
That's wrong
Israel wasawasa Portmore
The end-all-be-all only thing on the planet
Israel
I don't know I think it was just
Film the other country could think of
I don't think that's how people think
No
Indoctrinated
Rapidly nationalistic things
Nationalist
Like I don't have anything against
America as a
I like America
I think we could do better about a lot of stuff
Destroy America
But at the same time
I don't think we're the most
Important thing in the world
I think the world is the most important thing in the world
And I think a lot of people in other countries
Voorhees part of bread
They were maybe a Welsh
Oh well smash rejuvenation
I am
Extreme Dodge
Probably Alex
Technically Alex
He's Welsh
That's true but look I don't know nationalism
Alex goes off on some stuff later but
You can't be a nationalist if
If your words don't
Is Matt
Is not how that works
Welsh
Okay sorry
Degrassi pill
Great Scrabble words you people out there
WM
Should be a word but it is
Alex Jones
I meant he complains a little bit about his own personal plight
He doesn't like
More black people beat up white people that I've ever seen
Israel more than Israel
Not great
All these Arab countries won't let the Palestinians give them Aid
Palestinian conflict
What country singer used as a political football
To manipulate everyone
Is held to a higher standard
No
It's a paradox because
Never experience
Triology
Hatred
I have from anti-israel
They will make stuff up
Everyone is a Jew
Care of your Richardson green
Johnson
Sanchez
Cian
Really thinking about Mexican everyone is a Jupiter all-powerful
I never borrowed a dime
Multiplication tens of thousands of dollars from your dad
It's a very frustrating all the Nazi websites
Photoshopped
Videos
Israeli agent
It's amazing Untold
Roman stuff
It's alright
Tired of sitting here watching anti-israel
Degenerates by the minute
Situation I want prosperity
Brakes
I would say
If anyone
Is like if you had a high school yearbook and
You're giving up superlatives
Most likely to come down with Jerusalem syndrome
Alex Jones
He goes to Jerusalem he used
Iron Man
That would not be good so I just like
Palestinian
Try to overthrow every country.
Try and Destroy every country
Disparage
Definitely against every country of course evil and chaotic and Monster
Nature
But
Come on
Also aren't they just
We will get back to a lot of this is going to come full circle
Throw Israel so much as
Live
Yeah
Important point that Alex brings up in a little bit and we'll get to it
The biggest problem I have right now is
He's getting close to the territory of like
Who's there
Are you a Jew
Is that guy jokes
That's a really important distinction to make
Hold on to that until the next eclipse
Before we do that I want to talk a little bit more about this
Complained the dollar
What's has about
These anti-Semitic
Excites Israel
Iza Israel
Like
All of the people that he wants to be in government now
Well he's sort of I mean he nurtures these sort of
AP
There's a
I don't know exactly how to put it
I think he relishes the idea that
People make these attacks
Because then criticism of him is
That's crazy
Whatever whatever the websites in the world
And the other half say you works with
The CIA
Rather like that anybody was a legitimate criticism of him is like
Hey you know his rhetoric is really reminiscent of old anti-semitic Canard
Angie lies all the time and he keep saying
In contact with intelligent
Contagion season
Also wanted to be illegal
You don't get any tracks
That's why memes about him a really successful ever wants to make sense of it
And I know you like
Actual criticism of him is just loved in with like
Oh you one of those crazies who thinks he works for
It's a
It like he has
What's the love it because
Ideologically
He agrees with everything
With those
Anti-semitic like with a if you're talkin about an anti-israel website all of that is
All the other race
Will it gives him anti-semitic cover to a certain extent
But that allows him to distance himself
From
Agreeing with everything
He gets to be like well of course I'm not like Stormfront
I don't hate Israel
Israel you agree with everything else Stormfront
Front cuz they attack me all the time can't you see that were different
I don't agree with David Duke I had them on the show about everything but I pretended I disagreed with
Like I said
Nice quote we get into some weird
Ethnic talk
This is this is really weird it starts with him talking about how
Israelis did test
Did like
Testing
Jewish population
Make a lot of countries have that to a troubling history in their pants
No one gets pass on it but
Makes me deeply on
And by the way Israel didn't get caught on Arabs
First of all he's saying almost a responsible for everything that happens
Mister jiu's but also in there he's almost saying that if they had
Which is also I don't like that at all
Which genetics are true
Undisputed juice
They are
Free Arab
Before African invasions much of the Middle East
Parts of Africa
Artifact that's what heroes are
First of all
I don't like I do not like any conversation.
Don't like any of that that's not a good wine to go down
Genetic makeup
Anime
Stop stop
Please don't do it
Scrooge I don't know no no no no
Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex
Penny Ann's
Beginning of it there's more but
That's what Arabs are there a hybrid
Yeah I don't know
Stop
Please I could have stopped
Arabs
They don't count
Cuz they're not
I didn't mean to say oh boy
Now what I meant to say is there a hybrid
What I meant to say is that their lesser than juice
Sephardic Jews
When the world group Europe
What is Europe today
Ashkenazi Jew
North of Georgia
Asian gentleman
Babylonian captivity
You do have an Arab line
Genetics images
Morton
First of all
He never finishes I thought I'm very curious what it had thought was going to be
Powell
Is it Jews
Original
And then you got
What
Absolutely
The public
Correctly
All Jews are white p
But not now Jews
Zerbos
Arabs are white people is that
Trying to say don't know what you trying to say you should have said was nothing
Thanks Mike Birbiglia the only thing that
Like I can really take away from that clip is that whoever kicked in that music was late
Music should have come in what earlier
Feel like I don't know I don't know enough about like
Genetic fossil records in
It doesn't really interest me.
Into this
This sort of
Discourse
And you're acting like it
It means anything
I think you're already in
Bad territory
I don't know what point you're trying to make
I think it needs what you're saying that like these original Jews were from Europe
And then they got
They're white people and then they got ruined
By the Arabs I think that's what he's talked about that a lot about the
Greeks are only
Harry
Dark-haired because of Muslim Invasion stuff like that
Which is like
Hey buddy
Cut that out
That kind of that kind of rhetoric is unnecessary
Diversity
End it all
And then when you start getting
Who's a real Jew and who's not a real Jew
Then we get into real trouble that I think Israel has
And I was not thrilled with it but it's also their conversation to have
You remain in the same way vet like
I guess
I don't know it makes me uncomfortable no matter what
I guess liquor
I don't know
You have to look at it from an ethnicity and a religion
If you want to go with the religion it's
Totally cool
Cuz then you're like if you want to be a part of the religion key or the steps you take to get into it or whatever
But if you want to go with me
The ethnic version
Nothing's good there nothing is good
I'm trying to think of a way that it's like
Yeah I guess it makes sense to exclude people from your group
Play I don't know
Exposed
I suppose
It's like here's the weirdest part about this
Is that
As he is
Dancing
So now are we
In a certain
Incense is because there's
What time is it
I don't want to
Mister
And it's very easy
Say something about
The Israel situation
It's so hard to just wait
Like there's no there's no
Easy win on
So what does if you want to if you want to talk about the the religious
The religion
And the ethnicity
To the religion
Simply because
They've always been
Right
Part of your religion eventually if everybody's trying
The kill you has to be like
Well
We got to stick together
Andrew population
Population
Pressure you know anabaptist
Were slaughtered and driven out of many places in Europe
And so there is like I asked
It's not a perfect
Overlap but like Amish communities are generally of
Similar
That's why they end up with condition
Seems like maple syrup urea but don't exist in other communities
That's the right one example cuz I grew up Mennonite
Can Amish people at 7
My buddy's always used
The bully me about whether my pee smells like maple syrup
So that's coming from my own pain as a child is that a curse or is it a gift
I mean compared to other things
Pekin smell like
A bunch of populations that have gone through
It's just that
You're not a Baptist
Don't really have a
State
Nope
It makes it much more
Placated
I don't know
I mean then you get a
You know
Sufi
Muslims you go through
Dammit although all the name population with benedictum of genocide
You're going to come to go all the way across
The board man
It's just
It's just one of those things where
It's also probably part of why it is
Purposely hard
It to become a practice
If you are not Jewish
If you are not
Me too.
Religion
You can't just start going to the synagogue
And be like I'm Jewish
Like that's not quite how bad
To what I was talking about process of conversion
If you want to go ahead and join a Christian
Church play the wall a little bit but if you want to get more involved
The sacrament
You end up either
There's rituals that you can do on your own
So you're supposed
To do outside of messerly the form
If you want to become a member of your church there things you have to
You have to say prayers and stuff probably with the minister religions
Kind of a lot of people a lot of great benefits
Weston Florida
I just realized it whenever I take a shower at
End up with a little bit of a Curly Sue
I got a I have a I have a headache
Clip Alex
He's all over
Worship Jews
Boy
I don't dislike the NFL year
Israel
First of all
What galaxy are like two episodes of The League
Real people
I think that's probably what he's basing that off of
So he has to kind of view the world through his little
That's window
Anyway
Is very bizarre
Look up at 11
Even though
Example is like
Trivializing
Just stop talking about Israel I'm sick of you talking about it
Go ahead and love the NFL or Israel
Which is not dealing with the issue
Exact
I'm sick of hearing about it
I'm sick of all the people on both sides
Vitriolic big
You're definitely aren't
Saudi Arabia
Every special interest group
Show your work
Right and Saudi Arabia and George Soros
Nevermind shut down
Can't take your gun
All right here's where this goes
But then wouldn't that
Definition make all of his listeners go
Well then I hate is real out there trying to take our guns
Trying to take our guns
Fill in the blank
And here's the deal we've been doing a great job guys
I don't want
Israel
I don't want to
Bora Bora
German women
I'm hearing other babies paid for welfare
And she has to do it
You don't
I'm sick of garbage
By his own
He is saying that he is
F******
Zika virus
Others
I'm sick of everybody but the lights are cool
So if he's sick of unfairness I assume he's full reparation
The
It's really unfair that
You know people
I have been
I had all of their wealth
Destroyed
And then have been
Systematically oppressed
For hundreds of years
So it is unfair everyday
Like they've been forced
I assumed it
We have to make
You know
Reparation
This is foolish
Documented immigrants do not qualify for welfare food stamps most other public
Also most of those programs require proof of legal immigration
Status
Until they've been in the United States for more than
In 5 years
They're narrow exception
According to PolitiFact pregnant women and nursing mothers could be eligible
For certain benefits under the women infants children program
WIC
Which provides food and nutrition voucher
The low income
Some families
If they have a child that was born in the United
Their child could also enroll in Medicaid
Could not
So
The parents can't get Medicaid they can't get any of those program
Illegally here but the child can
Because we don't want children dying all over the place are they American
I looked into it a little bit
Which is the primary thing that these
Women who are coming over here in order to
Damn the government that's the
Basic thing that they can get
Well if there's one thing I know about government
Programs
Designed to help underprivileged
People is that they are
Steven Lee well-funded
Do everything that they
Cantu
I helped everybody
Buddy right there's no
Which started in 1974
Programming started
The average monthly food cost
A person that was on the program
Was $15.68
That's not something
People are
Camping
As much as they are trying to not die
Month
Monthly $15 so I looked at it a little bit deeper and I found Vapor 2017 we have this
Statistics
Hasbro
Since 1974
But the amount the people get monthly
Under WIC
Is $40.78
$41.24 inflation going back
$74.76
That's compared to
What it was in 1970
Before now the interesting thing is that over the years that a number of enrollment
Has gone up quite a bit
In 1974 when the program started there was 88,000
People who are on the pro
As of 2017 7000286
Thousand
Seems like a lot seems Seems like a whole time but if you look at
Do your numbers again
Can you have to look at the totality of the big
The number was trending upwards
Years
Pete in 2009
Wendy conomy crash
Will the stock market
It reached its 59 million 100
Enrollees
In the program
And since then
With the exception of the next year the next year went up like 50,000 people
But since then
It is trended downward
And now there are
Approximately
2 million less people getting it
Then there were in 2009
So Alex's idea
Tons of people are coming over here in
Scamming the government in order to get $9 a month
To get food
Equivalent to 74
$90
$40 even who cares
It's it's
In terms of
The things that we spend money on
Is it embarrassing disgusting
Use of him just
Lying
About statistics lying about the reality
Situation in order to
Downward
On disenfranchised people
Generally speaking when you have these people who are coming over
From let's say Mexico or China
These women who are coming over
Is it coming from China
Until fairly recently there's a decent chance it was because there's one policy and they might have their kid
Coming to America
In order to
Save the life of their child
And you're not going to be able to find a job immediately that got a f****** baby
Give the f****** person $35 a month to get food and formula for their kid
It's nonsense the idea of
This making him so mad
It's also not a program that you can be on I believe more than 5 years I think
Paid for Trump to stay in his own f****** hotels
Right right
What is wrong with us
America imagine a couple years we will
Eclipse
The total amount we spend on WIC
On Donald Trump
I imagine that would be the case
One hundred percent
So are you can't be on this program forever
That's definitely
Chase
Even if you do come over
A pregnant woman
And give birth
In the United States in order to have your kid get citizenship
And you get on this
Sweet sweet scam with money
You can't
Get Medicare you can't get food stamps
Unless you come over legally and even then you can't get 45
There are guards in place about this
It's just such a boogeyman is almost like
People come over here because they want their
Children
To have a better
Like just about every
F****** immigrant that America has
Is ever f******
Play the country f******
Started
Further they want their kid to have a life
Because if you're running away from
Terrible situation in the war-torn country or something like that or some place
We're like to look at some of these
Did the child mortality rate
In places like let's say Iraq is
Rest
Eat something to the effect
10%
Pooping
Is almost as high as ours
Ours is not grape
But it's fine but like a
Highest in the developed world
Like that it's
Not because you want to
Scam something
Because your desk
And I don't
Feel like
A great look
Turn off
With the rates of consumption we have in the
The
Has a country to be like
I'm sorry sorry
Yorgo died in that
Go die where you came from
Not least of which
Chances are
Chances are they're escaping where they live
Probably because of something that we did
There's a connection
Further
2006 record buddy
Institute on taxation
An economic policy
CU left-leaning research
Found it undocumented
Rents paid roughly 11 billion in
State and local taxes
In 2030
Social Security Administration report also cited a 12 billion dollar
Payroll tax amount I'm outside
To undocumented
Woodworkers
The Institute on Taxation and economic policy report also estimated the average income of an undocumented family at little more than 30
Thousand dollars
Well below the country's median household income of around 54,000
The report also said that the average tax rate for immigrants
To the country
Illegally is actually higher than the rate paid by America's top
Base that we're getting from illegal
Undocumented immigrant
Who can't file for tax returns
And s*** like that big hits
Screwed over with a much higher tax rates
Bitter rich
Right there
Now you understand
Bank of America's money that's coming in
If you look at the amount of money that's coming in
It's coming in
From undocumented immigrants here let's say it between 11 and 12 billion dollars
Payroll taxes
Federal tax
If you look at WIC
Is not only undocumented immigrants
It's also citizen
40 40 bucks
So 280 million
Knowledge
Because it's total monthly okay it's 5.6 billion dollars
Thunder
Half of
The amount of money that comes in from taxation of undocumented
Like this is
We're playing with numbers a tiny bit here just to give an example
The point is this is an embarrassment Alex Jones
Is the worst object cruelty masquerading as Financial
Anyway
Now we come to the shower Alex
Take some calls
Kohl's on Israel
This works colorism
Oh boy
What's your phone called in West Virginia
Yeah hi Alex
I watch the
Excelencia being introduced
Sing like a total dictatorship trying to preach to the US
Congress and I'm really upsets me
I think it was a vice versa that wouldn't happen
To me it is just a scam but he never did mention what is the good deal
What is he so upset about
What seems to be aggravating him
For Israel Israel history background
And the things we know we know the Holocaust every year we're constantly reminded of it
We never will be allowed to forget it
Hoobly
Well yeah I think the phrase is never forget.
Forget genocide
Never again was Elie Wiesel quote but
You can't really have something ever happened
Hey
The towers went down
That was but I forgot
That the Holocaust it was like it was like 70 years ago dance
Come on
What is the deal that you was talkin about
Why is he so upset
A deal is
And not be able to build up an F-bomb
I pretend
Not acceptable
That's not true
Acceptable
Everybody
Who doesn't have some sort of very weird vested interest in it
Everybody who's looked at that deal so this is a really good
What we did was give her on back
Their own money
Right and they agreed to have oversight
Of their nuclear
Power generating
Capabilities
Which is something that we couldn't
Before I fall
International Atomic oversight whatever I would be able to go in
Check if they were up to no good
Left it on devices they were
Trouble in the neighborhood it's entirely possible I'm going up to
100%
Randolph ideal allow the International Community to have oversight
If we do get rid of it
Aniron just gets to do whatever they want
So that's really stupid the deal was very good deal
You know what
If I think it might be a smart idea to have nuclear weapons
The furor Iran
At this point
It's like a smoke them if you got them situation
Right to the point where they no one can attack you quick
Cuz
It's about to pop off
We're the ones who
Gave them the authoritarian theocracy that they have now of course they should have nuclear weapons
Yeah there's a there's real trouble
I don't know man
Foreign policy
Easy to solve
Very much so
And then Israel will protect
This is where we get into a very busy
Deeply
Cornerstone a very deeply
Anti-semitic political thinking
A lot of people believe that if yours
Israel you get to run away to Israel if you commit a crime and I'm over here I'm on HomeBase
Dab
Is a real thing
It's for like high-ranking political officials
This is the reason why I want Alex Jones was
Complaining earlier about like all these anti-Semitic
Israel sites accuse everybody
Is because
People believe that all of these nefarious actors in the world
Are stirring up trouble and they're secretly Jewish and they're going to run away to Israel
And this is based on the idea of the right of return
Are you aware of the right of return
Yeah within 30 to 45 days if you have
No
So
Everybody's
Ethnicity
Was able
To go to
Israel
And become
An Israeli citizen
Brett knows the right of return
Of the people who were sent out
Italy dyaspora or whatever
Not it created an incredibly problematic
Is that like
Oh don't the Palestinians have a right to return as well so much
So they're denying the Palestinians their right to
Return while at the same time
If you were let's a Jewish
You could if you'd like your mother was doing
You could
Right now go to Israel and become a
Or go to
Hollister
From what I understand Israel's opened it up a little bit even to like
If you have a maternal grandmother who is Jewish
You can now go convert to like orthodox
Judaism UK
Can gout and become a
The really expanding the right of return
In terms of because they want to swell the population have all the settlement
This idea
Is it crazy
Like the reality of the right of return stuff
Is pretty crazy
If you take the part of it where you're not respecting
In the Palestinians right to return to their Homeland
You ignore that part
Mixed disrupted Community after
The UN has given out this dictate to tons and tons of
Groups actor
Like in Serbia after the Serbian war in the 90s
People have the right of return
It happens over and over again after Wars
Or terrible things like that that isn't nefarious
But the way it's being applied
Nefarious
And then Alex's
Understanding of it as being like
Jews have diplomatic immunity
And they can commit crimes and run away to Israel
Is
Like that's the
The Cornerstone of
Political aunt
So now Alex is coming in
Bonkers Alex is coming in with
Hot cooked old-timey archaic anti-semitism
In terms of his beliefs
About the Rothschild
And all the blood libel and poisoning the well narratives that we've documented
Over and over again in the past
Now he's throwing in a
Precious
Banana yeah it's pretty crazy
Cosmetic blogs
Confined
It's not true
Of course not
Can you imagine the very idea of like
You just commit some crime
And then like
Israel's going to take the heat for you if you want murderer Israel
Yeah that's that's real nonsense
Disallowing
Because it does reinforce
A lot of the
Again it's
It's the cover that he gets
From these neo-nazis
Somatic site
He's allowed to
Perpetuate
Is this one
Very close to home for me
Is very
What you think of Netanyahu speech and what does it distracting us from
Alan Washington d.c. go ahead
Hi good morning
Welcome to
Note that Chris Matthews on MSNBC right after the speech.
Too many people were smiling during the Netanyahu speech this another example of
Partisan division of a China sent you
But the bigger picture
I think if
Who is
Barack Obama
Anawanda
Alert you of research I've done I've connected
The Obama
Birth certificate cover up in Hawaii
To a Eugenics think-tank at the East-West Center
I connected the mother of
Plans to counter Planned Parenthood
Alvin onaka
Suicide connected to the population Association of America
Society
Organizations that go back to Margaret Sanger
Google
Hawaii official
Who certified Whitehouse certificate of live birth
Obama's birth
To u.s. government eugenics
He's going to look into it
Is going to look into it
Do you think Google has that on autofill can you just type
Yeah probably
Set the Ender results for Europe
When do collar even got back to what he's talking about that
Is eugenics
Honolulu called the
East-West Center
My dad had a three-year Fellowship Center I spent a lot of time at the East-West Center when I was a kid
Obviously Obama's
Now that's a conspiracy
It's not a secret Muslim dance
He took my dad got his Doctorate at Harvard
Religious studies in
Revelation
Biblical Hebrew
But after that you got a 3-year Fellowship
When I was growing up
And it's interesting because
Eugenics operation
Mostly about
Connections with
Eastern and western world
Find Solutions
Matching culture is
Been helping people helping people understand each other the abstract of one of my
My dad's Pub
Locations
From the time of use
East-West Center
Call the ancestors in post contact religion
Sounds like you stole that from Margaret Sanger
Sexually this was this was published later but it's from
Research that he was conducting
East-West Center
Conference on ancestors and spirituality
Coming to our human
Experience
We are all descendants
We all have ancestors who
Powerful claims on our lives
We live in the aftermath of contact with
Another civilization
It's now clear the native religions are alive
Contemporary World Justice
Abdominal area
The phenomenon of ancestors
Is it common to all human
Most
Indigenous
It's been suppressed in Western culture
This volume articulates
Crucial issues in the study of post contact religion
Do the themes of ancestral ordering of the world
Intense personal attachments
Forebears
And the catastrophes of clock
Colonization
Now
You know what's interesting about that
You just did some Buzz Marketing
No
Alex would love that
Talking about ancestral
How the West has been disrupted from connected
I'm going to send them a copy
Alright
I just think that's really funny and I mean
Buckeye
Admitted
Around the edge
At the time I couldn't have smelled out
A CIA operation
If my life depended on it
But everything I know
Children's book
All I know is that it
Not a nefarious up
I've talked to my dad quite a bit about it
Eugenicist
Where to take a quick break with this next clip where Alex
Take people with
Austin Chronicle
I turn on television
Alex talks about a Cop going to rob you all the time
He's very against eminent domain is very again
The seizures that you can make
Can make if they suspect you of a crime stuff like that
Vegetable asset forfeiture complains about cops robbing you quite a bit
I don't know what he's going to
Power Trip
I don't know if he was
I don't think he had a bad
Yosemite Sam
Oh yeah I think it was a prospector of some sort
Don't violate my first amendment
Person
I am not going to just sit here
Focused at the police
Veterans
They hate people trying to use weapons
They hate the police
Everything
Sunday
Will not
Along with that piece of trash
I see through everything
I really did
And you can see their battle plan all over the place
We reform our police
Everything bad
Instant shooting
Demonization of Patriots
The globalist have occupied the federal government
Police
Couple things
No
Checkpoints
Generally speaking Arabic
Because they don't have the money
And they're trying to
Like that
That's not the feds coming
That's we need to pay our budgets and
Beyond that I think everyone has tasers
I don't know
He's talked about
And generally speaking it's not the federal police or the federal authorities were coming in and teaching
People hey go ahead and shoot people
It's the local cops and Upstream people and then the feds coming to be like
We got to deal with this
Dog the doj investigate
Dallas cops
Well at least
The federal government doesn't
Give these cops
All of this militarized bulshit
The cops
The Patriot
You need to be very careful
Because
But they're talking
The feds
Are sovereign citizen
If you want a lump your s*** in with them
Then you're going to have to take on with Vape
And what they do
Is kill cops
For all his talk about like
You know black lives matter being all about cop killing and what have you
Breakdown
Stats on the number
Attacks on police that are done by Sovereign citizen
The number is much higher
And so when the feds are like hey you got to be careful about these
They are very wild
They don't think you have any Authority and they also don't carry ID
Also they don't think
They have guns
And they use them
So that if it's Federal authorities want to come in in
People how to
Deescalate those situations
Think it's
Also I'm thrilled to report to Yosemite Sam
Is generally
Depicted as a prospector Outlaw pirate or cowboy
He's not a cop
Apparently
Sometime is a pirate
I want that
Alex Jones is having a conversation with one
Climate expert
Something to talk for a little bit
They don't talk about the talk about climate change.
But I've got that out
Cuz it's stupid
Enclosing on the subject why won't the feminist
All sexy
No one
Girls
If you got all that this meeting there are folks
Jihad
Instant
Grapes
Alex Jones
Anyting
Furiated
Yeah
Ulta
Calipari
Just buy
Talking
Lord monckton
F******
B**** one of the things that Alex really never takes
Into consideration is that like
Or you not he knows this but he never announces it
It is like Lord monckton was
Huge player in you
But he's a really big part of the
UK
Party
I could never have guessed that he was
In charge of it
Copperajah
But I want to tell you a little bit more about Lord Martin cuz Let's ignore that dump
I think we can dismiss it by saying that Asians and people on the left
Two are actually
Working again
The things you're complaining about
Well you just score points pretending no one is working again
Some fun things I learned about
Mocked and recently
What's up
Lord monckton erroneously claimed
To be a recipient of the Nobel Peace Prize with Al Gore
And the ipcc because
He claims he sent them a letter pointing out something that needed to be fixed in a draft
Of their submission
For the Nobel Peace
So you're in the Nobel Peace Prize along with
When asked about it but it is still in his bio
Back in 2012 at the UN climate talks
Impersonated a Burmese delegate
To crash the event and save it climate change is happening
He was thrown out and banned for life
Good
So he also claimed that Margaret Thatcher spikes
Trying
Do you think he tried to do it
Oh yeah
Actually watch the video that he says like a salaam alaikum
No
I don't know I don't know what like
He also advocated that Margaret Thatcher's Spike the argentines water with mild bacillus
Would have an easy win in the Falklands War
This would be a huge violation of the night
T-72 biological weapon
He's also advocated for outlawing portions of the Quran
He's claimed that he has a miracle cure that can handle pretty much everything
Hiv-2,
Cold
Herpes viruses everything
In his defense
Infatuated
He he he has created this miracle cure as applied for
For every year from 2008
The 2013 at least
But he let the patent laps every year and then reapply
He never asked
To prove that the facts
I love you scaring people with it
Also Moncton Lord monckton was a cheap
I think tank operated by the frontiers of Freedom Foundation
After years where the data is available between 2002-2007
ExxonMobil frontiers of Freedom Foundation over $1000000
Pinterest
The news again
Climate change
Also
Where is Vestas really funny
He
He claims that he's a member of the House of Lords
Is that why he called
Technically did inherit
The title
From somebody
He claims it's a House of Lords member of the House of Lords
But the letter
That they posted the season desist letter on the parliament's website
Lord monckton is a
Distance scam artist
Either I learned all the stuff I like
The house of
Lourdes doesn't want you not at all really bad
Lord Marksman is come up and we learn about history
People everybody Alex Jones has on his
Con artist
They're all just people who can't go anywhere else
No one will have them because they've burned all their Bridges
You asked earlier
How's Alex going to deal with the fact that he
Can't side with Obama
You're sorry.
A great match
Mama
Everything Obama does his mama on the surface Israel
There's just major stuff
Your stops going on
Do you want support the transmission
Great
I've been raised cuz we haven't heard an ad
Sounds like
Cuz he's too confused by where to land and then also he's going on these weird diatribes about ethnic origin
That's such a
Perfect
Summation of how
The right views Obama
As
Everything he does is bad
Doesn't matter
Possible
To compromise to
Respect
Everything he does
Which is insane
And it does
Feel like
I don't think I can
Prove this
Feels like they're working
Going backwards
I'm saying like
Started with this We can't agree on anything they have
Well then they filled in the blanks and Alex's
Really great
Defied not agreeing with him by being like
Because he has a fake dad who's a
Socialist
The Soviets who is diagnosed
Indoctrinated him in
Cultural Marxism
But also trying to
Create a caliphate Islamic rule
Rain in the United States
Backwards
The train just
25 in Evergreen
As opposed
Stabbing like a maybe
Con man I keep talking
You are wrong all of my guests are con men and psychic Warfare guys
But Obama's
Or just straight-up crazy
Anyway we get to another Colorado
Listcrawlers
Librarian
You looking at the Six Days War after they establish their state
I mean
To my eyes that was just
That mean God and do
Providence
I mean
They were surrounded then and look what they accomplished by themselves
Do not go by themselves
That's what I think that's right and that's why people
It's not going to happen
Yeah it's important to have both of those nuclear weapons are great
The Providence of the
Christian
God
Sono
F****** stupid
This is where I wanted to get back to the nationalism
Most advanced
Text military technology that we are you shiting me
Fighting people on horseback
F******
Sane what is why
Providence Providence
So I want to go back to the everybody views the world is like
Which is this weird National
Israel has Providence
Switches divine
Basically
I wanted to read a little bit here from
Zinn Road in 2000
15in essay called the scourge of national
I think it's very pointed
I think it's in Port
Our citizen has been brought up to see our nation is different from others
Exception in the world uniquely moral
Expanding into other lands
In order to bring civilization
Can Liberty democracy
That self-deception started early
When the first English settlers moved into Indian land in Massachusetts
The violence escalated into war with a peacoat in
The killing of Indians was seeing is approved by God The Taking of land
As commanded by the Bible
The Puritan
Cited one of the Psalms
Ask of me and I shall
Give thee
The Heathen for thine inheritance
Uttermost parts
Upper thigh possess
When English set fire to a peacoat Village in massacred men women and children
Theologian Cotton Mather said
He was supposed that no less than five
600D code solos
We're brought down
The hell that day
It was our manifest destiny
Sunita overspread the continent allotted by Providence
An American journalist
Declared on the eve of the next
Is after the invasion of Mexico began
The New York Herald announce quote
We believe it's part of our desk
Civilized
Country
It was always supposedly for benign purposes that our country went to war
We invaded Cuba in 1898 to liberate
The Cubans in the Philippines shortly after
Is President McKinley put it
To civilize and christianize the Filipino people
As our armies were committing massacres in
In the Philippines
At least 600,000 Filipinos died
70 years of Compton
Elihu root
Or Secretary of War was saying
The American soldiers differ
Cancel the other soldiers
Of all other countries since the War Began
Give the advance guard of liberty and justice
In order
Peace and happiness
Devin says Liberty like math
Nationalism is given a special
Special virulence
When it's black by prophet
That's the point I wanted
Really drive home
Hey
God says
Whenever you mix those two things together which Alex Jones does
All the time
You get into a really murky territory wearing you're not only like I'm the best
Did the Gods
I'm the best
And that's a f*****-up
To put yourself in
Cuz there's other countries
In the world hey.
Nope
There aren't even other people
And if there are and they don't believe in God
Well they didn't they're not protected by Providence
Nothing I know if there's one thing I know about Jesus
It's at 1
He was a secret Muslim right
He loved Massacre
Totally huge thing
Can we just not call themselves
Christian's like I think it'd be fine if they called themselves
Weird biblical little
Maybe Old Testament motherfukers
Oh no
F****** assholes
Seems most fitting
So it's kind of ironic that Alex Goes To Break
I'm back from break a little bit later today
What type of talk radio weed Pioneers simulcasting television not just a webcam
Theoretically show video clips news articles
Hahaha hahaha hahaha
Spectrum Gaston who don't even ideologically
Hahaha
80%
But who genuinely want freedom
Shomer experts in their field
And also seem to be angry white men
With a couple of
Charlotte iserbyt
Real discussion
Charizard
The Democratic party especially
The country
Really want us on our knees
The terms of our surrender
And
They just hate this country because we were a Christian Nation were free market
Alex
Prove that
He says he document everything you guys like
Recite we got this
Broadcast like this weekend
Compulsively put up documents in Arabic
Neurotically even prove any of his claims
I watched
This s*** like
Primarily an audio video that I watched
What are we flash stuff up on screen
It's just a Wikipedia
If you want to talk about zoom in so you can read it I can't wait till we do this
Because I
I can't wait
Explain to you and our listeners
Just how bad Alex Jones is
Is in terms of citing sources for the claims that he makes
Holyshit
It wouldn't fly in a junior high
Quite frankly
Stop.
Total b*******
Totalboat
Joel Gilbert
On
Is a documentarian
And I believe he's the guy who made Dreams of My real father
Which is the documentary in heavy quilt
Pornographer
I am secretly a Muslim
I mean look
Watch part of
Documentary
I just turned it off cuz I was very bored
But like I find it to be
Troubling
I just
Think
When you hear these people talk about why they think
Frank Marshall Davis is his dad
It really makes me uncomfortable
Cuz they talk about like
Obama's dad doesn't look like him but he looks a lot like Frank Marshall Davis
Do you like
Just feel real weird
Because I don't really
Thinking Obama.
Resemblance
Argument
Seems racial exactly
Engage with that and then the only other evidence
The pineapple now I don't think his dad
Other things
Just like all the circumstantial b******* about like
His mom was friend
Frank Marshall Davis
Who cares
Nothing is concrete
It's buried
It makes me very uncomfortable
And so this guy
This guy is Joel Gilbert
His maid a new documentary
Is pimping is called
No place like Utopia
About how all of Obama's prom
Promises are
They want to tell you that those Utopia the trigger
Provide
It ain't come
I thought it was about how
Frank Marshall Davis
Judy Garland
As well
The next document that's worth
No place like the Dreams of My Father
Sound whenever I been around
Criminal
I've been around before
Behind the scenes don't listen
Blood
They really are.
Grandma progressivism
Is based on this information
And that's what the Democrat Party in the White House
There's voter suppression
A completely made-up story
Bulshit
That is a real
Thing to say when
All the studies of
Don Chao
Ridiculous gerrymandering
What am I
From voter rolls
That sort of thing
Interesting things you can do that is you can look in
Into the
Should have the right to vote
Especially different argument about life
Nonviolent felons especially
Violent felons maybe murderers Maybe
Baby I don't know
I think you could murder somebody and still have a relevant opinion on
The minimum
Alternative income tax
I agree that there are crazy or people who have not murdered then some people who have
But I don't know I don't know
I would rather o.j. Simpson
Then Alex
Gilbert here is talking about this information on
A disinformation broadcast
If you want to get
To real information you can look at
Entirety
Obama's
Cuz it's over
It's over now
Oh you can look at all and you can look at what happened
Under his
Presidency
Wow
President Obama addressed Americans widespread persistent economic anxiety Donald Trump
Might not be celebrating his inauguration
Almost there
One with enough money to invest in the stock market had plenty to celebrate under the outgoing president
US Stocks Rose an average of
Propresenter
S&P global
Is an article out of Fortune
That ranks Obama third among the 12 men who've served as president that's World War
P500
Only Bill Clinton
Under home stocks Rose 14.9% year over 8 years
18.6%
Annualize during is 29 months
Presided over better Market
So if you
No buts
Bill Clinton Obama
Best
In terms of the stock market
That we don't need to talk about you know that's not really a reflection of the actual economy
But you want to look at even more number
This is out of
11.5 million jobs
In Obama's 8 years
The unemployment rate dropped
Tupelo historical norms
Average weekly earnings were all workers were up 4.1% after inflation
The game was 3.7%
For just for duck
Non-supervisory employee
After-tax corporate profits also set records as did stock price
The S&P 500 Index Rose
The number of people lacking healthcare insurance drop by 15 million
Premiums Rose
But more slowly than they were before
When Alex wants to play the chief
F****** game but how
Premium
Arose during Obama's administration
They Rose 90%.
George W bush
So that
The only thing that you really end up with
It's kind of like
Like negative stuff for Alex's that home prices
Cuz Rose
And homeownership rate drop
Which is
Kind of because in 2009 that was a big part of why the economy
I was still in a recovery in terms of that
Maybe coming maybe
Almost certainly won't happen also illegal immigration declined
Was 8 years
35% fewer people were caught trying to enter the US for Mexico during that time
Also Alex Jones should be thrilled
Production of handguns Rose 192%
To a record level a black man
The murder rate dropped to the lowest on record in 2014 then Rose
Is my Obama took off
Conserve those balls
Gesso
Remind me to Salt Lake
Play Call of the
The stuff that he's talking about all of this missing
Information
Cold hard facts
Are the
By which they measure thing
But I don't necessarily agree are all the real things we should be
Basing Oliver measurements on
We're so much better
Obama
Billionaires didn't get it
Yeah that's
Yeah I guess so
And so
I told you so
It's like I don't even
I'm just glad Alex Jones documents always playing
I'm just glad that he has guys on saying all this b*******
That's not true
If you were
Heated loud enough
Dumb people
Doodling
Itself
Hitler had a quote about that
Anyway
Another clip from Joel Gilbert here so Whole Lotta
Thought bulshit
According to
Exmark
Everybody's fighting for the door
All these different special interest groups
Faro support
So sick
People don't realize
On Earth
Is America before Barack Obama America as a constitutional government
With
Free market
It's free speech limited government
The Americans
Razor shaving
Most unhealthy highest death
All sorts of
Exactly
Michelle Obama Barack Obama
They cannot
Justify
If everything is going great if we have free market
And a great economy
They have to tell us that
Everything Is Broken
Immigration
Everything's embarrassing
And their solution is give us the power
And we'll make it right
Realize what they're doing
Externalizing their own psyche
That's entirely what that's it that is
The idea that like Obama has to lie about all this stuff to justify the things he's doing
You're doing in order to just
Sapphire big
That's why they that's why they
Have to believe this.
Is because
Cannot
Except that
Other people don't
Do what they think that way
Except
Money-wise
He was not a secret socialist trying to destroy the
He was the exact opposite which is why we're in the situation we are now well I mean if you was less competent we wouldn't be
In the situation we're in now the crisis
2009 Wood Ave
Extended
It probably gotten way worse
We're in the position we're in because of the competence in great leaders
Louisiana much better position working
Some sort of a bizarre
There would have been still many more Public Works program
You already f****** Bridges need to be restored
Massive debt
Absolutely
For people to buy home
Forgive College loan debt now to this stupid idea of
Socialist
Firebrand or whatever
Utopia that we
We had before Obama
Yeah which which one
What the f*** is he talking
Name a Utopia before broccoli
Is that really mean is not what he saying like Obama came in and destroyed everything I guess that's
Must be what he's talkin
I mean I'm sure it didn't have anything to do with George Bush's
Massive tax cuts
I'm sure there's no way that the
F****** deregulation of everything
Under his f***
King Reign sure there's no utopian
Until Obama took it over
When
The country
Consistently had growth
Whenever is secret socialist was the president when he was almost assassinated by
But like I think
Do you know why we have
Because whenever we had a
Complete free market
There was a massive
Market crash
Because of the deregulation of the stock market
It's going to lead to the neck
Crisis
If we didn't learn any
Anything from 2000
Whatever we had the last
Which we obviously didn't learn anything about what
The last financial crisis
A f****** 1980
People are so goddamn
Driving me insane clearly
They're saying that we're the ones at fault
I can't watch it don't you
You should be able to Process Equipment
Because it is just in this
Milia
Of blaming the victim it's all of this stuff
These Chinese women were coming over here to have their baby
Blame them blame them blame the poor for not
Picking themselves up by their boots
I don't work hard enough
Sure they have
Three jobs in works
60 hours a week
That's laziness if they were really working they would be rich by now everybody knows
You don't really need to criticize him for
The way Obama traded people it really was
Isn't that you f****** tea party losing their goddamn Minds
To the point where there's a guy screaming
You lie at the president
I'm in trunk comes in and he's like
People didn't clap for me so their treasonous
50s f****** insane
Hate I hate them so much
That's the one thing
The biggest problem that I had with Obama
Is the same problem that I have with
The Democratic Party
Since f****** bill
Which is this idea of like
Compromised
They should be ignored
Can't communicate with people who say things like
Everything Obama does wrong there's no communication
That's not a conversation you cannot compromise with somebody who is pitching
Using it
Possible for you to do something good it's an impossible starting point to engage with
Because once you
Join in my conversation
You have to exert so much forced
To get any
Reasonable thing out of it you know
Like
You can't come to the table in a negotiation with
I refuse to believe anything you say well alright well this is not going to go well
Anybody but like time there's like a profile or a
Pieces like
We need to understand these people it's like no
We understand that them
Ignore the one of the problems was that
I don't think enough people there were a lot of people who were sounding the alarm on this
It's too bad that
Most people and perhaps myself included even I wasn't really
Paying attention
As closely as I should have but
People didn't understand what was happening in terms of the Overton window being moved
Wow the people on the right working
Complaining about the Overton window moving
Removing it
That hard to the right
To the point now where we're in the situation
You were just
Screaming about
Acceptable
Very acceptable pieces about weather
Sargon of asgaard is just some sort of Mary a YouTuber as opposed to a
Out-and-out racist white
You have these conversations
Think about whether these commenters are commentators are mainstream
Is Jack Paseo be a journalist
Like these sorts of conversation shouldn't be happening
Write the idea that anybody like when
When Alex Jones had that charade of him getting press credentials
No one should have taken that seriously
Like no one should have been like
Are we going to
Alex Jones
Is a journalist
Career well
Definitely now is a good time to see if you're trustworthy it's important to pay attention
Attention to these people but you have to treat them like what they are
Play you can't ever give any respect
I4ni now I sound like what you were just describing
I would say
In our Gear Long treatment of Alex
Giving him credit where credit
He's generally
Propey
Goodnight interventionist
Comes along
So I mean there are things
I could come to the table with that in terms of like we agree on this
And hope for some sort of a conversation
You can.
Nada
Do you know why because you're a liberal
Your liberal so you come to the table and you say hey Gris with you we shouldn't be f****** fighting
Wars in Iraq Anita Blake
You're right we should be
Flip it on them
Stupid Alex Jones
Seeing something
Senior stimulus in the wild
And completely misrepresented
Go to Whole Foods and places
But you see the magazines
Learning to have less
Suggest
Probably those magazines a response to people haven't
How do you how do you live on a budget
As opposed to making that an attractive way to live
Anyway
That's catering to a market as opposed to creative
Comparison essay
Right thing to say at this point
You should not celebrate
GoFundMe campaign
Finally making
Enough money to get some
Somebody to pay for
That's how they celebrate
That's the saddest
Quite quite
Continues from there and then Alex gets
Sent you a call that
He accidentally reveals
Very fun
F****** weird at the end
While they charge
So much
Nice pictures
You can
Let's go
Thank you for holding your on here
Thank you for a long time my Prison Planet 2
Yahoo
America win
Useless people in Congress to stand
Someone who
I think 2,000
Listen to I have a
Who said America can dry up and Blow Away With the Wind
When we have finished with it
America
Can dry up and blow away with the
When we have finished with
Now that's not the quote
What's the source of that because I
TV quotes about myself
What's the source of that
We got it on the internet here I have a sister
BMX gear
It says Netanyahu
For president of America
Veterans today website
I mean not yeah that's
Consider the source
Real quick
Clip isn't on but just for fun
Does the spoiler alert for the endgame documentary
Alex Jones highlights
At least four quotes
That are fake that are straight up
Quite a few look at the bibliography he has no siding
Because they weren't
Force
Where's that Netanyahu coming from
Ridiculous
You
He is all over the
But
We have not yet got
Very weird admission
What's their Source Abbott
Their source
Do you have their Source on
I'm not sure I don't have it in here
Oh okay I see story is that it wasn't
CIA
Overheard
Conversation
Criticizes
Not know that
Besides
Basically approach
But but other than that
That is relevant
What
Happening
Why did you say other than that
Sure I was threatened by an Israeli intelligence officer a famous agent of Mossad came to my
My office and got slightly threatening I don't have any other connection to Israel other than that
Did you report that to the FBI
Like now we have two instances
Russian
Donaire
Yeah no
What is Israeli intelligence doing going to the second
I didn't I didn't hear that
I believe him
I believe
Wait or was that
Netanyahu supposedly said he put a time frame on Wednesday massage
I believe
I believe that is
Incredibly in line with Alex Jones
Throwing something out
So there are three guys in the hot tub
Israeli beautiful two-story six different ways for a week
Certainly the way he does
Describe the interaction on RT that he thought was an interview I believe that and I believe what you saying here
That's true I've listened to him
Everyday for over a year now I think I can
I can get a sense of when
It looks like he's
It's almost like I have an EKG on him
Seeing his face when he's
Spring for something and when
Savage
It's kind of interesting that you have never been interviewed by any of these people because you're literally at this point the world
Foremost Alex Jones X
It's also interesting to no one
Responds to
What I sent them to
Various Publications probably committing a crime here
But already
Give me a meme
We need to make sure we need to make a meme out of
I'd like people to
Israeli intelligence
I feel like
Just I don't know what it is at the
The Hatch Act
What is what was the actor you got a report that
No idea
You have to tell somebody about that probably
I'll be in touch with spies that you
Very weird episode where Alex
Is that all over the place
Israel
I don't know if we figured out exactly where he landed on
He figured out exactly where he landed on the wrong side of stuff
I know that
But I don't
I don't know debula sway
Yeah it is sort of holistic
Where you can pin him down you know he's wrong why are you even talking
Why are you getting into gorgeous
Think about Israel
He fell down real
Conversation
And you say
You have lost you have
You are not going to you're not going to come out of this unscathed
By which I mean European Jew
And then got ruined by all of these African people
God so much for contributing to the show and making up go through the
Happy birthday
That's what Alex forgot to say
Yes your birthday will be coming up happy birthday on March 3rd got to Montague
Don't
If there's one thing that we've learned about Israel
Don't drop just out
I'd like to find out more about the show the website knowledge pike.com
That knowledge
Underscore fight
Andigo to iTunes
Bro you were still listening your interested in the show
So we've weeded out all the people who are Johnny come lately
Do the plugs if you're still listening I have a special edition
This is The Avengers
Position
Where I believe that we are not going to
To make forward progress
In the projects
We are engaged
Without
Expansion
It's very difficult to expand without resources
But what we can do is
Encourage our listeners
To post about us
On bus
Message boards
If you
Grand other podcast message message board
Unrated or anything like that
Please
Help get the word Outpost something about us
And if you do
I'm going to say this
I'm creating
A very long
Very special
Drop
About Alex Jones saying ridiculous s***
That will be exclusive
Only for the people who send me knowledge fight at gmail.com
A snapshot of you posted
Put someone else's message board
Try to get the word out cuz we need
I love those words that we have and it's great that people are listening
We got to find a way to
Widen list
We got to get the word out
Yes so bad
So for the first time
At this weekend
Sold buttons and telling people about the podcast Google did like a five-minute sing on stage
Are you going to leave it into an old joke
Was terrible it was
I have a podcast
I'm sorry
I have buttons
GB clothing
At standard Road Stow
And what have you but it was
Soul crushing to stand that emerge
I did it when I was in
Tongue out at the booth with him and it was
Not good you got to do it
You got to do it if you want to make that road money oh yeah please if you like the show how much better
Would it be if there were ten times as many of us
Appreciate it
Crazy together marriages that have happened because they like my
Meetups we've met a couple listeners if you want to get married
Cheryl
That's what makes me very uncomfortable
Also listen
Listen if
You need a gift for this valve
That's going to make you fat
Button
Put it right
It vibrates I don't know
I'm done
I'm bad at the merging not think about north of the cock ring don't sell it that way
Are yogurt
Ridiculously long weird drop of Alex and tucked up stuff and
If you are at work I also understand
Just appreciate you listening
Anyway
Who's on your mind
To call out
Oh man garbage
You know
That's it that's an interesting
I want to I want to go to Subway
Attention to anybody other than
The fuc
Tortoise
Yeah
Yeah but will use him
But I also want to give a sub
F*** you
Jon rappoport
Cuz he called in sick on Thursday
F*** you John Rappaport
Go fuc yourself
Alex
I love your work