Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Different positions
Zombie videos
Also sorry you apparently by ghetto cowboy
Ironic
Frustrating
Podcast
When we do these shows live I put together playlist
Do not like the most thugs family ghetto cowboy that is not hot
Put together is probably not the word
Inflict
Playlist
I know
Lyrics to ghetto cowboy
Text came out with Bone Thugs-N-Harmony were still legit
Pittsburgh Strip District
No that is the one
Situational music where we agree
We are in the middle of
Towards rmj documentaries being released
It's difficult to put in
This much time listening
Forgot I could do that everyday all day
It's getting at me through it is
In support of our listeners
Give a shout out to a couple of new donor
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much Jim thank you so much
Jim has donated on the time-travel level
Level also
By the way
We remember there's a time travel
Mickey
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much Nikki Nikki
Also
Couple people have already responded
The Avengers Initiative
You don't know what that is go to the last minute of our last episode
If you are if you don't listen to the last minutes of our app
Episode
Totally respect that post-credits sequence
I got it
I got it.
Before we could go in here explained what we're up to but before we do I think I might have a slight problem
My iTune
Speedway audio
So let me check
Something really quick
A little bit
For the people
Am I still available
Please alright let me tell you something about the Black Panthers
I fixed the problem
Anyways
Anybody who disagrees
They Musta forgot
Do the actual best rapper of all time
Roy Jones
Studio album called the album
Don't know if you did anything
Anyway
I was tempted
To do a project Camelot
Episode today
From Alex Jones
NeverEnding and games
Appropriate for us to do something like that
Give a break
Through the annals
Project Camelot
I don't remember which
Mark Richards episodes we've done
I don't want to do enough
I don't want to look through it I don't if I can do this
So I kept looking and I
How crazy is Mark Richards
Bet we could probably do one of the same episodes we did before I knew things things that are crazy but
Started
Like because I was searching
Project Camelot stuff
I started to find a bunch of like weird alien
Life affirmation
Maybe 20 minutes
I used the Power of Now is very important
Such a weird things
To discover about you
This login
Do the podcast all the sudden everybody's like
Wait a second hold on
You're into motivational speakers okay
I mean let's
Let's be
Totally transparent
Sort of
But with a grain of salt
I will say that burned down like sick
6 years ago I lost all of my books
All that was left
Eckhart Tolle
I was wandering around the streets
Cuz I had no home I know where to go
Bookstore as I am
Real bumblebee
PetSmart Olathe Power of Now and I was like
Reeboks
You just
Describe how people join Scientology
Exactly what you just did like that but I guess I read that was right next to the power of now
We would never have seen you again I read it and I thought it was
Define betray
NeverWet how much further
Respect some of the ideas
Nobody puts out
Anyway let's not dwell too deeply in that I want
Have a good time I found an hour-long interview that Milo yiannopoulos
Did with Alex Jones
Will be fun I have to listen to him talk.
No cuz I'm not doing that
Blustery b*******
I thought it would be Alex actually opening up in
So weird weird thing was interviewing a
Yes
Milo's YouTube channel
Gross
Just right now it's Jones
Relieve it being an interview was almost like his show
You know
You just spit narratives
Acted like it was organic
Conversation between
Two people
Then
I stumbled on something that I
Long known as exist
But I forgot
Probably
We talked about
Actually going to be an interesting lead in
Because this is something that is
Mentioned
But not covered
In-N-Out
So when we do our
This what we're going to talk about today
Is referee
Preemptive
Indeed
That's a great idea
In 2007
So what you're saying is if you listen to the show passively f***
Get on board right now otherwise be endgame documentaries going to make no sense no no
Trying to do
I'm trying to sell our goddamn
Everything is Standalone everything is fine
In 2007
I don't know if you recall
Not well
July 7th
Around the world Al Gore and Leonardo DiCaprio climate change
Live Earth
I was in Greece
When it happened
I was drunk on the
Streets of Athens
Stumbling around
My brother was staying at a hostel
I have no idea that it was 7707
Square
I made setup a giant
Projector screen
The middle of Athens
Commons area
Greece was still happy
Like that but
Be that as it may
Stumbled
Whack rapper Teresa
I stumble into tons of Greeks
Sitting around watching
Oh my God this is American pop culture
We got because I got to sleep. Those exact words
Okay because I saw like a Metallica in like
Thought this is not this is American pop culture
Any TV for like a month
Corinth this Tiny Town in Greece
My family
Until I was starved
Great
Nearby there's a little
Like snacks and beers
And Eckhart Tolle books
Just to have beers and so I drink a bunch
Hyundai watch
Pop culture all night
Scrape
At the beginning of the night
James Blunt
Yeah he sings baby baby it's a wild world
He covers Cat Stevens
I don't like this is terrible
Is terrible
The end of the night when it seems like most of the people are
Leaving
Two more beers
In order to help you find your way back to the house as I'm finishing up the last one
Real Cat Stevens
Comes on
Is Cat Stevens here I'm not entirely sure on the details powerful experience for me
Oh my God I think someone is.
Roy Jones jr. in the chat room
DriveTime
I assume he played father and son
Tea for the Tillerman was a great album
Great
First Cut is the Deepest
Much better than Sheryl Crow
Absolutely
Very powerfully moved by the entire spectacle of it and it's
In my mind
Is one of the
The like
It really early beautiful mama
To my life being able to be in the middle of Greece
Among a bunch of strangers
Most of the number people talked to me and we had a great time
Performance by someone who I never thought I'd see
Do you live again
Because
Giving up on his music
This is my long way of saying that that concert
And now we're going to break down that concert snow
James Blunt also gave an interview with Milo yiannopoulos
We are zero calorie Arnold Palmer
To the chat room
Also
One of the
Funders
And Packers
The Live Earth concert on 7707
Was a man by the name of David
Rothschild
Okay
He is a member of the Rothschild family
Son of one of the Rothschild errors
London
For reasons that are still unclear to me okay
He ended up going on in Fort Worth
Yeah
Good goodbye
I don't know man how long ago
In preparation for it
Spell the unity of the world against
Climate change concert
Alex
F****** John written a book about the dangers of climate change in ways that we can prepare and help
Stuff like that
I'll give you full disclosure ahead of
Getting into this
Slides
And getting him onto the
Cuz I think he probably said we'll give you a platform
To promote your book
Or something like that
Alright
Is
An interview between a Rothschilds are and Alex Jones
I am
Stokes
She's going to
2bh
Trainwreck 70 prediction
About atonement
She's going to take
14 people are going to die
I think that's probably going to be the case
Is it just going to be like
Accusing him of all the world's ills
That'll come in
I don't know if uses the word think it does
Use the hard drive
Do now I don't
I can tell
David Rothschild David de Rothschild
Is like a really cool dude
Right around this time a little bit after he created a boat
Entirely made out of
Recycle
Plastic bottle
Okay to demonstrate
The
Just four more bottles or whatever
He seems like he's a pretty decent dude but even though I mean
Do you have enough wealth to avoid happen
I've been all that stuff
Fuller
Necessarily mean that
The comfortable life
Like milk
I'm not.
Totally supporting him
He's an awesome
He did go and get like a natural path degree
You did
You started a couple minutes.
He was able to do all of those things
Because he had the luxury to
Middle Ground
He also
I have the possibility
Just live on his ass
Not doing anything pretty good approach to
Being lucky enough to be born into wealth and it's only more people would do that
I'm just saying that
Set my prejudice against
What's the rich
Could not be higher
Yeah I know that
Paid for my cancer medication
That'll be like
Kill you
Disagree with that as a guiding principle but at the same time I think
You got to look at people as they are not as big
Noting
Stanford
Yet
So
The other thing
I need to tell this very seriously to you ahead of
There's going to be a bunch of stuff about climate
Okay
Hair trigger
Ever everyone everyone in the chat room so fat
I need for you to a year into months
Denialism makes you angry
I get that
But you're going to have to stay that anger
Because otherwise this isn't going to
Okay you're going to be screaming over these two men bickering
So so what you're asking
Give me is not
To become a
1/3
Man bickering
Deal with her stupid
Idiots I mean like
I know you're going to have
The feeling of wanting to scream this entire time
Read please
Try and let them into it's a rare occasion when a Rothschild
Are about Alex Jones Michelle with the level of risk
I appreciate that
Look for a 23 minutes from now
The first one
Just get it out
I think you already have
Information War continues
Global pledge for the young people going to the concert
Wonderland
Child
Normcore
This weekend
Born in 1970
He's the youngest of the three children
Arrow shooting out
Across the planet
Invigorating
Object sarcasm with witch
She said all of that stuff
Being a little bit of a dick
But it
You know it's restraint
Honestly
If I were listening
Like just
I would be like
How he's going to do a voice
David Rothschild
Not calling
Alex Jones is just doing his right
Over-the-air you here like
Oh hello it's nice
What the
Near over-the-top it
Anaphora
Alex Jones
It's are we get into we get into our adventure
With David Rothschild being very polite
Yes
Phillips will eventually be his downfall
He's here I don't know what's going on
You must not have a Publix
Something like that I don't know
Yeah but let's see how the
Right now
Solideal diseasel complex
Landscape
As we know it
Why I
I dedicated myself
The
Not going to eat at all
Alex's coming in
Intubated
Probably best
Use your
Best or second-best
8 first
Who's your second-best point first leave the Haymaker for last
When you're setting up your set
In the middle you close with
Is first comes out there's a polls
But a lot of people aren't
Convince
Of climate
Yes
It's not because
Do you know
We talked a lot about and I think
I'm going to bring this up
Mislead people about it but the idea that there's a
Consensus
Scientists about climate
Absolutely
Consistently
For years but there's even ExxonMobil
A study has ever found
Midterms us tracking
Consensus has been 91
Percent
Suspicious study
Albeit one of the other thing
Things that they've studied
But there is a
Positive
Even the suspicious studies are above me
Dim study
The correlation
The content
What does it there is
Positive relationship
Between
He's in climate science
Believing
That they're being a
Experience you have
The more likely you are to
To believe that climb
Right right exactly
In theory
Course you're always going
To find the public doesn't
Necessarily have
Step2 all of the
Understand
Basically what America says all the all the time
Sixty-seven percent of the population doesn't believe that
Climate change
Just means that
Sixty-seven percent of the population
What is wrong
Tobacco
Need to do a better job of
Convincing people
Or the media has done everything
Impossible to keep
ExxonMobil
Spending millions of dollars at to sow dissent
Wonder why
Camp
Climate change
Brain
Global warming or
So
No
Alex goes on to say like
It's
Hundreds of news
Pavers
White papers
Whatever Alex
What is the science
I feel like you should be asking
What is
He's asking I mean it goes back to what we talked about a lot like
It's a bad faith Quest
Cuz he doesn't want you to
Answer with science
You do right as a trap
Any question is asking as a trap
Course very very uncomfortable
So I don't know man
What are you
So far we have a very
Right now
The Rothschilds
Isabel and like
Okay I'm
Do my best to explain
To a child
What
Climate scientists
How do I think he is coming to this
With nothing but the best in
Alex has an a
Until like
Bright sky is
This guy is a dick
That's just
Keep moving this is
Free video chat
There's no there's no Skype going
60s
Free video chat
That. I'm saying that they're not
I believe so
Because if Rothschild could see Alex he would be like
Clearly.
He's talking about like I was
The massive scandal
David robots
Sanaya reasonable with Alex
Places to eat
Clothing
Right now
England
Well there's always
When your family was so active
Already
Accusatory
Well
Already into
You're the reason that your family
Market
It's interesting that this is where Alex
Ringo's
Cuz
This myth
About Nathan Ross
Child having
Someone
Who could
You know who is at the Battle of Waterloo and then
Came
And told him this information
Not true historic
Alex is bringing this up
My contacts
Of there being like
Heavy weather pattern
Like that
Bright even always driving Waterloo
Whenever you were causing all of the world's problems
Do you know why the weather
Severe triggers and
His mind
Because
He believes that the
The globalist
I've had weather weapons
Simply
No
Because
The narrative
Is that
The messenger
Came to give Nathan Ross
Child
He had to bribe
A fisherman.
To take him through a very serious storm
That guy was
He's talking about
Yes climate change is it real
Because one of the Rothschilds Messengers
He's just
I've always been all the 6th
Extreme weather and stuff
Then make reference
To the Waterloo
Situation
There is weather record
There wasn't a storm that day
There wasn't
Sandstorm
The only reference
Through this
Is a
There is a
Periodical
Periodic
A pamphlet that went around the Richmond
But the nom de plume Satan
It allegedly thing
Right
And
It was the basis
Of Nazi propaganda
Great it was the basis
The
The Rothschilds share in Waterloo
Alex is legitimately throwing Nazi proper
Buganda back in the face
Hafiz guess who is being
To me is onyx
Acceptable loss
So Alex has reference to Waterloo
Thing is clearly about
Storm that Nathan Rothschild or this messenger had to go through
Which version of the story
You end up
Unfortunately
Insecure is not true
There wasn't the storm
This is
If I remember correctly
The messenger
Fell from the boat
And then was
That's true
Play Rhonda Lord allowed him to
End
That's why we
We have climate change
More or less
Bitterness and anger of the Gods
Not for nothing that well baby
That is the greatest
There's more.
Waterloo
When your family was so active all sorts of fires and storms and
Organizing
Taxation
Sensitive
650,000
Nathan
Sable weather
Or or what
So we have a foundational issue here
Mistake
Weather in
Climate
But I mean even like I got
Westerly weather
Weather logical effect
Certainly
At all
Play a really good question for Alex to Havasu
And the answer to that is
Actually
Another explanation of how climate
So much
Was put into the app
Just
Not the weather
But the climate
Temporary
Urban natural cycle
So much f****** debris end up in the atmosphere
Everything was much much colder immediately following
Exactly
That is not
Weather whatever you talk about
Feeling sky with all of this b******* you're going to you're going
2 Chainz
The entire weather system
The weather
Absolutely climate
Is the larger issue
The volcano
Is a volcano
The climate is what the vault
Volcano put
To the app
Put all of that in the
Emisphere
Consistently
Over and over and over again
Then you're going to wind up changing
The entire play
Introduce
Into the equation that already
Store balance
Nature Valley
On its own introduced all the
The coal-burning Oliver
You end up
Call settings
Anyway
Thanks for joining us
Temperature at room
But the situation that the first thing that I disagree with
Yeah
With no with
Rothschild
In the way that he is
Describing
Picked as an ambassador
You have a good enough job of the simple the simple
Is
The argument that a lot of
People say is that
We only have one planet so we need to take care of
The planet
And it's like
When is going to be fine
But I think
Going to
Way longer than we are here but like the ones we need to take care of
Is I would say
In the same way that Alex brings up the 67% in this pool don't believe in man-made climate change
You need to wait
Humanize it make it relatable
The ideas like these
Impending disasters
And stuff like that
People can easily dismiss that sort of stuff is like
Sensationalism
I don't see the proof of it happening and you make it very relatable and you make it like this
We need to take care of our home otherwise there's going to be a leak in the roof or whatever
Write to you understand what I'm saying maybe it's not the most accurate maybe it's not the most like
Tough talk
The people need
But it is
Possibly what peep
People could listen
Cookie
Right I feel like an appeal to Gaia
So to speak is
Not necessarily the best way
How about that
What is doing a better job of convincing people in regards to the climate change
The guys who are f******
Fear-mongering about how the climate change people are going to
To turn this into a global carbon tax
Or the people who are reasonably
We need to take care of the Earth
Who's more effect
Maybe the issue is climate scientist
This is
I think one of the big
I don't I don't want scientist
To become the other side
If that's what you're proposing
Maybe they should
You can lead a movement to be the other side and I think there is that voice
In the public sphere I think there are
Shockingly never talks about that there's all kinds
Climate Terror
And stuff like that
Who like
You know
Burning down a building or
Or just tag
There are those people who are out there
Active
So I mean it's a smart idea
Weird that Alex never talked about that
We should all be bombing
Keystone pipe
Is that
That's a good
Nothing to say
Keystone Pipeline
Destruct on its own
That's clearly
Oh not the rest of us
I should be saying Native American
Who cares
Amoebas go back to the wildlife preserve standoff
No just needed
Things that were sacred
Sitting next to a steak
Next
Yikes
I have a very difficult time cutting this into clip
Because the two of them
A bit of a back-and-forth
Define places
The cut
So somebody's clips
Going to be a little bit
I don't know
Little Walgreens
I want to present this
Contact David Rockefeller
Rockefeller
Too many David ours
Rothschild
Alex White
The idea of climbing
What's your what's your issue
Alex goes off on a rant
Doesn't really answer the question
What is the downed what is the downside why why don't you
I'd like to tell you number one I read the documents
Prince Bernhard was pushing before he died now course Prince Philip
They want to exterminate 80%
Misreading
Planet
Real quick
Just because
GameStop
Stuffies lying about right
Immediately thought of whenever he said
They're going to bring about neo-feudalism
If you recall the guy that we talked about the Russian guy who wrote for what's his face again
Who wrote for Duggan's propaganda website
Malthus
Real quick I want to talk about that for a second
Alex
Patriots
Created a
Boogeyman in the form of globalist
We all need to take care of this
Second president
Destroy your house they don't know.
Hellboy
That is
Way too soon to say
This is early in the interview correct a spoiler alert that I probably
They shouldn't give you
The interview goes like 40
How is that possible David Rothschild
This was supposed to be 10
So at this point
I think Alex
Of the Rothschild house
Brothers
But he's also
David Rothschild
He thinks it's a 10 minute interview and so he's got to get his licks in before it goes off
Cuz he can't have a Rothschild on his show and not attacking
Guy being completely polite
And just saying this is the reason why we believe in
Climate change
I've gone and
I got across the
The polls
Yeah if you look at the science
If you really look at it there
90 goes into complaining later about the idea of greenhouse gases
And all that stuff that
The rudimentary version of stuff out
What should understand
Cycle that's a tiny piece of it
Solar flares dad
I mean
It's not
Zennies it's always funny
Whenever you get this kind of
Is like
Okay this guy it has
Is traveled around the world
Turn people from many different
Science specialties
Who is spoken to
Geologist
Spoken to climatology
Who is spoken to Ocean
Oceanologist like all of this stuff
So many different
Has stayed in Austin
Maybe read a book travel Alex Jones is in
Forget my dude
He is talk
Lord monckton right
Letter from the house with lower more specifically in the way the
These conversations
You know like Alex
Is a farm
Diversion
Guy in a small town saying that
Essentially global
Trying to
Access into
Slavery
Who is never gone
Section of the show
I'm not your slave Rothschild
It feels like he should have hung up there right
I'll be honest here you should have maybe
What I hung up if you hang up at that point you kind of give Alex Potter
Exactly
Cuz I think I would have hung up but
Before I hung up out of bed like
Yes you are at
And then hung up
Great
Rothschild
Sticks around
Any in the last clip for Alex
Ended up screaming
I'm not your slave
Music
Your
You're peeing
You're into denial
This is Ludacris
So anyway
Teresa
You cannot deny
Species
Community
And about maybe
Jason Brown
About how his family-owned oil well
And then I have a
And also ExxonMobil is paid a bunch
To the money to the organization
Works for the TSA
Paula CA
Advisor for or whatever so he has
Company money coming in
I'm supporting him
Alex Jones broadcast
The Genesis
Is Communications network resources
They also have
Oil wells
I'm not 100% sure on that but next time
I found some documents that indicate the
Midas resources own
Samoyed
I need
I need more documentation
I just found something
The foil.
Is there an outside possibility that
Another mighty
Just resources
Maybe but I don't know why
I found another Midas resources
Remaining calm
Australia
I don't know why these for your
Come up with them
I don't know
Interest anyway
Alex
Chimeras are going to take you down
David Rothschild
I care about the environment
And how I care about it
Is warning you about that
And also I'm going to use Nazi propaganda
Whistler your family and then claim that is just about your family trying
To create social control
In order to create a.
You got a Nazi
And like I said we'll go over in Greek
Detail those things
The Man games
Stuff about the elimination of 80% of the Paw
Population
Fleet horseshoe
And it's just Alex Jones
Don't know how to read
One thing that we will talk about I can't explain any of this
One thing that we will talk about that game
I will say
Maybe it's not a bad idea
You will probably pause
Is it that and I will say
A little hasty
Bankrolling
I've been a lot of places
Wolf
There's a lot of that
A lot of that going on
I got the quest
Also
Rothschild
Have you ever left Texas
Might be a little bit
Really projector
Sing his own insecurities about I haven't really done
You're projecting
So much
Hahaha
So at least you got that one in there David before you got
Yeah
He made that boat out of recycled plastic
Something about chimera
You become part of the
David Rothschild is not dead he is just part of
Panther
Rothschild
What else you got
Yeah let him fly
Just getting done with a stupid rant about to how all these
Aldi's
Climate change
People all want YouTube
For the polar bears
Propaganda
12 vets
Almost every man book
Especially ones that are around water
Booyakasha
Well if the issue is also more than like
As ice flows
Melt
What have you
They have less access
To where they get there
Destroy a habitat
That usually that is
Is more about destroying the
Disruptive
Skip
I just got it.
Because I can't have
This is right after that
After his polar bear
Riff
Gorgeous
Cross-species
Forrest I am worried about
Ancestors dead
I think it's the common translation
Rothschild
I believe
I'm not entirely sure but
Conspiracy
I don't know if it's actually the translation
But I can tell you this
When you're getting worked up and yelling at somebody
Configure money changing ancestors
That's f******
That's worse than a hard Jew
Really bad
To me is like
Oh boy
I can't believe that they go to Commercial and Rothschild still
After that
We have to do The Merchant of Venice bci's to
What is wrong with you
Brittany
I wish I had this kind of time on my hands
I was supposed to do 10 minutes with Alex Jones you started screaming at me and like
Temperature
How many years
Enikos
You enjoy me red shield
The big thing that Alex is doing their is appealing
To like you're weak
Like if you don't stay on the line that's because your weekend I'm just going to dunk on you for being weak
Right
You're too afraid of
You're not a
Semantics
It just out-and-out Integra
Which it doesn't work with David Rothschild there cuz he's not taking
Yelling at him like you're stupid or anything
But for some reason
Patiently trying to
Explain to it
Child what is
Is going on for some reason he still doesn't
Hang up I don't understand
So they go to commercial
And then they Come Back Inn hours
Go back from the break really Petty
But then he gets conciliatory
For unknown reasons
Like I have to imagine over the break he was like
I'm sorry
Of course
I don't know I think it's
It's probably more like Alex had no idea
Going to stick around
This is not going to wait
He didn't talk to him during a commercial break is 3 minutes
During the commercial
Alex did not expect this interview to go this
Alex has been
Yeah this entire time
You are weak
A look at how much of a man I am going to run away
I really do
Exactly
I'm still here
Keep this level of enter
Energy up so
Let's talk now
Might be that might be a pretty good
Something I'm coming back from
Because there's a war on for your mind and I hate the Jews
What most powerful
Powerball
Global ad campaign
It's official.
Pictures for them
Rothschild
Fluoride
Go ahead
This is
Every British joke about how polite British people are
Like this is every single
Even there
That's okay
Alright
You're going to act like a child so
But I guess that's where we're going to that goes
Why would you write a book
Plan is
Keep people from learn
Is very counterintuitive
Just for a little bit
Facebook in a little bit
Talking point
And David tries
I think you have to look at all the other things
Music free
Great job opportunity
Have a win-win situation
Is it
Cuz we need to stop
He's hitting that a little bit hard but at the same time
Do that's that's the reason
How many people
Change game
To all of this
Opposition b******* is because like
Oh I got a lot to lose like
He's as Rothschild
Before where we are now
Even then cleanup you wasn't growing anywhere near as fast as
Is it is right now
And right now it's
Bloating
Of course the best thing economically is to invest in
Clean energy
We're not doing that
Instead Trump has gone so far backwards it is offense
Beautiful
Clean Coal
Three words
We can't just continue to talk about
How how Trump is
Dealing
It's from people
Like if you want to talk about job creation
F****** subsidized
Creating all of these f****** jobs if that's going to be
It's all about creating jobs or whatever it is you do anymore
If your subsidized cleaners if you took
Half of the subsidies that you give to boil and cold and all that b*******
And gave it to clean energy
Go banana
Rebecca quick
Your bottom line by incentivizing
Let me be clear on this
A renewable energy
Carburetor
Solar cycle
By Major scientists of my Channel 4
The glaciers on Greenland
Your boy
So that's actually a really interesting
Funerals in increasing
CO2
Hey right now we're in the little ice age
Coming up over and over again like recently was
Steven
Crowder on louder with Crowder
Is it is a horrible
He recently on his website
Someone wrote about that
About
CO2
They got their information from an article in a tabloid called
The UK Express
The satirical article
Written by a guy who also wrote that such articles as moon is Hollow
That sounds right
97%
Are aliens green or solar energy
Images of monster UFOs circling son emerge
Alright that's okay
These claims
We're source to Evan claimed it was NASA
The Onion
Is
Reality there's
Pretty decent
Chance
Alex got his sword
Similar
This piece from
Express
ESPYs
They probably came from
Proto satirical
Using the same
Tired premise
Just misreading a an actual report
Entirely
Because there are there are sound
There's some reports
Come out that you could
Misread but it'd be way too difficult
Figure out exactly what
How do you say
It's just interesting
Difficult
The CO2 burning
Causes Cooling
And keeps coming
But be that as it may
Should so many
It's it's
Immensely frustrating
Because and this is this is another
This is another b*******
Think about it
Alex just says
No
2 facts
Right
Just look
You got your science I've got mice
My sinuses just
She's good as yours
My science is
Made up
Jim
He's a lord
What is science
Is what Alex
She's always ask
It's like seriously what is it is it
What what are we do are you studying things or are you just saying
You know what's the problem is that the scientific process
Requires like
Repeatability
Could ever imagine doing
Something difficult
Twice a review to my parents and that's
I can do that
So it is next by we learned that people is a scam created by British
Petroleum
Still struggle with why the f*** hasn't David Rothschild hung up the phone
You just said
Well that's because he doesn't know what he's argued
What we're saying is CO2 elevated levels
Please chicken out please again
That would be the best thing that could happen for me
Please do this don't
Stick around please Alex is like so pissed off
Come Around by this point he would have loved her perfect opportunity for us
Chicken out
They will tell you that
Does a pretty terrible
But there's no other way for this to go because
I think you're totally right he has to escalate it and keep the
I can't
Not to have the upper hand whenever this
Position that we're in
But
So when they go to Commercial and they come back
Here is Whitley
You can you can make whatever arguments you want they're about
You know
In terms of his rhetoric
Rothschild
You know you can say that that's fine there's an interesting conversation to have there
I don't think it's wrong
But I will say that I think he says
Totally wrong in this neck
He has to go to the play
No it's just in passing and it's not
I'm so like about that clip
Play boys hymns
Find me a science
Because that is not a
Textable
Against
These are
There's always going to be right
The scientist but
But if you if you say that they're going to find
And then
You're going to have
How to say okay well
Here's their source
This source is not pure review door if it is pure of you.
It's been debunked boring girl talk
Stuff
The moment that you engage on
Level
But unfortunately because David Rothschild gets
The order of the planets wrong in
In passing
He's going to go to town but it's the only thing that brings up whenever he discussed
Is this interview
He thinks Mercury is father
Closer to the Sun than Earth
Anyway
Discovery Channel
Faster than ours
When I'm at the Moon to Saturn and Jupiter
Rothschild
Define right
Continuous
Found that there is
Melting
S*** on Mars
Here's why it matters
Because Alex
To use this point as being like
I'd like a we're causing that
We're causing put stuff to Melton and it's stupid
Because
No one is
Disputing the idea that the
Causes
You know like that that sort of thing
Look
The Sun causes heat
He probably would say no.
Songs Frozen
The issue is
Specific numbers in front of me and I don't think I could
Explain this all the science
I did
Future climate scientist
To figure out o this is the portion of increase the
It's caused by
The solar
Affluent
Here's the amount that's caused by CO2
Here's what's caused by the increase in CO2
No there's been deforestation that actually bumps us down weirdly
Aerosolization
Reflect light back into space
It brings it down a little bit story out
Figure out where the
The stop is so this one here this beginning one
First one
The Sun
Part
Check the other planet
Right
Tugboat
Testable
Minimal Park
That is
Besotted
Who plays in our own
Climate change
As opposed to the other piece
But have much more
The consequences
Cosby
Are being affected
The planet
Also Mars
An interesting planet
Everything
Atmosphere which means there's very little thermal inertia
The climate is much more
Susceptible to change
Caused by
External
That's the reason
Life exists here and not there
Bright and also here's the other part like
David Rothschild is wrong in terms of like the
Orbitz
Perfect Circle
And so sometimes
Planets are closer to the Sun than others
And sometimes bars it
Because it has an orbit
Distance
Between
It's closer than
We are too also means
Is that certain
Times are going to be much
Warmer is it
The Sun the Earth is going to be
Hotter it's
Call Dara.
I had an Amana
Make device to remember the order
So I wouldn't have
By David Ross
Rothschild
Really what was that
I am ashamed of this but I came up with it in like 5th grade
Is what was it
I my very erotic monkey Jackson
Best pillow
It works
And it just stuck with me
But it's hard to forget once you hear that is that your brain
Brake fuel line
Mentality
Respect your opinion
If you look at the sign
The police's about planet the company
Definitely think
Accompany
That's a very important
Pizza Vista Alex never
Of course not
The climatic stuff
Carbontex Duffy's
You
What's another
It's polluting business
Assistant
Your children
Married
What's your favorite song
I think it's going to be something along the lines of
You p**** ass holes says what
But I heard him say that I'm like
Man playground time is, childish
We have 10 minutes of audio lag
Haha into clips
Cuz I just couldn't cut him off
This is just
The first one is labeled this is a such a mess
Evan the next one is
Disastrous M2 the call
So you got to look forward to
It's never it's never going to help me when I need to find
Six months from now if I can find one of these clips what do they say this is a mess
Don't help
That's it.
Argument
He's always like
Look at the Sun
If Alex
Capable of looking at
It would already be right
Fifty-seven percent of people at this time who don't think man-made climate
Of looking
It wouldn't be an issue
Be done
That's why they are
You can't
Like there's no way
Kicking and screaming
To survive
Because they're going
Look
That's
For being more alarmist
Is
Less about
This is how we should
Convince
My suspicions
That beat
Cuz scientist
Have received
Blowback
Search of a fight all across the board
They've been far more
Conservative
In the way that their couch
What about of them when they're wrong about anything
So sure and so conservative
They wind up
Underselling
The issue
Like if you say
The climate is going to be destroyed
What you should be saying is that the refugee issue in
2015 or 2025
Is going to be so on
Untenable
The world is going to
Eat itself alive
Population is not going to
To be destroyed by
Climate change
It's going to be destroyed
By the way
Climate change
Nexstar political set
With a serious with all of the
These places when you start
Massive drought
That last
For a long time
You end up seeing this place
When you
Displacement you see people being f***
2 people who have
Nobody likes
Refugees apparently everybody hates immigrant
Send this f****** country
What is going to destroy it
It's not going to be massive
Weather patterns is going to be the small things
That you don't rip not small things but
These these long-term things that you don't really
The main
The main result of climate
Change
The
Like
Your set your talk
Droughts and stuff like that
If you look at the history of like let's say China
Even in
Non
Climate change
Massive drops that have left
The millions and millions
Now you see that pattern of weather shifting a little bit worse than it
MC millions and millions
Tens of Millions
Dying
That that extending into parts of Russia
You know that's what those weather pattern
I'm going to end up with
Everyone's
Do I get a really interesting
Sing today about Finland
And the way that they responded to
The starvation
Experience
40 years ago something
Along those lines
And the way that they reacted to it is
They're like the argument was there now
Nationalist
Much like
You know
Nationalism
Born out of
Destruction
It's like we it's up to
Against the world.
Their nationalist however
We're run by college professor
And all the sudden in that time frame now Finland is
In the top five in every possible category
Successful
Nation probably
It's
It's so it's so
Bases you will wind up building something
That is so much
Much more solid
And so much more
Stable
You could
Let not
Please run the government
That's also
That's also a possibility
Cuz this is the
It's a little long
One more question for you
The fact that
NASA
Shower system warming and its
Record show
Sorry recording glitch
Lots of carbon dioxide
Muddying of the issue
He gets into
We are now in a carbon
So that's that's what happened
Really been in somewhat of a dead
At the North Pole and the South Pole
Ears
Weekend
Very stable
Directions incredible
Weld
Differential differential
We have one planet
We know the office
Change radio
Here's working
Real ugly
This is where it's going to go
He's calling
I'm afraid I
I just want to tell you something
That is
All of that
Like that
Not going to end well
Tell you something
You're great guy you know what I really think
I love that he's been in a relationship
He's been on the line for over half an hour and like just been putting up with Alex's
Patty abuse
And nonsense
Circular thinking all this diversion
In arguments whenever he's trying to make a point to some other nonsense
I'm finally he's just like
I got to go
You don't have any common sense
This is this is not worth it
I've got a guy got to go
Mallory tell you this
He doesn't go
You still on the line
Until they go out to commercial break
Which
Is weird but he's I got to go and then here's why
Your family has caused a lot of pain in this world
Look what you're doing
I love that he's like your family is caused a lot of problem
The time in Napoleon
Talking about and I loved David Rothschild
Response was
Okay
He hasn't heard all this stuff before
Email
Alarm
You can come and join us
He's coming family reunions
Alex
I will fucken take him up on
Hilarious
There is no
Cannot do that
Because if they were kind to him
It would be just like if it like it's just like the Nation of Islam
You know what they want if he went to the family reunions
Are the Rothschilds
I used to say they were globalists but I'll tell you what they're actually
Secret infoworld secret Patriots who owns child
Apply for the Patriot
Flag entire worldview
Such nonsense so you know what I bet
Which we all know he is
He's actually
I found the clip it I'm not playing here
Estrella show I don't remember exactly what it was but
It's definitely during the presidential
Campaign
And Alex has Daniel estulin
Went on who's the guy who's a Bilderberg
Researcher
Games
But I do
I don't know how I didn't catch this interview
But Daniel estulin
Hillary Clinton
Is back by the Rockefellers
I'm Trump
Is backed by the Rothschild
Another Rothschilds are actually on the good side of things
It's like
Alex is nodding and being like you
That's nonsense
There's no
Ruler
Alright other than bigotry
Coming to dinner
But
Alex
Merryweather rocket
Exactly
Oh yeah
So anyway
I love this
I think it's really interesting to point out I saw this in the chat room that
David Rothschild
Does making
Do not hate the ultra-rich so much
Right and I think it is important
To remember that they are people
Still
And often people of good humor and I think on a case-by-case basis someone like David
Could be
Using his wealth
And his time and effort
It's in really good
Soup like ways that you would support
Probably have a really good
Sense of humor about himself
And be well-adjusted and a pretty cool guy
It seems like that's possible
Even if
Unattainable
Strata of
I've been born into Billy
You know it's not
If it's not mutually exclusive
It's a percent
Percentage is bad
Right
Listen
Find me a rich person
And I'll look into it
Lego
97% of rich people agree that we
Tell rich people is that what I'm saying
Statistics from
Northern California
Your family
The strictly speaking
You guys are worth trillions of dollars
So Alex is
Belief that the Rothschilds run
He's right into the 5G
Do bankers conspiracy
I found this really interesting breakdown
Like these claims
Things with the Rothschilds
Own the
Monetary fund
And all that
Will they keep
Like
The people who make these claims
Keep reference
Rothschild Bank
Those Banks Donuts
Do they keep referencing like these ads what they want
Well they aren't
Real real
So is all of this stuff in it it does it does
Sincerely come back
2D 5
Kind of ideas
And the fact that Alex Jones is
Repeating is Waterloo bulshit
And this entire narrative memes
Of course
Bohemian Grove
I want to know if we'd like to talk to her
No
Because
I used to run an open-mic where people could
Could just talk about whatever
Me and my friend Matt
Interrupt
Ask for clarification
I'm trying help improve their jokes
And one of the guys who came to the open
Said that he worked Boheme
Mangrove
Me and Marty DeRosa we're doing the show later he happened to be there
He came onstage and we talked in bubble Union Grove
Haven't seen
I think you just moved
That's entirely possible.
Can any risk when talking to people who may know something they shouldn't know any of that stuff so anyway
You think I'm sorry
What was it
Situation
Infowars.com
Any other information
I was
Good night.
So anyway
You've written a book for children
Ridiculous what is
Is that's so great
So great
F******
Trying to Railroad somebody never speaking
Trying to get someone to fight with you and they're just not playing it playing along
Play the recording of him
I'm talking like there's no reason for David Rothschild
Be there
Alex just wanted to yell at
It's pretty weird though
I mean
There is a reason in the Granderson
Can say that he has him on the Shelf boiler alert
Endgame the only
Miniclip they play which I don't
Coincidence
Is Alex Jones screaming your money changing ancestors
That clip is what they play at
That's the part that
This is dog-whistle somatic literally anti-Semitic
Just does not mean anything different no other different meaning to that other than
But he can play like
A couple of clips of like
Screamed at a Rothschild have you
That's her thing it now but I've written the children
You can boost his stature in that Community because
He has like I got the job
If you listen to the whole thing
He's being very reasonable and very polite
This is
I wasn't
Whenever we started talking I was kind of hoping that
This would be
More fun
This is really sad
This is pathetic
If you if you listen to
Listen to this
Alex did a great job
You're a sad person
Like there's no other way to describe this other than
A pathetic
Weak-willed man easily yelling in fear if you if you buy into anything
You saying like
Like you're just either easily distractible you're not following
Conversation
Whatever
I do support people putting
Stickers over-and-over Infowars
To the chat room
But I will not make it knowledge fight
Cigarettes cuz I don't have that kind of money
I don't have that Rothschild money.
Yeah let's finish up this the end of this clip
Lord Rothschild you know that your house will fail in the end and you know
I want to let you know that anyone who supports the New World Order
There you go ladies and gentlemen
Bring me some food
Having a bio out on yourself where you call yourself
Unadventurous
So that's how it ends
You're going to prison I know that's pretty great
Just want to make sure you know that
He is to die horribly
Okay could
You bring me some food in prison
I absolutely love David
Rothschild
Response
You go to prison
Sure sure
They're Alex
Will you alike
Okay will you come visit me in prison
Maybe bring me some
Some food and then Alex's
Bring me some
Bayou
I pulled up Alex Jones bio
Infowars.com
Since the beginning of time
Since the beginning
Constitutive
Enslaving subdue the human
Spirit from Barbarian horde streaming down the mountain
To the Stasi secret police
Torturing
In this age of rapidly accelerating
80 technology
The threat to our liberties
Is very real and a present danger
Voice
Through the information it exposes the underlying intention
Every time he read that he
Calling yourself an adventurer is not
That much
Wharfside save insane
You're the voice that technological Barbarian hordes yourself
Purple
Better or worse than calling yourself
The savior of humanity
Alex Jones Infowars from-the-ground-up
Prophets
Grow exponentially exponentially is cap
Alex has never taken alone
Is the hold is not Behold Him to advertisers
Anymore
Investors or any other group that could center influence
Disposition
Are Alex's Park
Or customers
And Israel to honor their trust
Truly and depend
Until it is firing authoritarian comes along
This guy is great
Yep Alex Jones
The internationally recognized by many
Is a trailblazer of New Media icon
The burgeoning Liberty
This goes on it
Really long
Mac Jones
Constitutionalist idea
In addition to what he has coined
76 worldwide
Promoting a true culture of Liberty transparent
Empower Humanity
Bobby Bentley opposing Agenda 21
His bio he's 21
Sovereignty
96 worldwide
But also he's fighting against Nash
National anybody taking down Nash
National sovereignty
How is that possible
Wiggle room in
Spirit of Thomas Jefferson and George Washington
Passionately argues against
Political labels of left and right
Instead focuses on what really matters
And wrong
Which is always the left there is a right
Career
Reading tenacious journalist
Yeah
Jones's recognized
Dead Space 4
Yeah it is
Alex Jones is recognized
Hard-hitting interviews at the wide range of gas
Prominent guests include Willie Nelson
Charlie Sheen
Joe Rogan Russell Brand
I got to find the Russell Brand
Norris
Lou Dobbs
Incorrectly
Correctly
His incisive interviews
Yeah he only listen lever
You know what's weird the next paragraph includes another list of celebrities
It's still going beautiful David Lynch
We got to fight back
Absolutely
Viggo Mortensen
What
Alex misses more surreal than anything I've ever made
Gore Vidal we got to fight that God dammit
Public Enemy
Disputed the official explanation
Received the bench
Stream notice
CNN Showbiz tonight
Cuz it was Charlie Sheen
Okay
Alright
There's even more this goes arms
Aunt Bee
There can't be more
Wow
Documentary
Endgame terrorstorm
The order of death
Obama Deception
Fabled enemies
Alright
What that bio is
Is
Kim Jong
That's what that is
Fearless leader
Right there
He is he is all of these things the more you have to list your accomplishments all day unless you accomplished
Sprite
I'm so Eva Springs
Once again pushed us into an unfortunate territory of
Defending someone who is a billionaire
Yeah I'm alright with it
Like I believe
In
Organization of
Like workers organizing and gaining power over political system
Or workplace systems
I believe in that wholeheartedly I believe in
The average citizen being
Mostly in
Control
With some exceptions
You got to live in essence
A political system if you are going to
To build something along those lines but it's actually sustainable and that will a
Provide
BFF the incentive
Search produce
You wind up creating a system wherein
You have a
Very high bottom
At a very low top
But there is still a
Between the two
Like there's always going to be
A division of
You know
The people who are
The most
What
Celebrated or celebrity along those lines
If you're talkin about
Absolutely
If you're talking about a sustainable
Economy
To be an incentive for you to
To create things
Incentive
For you too
Expand your business other the
Them just like
Status back
Enter whatever it is you have that higher level
The company
But if the guy who owns the company is making
Times with the guy who works
Search for the company is
It's an unsafe
Sustainable systems
If the guy who owns the company makes
Three times with the lowest what's the lowest guy is
Then you have
A separation
That provides the incentive necessary to
Want to make your own
Company while at the same time giving you the Comfort necessary
In order to make a sustainable economy
Anyways what I'm saying is that it is not necessarily the fault of rich
People that the rich are the single worst people that have ever existed
But what I am saying is that
Guillotine
A great idea
I wasn't how I wanted to end this
It's
No
What
School
I want to live
Interesting
And what we've
Experienced and I always
I always enjoy forcing you to humanize
People that you scream about
It is such a
How awful is Alex
Jones
Generally speaking
The
Like just
Having a basic level of human
Makes me like you
Like something that should be
Love you I all the sudden become such a rare
Commodity
Right
Yeah you can go to iTunes or you can join the Avengers Initiative
The show
Knowledge fight Gmail.
A screenshot of yourself having
Posted
On an internet forum
Some sort or a Facebook page
I'm some sort of another popular podcast
Or show like to help us ride other people's wake please do so
Trying to expand
Message
The way we're doing in terms of like Facebook ads
Twitter ads or any of that stuff
Don't media want to cover us and no it's not going to work
So if you
If you can do that we would appreciate it
Take a screenshot
Send it to knowledge fight at gmail.com
Coming soon
There will be a special
Soundbite
It will be
Ridiculously long
Full of Alex Jones
In the style of the policy wonk
Not using
I found
An exclusive
To what I think I'm going
Each person who does it I'm going to give them the name of one of the
People in The Avengers
So I think Ironman and Thor are taken
You guys
You should be ashamed
Judging by your face
A little bit
Anyway we appreciate everything you're all so much
This is been a delight
So who sucks
I think
I'm going to have to go with go f*** yourself Lord
Moncton
Holding
Sprouts Market
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work