Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Infowars
Over a nice glass of wine with my friend
He is
Today we have
I've been thinking about I know that in our early episodes you speculated that we would find an understanding evolve
Alex so that you start to empathize with him
I've got to be honest
I'm starting to hate
I used to be sort of amused released
Curious I think I hate him
My feelings about him are so very complicated
Sure physical attraction
There's no doubt the super male vitality
I don't have a clip of this
It's called caveman
No
You know what it is
I just hope it's a big slab of me know better
Ground-up bones
An actual they break into the ocean
Listening to the commercials but he was
Explaining how like animals or go after bones first cuz I want to get the marrow and all the stuff around
I'm on board so far
Do they grind them up
They put in a pill
And they sell it to you
What
Delete sense of anything I've ever heard I think that's what the product is
What is
That is legit
The best way for a serial killer 2
Keller
People in
Don't know if the FDA has got to get involved
Vitamins
Sure they're good
It was just announced
Wednesday show
So this is breaking
This is gooses huge
Time goes on
Today the reason that we had to do what we got to do this episode I know we had an episode come out yesterday
Mental Health
Scare of the world
Panera college campuses or
But it was important
Looking like lurking like
A Batman
But we had to get back together
Evercord another episode because
In the time between when we recorded the Rapaport episode
Mike Flynn
General Flynn resign
Finally stepped down
Fastest
In history
Which is just beautiful
Yeah we're living we're living in
Perfectly normal time
Yeah I have a response
Let's do it we knew that he was going to he loves General Flynn
Swimming towards link
Like he's like the two of them
I'm certain that Alex's doctor
I'm certain
Conversation
And unlike where else is playing
Flynn has his own Supply
It's not need anybody else
Albert setso
Look
Start a farmer
Something like that
I will look at his future career and retired General
Did the
I lost my train of thought but we we knew that Alex was going to be
Like losing it
This is my thought
Next week
All he was talking about is like I got inside information
Reince priebus
Booty calls
Is going down
He's a snake in the grass
Priebus
He's the one who's leaking that like
Trump is wandering around in his bathrobe
Paul Ryan acolyte
Who is actually funded by George Soros
Yep.
Complex deep state
So for the whole last week is going down I want to break it for you on Monday
Tomorrow we're going to get into the Lakers
Tuesday
Flocking
Is Outback
Rebus Stillwater
Stay in
The office
What do you mean
I mean before because all over the place
Square
The day before Flynn resign
People were being like
Are you still going to stay in there this it is
Completely unstable it's all it's all fake news and
Forget anything that's negative Alex doesn't talk about
Inconvenience
He'll talk about the leaks in the inside sources that he has probably telling him
Like 2 days 3 days ahead of time
Probably out
You not going to talk about that on the air
Really so you know
Don't actually have sources
Yeah I know kid we've established that most of the stuff comes from
Call Ann from people who direct message Paul Joseph Watson on Twitter
As well as evidence examples of that
Still however imagine
Late night song
Dude I thought they liked me
Alex
I know but I got some
Bone pills
You know I have my own
You don't know what you got
Until you don't
You don't I'm getting it anyway you don't have
On Tuesday
Pennywise
Yes hey let me tell you what I found
The sliny was okay nevermind
Book for his broadcast
Cuz he needed to make an emergency
F******
Signal
Bat signal flying he put out an emergency broadcast before
His for our show you put out a 40-minute
Quip
Infowars.com my friend
No wait on their YouTube channel
And it's
What were mostly going to be dealing with
Is this broadcast
And here's why I'm is it a drill
It is not a through hell
An emergency
Yeah
More than the actual episode Excel
Is because the actual episode
Is super repetitive
And he's just hitting talking point
And over and over again
Escape
Adjust Hammer this repetitive eels in the mud
80 in this image underground just go to that lalalalalalala
On his show for Tuesday
Okay
But
It just went out today
The faithful
On his
On his own network yet supposed to be broadcast
On all the radio.
Virginia
Didn't hear
He gets weird
Ono so this is pure concentrated Alex
Okay so that's what we're going to be talkin about
Here's the first clip this broadcast
And get to
To the central thing we should all be afraid of
It's Tuesday
February 14th 2017
I'm about to go live
RadioShack TV broadcast in about an hour and 8 minutes
Dude weedmaps.com my show
But I had to come in early
The breakdown
I want to say really quick to
I didn't lengthen any of the
Deposit
To get this emergency message
Slowly
The clip has started
Samantha
The reason this is so important
Is that I have studied
The Deep state
30 years
Completely active the 25 you know that I never 21 years
Books on eBay
If you go back and read those books
1670 18th
20 years ago
Well I wasn't present
The Grammys in the enemy's in
What big TV show
That is dumb down just information but
Like Foreign Affairs put out by The Washington Post
Council on Foreign Relations
Application or bi-monthly
Tell you what they're doing
Articles in foreign affairs that came out yesterday
Now this isn't to Hollywood producers
This isn't
Hollywood
Dishes
Cheese
Our Lord
Snowcoach
Is it totaled
Roll over your dead
So here is where we finally understand one of the things that
Play goodness for a really long time
What the f*** is he talking about when he talks about white
Yes
That is exactly what it was like
Newspapers like what
Red and black and the white papers
Both of them the global if they're speaking to
Indeed
Fuel for the Illuminati
Foxtrot
Heathcliff
Lived in a f****** dump
Not adults are you lived in a junkyard
Oh that's right
1st phorm
The papers are part of it
And I'm not saying that whenever he says white papers what he's talking about is
Is referring to is
He says
Foreign affairs
Turtle he's actually talked about it called foreign policy
Write an essay I know that
Yeah I know that
The other one that he mentioned
Yeah wait by the Washington
He's not himself later
Foreign policy
There's a little bit of a denser news
Where is the Council on Foreign Relations
Could not what they're going to do
How do you get to save
How do you get to say that like that
They put it out in public
Just do it
Is there going to kill Trump
Well
Here here is where we're going to be being literal or
I think you being literal equations that I've had
Succumb to the beginning of the show
I have to temper that with
Again a little bit of pity deep-seated
Didn't animal love
Lacks the ability to
To comprehend what he's reading
Sometimes
Deciding understand what they're saying
There's a third possibility that I think it's more likely
Human bites
Have a slight
Paranoid
Schizophrenia
I know somebody
A really good question
We're going to start to see him reading a ton of things into stuff that just literally isn't there
Holyshit
So the foreign policy article that he's fighting
First of all doesn't say
In any way
Suggest that people should kill Trump
That's probably a prosecutable offense right
It always say putting it in a major publication
It also doesn't say any of the things that he later says it's
But also
The idea
That there is a magazine
Foreign policy
That for 20 years
Or however long it's been out
In existence
He's been putting the Illuminati
Play book out there into the public
And for 20 years Alex Jones has been on the air yelling about
30 years
20 years on the air
He's been yeah yeah yeah
He's like 42 or something 47
Just call it the moment he
Papa pube
Peter peace
He was so afraid of
Immediately went directly to foreignpolicy.com
This childhood I think his dad might have had some of that paranoia
I don't know
Because because even if we go back to our
That was full-on learned
Right
I think he is
Right now
Finally watching the full on break from real
Reality starts to sleep in and more people like Flynn
End up getting indicted
He shut those strong indications he's straight-up lied to the FBI
There's
Indication
They're not strong indications their actual from information
We have
The truck
In the media is a really good point because a lot of information
Are relying on is released by the
They are and have never been
Trustworthy
You have to take things with a grain of salt
It does have that ring of because
Trump in Flint
Talk s*** about the
Communautaire like
Go back to the code of the streets
You think about
All of the s*** that Barack
That seems so out of
Character for what
He really
I like believe what you would imagine
He seems like a guy with compassion
Wouldn't want to go crazy town
On whistleblowers and
So you start to see all of this should come out
Quickly these guys are being destroyed
What they
Huh
Yeah that he
Frank Marshall Davis was his dad
Crack addict who has a transgender
What is he
Just really was
That's it that's it
Smoked
Remember remember when we were mad at
Smoking
Freezing anyway
Speaking of that light treason
Archie Bunker
Divide Illinois
Drinking Boone's Farm cuz we don't deserve nice things
He gets into the situation with
What's playing and his interpretation of it
And when he's done we can agree
Of course his resignation
Now
Truth-seeking in Flynn's resignation doesn't in controversy surrounding White House
General Flynn
With other military leaders to say no to backing Al-Qaeda
In Syria in The Killing 100,000 people
It was a great moral moment for our military
Decided to not follow
Criminal lawyers
Play the following four decades
Bala
Jesus mom
And so she knows about all this plan
They released the communicators that Flynn supposedly
Security advisor
At that time December 15th
Who was the president elect
Working around the clock
Against the law
CIA
State Department
He's supposed to talk to you
He said the president's policy
The president
The present
Exactly what a Russian spy would say
Inflating the truth
Like
Until
Your brother
Europe
But still
How did the Riviera Resort
Citizens
Adventure sworn in position
I was just straight-up I have been
Released
Recording they absolutely have it
But from sources who have listened to them
They all
Save that he was very
Who is it talking about
One Source even said
It isn't possible that he wouldn't remember talked about it the entire phone call was about
Is Slim's phone and spying on him
Tapping the Russians phones
I actually have always monitored
Those
That's the thing that came out
Was under underreported text
But
They're listening to
The American communication
Fuquay-Varina
They are listening to
American communicate
But that's not necessarily have to be true
Miki spying on Flint
They were spying on these it was collected
Like this story
Save
They saw that Russia wasn't
Retaliating
Which seems so out of character
For them and they were saying they were surprised by that to the point where they
Dick Baxter this
Length of time
50 what may event was communicating with Viaduct
Caught up on
The tapes
Communicate
Now
The interesting fact
The case you don't think so I think they were listening in real time
How I imagine a reel-to-reel
You're talkin about
Okay you're right
My fantasy is more fun
What was the Logan Act
They were like the more you read about it
Avista Subs
And nobody has been prosecuted will doors one guy
The new movie coming out
Predator
I can't I can't believe that it's never happen
In that length
Sure
It has to have there has to have been those civilians that
Have gone outside
And negotiated
Almost there
I don't
Could have imagined
This
Sweetly blatant
Pretty obvious the laws there breaking are ones that
People don't even
Think about
Because it seems so stupid to break those laws
The way that they're doing
Brazenly
Brazen the phone calls line up with when
Trump was like very smart of Vladimir Putin.
Insinuates
Agree with Alex
Hey I'm resigning is going to just put more blood in the water if not allowed him to
That's a really good
It's kind of showing a little bit
I'm showing that You're vulnerable
He doesn't want to give that perception
He's not playing a good
Kmart
Cards here
Soccer never had to play this game of cards as bad as there's a lot of Tails going around
It seems like it's
Seems like they are
They're just
They like the Republic
Congress is
As much b*******
7 / 0
Exact
It's not not going
Based on what
True now
I do I do
You absolutely believe that
Should be
Arrested
Prosecuted
Interesting theories about him that I can't because I don't
I couldn't articulate them well
But I've read some interesting write-up
That suggests
Might be
Not as bad as dude
Is
It appears
I'm not sure about this and I don't want a voucher that cuz it look bad
Basically ruined America almost 8 again
This is a pretty compelling argument
Carolina eighteen-year-old Russia
Hackerone that's it I strongly recommend you guys look up the
North Carolina
Russian hacker
Basically
There there
The theory is he cat
Anthony Weiner
16 year old girl
Yeah
Was then the
Because it was a crime
Look into
His laptop
And that's whatever some
Hillary's emails
It seems like the most
Rube Goldberg spy right it's not
Super like
It's not the most believable
But there's some pieces of it that kind of
You know it makes you think a lot
I end up sounding like Alex himself crazy nonsense
Visit these are interesting ideas
But I don't know if they're true
I won't
Blame
Spiracy
Whenever
Ignorance and incompetence
Yeah
Speaking of Icarus
Alex wants
So tell you
Jordan
Jordan Holmes from
I will be so mad if you got a shout-out Netflix
Clearly because I'm the least dangerous between
Every single time he says
I'm so convincing
So you're basically as much as
It's just getting close
Getting close little flickers going on
In the world
Explain what's going on here
Rebellion
Speak that if you don't
No we can think Machiavelli we know it's not good
People
Let's build an infrastructure let's build a space program
Technologies developed
That's not a wimpy
You know silly worldview
Oh you're silly everybody's evil that won't work
Usually doesn't like to use
There's already.
He's not a goddamn Russian
Because it's not playing all these really
Here you can see it in his face
Pissed off
And then
Like that
Bulshit he just dropped had a lot of
Couldn't stop it from coming out
The Regular Show
He means more
Is this sounds very real
Foreign policy article again he calls it foreign affairs
He will straighten
Kind of sidetracked
Really nobody
Paul Watson link to the
Fidget spinners
About Trump
Read
These articles
I'm guessing because
Read
He does not
$3
The mouth of Lucifer
They say they're at
Foreign affairs
Which again is only for love
They put it out
And
They're like war on truth
Get your truth here but now
Whatever
He says someone else is doing is what he's doing he has about the globalist putting all this stuff
Up and didn't know that you're too dumb to go read it
That's him talking about his listeners
Reading the sources you talk to
He's projecting his own feeling of his audience being dumb
I bet it has to be
The articles that he cites contradict what he say
Consist
That's a really good
That's a really good point there's almost like
I don't get the
Complete unconsciousness
Is it like somehow the truth is trying to get out
This goes back to I think that the truth about him is
One part may be a little bit bigger part paranoia a huge part lack of writing
Yeah lack of reading comprehension
Okay
Baby
You know Texas Public Schools didn't do him a great service
Want I want
No more about it
Personal life to see if there are like
Full-on paranoid
Schizophrenic
Really
Scary to think about it I tried to find biographies about him or anything about his life in
There's really not a ton about his early life but you can find some sources
And actually there's an episode of the dollop about Jade Helm where they talk about his early life a little bit
Some sources talk about is how when he was in high school
He was convinced
That people selling drugs
To the kids
We're working
Are they were like
Entrapping kids
That works for the school
Yes been that guy for like 30 years
If you've also based on his self-reporting of himself when he was younger
If you believe him he did have a paranoid
Sort of ideations when he was young
Who cares
Concern
Yeah
To laughing at a mentally ill
Who needs help but the problem is
He's a great showing
He's a great Showman
And
His entire premise is
Anti him getting help
Such a damaging awful part of our culture
We can't
Okay now
Here is my theory based on what you just said for why the print industry
For Global
Yeah there can't be that many
No
Published
For Global oh man we're going to learn something else about globalist
It's really tragic
At the end of this episode 2
They realize the lies don't work
About to execute
Really horrible devastation
Starting huge Wars
DC anyting
Obama
Bunker
Is it in the news
2 miles from the White House and is recruiting with Soros and army
Bolshevik Revolution
That's not true
What what news would have that on there without there's no article on Breitbart
Ugh by the very barrister
Definition
That links to an article in the New York Post
And that's the only source on it
Pulled it up and read it
There's no real evidence
That
Militarized bunker
Throwing the article in the article
Institutional scholar is
Recruiting an army
In the article the only relevant
Citations that are made about Obama at all or 1
Hyperlinks clip
Are I'm sorry
How that is
Is about
Obama
Protest
I'm deciding
Former President Barack Obama
Anti-trump protests
He was sending a message of approval to his troops
Fruits
Yes
Obama has an army of agitators numbering more than
We'll fight as Republicans
Historic present
Already showing a little bit of
What does no Citation for this 30000 number or the fruit this is absurd
Give me an idea of
What
The hiring process
Well they put
Know what it is all about is that Obama is working with that organization organizing for action
No community
I like how a cow
Still on
Is there big
Boogeyman
F****** with the middle of nowhere
Orchestrating all of
Trump millions and millions of
All of them names
The claim that
Soros
Got this bunker in the army
Bolshevik
That was crazy
The only way you can take that is truth is if you read the Breitbart article that have no source
Okay go ahead and read that it's not it's
Not news
It is absolutely not verified it's not source
It is
Basically you're not smart enough to
To see that that's the only way globalist
Communicate with e
Each other is on
This isn't even in foreign policy
Lincoln
That's right it would have to be
Guys get excited Obama starting this bunker up
Foreign policy newspaper that
They send out
To each other
Mostly about
I woke up I've never.
You can see little actually
You don't feel like there is a
It was a coup Over America under globalism by stealth with a counter-coup a trump
They're launching a counter counter to right now and there's
Incredible things going on right now
This is an amazing time to be alive
I feel sorry for
Weather
When they come out
And these articles
And they say everything I said but from their perspective
It's
My analysis
And not because you listen to me but because he
How old
No hard good people are fighting to try to give them Freedom it's just
I think he is
It's almost too much to ask
It's it's
Okay we're not going to lie anymore
We stole
System
He wants either because they want their own power
He's going to bring it all
Pictures of six.
This is the devil
This is trying to say that that's what the article is saying
The antitrust
No
You saying that the globalist
Through this foreign policy article
Are trying to say to the Russian
Hey guys come on come join us against Trump
And that's where the counter is happening because the original
Counter-coup was when the rush
Actions were on his side
No no
You're so wrong
Tricom
My bad my bad
Cooler
Product
Come see Avatar knowledge fight store.com
The original
Was a soft
That was done by Hillary Clinton
And George Soros
And Barack Obama
To get her the Press
Yes send it to Merica with jihadis and we'll have you and sell us out to the chai,
That was the original
Behind the scenes there was another soft coup
There was done by people who were
In the intelligence communities
Working with Russia
Okay so we all want to talk about
Do Russians were kind of working on it
Patriots within the intelligence
Community where the ones who leaked all those emails to WikiLeaks and what have you
And
That's her counter kittens original counter
Spouted by like Rodger Stone
Steve pieczenik whenever they come on the show they pitched the
Counter-coup narrative
Yes
Then the counter counter-coup
I suppose
A man
The globalist fightback I don't know
Counter counter counter counter
Doobie
I did I do I reject
That arguments
To be like
Coup as an artist
If there's a coup
And you're saying that there's a counter-coup I've never heard this many times in a row
If there's a counter-coup
And you're arguing that
You can't then be surprised when there's a counter company
Text Justin
There hasn't been one kuya
No we're just on the run the roads
I got like a
So yeah you know Alex
Roosevelt
Takes a lot to get him scared you scared
View
Reading way more devilish things into this article that
Very clearly
I've read this article 45 time
Yeah I've read it over
There's a couple things that I think you could really seriously misrepresent and I think he does
And once he starts to get into
More of a substance of it all explained
Describe what the Arctic
But for now he wants
What's the talk little bit
About
The
Can you get the little bit distracted again
Always gets distracted which with
Which dimension is he
Distracted with this time
This clip is where he realizes that the name of the
The article are the eternals
Himself
So ends up having a Phillips
Discourse with himself
About the nature of honesty that is
F****** fantastic
I think I can't wait to listen
He says that is if it's the article's title
It's not
That's the title of the article on Infowars that tall Joseph son wrote
Which
Which uses
The article in Florence
But it never says that anywhere inside the article name of the archelon
Then the extra cold because their propaganda
Gina keep in mind
Is just literally
A weak lie
Now we'll get to the office
I see foreign policy but
I always tell the truth even when I make a mistake and policy is find a article
Emma Watson post public
Your brain takes
Information
They just want that stigma
Compare that to the average person who's totally unconscious cannot please everybody feel like me
Stolen
Proof
There's a lot there
Crazy
Yeah there's a lot there
That's
Play that again like halfway through
Okay
Like I so hard that you liked
But your brain takes
Information
The average person who's totally unconscious
He could have
Oops
1000%
Spiraled into some kind of weird
Have to be always right
Even though I made a mistake
What I really did was that a Freudian
Flip but of the truck at the beginning when I was
It's forward affairs with foreign policy
I wasn't saying that I was just being fully
Informational
Championship
20 times when it was Gavin McInnes
Super easy to make
You know what I was being truthful even when I wasn't because Nigel McGuinness is a pro wrestler
F****** crazy
Used to be like me
What is what is that years ago everybody used to be like him what does that mean
You might know that because of ancestral memories
Descendants
If if there is like if
If he really does have a narrative
Through-line
Everything he believes
Like if you just be the whole pie
Picture like
Beautiful makeup
Zodiac Killer the guy searching for the string
Volume up together that's
I work at a straight-up
Just turn this into 1
And then I'm just going to start peeing and all these empty wine bottles never never leave my room
And that's how Trump
He's finally gets into a little bit more about
The article
But still doesn't real
You read this stuff and it's just like
Revolution
Come up with Garrett with you
Chilling
We're going to kill him
They even announce the one lie they tell is their biggest truth
They say in two different articles I read that go
Is canceled the Bolshevik Revolution celebration
And they say
He did that
Revolutions now
He's part of the revolution
And they're trying to mop-up timing is entitled hardliners in our government right now
I'm going to go ahead and more of an old hardliner than Putin himself
Probably not a single most hardliner they're also he
He came up with an amazing zip code
Telling is actually the
The truth
That is the sound of one like lap
That's amazing
I have the article here
In 2016 a senior Russian official explain to a group of visiting for orders why the government decided not
To celebrate the upcoming 100th anniversary of the Bolshevik Revolution
Yes it was a turning point in Russian history he argued and yes
President Vladimir Putin
Please today's Russia is
Successor to both
Bazaars and the Bolshevik
But celebrating a revolution
It would send the wrong message
Society
The Kremlin today
Today is
The visitors were told Enda
Skittish about eulogizing 19:7
They plan to use the scent
Centenary
Santana Row
To solve social and political
That is the
Fat
But he's taken
That part from
To regime change
Especially when
Russian
Regime-change
Right
You see the difference between the text
And what is interpretation is
The other stuff about
Okay the others always keep
Hidden between the
Course
It's always
You tried like circling the
The first letter of every word in one of those
Susannah putting it
Together
Haven't seen what the
Do I did put like rice wine vinegar on my
My phone comes up after text
So far.
My phone is not operating very well.
Little bit more
It's a little bit more religious
Revolution now
He said it was bad communism was bad
Christ Providence
Huge
None of that was in the article
Is there any evidence
Other than
How much
Gay people
That he is
Is in any way a like a
Christian
I don't know
This is like does he attend like a Russian Orthodox Church
I don't know I've never really been too interested in just lives
A shirt
Chico's
They would be disrespectful
It would be disrespectful to a spoon
Dwyer shirts
He would take it as a sign
Exactly
Edgar
I don't know
Yeah you did
He's just out there and an hour to bring up on a later show do the talking about how
Tin with the money changers
Keep beat their ass
Do you make a good point out of Christ could fight if he wanted to
It's like Christ
The bringer of peace and love goes into the temple is like
He was making the argument that the reason price got mad about that was because they were using
Like I different
Types of currency
In order to Belk people out of money
That's what he was mad about
To the church
Or whatever you look at the
Varying interpretations of what
Christ was actually mad about in that story but
Is Big point is that
Before
I've never thought about how out of character that is for Jesus
Just talked to him
It is a little weird but there's a whole bunch of stuff you look into like
That is true the real weird when a kid
Come on
My favorite book of the Bible
My bad
You know we're making a lot of jokes about the globalist
But we're always taking
Are killing the family right now
Final cliff
Cultural and spiritual death
The Brazilian the Italian
I don't want to not have kids I don't want to give over
Elon Musk Tesla
Merge with machines are dyed the global draw announcing their their crap
Composite engineering humanoid
Plans
Childbirth we're going to have a slight disagreement
I mean you might be able to eliminate all sorts of very tragic.
Diseases and stuff
There's also an argument to be made that
Variety is the spice of life in the last episode
Even some mental illnesses or strength
One-of-a-kind
Airbnb
But you must doesn't say that the article
Who is also
Workers unionizing like
Elon Musk is not some kind of global as hero hero but he is the closest thing that Alex knows to like
Okay
He's using it there was an article that have come out recently where Elon Musk was talking about
How because
Because of the rapidity in the
At the speed
That technology is evolving in
Emerging with Humanity
It might be in the necessary piece of
He's talked about that is sort of a
Hypothetical thing
I'm hoping that maybe coming down the line with the
You know the nature of
How are technology
Birds with machines or deities are saying they're like
We might end up becoming cyborg
I am officially saying it here merge with machines
Countries that he pulled out of his ass
Where my favorite random country America Japan Brazil
Italy
Like those are his world superpowers right by
To pull out of
The EU
Example
So it's always on
Yeah much like Georgia
Georgia is on
Next on that
It's a good thing
Nationalism never led to Fascism in it
Great track record
Never repeat
Repeating the same
Exactly
Years ago ever
370 years
I don't know what's going on in Brazil
But
It's not good Brazil is a tiger
Play the bat
Is worse and more corrupt than our
Kidnapping
Economy
Actually with a real coup
What's the temperature
Well unless you count the first
I was getting rid of the military dictatorship that was the first Coupe
The first clue than the counter-coup is white
People doing what we do best
Carriacou
Yeah so this next clip
This next one
You might be thinking like
These painting a really Bleak picture
The world and she's pretty back
He's a really depressed about it
In the depressed
Okay he's got a solution for you
Do you know what that I respect that allotment
Because most Republicans
Do not go that far
Open the mainstream solution
At least you got
Like they're saying they want to get rid of even close to it
Repeat
At least Alex Jones is like hey
How about Healthcare
From the 11th
He's not even going to be that specific and also
At the end he's going to talk about
Okay good
We have to organize herself into chivalrous good
Strong organization
That that that read invoke the rituals of
Also I want to interrupt
The beginning
You think you talk about like night
Think he's more to Orange doors open
Replied like
And women
Chivalrous Society
Jamal from dragons
Alright
Definitely not going to leave
Some of his f****** listeners to end up like Don Quixote
We have to organize herself into chivalrous good strong organizations like
Rituals of the birthright
That that that that
Flower supposed to be
Meijer humans worship God made because God is what we worship
Like the ritual
We can do anything this is all the tests
Level
You don't just think God just gives his creatures unlimited power
Spoiled children
No wonder these luciferian khilona power of the universe
Hellboy
Full on fire and brimstone
Not scarjo
Long live like he gets a little Jim Jones
Sinners in the hands of an Angry God
The feeling that I worry that if things get really bad
To be either take to the streets or
Right like globalism being a literal death cult
So we need to do it first
It's possible I don't know it
Really weird though like
Again
Ice I'm not taking him out of context play I'm engaging this with the source material which is
Just his talking
He always likes
To say
I don't believe these things it's what the globalist
Believe
Children on there like at the beginning after work I don't understand
Second
You know what the second does Lucifer give it to the sickness first
I guess so
Implicitly saying or even explicitly is
That is a good point
Explicitly say
50 good
You folks
Himself good powers
Where these evil people are just given evil powers for joining up it's a complete psychotic break
Living in an in Dragon Ball Z
Superman you got to take super male Vitality Pandora play Goku over 9000
Caveman
Recharge up
Shoe Up Bones
Yeah she's a fat correct
This is ground up bumps
Marshmallows
There's a lot of
I think the whales are great and the elephants are great but you know what
Grand Blanc trillium times but I do like animals all the time
Doesn't say that is a recurring theme
The animal gets into
S'more Satan talk
You look at Chucky Schumer
You look at all these newworldorder people and you look what they're doing you look what they're involved in and they are
And there is a real
Struggling
Taking place right now on this planet
Are you look at the
Michael Moore's and the
Gloria Steinem zanzea
F*** you
Maxine Waters Nancy Pelosi those are empty husk
Zombies
Again
Again women
It's always about women
It does seem to be has backflip with Maxine Waters and ants
Pelosi so they're fresh on the mind
Takedown glorious
Well because he founded
A f******
Handle the Glorious
Nobody alive
Ground up ground up into bone right now
The reason he's mad at her if he believes this
If you work for the CIA
But not the devil or does the CIA also work for
Load chart
The org chart
Specific
Bulls or work
For the CIA
But also the devil on a false
His idea of the hierarchy of thing
Cuz we know whenever I get a clip
Current players this next clip we learned a couple things
First Iraq turns out the Jerry sandusky's son got arrested for
Children
Send something that is generational a lot of times cuz if you are kind
Hundred percent is almost no
Doubt in my mind that that's that's that's a real tragedy
And how it is
They're part of a bigger system
Course and this is also a clip where we learn
That recently
Future
Told you anything like that
Ever
Lascivious
Fuk was that also I don't know if there's any evidence
That is true
That they were
Brookshire
Children are there pedophiles
Yeah it doesn't matter
Using that
Such a
Exploitative Manor because you have to juice up your base you have to make
You have to make the people even matter
Chucky
Bike
Bike connection to this
It's insane but anyway
Very animated
Because this is the evidence
He brings up
These references
50 *
On the last
Three episodes
The shout
Someone had a conversation with
Great Gary Oldman portrayal of Dracula
Really
Speaking role
Is bad for him
Area
He was only
Barron Penn State
Count Dracula
Only gets the trainees
Just wright
B license
Torturing
You sign on to this evil
You keep making your jokes about Trump what's happening
Is there a red pedophiles from Pennsylvania to California as Weiner prepares to be indicted
As all of these criminal groups get rolled up
You just remember what side you were on
Good God look at
Look at how
Physically ugly cheerleaders
What's a manifestation of the fact that that's their spirits
And that's what they want and they want ugly
Okay
Before we say anything else
Yeah he is just opened himself up
Personal appearance
He looks like s***
He looks
F******
Garbage
Do not
Your physical appearance is what your spirit manifested
Without you looking at a goddamn mirror
Real f***
Smokin hot
So she's cool
She's called David looks like a
Tracking Santa Claus
We got
Easy
Looks like an owl looks like he has been through the Unabomber ringer
Looks like
Biggest person in the world
If you didn't talk I think you probably
Visine Visine in your eyes Paul Joseph Watson
You just you just described
The Tinder date you went out
What social justice Warriors would have enjoyed our coffee
Super offensive about that clip is the insinuation
There's only two sides
There's like
If you're not on board with Trump
Yeah you are one of these pedophiles
Everybody everybody is associated with
There is
Any
If there's any news about a pedophile it will immediately be
Into Hillary
Living your
He's talking to seriously about that
Can just people and then be like if you don't want to be like that you got to be on our side
Really dumb people but also strongly
Also a lot of these reports are coming out that are being used as evidence that Trump is rolling up
Pedophile Networks
There's a bunch
Stefan licking
Conspiracy blogs
Message boards
About these arrests
They're going on
And a lot of times they aren't
Pedophile ring
Adult
There prostitution
Goddamn things
But also
Human trafficking is just what a lot of
Tatoosh encharge
Just get ended up
Being propped up to
Oh really yeah getting arrested are just small-time prostitutes
Or a pimp
That's not good
Throat industry should be legalized I think that's a good thing
There's to be protection
That is not the same thing as human trafficking
Which is
Horrified
Absolutely
Everything is truly horrifying
Complete those two together can a hundred percent
A lot of these sites are doing
I can't I can't say that for every single incident
A couple of them I looked into
This is just a run-of-the-mill prostitution
The big point that I want to make is that you can
Very much be against
Pedophiles
The appointment
Somehow we're in that world
We're in The Darkest Timeline
S*** about
Land
Alex
Tells a little
It's a dinner
Does it all God is somebody going to compliment car again
No it's
Even more insane
The globalist the Breakaway deepstep was spying
So good
I want you to talk to Trump about
Nuclear submarines for Taiwan
Laker run back seat
Here's Jones acting like he's got contacts
That's how it works
That's not how it works
Is not hot
He's a really bad spot something might have happened
Is probably our submarines
I imagine if this did happen it was someone trying to prank
Yeah it was Intelligence agencies
It's the intelligence community
Hey Bixby
But
You do have
To give them at least a basic level of,
They're not going up
Hey man
You been doing any
Best Buy you got do drugs like
Crazy
For someone who claims to have sources of know how things work on the inside with anything other than
Someone
Possibly it was it's just him
Something
Scourge of the entire thing
Most likely
I like how you use the
The
What's your big
SWA
I think it's
That I'm just
To genuine integrity
So much I'm too nice I really am just such a
Genuinely good
Finishes up his dinner like
If you do some role-playing but what is firing my life
Wolfgang Puck
On a weekly basis
Try to do the job tell the truth
Oh yeah why
When's been blackmailed
So that's that's basically the thrust of his eyes argument
Flynn was doing talking to the Russian ambassador's was actually saying
I can't talk to you about this yet
Artfully Dodge
The question is
Absolutely
Anybody
Genuine to lie about what it was they talking about
But they just asked him and he said I can't do about it so when he was asked about it
You didn't think that that qualify
Wow
Which
A thing where you're like
Hey I think
That might be something to report
But it's Alex's version of the truth was real
It's not very different
Scenario I think
I don't think I would be that worried about him saying something like that
That's not true
Opposite of anything true
I don't think people are so
F******
Boner doubt
To make a case against someone
That they're going to Trump up that
The laziest
Sting
To also he claims
That he knows that this is what happened because
So he's
He's fighting something that isn't
Public
These transcripts
I do like how he describes
Woking
He has to deal with
Russian with a video camera
Just absolute Saturday anyway here is actually the roleplay
About
And of course the president then I guess got advised or Flint
I bet
The plans you said sir I don't wanna be a distraction
That's awesome
Keep advising me behind the scenes
You have to know you can't do that behind the scenes
It's really important that there are those things
You can't just advise him behind the scenes
I think it's good that he said I haven't talked to any of these people I'm just guessing
I bet the way window
Cuz if you had talked to them that this was like what was going on
Pictures of trivial
Against the law
Nobody is listening to Alex Jones
Everybody does not care if they want
Russian
Russian hacker
Teams
Though the hacker farms and they're just all doing the the views
Just over and over and over again
So he was talking about
You know selling this stuff doesn't
Fund the operation the way you need
I would I would like to
2 track
Like his tax returns
It's too late for that
It's too late for the
The Republicans voted against
Coronavirus tax return
Because it's time for us to just move on we get Freedom of Information Act Alex Jones
Night
Not yet
We got to wait 25 years or whatever what's Obama gets his
Street soldiers out there baby
Which is about 2 how all of this
What's going on in the world is preparation
For war
And then he talked about how Marine Le Pen
And this is for when they start a war with Russia
Products they're saying in France they're saying in German they're saying everywhere
In-N-Out
I don't want anti-christian groups everywhere will you know what
They're secretly
You heard him first
Russian spies
And the state department
Against Trump
For good reason
A Russian agent
Who says that
And then they got spies
Around the clock around the PIN
Waiting for her to go to a cocktail party or an event and
Shake the hand
It's just his Wolfgang Puck
Story again
These arguments people are saying that she's a Russian
She's a f****** fashion
She's rushing Russians actively
To get in the shower because it facilitates
Someone called her she sued
They went to court and it got thrown out of court because
The Court ruled that your opinion and her philosophies are legally
People are
70 Court case
Rita
Excellent
But that's that's his whole thing is like
Russian agent
I don't necessarily disagree with them that
Phobic in a way that isn't
Productive
There are surely times where I've seen
People say oh it's the Agents of the Russia
Who are at fault for all kinds of things
It's much more likely to be just basic and calm
It was a
Basic
Phishing attack
Two did was click on a link
It was a Russian hacker put the link
Also
Internet
The biggest problem with our government as it is right now is that it seems like everybody in power
Googling
People stay in power for longer than they should
And Technology moves way faster than anyone
So you end up with people in power
Who's been there since the internet was young and how all this stuff works
I don't fucken understand all this stuff
And I've grown up with
What Trump is a seven-year-old
He's f***** imagine
Every seven year old man
They're all of their Collective internet knowledge
Together in a golden toilet
And that's what Trump
How you end up reading confidential documents with a cell phone flashlight
Crazy
Look
Yeah you know how they put their f******
Phones in the
Freezer
Because they might just even be listening a little bit
Pointed
Phone
With
Flashlight
At classifieds
F****** doctor
At Mar-A-Lago
Ada public dinner with
The Japanese prime minister prime minister man I have tape on my
Computer's webcam
Because that's how they can
You can watch
Bloom one part you 70 another part like
Oh my God
They posted a picture with a guy who
Carries around the nucleus
Football
I'm sure they've switched it out and it's a new guy now but like
If you are like really doing
Security for the president you see someone like
Buddying up to the nuclear football guy
You wouldn't get that guy a waste
That is insane
Strangelove territory that we're getting the better of trump being allowed to use his own private
Security instead of
Trained
Secret Service
He has his own like guard around him and they don't know what is
What is dangerous what's a leek
What's the
Acceptable
It's not and it's going to get so much worse now.
I mean
Jordan it's all progress until the end
Do progress until the end
Avenue story for you
So the globalist
They trying to do
That's on God
The first going to make you ugly and stupid
Poison get you accept evil
Do you
Because if you declare your Birthright
Unconscious
Will that you don't have a
Play Store
I don't want to be
Those walking
Everytime I look at Nancy
Pelosi age
Your life
What is
Whataburger
Usually usually
Looking at his whole Satanism talk as like a
Thinly veiled metaphor
Where in holy war
Cuz he does spell out some more in this next
This is for this is
Like left behind
Novels
Situation
They're Renfield
Dracula
Hundred percent of Jewish
That is definitely a Jewish
People make fun of him cuz he looks Jewish
Why
Are anti-semites still allowed
I don't know if he actually is
He's subconsciously doing that
He also said that Michael Moore has
Not
Totally juve's
But man
Come on gal has the look forward little more carefully Alex
Just please
Don't accuse Jews of having that evil look
Yeah
Doesn't have to look I can't think of a reason why
More Dracula
Pelosi
Are you doing
BOCES a little zombie
Totally freaked out by Washington Mall
Narcissist
Schumer
Walk in this
A Michael Morris kind of
Reach Dracula level
George soros's
Big old
Big
They turn themselves over
We're stopping on unit
Honestly
This sounds like a drunk guy to salute
Really cool weather
It really doesn't so he's doing
Yeah cuz that has a
Val Kilmer
Liver that exact same monologue in Tombstone
Tales of Alex Jones don't worry about him
They're probably cuz of the blood
Oh okay
Cuz all the blood rushes to their
I don't I don't know
He wouldn't say names obviously cuz that's okay
I'm alive
Paranoid
They're even bigger ones in the shower
He's picking out names
But the bigger ones in the
Confusing and worrying
Cuz he does mention the names like Rothschild
Modern Boogeyman talk about George Soros
Who is over them
And it goes back to life
Conspiracy narratives As Old As Time
Power Players
You never hear their name
They're the ones were pulling the strings are okay
There's a hundred percent undisprovable so
Let's just have fun
Speculating wildly
Bigger
Do the bigger one
It's very weird but
Totally would
Fear of God
Ever submitting them is death
When is death not for me not for my ego
But for the species
Oh I'm selfish
I realize my life
Like that part I
Nowhere better than them by
Trillions
He doesn't know how to
Total differences
Ligers
Dementia
Complete different Paradise
Totally different
How often
Is not about it
Is ego
Seems like it's a lot about
There's a b
Is a bit of it it's
Feels that way
It's difficult
To wrestle with like
Okay
This guy is talking
About
Renfield
And Dracula's
And pick Dracula's
End
And he's a policy
You don't like just
It doesn't
It doesn't work
The two don't go together
You would need real catalogs information about these here big Dracula
Glitter vase
Is
Decreasing since he
You started going
Enjoying the ride
Anyone
Gurus
I don't want to say if you've been listening to Alex for this long you're already all in
You're just going to follow this to the end
Austin post
Saint conspiracy
Boards about him
In the last
Couple weeks
And
Unfortunately
A lot of people who watch The Joe Rogan
A lot of them more like
You know what it was kind of slow but at the end when he started talking about transdimensional stuff that's when I realize
Is this guy gif
No
Boo
It's so I think actually he's probably picking up that
Dom psychonaut
Kind of group yeah and I'm not saying anything
Be people who identify a psycho.
Isaac hallucinogens are real cool
And I support people experimenting with them
And all that s***
There's a lot of really dumb people in that group
Yeah but fry their brains
I think you picked up a lot
So when he started spouting this Dracula ship they're like
Man
Tire world
He just brought in his base
As it gets more and more crazy
To the
Did the Big Ten
Republican ideology of
Baby amazing
Because he's using all this
Dimensional language
And Dracula's
And coupling go with something that is as repugnant
And universally hated
Child abduction and murder
The people who are like
It's it's better emotional manipulation you take this
Frazee
Paranoid delusions
A match them with a real-world issue and all of a sudden you have
An argument that people
They don't want to argue again
Cuz you argue against his Dracula metaphor wait sound
If you're not
If you're not thinking it sounds like you're defending pedophile
It's very much like in election years for judges
It's it statistically proven that that year
They're way tougher on
Crime that other way
Because you don't want to be the guy
Who is
Not punishing
Pedophiles enough
Or if you if you accidentally lock somebody up
The public isn't as
Turned off by that is if you let someone go and then another crime
That's interested
Futurama joke
Like
Yeah
Yuck
Anyway
This is where we're full-on in
To where Alex
We're not on the major broadcast so he's really allowed to go full
Trillions and trillions of light years away from anywhere resembling
Yeah
And the rest of the clips that I have are essentially a call to action
And
Furtherance
Okay enjoy this one this one is why we actually maybe
Shouldn't be all that afraid of globalist probably
20 more years and they shouldn't
Be a problem
Jesus
The good news is globalist can hardly reproduce
And their disease and mental health that's why they're obsessed with technology and science
Because by the inbreeding they have made themselves susceptible
What
What is breeding
They've made themselves
Susceptible
Disease they already have
Which is what
Globalism
Have we established an actual disease
No but it's just trying to pair the ace
Let's call all globalist
Have pneumonia
They're inbred
Reasons
Because of inbreeding inbreeding it's it's it's
Just trying to send as opposed to being obsessed with weird creepy
Yeah
They can't reproduce
Is just trying
How to connect in
Like it just people's intrinsic distaste
Spur like Blue Bloods
All the stories of the past and s*** like that
Toxic mask
It is all about
For you know I should be able to fight him
Perfect sperm in yada yada yada
So all of those
Emasculation
Narratives can always come
Whether it is
But also
Weird experimentation
Body glove with Dracula you see out walking around
5 or 10
Experiments they can't do it
Complete
Do they need the blind
Metaphysical
Everyday
Or their God desserts
That they're the most
Horribly Fallen enslave people
All they have is
Demonic will to crush good people
Man-o-man
Call
Demonic wilda Crush people
We have not established
Possible win scenario
Do they get rid of all these people
Is soy
The comic books
He's driving
Outback
Alex Jones hazard
Globalist wanted to be famous and there were no globalists
What you might have been enemies
Right that's exactly what happened
Yemen
A lot
All the time but it it like
It's so it's like we're seeing this it's so manipulative and so stupid
Like the Royal Family
Pyramids
For every vampire
Clearly
But it's not easy as not being literal except
Let's go bring it up goddamn Renfield
So you're really boring
Economics and xenophobia
Watch the movie witch
Gary Oldman
Disappeared
Amazing
Acceptance
Disappeared
So for every one of those used deformed
Experiment
So so again we came
Moving back and forth from the metaphysical to the physical
Because what is the
Deformed experiment look like
Do you not see it walking the street
They're Shackled
How many global
Is this never seen the movie but is this a Man in the Iron Mask
I wrote it down before you said it
Again
Leonardo DiCaprio
Disappears into the role of the Man in the Iron Mask who looks exactly like
Not the Man in the Iron Mask
Yeah I do
We don't know how many globalist are those there are those Legends of kings and Royal Family
Have the deformed child that they
Bend Indiana correct
I mean the result of inbreeding
If you want a conspiracy theory that then yeah you
You could stay
How to create an Ultra
Royal family
Or do you want onions
Throwing spaghetti at the wall
Very unrelated weird
Scary things
Yeah
Let's always doing
It's it's
It's a basic
Gestalt
As you might put it
Object
Fear it's a
I want to know
Does he ever have
Possibly have nose
That's no so he is just
Improving the s*** out of it
Yeah he is a master improvised
No
Improvident
I could do this
You didn't know you
You could not I could easily
3 hours a day with this level of
And you gave me
Unbridled testosterone pills
Built-in narrative that there's evil Boogeyman
Around
You give me everyday like three news stories that I barely understand it gives extrapolate on
F*** yeah I could do that
I think it is exactly like one of those situations where a world-class athlete
It looks like I said I could probably immediately compete with that
Everybody's
Yeah
Effortlessly without an hour and
40 minutes
40 minutes exactly
All right we could do
First of all we could do 5-hour
1/2 hours on our own
And if I'm feeling like
I got to kill 10 minutes I'll just throw it to report or something like that
That's a t-shirt
Yes that's a shirt
DJ dubplates sjw
Can't reproduce
This makes clips
Southwest camp
Tubi
Literal
Genuinely think the globalist Contra 4
I literally don't know how that could be a metal
There's no way
Other than maybe the ideas that their ideology cancer
Triplett
Eclipse features
Jomon like
Swing and I couldn't do this
3 hours a day
Kizi
As a performer I think he
He's really good at this let's not interrupt this just you can enjoy what I will admit
I couldn't do
I've set my will against them
I'm asking you to set your Wellness them and Trump has said his will against him as well
At work like a laser beam
Particle beam
It just gets stronger
Stronger and stronger running has focused and focus on them and be do good things in our lives to be honorable and not
Focus on God and focus on life and focus on blue skies and Greenfield
A little fish swimming around happy pond
Happy Trees in this Focus
Subatomic shelters
Focus on them around offending them
Thanks
I can feel God's will
It will fall forever
Young about 28
38 minutes infowars.com but this would Bellion against God will fall
They already know they're following already know they're losers are not to take us with him
And everybody knows that their heart hasn't been in
I haven't been in
Affected by it
Full
There's a reason
You're not in every movie that's been made
Since the 1990s
Well I mean did you see that
Swing from Talking Bob Ross happy trees
I think about what
Has been crying
Yeah that was vengeful Wrath
Like he's showing so many
Jericho
If he's actually feeling of things he's presenting he's feeling
He's in trouble
Ncmo
Paranoid
Schizophrenia
Yeah because
So what is it
I don't know
Is He-Man
Is he some mix of the two I think he is teething
Give tinges of paranoia and then also portable reading
I think
Possibly
The most dangerous,
Yeah
I don't know I don't I don't think
You could function the way he doesn't actually
Vistaprint
Too easy to function
Yeah we don't like to think about the idea that this big of a liar could
Best in the world
Yeah that's a good point
But it's entirely possible that he gets off
Berenices
There's there's every
Monster in the human race
Send it seems like this one
Costumes that are recently came out and said that he's a complete sell-out
There's a guy who was interviewed who I used to work with David Knight
Before he went to work for Infowars who
He was kind of a Libertarian guy
What's up the theory that this guy had was that they know they're in on the joke
They know what they're doing
Also apparently it's come out that Infowars employees
I can't find absolute proof this but I've seen it cited a couple times
That's a Infowars employees have signed lifelong
NBA's
Non-disclosure
For the next 10
Millionaires
Basically
It's entirely possible illegal
You can do that you can never talk about this
It's a willful entering into a contract
That's true
You can do it it's just sketchy as fuk
F*** cuz it kind of implies that like if word ever gets out that we don't mean what we're saying
It's going to be really a non-compete agreement
Don't
Tell that we're lying
Goodbye goodbye
Here is where
This is huge encounter could my argument
It within the next flight
We have the technology to will the culture the spirit
All of those things together
To build the stairway
What building is what does it not airing now
Interface with
Take it down
When the rebel Falls it will
That's one of the greatest mystery
How far to go
Because
On this plane of existence
Good Fight Fire With Fire
You good wanted to be evil it would be
Infinitely worse than what these following people who would imagine
That's a really good one
Because these Fallen creatures
Party smart
As we are
That's a weird rationalization
Summation of the way that
It's kind of moral
Society
If you are good
You always have to
The fight against
Yeah
You always have to
Have a joker to fight
Creating
Your own evil
Right
That
We can go to
Safari thing is
The is the
Reality of any kind
Morality
System
It's going to require a
Purity
Little girl I don't like the idea that it's going to crush the Innocence there's going to be collateral damage
Be careful about what we say like cuz we bring it into the world
We've done maybe 10-12 episode
Most crazy thing for him to say never
What I do know is that he is never stop yourself from saying something
Unless it was intentional
Classify the only time he stops himself is when he's like
Yeah
We're going to go to
Break this special report
Which again was supposed to be about
Foreign policy
Every time we get to the end of the episode I have no idea what we
Started the episode with and about the the article in foreign policy
Even though it's not actually called foreign policy
This is parting shots the report which
I want to warn all you that are Senegal and giggling
Solat
I'm out shown
You have been warned
You have
Ben Warren
You have been
I don't want to go into vampire hold
Fire holes or Alex Jones
That is a Rough Rider
F*** it why did I get born
Seems pretty alright I would go down
Twilight
If we're talking literal vampires
Maybe weird child blessing vampire
No that's
That's a very bad
Empire
Sliding scale of morality and then you could you could be a good vampire
K-Love
That is
Healthcare
So that's the end of this special report
Oh no no
Couple bonus
Clips from Tuesday's episode
As you'll recall
He said
Special Report
Witchy aired
His Tuesday show
Yes you said he was going to read that entire foreign policy article on the show
Yes
And I told you
He did he did
But
He keeps saying he's going to
Throughout the ship
Super clip of every time he says that he said that cuz I have a nine-to-five job
The times isolation you are slacking off
Sean Spicer is doing a news conference
Go to this
Wow you just cuts away
Distracted
I have a couple of them this first one is about Fifty Shades of
Gray the sequel
It's sort of a bad habits
Eventually going to lead us to movies by High School
That's what's going on in this country
Come on top
Bad stuff
I need to get in there Club
That's again his whole idea that in order to get into the elite
Too f****** kid getting jumped into a gang
Yeah it's basically that everyone has to have blackmail on each other also
Doesn't work
I don't believe it that's how the world works but
Beams on 10
Is in trouble
That
Their whole shindig
Isn't it so far
Publicly shame it's sexualizing
Mothers and fathers are bad
Knowing to the mothers and fathers are bad
It's not from Arrested Development
Now that's better boy
Probably Sandler's 50 100 genders in
Total societal attack
And the intelligence agencies
Help
All the weird Copic stuff that the butt
Different
About enslaving
That's why they've got you know Fifty Shades of Grey the new one comes out and it's more intention
Hospital
And the next he'll be killing somebody
Successive approximation
Slap your wife on the butt
That's fine
They like it you like it
All right where's this going
Right
Pickup
Summer daughter
Want to go out with some Potbelly pedophile
It comes knocking on your door
They're not
They're very much not a potbelly pedophile comes to your door and says I want to take
Your five-year-old out on a date
Definitely
Even if it's legal that's just bad parenting
Think about this
To get into like
Another
The nations of Renaissance
The Great Western cultures
Look at Greece
And angry
Only if it wasn't based in
If it is based in love and respect generally underage boys
It was generally that early man on man nonsense so
Not doing this
Western Civilization
For both people
That's a crazy swing very quick escalation
But the other thing I want to bring up is the idea that like
If your kid wants to
The fuk is Potbelly pedophile they should have the right to
Twice in the last week and a half or so
Milo's talked about how when he was underage
He f***** older dudes
He was the aggressor
What Alex is talking about
Right now are you making me
Feel bad
So I mean it's just like it's a little
Going to grill him on it
Milo
Commentary
And I don't necessarily disagree with
Criticize
I do want to make the point
That Milo is a Nazi I'm all conversations
Don't
Don't antagonize the good
I'm sorry
I will say it was
A little iffy of us not to listen on the show to the thing that we said
He made me feel so bad
I'll tell you this
Susanville
In this clip I believe Alex Jones makes the argument that science-fiction
Like at work Reddit
Putting moles in everywhere I mean this is so seditious and then they tell us when they're the globalist Takeover arm
By the way I want to say this real quick cuz one of my favorites
Survivor pulled
Good get ready for that
Okay
But this better deliver is also further Evidence
That Alex
Believes the stuff he says
But he doesn't believe
Such a conundrum
New York Times
Is
Every major culturally non-Christian
What
British families
And they
Start developing it
Couldn't come up with it but they've been given the knowledge
Thanks for the basic template
Build
Wait
What's real.
So Satan's up
Right
And he is a text to mention it to me
Demons or whatever
Paneling
Force I thought we were starting with off-world entities that
The Christians and the Jews believe
Appeal to the idea of like
They believe in Satan he's a fallen angel
So that's what we're talkin about is off-world
Because off world is kind of very much like
Hey you know this
That knows our knowledge that these things are
Planted in the brain of h.g. wells
No he did build a build a working time machine
No I think we all know that's true
Great podcast.
It's very much
You're skipping
You're skipping a step
The globalist
Trickle this information they find all the knowledge
They want to tell scientist to make it
Yes but they know
F*** people are going to know we got this information from somewhere
Right there going to be free
To write
Stories definitely freaked out by that at all
Demonic information about so when the public finds out about it they're ready for it because they read about it inside
Complicated
We talked about Occam's razor
Also
Like apparently you can sign a non-disclosure for your entire life
Other means you brought up the time machine that's a book by h.g. Wells still don't have one of those
Invisible
For June
Programming
Invisible Man
We haven't War of the World
I don't know the rest of HG Wells bibliography but
I think you got the highlights
I think none of them have been invented anyway espoused
Hugo's moron this
The end of my clip
Description is just
Alakazam
UFOs
The other dimensions
Movie Pacific Rim
Energy of motion
So wait that was real
Dinosaurs
Cuz that would be way more fun
That talk to top psychiatrist psychologist
It was in the days of men
The seed was it clean because they
That's in the Bible
All the come up.
I think he was saying there at the end the dinosaurs are free
Vicky Eddie Bravo this c.s. Lewis
Off this planet Trilogy right there
I don't I don't know
God dammit
I don't know book series of
Science fiction novels
Which were
Weird
Let you know how the
Availed
Allegories
This one
Is even more better
That's basic
That's pretty much what he was just describing right
Also
What the f*** was he just describing right there
I'm not going to do this cuz I Clips really long
But I most wanted list
Kind of do too I still don't understand what it was
So-so
We're not billions of years old I think we can establish that
Right so
Has he made that noise
Even way back when
People were genetically
This TV
Cuz there were giant people
Moving like 2,000 years old
He is referencing the
The flood which is only about fourth
Thousand Years lyrics
Again in the Bible
Lucifer the Fallen Angel there's no devil couple of verses
The talk about like a Angels came down and bread with human women
There was an abomination
There are a couple of
Weird verses in the Old Testament
That could be
Well because
Could be metaphorical also
F****** Giants
Terrible lizards
Say that
Giants are probably why we have
They would still be right above the water they still be able to breathe because that last exactly
Snorkel
They can't tread water is
True facts if there's anything you take away from our podcast it is better
Giants can't tread water
Okay
I just reverse engineer that the study didn't read the writings and watch what they're doing
But
I'm not saying I believe any of it
Or
Western Society
Absolutely hate women
Global estate women
Wawa
Okay so one that dinosaurs
Only 6,000 years old
Because of that
Because of that we know
That Western Society is opening its doors to Islam
Because they hate Christianity
And I hate women
Does the guy
Call that woman sweetcakes
Aggressively
Yeah
So but like
I want I think that's f****** crazy
I don't believe
Using that word for minutes
Was either they believe this
And they're insane
Or they're just insane
Fort I mean
If you had One Moment of clarity guys
I don't know if I actually believed it.
Colonel Kurtz
He dead
My own supply line I don't f****** know anymore
It's blue
Bone pill
It's like you see how far you can get before people like uniformly
Shut the fuk up
Is there is there high performance trolling
That's that
Is there is there anyone
Do you think there's any line
No
No it we're already past multiple dimensions
Vampires are real
Everybody on his side
Yeah dinosaurs
Maybe.
Transmission
How the globalist
Technology from the dead
What is
What is there left
Only
Turning it into a Nazi Oregon
Like really
Weird
It's not on the edge
No way into not the organization
I don't think
I don't know how much
It was audience with following
Guys
Got to be honest
You know what you're right
You're right I think a good percentage would but I think you'd lose
No because yeah I think you're right
Because he does go out of his way to be like
What was it what was it that he said that
Trouble going to build factories in Black areas I don't know what it was
Is that a good thing
He's harkening back to the idea that Trump knows
Is that inner cities need
More jobs and I will fix everything and that you're going to
Again
Not not
Just black people live in inner cities very much true also reductive in terms of what the actual issue
He's saying that like he's a racial Justice Warrior when it's
Not a fan
But like
I can't get away from this
Yes
The argument that he's putting forth
About satanic forces
Giving of the globalist
Their information
Then fed to HG Wells
That's not what the globalist believe
He believes that
He believes that based on his quote on quote research
Is reverse engineering
Which is
Sure
That is he saying I don't believe this is what they believe
Anything else is
That was the one that week
Point
You really believe that today
It's part of that last text
And if you try to dodge the idea that
Do you know
Satanic forces exist
They can influence people in these
Is global real
Invicta
He literally think he believes that Satan
Technological advances
He has to believe
That what they believe is real
I don't know what the other options
That's what that
Just like
Just like just like
That is the tagline to this park
No there's no wait no
That one's not
I have one more clip and it's from an hour and 40 minutes into Tuesday's episode
1/2 hours into you finally gets into the article
He finally gets into
Oh no actually you don't you already know
I'm going to go with he manages to make it
He interrupts
In the first time
He makes it
Total
Through
Four sentences
Maximum
Making a mistake I caught it before David Knight comes out
Starting to worry about Trump
About that is communication the world
Actually Spanish
I'm sorry if I interrupted it but it does quite a bit about that
Okay
CenturyLink
What's the 2017
A revolution of the past
They say they're for the first
Read any of the actual article
I read that first paragraph
Revolution
The hundred-year I mean him just now
Interrupted with his own commentary
1.4
Was a secret Ally of Alexander Shelton
Minnie Mouse
Communism
If you want to
Become a superpower at least wrong
They're all great
Great
Hey how about
F*** you you know they're making it's not a crime to be
Beat your wife yeah I know I saw that
Globalists job Christian all of the all of these globalist
Making it illegal to beat your wife
They're the opposite of Hollywood
Hollywood knows it
Christianity coming back there it's real and all the Cold War brain washers don't want people to believe the proof of what
What's happening
As a result of the Electoral victory of Donald Trump
Rebelution
Irrational each that's not true
Completely free market model
Now there wasn't
You don't think so
Well I know he transitioned into the words of the article because those were not
Spider-Man 3 tenses
But hate that he is like that
True
Trousseau
Narcissistic
He's actually hardcore revolutionary
What song is this
The focus on his disturbingly
Vindictive simplistic narcissistic insecurity
Yeah that's a really good idea
Exception being made for those conspiracy theorists
Like Alex Jones
He's worse
CIA agent
Spelman
Revolutionary
And that's the secret then they go on and say Russia they're going to CDC
Come on come on you don't really want to do this
He's going to take over
Facts about snow cones in hell
Everybody wants one
Snow cones in hell
Jeffrey the globalist the free yourself from the globalist everybody wants one it's like selling snowballs in hell
In order to
Okay now I get that
Reading
But the important
Were there I think
Reviews
That is a true self as a revolutionary insurgent
Anthony
Himself as anything other than
A big baller
Small Trump
Where am I
Could be generous perhaps
Protective Circle
We belong in the classic revolutionary Playbook
His shocking off style of executive action
Is designed to rattle
Sketches Pony
Unprepared
To wage war on
That's a fair assessment
To keep people on their toes and my nephew are dealing with Congress
Yeah but what he says is called
The Kremlin is starting to be worried about Trump
Call I'm sure they are the other
Russia
Never talks about the American government ever why would they
The fear of color Revolution
They understand better than Americans and Europeans the radical nature of political change
Describe
And the revolution
The Germans allowed to go on with
The Bolsheviks
How
The conversation with Russian
Indicate they're starting to have similar fears and doubts
Today
About the revolution that Trump is going
Baba baba baba
Celebrating
Of course I work now.
Doesn't our political Elites in Moscow.
Cheering
They believe that they recognize that position has become abruptly and agonizingly
It's true that trumps Ascension opens up the possibility of normalizing Russia
His relations with the West
Beginning with a reduction or even elimination
Directions
It also validates a lot of rushes
Ideological
Criticisms of the liberal order
They may perhaps or Shadow policy
Such as the Cold War
Alliance
Breaking up
Do you know what I did
Consider until just now while you're reading
Ventnor adopted this is boring although you did say that off
He just told me that this was boring
No I didn't consider it
Yeah we got to go
I didn't actually consider that maybe at this point Russia's think
This is going to blow up in our f****** faces
I know what this article is about
Looking at what's going on
When going down
Has to be the one where they're like
We did not see
Oh s***
Yeah that is a big ocean
But illusion is also ushering in a period of turmoil and uncertainty
Including the hood of self-defeating War
Disintegration of the
Present leadership
Has no appetite for globulin
Instability
A little bit later about how
Because Trump is erratic
Unpredictable it's taking away that as a
The tool that Putin
Continues also because he was the one who would
Like go around normal tree
You can't use that as as heavy a punch
He created a monster
Robux
Unless
He actually
Really then puts into question whether or not
He really has black
Metal Terrier
Because right now
It's on his way
Maybe not in the short-term
Well we haven't lifted the sanctions
No
No sew
Do you think I would be a calamity
No I don't know so so the stated objective for Putin I think
Not
Did you create that in
Disability
In America
That way he can dismantle or at least pick up
The part of the EU
That will give him the opening to then create a grievance outside of the
The only possible in Game of creating chaos in our political system
Retaking the Soviet Union because Putin's is really just kind of nostalgic but that's almost exactly what we
We speculated 10 episodes back
It based on
What you're reading right now
It seems like
That's not going according to
2 plan
The blade
But
Solid quality with our our
I'm going to talk about
So they're going to kill Trump
Yeah the only thing I can base it on is this next line
Okay
What the what the Kremlin fears most today is the Trump may be ousted or even killed
That's the only line that has anything to do with it
Is it that would be a bad outcome
His outdoor Kremlin insiders argue is
Some campaign in washing
Therefore
Success
This seriously restricted Russia's geopolitical options
Russia
To discredit and possibly impeach Trump
Well Republican Elites want to use Russia
To deflate and
Blind drop
The Russian government fears not only
Of course but also the possibility that he could opportunist
Quickly switch to a tough anti Moscow line
In order to make
Republican leaders in Congress
That's what's in this article
Really
No matter how much
Think about foreign policy which I kind of really think about it a lot
Is constantly reminding me that
This game
Is so ridiculously complex
Yes Trump's presidency has also complicated moscow's relations with China and Iran
Check on Scout is interested in normalization with away
But not at the cost of joining a coalition
Which Trump seemed insistent on creative
220 million Muslim
And therefore cannot indulge in the radical antithesis
Holyshit
Yeah
This is
Yep
You're looking at
If Russia
So they did have an influence on the election there's no denying
Yes but this article even whatever they're talking about that talk about
Clear what kind of
Definitive role they played
Or if the influence they had was decisive
Whether or not it was a deciding or or whatever it was
This article would argue that
They were Putin was mostly against the idea of Hillary
Because she was against
His actions in Ukraine
And white
Yeah
Mayweather
Too strict is the the worst thing
What's going to happen when you push a little button
Because now there are ten million
Scenarios that might wind up happening
Agree
If which it seems enough
MP
Probably
It will almost
Because of his ties to Russia
Bad guy
Yeah it's it's
Read.
Coming out today of
Russian
Fighter plane
Buzzing are shipped
War games
Testing
Yeah I don't want to be the end result
I think
If we could all just go back to him a maintaining of what was going on
3 months ago maybe it would be pretty cool
How how crazy is it
The Declassified
Information
I don't know if it's
But it's information that snout
Where there was a
U.s. military
Training exercise
That showed up on Russia's intelligence report
As being exactly like what would happen
If America was launching a
They sent the order
We're Italian
And it was because of one dude on the on the button
Stickley who is like
Let's hold back and wait
That we don't have a massive nuclear war
Yeah
Like you go back he got a medal and
Ronin to Siberia never to be heard from again
Comes
So it seems like that we're one p**** hair away from destroy
All the time
Let me wrap up this article
This display is pretty address
Anyone who spends any time in Moscow discover that ordinary Russia
In contrast with a majority of European
Feel surprisingly positive about Trump
What reason does the fairy exist
It rushes confer
Temptation with the West
Another is that they share Trump
Cynical borderline apocalyptic view of international politics
They never believed
Most interesting lie of all
They readily compare Trump to an early Boris Yeltsin
Impulsive
Trusting only of his family
If that works
Does the mattress hold on power
The problem for the Kremlin
Is it Yeltsin was a revolutionary leader
And Putin has decided to make 27
15 year 4
Deploring not celebrating Revolution
Which goes back to the beginning of the article when he's talking
About the Bolshevik Revolution
To tie the end back to the beginning of a foreign policy
Free stuff and it's kind of your in the weeds a little bit like that article
The ability to bring the end back
The beginning first of all I tip my hat that's good right
And then second
I mean like
When do you know anybody says but like it's deploring obviously that's a little bit of a tip of the cap to the deplorable
Blair
Very well written
Avoids my most
Thing that happened
The news right now
Especially a penny
Bulshit
At no point in time does that article ever go with
Trump's own particular brand of populism or whatever it is right right right because that's the laziest
Dumbest thing you can say
It's a shortcut for you're an idiot
And that article
Well research
Point-by-point has really good analysis
I have nothing to do
Is that Alex has a
It's great writing
That's really good
This
You find it in
Magazine no matter what
It was written by
Relationship
Okay
But yeah
Good job
From the bottom of our tiny tiny podcast
I mean
Juno
This is just yet another example of
You know
I am taking a source
He created an entire Special Report
From the flag
Patrick Flynn
Didn't say what he said it's
Used as a deflection
From his main man
Michael Flynn
Having to resign so we didn't have to talk about that
Yeah except about the transcripts and what Michael Flynn actually did
Two genuine analyzed
Not
Because he was
Maybe you're doing anything wrong
Cuz he's a martyr for the cause
This without talking about it for 35-40 minutes in the Special Report
Write about it without actually getting into it
Science fiction is an Illuminati
Rumsey
Fantasizing about Dracula's and lasciviously talking about
Pornographers and child murderers
I hope you're not on his side you're for them
It's Insanity as much
It's like a like imagine there's a bullseye
On one side of your wall like a dartboard
With Mike
Michael Flynn
Right now
And throw all of the spaghetti you've ever seen deer entire life with the wall
And just hope people don't look at that
F****** dark
The evidence is not crazy
That mean
I don't know how you'd pull
That level
Of not dealing with it
If you are crazy
Denial be like
You have to be intentionally dodging s*** or else
Yep that's right
Jordan has been fun trip through Tuesday's event on
Floors website cuz it was just a show today
Special Report
Knowledge fight
Send us an email if you think we're over at
Knowledge fight at gmail.com
If you are
I need something
So if
Tell me about a machine I will tell Jordan about it and we'll get there
Will get it done
As always
Catch you next time
Efecan polish
Holding
Alex