Alex special edition
Should have knowledge
What's Jones
Is there a special hook
That perhaps is not the case on other episode
I know a lot about Alex Jones
We don't need to do this
Can male betta
Start a lot of the b******* that he says
And today we are awarding or punishing our listeners one one way or the other
With a long-form episode
The entirety of Alex Jones documentary
For Global enslavement
Listeners
Send an email to knowledge fight at gmail.com
And how great I am I think a listener actually suggested
I'm only taking half the blame
Birthday present for all of you assholes
It took me for f****** ever to research in
I'm glad it's over
So also what time was my other we're going to run into some of things
Alex Jones says that we're going to discuss
We have discussed on past episode
Go to the podcast
So there might be a little bit of overlap if your regular listen to the podcast
Fever before but I wanted to stand alone as a thing
So I don't I don't mind a little bit so just
This is it this is our listeners this is for posterity when
Run
This great land of ours
They will look back
Those two assholes got it right one time
Squirrel leadership it's as forthcoming
Yeah thank you very much for taking down the spider
We are going to try to not drink
Until late
But we will get to the booze eventually and then that's the high gear
Rivets for the silver part of the show that after a while
And then what was the last thing
Everybody listening
There is a bibliography for ended
Geography
Really troubling about it
Like as a works cited
Cuz we got a situation here
In the bibliography like I'll get around to it later never filled it in
What's a bibliography
What you doing later
Cuz they're trying to make anybody insert to your proof the Rothschilds are evil
And then the other thing is
Later about how he came up
Encyclopedias but his dad
Unfortunately I would say about a
Third of the references
Carta
Microsoft Carter Pages for like Play-Doh or whatever
That would also come with
12 hours of free internet
They're not online
Anymore
All over the place
Also uses Wikipedia as a source of bunch
Also
Sons of his own work
There's a ton of Infowars in prison planet that are used as work cited page
I don't believe anything ever made
I've respected more suspiciously similar to the Civil War
To Garner a healthy level of pity before we get into this
Through that mud
To get to a lot of this stuff
Let's jump
Begin
The Alex Jones
Documentary
Oh man
I'm already out
Countless
The New World Order
Protesting
I already have to pause
By h.g. Wells
I already have to pause cuz
This is the New World Order
Contact I read the entire book
In order to
That's 60 seconds and already got it already off to a bad start
It turns out he was talking about was that there was a massive chain
The world
Under-educated on Durham
The problem was only going to
Who's going to necessitate
Things were operated
It was just
Inevitable
Any hope
For most people be able to
Continue living
But what Alex is doing
Cutting pieces
Of the quote
He's reading the quote and not
Mentioning
He's cut out
Deer from the actual text of HG Wells book
Here
What are you cutting out
Quotes
Countless people from Maharaja to millionaires
Pukka sahib
The pretty lady
Will hate the new world order
Be rendered unhappy by frustration of their passions
Fishing
Through its Advent and will die protest against
So what you saying here is he
Conveniently cutout
Are the people who specifically h.g. Wells
Will be against this new world order of equity where people are able
To survive
These people specifically maharaja's which is
King
Millionaires
Lucas
Which is a term
The colonialist made people call them
The British
And particularly when they colonized
Which basically translated to
Gentleman
And pretty ladies you know that's just turned
Time for like
Social
High class
Damn you got understand h.g. Wells
Lady isn't just a woman
It's a term
Evaru title
We are sea
And Alex Jones
Should we use
I hope they die
Activity
This is Smedley Butler
I'll get it to him later
No no
What it what is what is going on right now
This is cats mate Potter pure bright
You're good. Good lad
The potential
For the disastrous rise of misplaced power
And will protect the very word secrecy is repugnant
In a free and open
Society
And we are
Inherently and
Historically
Opposed to secret society
The United States
Or the people of the United States
Secret organizations of the world are no longer Secret
World domination
Lot of tiny little bit
Broadcast I'm Tucker
30 years
I'll never
Jim Tucker
Government
Now we can see a new world coming into view
A world in which there is
Prospect
New World Order
Not really
Bilderberg is a bad guy
Well I want to talk to you a little bit quickly
Documentary
Literally everything else
Bilderberg for 27 years
Appointments documentary come out exactly nothing to show for it
Real definitive
Information if you really ever put out
Yeah if he hasn't like
Do you have any real proof
It will be in this documentary and it is not one of my guiding Prince
That's probably
Cryptic about it
Has some guy
From Europe who he doesn't know who it is who sent him a list of attendees every year
That's all that's all
I've no idea what the US every year
I am struggling to find the French word for deep or the French word for
For throat cuz I would have
Totally tossed
Like a deep throw but I would have used a great
My complete lack of multiple languages
Destroyed me
For publication called
Spotlight publication
Is referred to as very anti-Semitic
Editorial
Literally called
The defamation League
16 million-dollar defamation lawsuit
The spotlight
The charges raised by Buckley
Were they constituted libel
The first one was charged that the National Review
Had promoted the right of militant
Specs
Deviance
Doublelist
Small children by publishing both sides
Homosexual rights
Okay
So you understand
The judge found
That the National Review
Was not promoting
Militant sex deviance
Deviate
Being like
Was bored
The second one
Involved
Repeatedly claimed that the National Review at surrendered its editorial Independence
Design Tower
Through a deal with the ADL
And they found that there was no proof of that and that that cost
The power to broker deals between
Is that what they do
Are there perfume
Yeah but whatever yuty is it go to the ATL
Get the people whenever they do this
I'm already angry where
Yeah I am 12 and a half hour long
Yeah
Need it whenever people are just like
Oh yeah it's Southern Poverty Law Center deal between Iran and
Secret Patriots
Welch
Look at what they do
Goldman Sachs
Negotiating
Negotiate
You're a fool man you're a fool
Boardrooms were there
Is the best way to screw over the Zionist like what are you doing
Goldman Sachs
Use vatf
So also I wanted to point this out
You can find a back pad log of Jim Tucker's writing about the Bilderberg Group
Holy
It's all in G
Might as well
It's just full of conversation
Bear Wild overwritten
The dialogue globalist
Is there
I think it's probably a lot
I watched another documentary about a little bit late
You made it perfectly clear he's never gone
Bilderberg
Every year and then chickened out.
Cuz he's afraid that they're going to take him out
Okay well then why are you still playing
Cuz he takes
So you got it
This is why
Is ultimately an adverb
Never
Commitment
Still f******
Video
George h.w. Bush
Right mention the New World Order and it's really really important
That people take that in its proper
It's really scary cuz he said the words New World Order and now everyone's afraid
But you have to understand that speech
Was about how a rock hit just
Invaded
That was the context
The speech the new world order was not about how
D-roc had just
Defeated
Hulk Hogan NWO
Wrongly
Rockwood wws all the way
The WWF Attitude Era slogan
WWE slogan
So the new world
Pretty Club not bad not bad a result of being sued by the
Worldwide
Bush was talking about
For decades the cold Ward been creating unsustainable tension between the US and USSR Wichita
Improperly
The two largest powers in the group were at odds with each other and they would constantly look to face off with each other in proxy wars
Bush announces engaged in talks
Gorbachev in Helsinki
We believe the racks aggression
And must not be tolerated
No peaceful International order is possible with larger States
Devour
They're smaller neighbor
Clearly no longer
Dictator count on
West confrontation
Concerted unx
Digression
That is pretty funny in hindsight
Anouk
A new partnership of Nations has begun and we stand today to unique
Extraordinary moment
Sent you a new world order
Some sort of spooky One World Government as much as it is
The new way of things being done is
Dictators can't rely on this idea that there
The superpowers are going to be otherwise engaged
Practice it didn't work out that way
But that was what he was talking about
I think that's important ultimately what
What is
Any day
You're talking about
The New World Order of today
The world order of
World Order of yesterday
Like new does not mean it's a massive
Changing of the Guard
Before we used to be busy with all this s*** now we got to kill you God damn it I mean
Directions over here
Figured out that
We doing that
Anymore so now we have both
Massive military budgets
Guess what
Gulf War
You do it
Honor problems
With the conspiracy community
Rush International Paradise as opposed to New World Order
So much easier like those terms
Mixtape
Situation
Find myself in mixtape
Is fresh
Absolutely
I really don't find a lot of
George h.w. Bush
Was admitting to
Anything along the lines
But never seen
True
Council on Foreign Relations
Been a member for long time and was actually a director for some period of time I never mention that
When I was campaigning for re-election back home in Wyoming
Series I do like this
Bilderbergers right there
What is
I'm flabbergasted
Documentary about really
You're really quick because I think that
Using Gary Hart as someone whose
Pointing the finger at the bushes
Is not a good way to go about
Run for president in 1988 against then-vice President George HW
W bush
I think as I recall it was when he
But it was during the time that I was when him and his wife
For separated
Really infidelity but it got really salacious so weird to go back in time
Those guys down the front runner on the Democratic side
100 years
Incumbent VP
Really like he was going to Frederick
George h.w. Bush
Screwed him over Royal
Also Bill Clinton put Gary Hart on a national
Security Board
Is a bipartisan us Commission on National Security in the 21st century
Security issues and what-have-you
Sure sounds like
Changes were needed but no one
Implemented
And then 911
The lady
See problem as broads
He
You probably had access to those warning
Things that you know
Bin Laden
Determined to strike in the US again
Because in the lead-up to
September 11th
He was going around being like
And no one listened to
Well
Osama
It's not like he was just talking and back room riddle
I'm going to a
Like I did years ago
I'm going to do it at
No one could possibly see this coming
The only thing
Listen to Gary Hart
Order will fall
Will
The prettiest European guy
Furious 9
This is exactly that
Less based in reality
Near future
Stromedy
So real quick Alex is about to launch into essentially just
She has nothing back
This is really just in speculating by what
He thinks is calling
Styx our dreams of the Future Vision
We just get to watch it
Oh no
Difference
Is upon mankind
Countries
Every
Evil individual Excel
Close to 80% of the Earth's population
Are forced to live within highly control
Beaver seen the movie
Superhighways
Megacities and keep the population from Enoree
Dixon activity authorized
The danger zone for B
Prison Planet
Drop dumpling.
This is the vision of the global Elite there go
Program
Humanization
Where the signs of tyranny is law control
Designed to ensure the overlords Monopoly of power
Our species will be condemned future unless the masses are awakened
Your plan
He said
Wrote this
He wrote it
I'm sure he said nothing
Nothing except for tons of documents at all
I got to be honest I already wanted
Definitely shouldn't but I already want one
Kind of shut down after he's dead
After he started talking he was like
Countries are a thing of the past
Countries I haven't really been a form of Independence
The family really those are forms of collections
I don't understand what the point that he is trying to make so far yet is
Cuz it's not based on
No but we've already talked about this your kind of all right with that
Bad idea
It being in here cuz he's lying
About
Specific document
Really real
Right don't want
Let's move forward
You be here all night
Mobile
Defeated
My secretive group
The Georgia Guidestones
Testament
Mobile Court Apartments
Population
I mean you can put anything in stone really so you know about the
The Georgia Guidestones
Anymore
True
Built-in 1980s financing
The penis
So for those who don't know what the Georgia Guidestones
Which is light a bunch of a conspiracy theorist to believe that he was a Matt remote control car
No he was a rosicrucian that's what the
Rosie Rosie Riveter
Rose crucifix
That's about it
It's really crazy
Because
It is still a mystery
No one really knows a lot
Problem solved Mysteries
1 documentary enjoy that
No-one speculated that
A number of people have speculated that it's
Because it's in Georgia Atlanta
Call yourself
Starseed Buffalo
Excuse me
Give me the idea that this secret has been not managed
Be kept
The tablet
Better setup
There are messages
Not Commandments
Messages
Arabic Chinese Russian
Swahili
Write the first one is that
You should maintain Humanity under 500 million In Perpetual balance
And that's the only one
Conspiracy theorist
Could you pick up some grocery
Cool
Be cool
Protect people in Fairlawn
Just courts
Internally resolving extra
World courts
The common sense
Another one balance personal rights with social duties
So I mean it's not all like some
I'm sort of looking both ways before
A lot of members
Superbad
I talked to the Quarry people
You said that he represented organization that wanted
Create Age of Reason
Speculated that there's two possibilities
Possibilities that are possible
At all
The first is that it's a well-funded performance
That is possible
I think it could be a giant
People are buying into it Whatever Gets all hot and bothered.
Or two I think it's entirely possible
This guy going by the name Marcy Christian was
A front for a sort of apocalyptic group
I believe the disaster was in
I knew that this land
Georgia was not going to be flooded
Immediately by Rising water it was a lot of up
It is really well situated
Natural disaster
Everything is setup astrological
Like the different tablets or setup
To be like
Maximums and minimums of the
Wobble of Planetarium
Alien
Scooby-Doo
This is the way I would I would have sent it
If they erected this Monument to
To serve as a message to
Survivors of This Disaster that they saw coming
So that these survivors could avoid some of the things
That got us into trouble and hindered our ability to save ourselves from whatever disaster
Misguided or not
I actually like this a lot more on their side I am on anybody else
The other thing about it is
Making a documentary that doesn't have a 37 minutes
Give me the astrology signs are and then they build a thing
Like that's
Trail that's got a thing for something
They don't have musical accompaniment
I'm pretty soon after the building of the Georgia Guidestones
To Elbert County Georgia
So if anybody
Yeah that's not another look
Temperature
Anything
Nonsense like Mark Dice and Alex Jones
Petition that the County Government
Government believe that
Nefarious
Some sort of evil thing they could take them self
But the reality is it staying up is profitable
For both sides
Is if it went down then Alex wouldn't have this
It's good for tourism
Elbert County
It works for everybody and it's interesting
Thought-provoking
There's no doubt it
About that
Later
Hours
Man this is our own money
Alive
I guess I'm not doing it
Jump back
In this film
Intelligence Network
The published
Special
Not much
Anytime Alex credit is
He is a published on Mike's
Give me a name and then give me the one thing and then tell me exactly how many
Really fun publishing talk about Michael Kaufman
Information about brothers
Absolute performance artist
Author
Information about Michael Kaufman online
Websites like him
Like Alex Jones's website is responsible for getting the word out about Agenda 21
Globalist plan to take over the United
Was that in one of his ecological papers
Probably
He did so and actually some pretty deceitful ways that will get into
Wildlands
Get ready
Take off the sweater
I'm looking at the
What time and where six-and-a-half minutes into this
BoBoiBoy 2 hours and 20
This thing so it will post on infowars.com
I don't know I don't know
Kaufman have cancer
Recognize that he was dying
This is like a farewell to that community
As a researcher in the American Paper industry I ran a multimillion-dollar research project on the effects of acid rain
When the results came in
I was told to quash my results or find a new job
That was when my eyes were opened to the fact that it was politics driving the science and not the other way around
Now I would say that the most likely real-life explanation
Terrible job on this study
Because you forgot
Instagram is a actual problem
Think anybody's ever said that it's not
Problem
Acid rain from the sky
Is not an issue
Acid rain causes really serious problems
Fleming first of all just
Water life-size end up
Killing all sorts of
Is daddy and how its setup I cannot find it
Can acid suit
Okay now sprays Mastodon
I think more likely the story is a
Not real
I think you just talk
Kinship
Because
Vinings betabrand
Completely unbelievable
Except possibly
Situation where the paper
He was working for one
Change is finding
But that doesn't make sense
Because they would
Be more interested in what he actually
Claimed to have found
Acid rain
No one's motivation makes sense in the story and the science
So I'm left to believe that the 160 left behind
Farewell post
Was a big live at
Makes me question any
Forest ecology
Ecosystem
Vacation
Dr.cox
Ratification
Convention on biological diversity
The concept
Been around for centuries
It's been receiving
Tremendously
20th century George Bush the first female president
George Bush use a lot of his speeches implies that he really want
Which we have
A universe
Who are Global type of government
In which every human being
Ultimately responsible
Policies
It is
A new world order
I don't understand what you're trying to explain
Alex will try to
The world does it's a good right
I think what they're missing
Is like
Dia is bad
And not the fact that everybody that they wanted Powers the worst person
Execution
Conception
New World Order Westside
It inside
They're working right now
Play for a North American Union
That's why there's a lot of people watching
Way to go around some fun stuff about Ron Paul
I just don't care what you think about that
Put out a newsletter
Really f***** up stuff
Here's one example
About the LA riots
You said was only restored in La when it's time for the blacks to pick up their welfare checks.
Virginia
HIV crisis
Cuz you said that
I guess that's
Relatively immigrants
How black people in general
There's a quote
In general.
That usually means
If you ever been robbed by a black teenager
Roof
So anyway Ron Paul claims
Let her know like the Articles don't aren't sign
But other articles that were written
Newsletter
What's a little suspicious
My assessment is that either this is him lying about what he's written in the past or a completely unacceptable level
I don't know I don't even know where that came from
Question your attention to details non-interventionism largely I
Anti-war in Pro marijuana
Correct
Philosophical beliefs
National Soccer
It's also the reason I
Very strong suggestions
Security
It's really always the same
Roman Empire
Hitler during
Binoculars
He's just I mean I don't even know what that means
Is just like using examples of respect
Rich people
That's proof
He's also comparing Empires and
That is what
Because there are benign insensitive
Three examples
Call it
What you doing what you doing here is yourself only trying to be anti-government
Totally anti-government that's all you're doing
History always shows
Conquest in Empire
Babylon
They all Empires
Those are the only ones
Dominated
Complex governmental systems
To control
Population
Some of them were born
Successful than others
One of them
Genghis Khan
Was incredibly successful you know
One of the big reasons why
Allowed
Himself or
On Empire
To be absorbed by local population
And took them
To I-20
Talk about killed everybody who refused to join
Perfect
Other patterns of Empires
Exactly like
Just be like
Where were those hats
Like that's a great hat let me put that on we're all friends imma get out of here all day
Empires emerge
For Supremacy
In class were financed
Private Banks
Many of the Great money houses
Hedge their bets and finance both sides
So if Alex just wants to
To save that
I like Bank
And stuff like that
Investment
Many of the weapons were made by
Right
AltaVista
Insert referee
Sophisticated intelligence gathering Networks
The financiers a clear Edge
They were slowly getting control videos
It was it was three paintings of a guy at a door
Just hand over there like sophisticated
Does a guy with a glass on the door
Agents
Fought desperately to save his army
Napoleon
20 hours
Nathan Rothschild
The Rothschild family
London Stock Exchange
Stocks Plunge
Rothchilds been able to buy off the entire British
We talked about this a little bit in the past but I need to tell you this.
Being 9 minutes into Alex Jones documentary
Should disqualify everything else he said
This is unbelievably bad
So Jordan
Where
Professor Brian Cathcart of
University
He wrote a book called the news from Waterloo to breaks down exactly what happened
The Rothschild
Early information about Napoleon's defeat at Waterloo using set information
Stock market
Reduced-price
Is an absolute absolute
Medicropper
In the summer of 1846
The story of how the Rothschild was physically at Waterloo
And saw the crushing of the French army first
He knew he could use this and I threw the bat
Everything we could to rush back
It would pain copious amounts
Does money to a fisherman
Taking through a storm to do so
Arrive in London
24-hours before the news of
To make 20 million
Same with pen name of
Derek Vail
The Rothschilds
Specifically in general
The pamphlet was written in 1846
Not around to deny the claims
The Lord over there yes he is known as a
Enemy of Nathan de Rothschild
General
He was not a fan of the Jewish population
So
Leaving now with Nathan who died 10 years before the sampler
What was written so possible to look at the claims
It can be proven that
Absolutely somewhere else
Stock market crash
It seems like that would be
Really easy
To find out good records of the stock Miami like money is a big deal and they like to
To keep really
Good Records
Obsessed
Grants
The show the the progress
Okay so as pieces of the story from the
The bunk the story began to change
Could not have been
So you get around these little Facebook
Documentary debunked
Into something else
The evidence that people site
You know what I would call it
Cuz it was after the original Marathon
And it's also
Myself some 5
Put that down on the board
Full site to verify this conspiracy
Incredibly
There's a newspaper article
From June 20th
Two days after
The Battle of Waterloo
Which states Rothschilds purchase isn't stock
However this is a forgery of the original newspaper
Those words do not appear in the real surviving copies of
Need Archibald
Allison
Two years after the
Pamphlet circulator
All European nations good for them
18:50 ostensibly from an American visitor to London
James Gunn
I'm right quote they say Michelle Rothschild has mounted a couriers
From Brussels to Austin
Fast clipper
That's at the moment something is decisive one way or the other
However in 1950 the diary was exposed as a hoax
Even though
Sure
Waterloo a bank employee in Paris Road Nathan a letter that said I'm in
Done well in the early information
You had of the victory game
At Waterloo
Fresh air
Which allows us to finally put the story and its proper
Papers published in the week of Waterloo
First person to bring authentic news of Waterloo
Nathan Rothschild
Rather it was a man who would learn
Belgian City
This guy was only identified as mistress
City of Dover
Who's telling the story
Who's telling the story in the morning of Wednesday the 21st of June
12 hours
For the efficient
Official news
Had arrived
At the end of the battle
It was published in at least
Three newspapers that after
We also know that the news report written
412b paper
Referred to Nathan Rothschild received a letter from
From one of his information
Mr. C of Dover
I'm passing the news on to the
That's the first thing that he did
Though this is noted before to other similar other people
Who are name
And vilified by history
People sent letters
Yes
Proof
So I
The question is did Rothschild have time to buy stocks
And chairs
With this information that you've gotten from lettuce
Apparently
But in the cymbarka does it. It could not have been enough to accumulate Holdings
Sufficient to earn the million
What about the entire Bridge
Inflationary
North markets double is game
Open stock prices that way
Nathan Rothschild may have done well in the purchase
Stocks that Rose sharply following the confirmation
Dwarfed by those of numerous tribal investors
Without any information
Hey Bucky government securities earlier more cheaply
200 years on from the Waterloo
Not much
Is Western State entail
It's just possible to see
Spectral elements
With belt
This is just
Of
So a guy named Bill
Still called the money man
Which retails the story of May
Bill still
That's rough
Stay real Phil
Slow
So he tells the story of Nathan Rothschild manipulating the British market for his own
Courier
Who brought him
Mission about Waterloo
Interesting Lee the only historical reference
I'll take a look I've read better fantasy novel names
I'll tell you her name.
The right lift
Prince you can find for the name rough worth
Contacts
Is the name of The Courier character in E90
40 Nazi propaganda film
The Rothschilds
Now for a net
Punchline
That's where is Bill Stillman from
And here's the final punchline
Alex Jones that bill still on his show multiple times
To the spouse
So also there's no major crashing
15 m p and Market
Nathan made purchases in July 1815 after a very slight dip in the market
October 18th
Lb worth of shares
On October 8th
Then finally sold in November 8th
About 40%
Course
6:30
It's good but it's not nearly
But it's not nearly
People present court all of that information is available you can find all of it
If this is some of the easiest
The bunk
Right there
This is perpetuated three years just because of the desire to State Road 2
Still doesn't believe
Probably
The gum around until the cotton gin
That other guy we learned in school
Alex Jones is a repeating
Nazi propaganda
Congratulations
What the news of Napoleon's defeat
Finally arrived
Stock sword
Bridget
And walk child
Already dominant British Centerfire group even more aggressive
Our troops and bureaucracy spread across the globe
The Sun never set
Umbra tenuous hold
This is really bad.
Pretty bad
And of course
They're getting the interest off of the loans that they've given the various governments
The wars that they have actually helped emulate and
Create
Real quick I wanted
They're real quick to the really put a button on what they're saying
Make a profit off of selling
Companies
Baby
You should probably be
He talked about 2 yes absolutely didn't want to talk about that
Like the guns do a lot of
Lot of the killing part like maybe we should take
Send
The thing that I wanted to bring up is the effect of what they're doing is teaching this narrative wherein
The two belligerent actors in a war aren't really to blame
Thanks for manipulating them into fighting so they can be put into debt or whatever
And I just want to be super clear about that
This is out of the protocols of the Elders of Zion
This is other propaganda now being spread by Michael Kaufman
On the documentary
It would be nice
By 19
Sherman was a rising Force
Leader Bank
Funny both sides
Scent of insert rep
Ali Industrial Revolution
There was absolutely no reason to have World War 1
Ideal opportunity
The banking cartel
On June 20th
Austrian Hungarian throne
Franz Ferdinand
Was assassinated
While traveling in a motor
I was just a video of him
I'm pausing it right here because I want you to
Take very
Notice
Lot of hats
I'll just tell you this while this picture is on screen cuz it
It's fun
Dangerously close to
Fezes the assassination of Archduke Franz Ferdinand is named
We'll talk about him a little bit
Not him
Now Alex thinks.
Christian Bale from the this is actually a very famous
A lot of people
It fits this is from a book called the trigger hunting the Assassin who brought the world to War by Tim butcher
The picture is not Gabriel
It fits so well with a narrative of the desperate assassin
The countless astorians
Reporters broadcasters and filmmakers
Have claimed that the subjective
It is not
Subject of the picture is actually an innocent bystander
Sandra
Ferdinand bear
Who is caught up in the sweep of arrest following the shooting
This is very easy to find
The fact that Alex Jones
The presenting
Embarrassing
A Serbian secret society
Connections to French and British
So what was that
Star Wars theme
Alex is only reference
For this and it bibliography is the Wikipedia page for black ant
Which is not good that. That's not going to cut it
Abscess
That was responsible for
Committing regicide in the early
India
Supposed you would be killed by Pirates
So most of the claims that the black hand was deeply involved in the assassination
Archduke Franz Ferdinand
Testimony provided in
Against
Chief
Demetria jevic
Historians believe was exaggerating the roll
The Black Hand
Blade
The death penalty
He was involved with black hair
It was like
Conspiracy of all these people he might be able to spare himself
Involvement in the assassination of Archduke Franz Ferdinand
They provided Gabrielle au Prince
His accomplices with some weapon
It allowed them to travel freely to Sarajevo.
Every low and his crew were the ones who planned it
And they were not part of some massive International conspiracy
So is more like they just wanted them to buy
Yeah they were motivated by hatred of the austro-hungarian Empire who'd been oppressing in
Destroying their home
Not unreasonable
The situation late 1800s early 1900s
Complete mess of the Balkans
Populations were not being heard by anyone in power
Story before never
Never recently been towards the Ottoman Empire but they're over by the Oscar
Empire
1870s
Meanwhile Serbia
The Ottoman Empire in the late eighties
And abolished
Feudalism
So it's that there was like a shining example of self-rule that was possible
We have another that so gay
Small town
Fuel situation
They were completely oppressed
Everyone was Miss
Should just have been happy with
What's the weather like
So as I bought he thought that
Depressed musics.
It was all because of her
Ends up happening to folks like us
School in Sarajevo
In order to
Footpath
To get to a train
In order to reach the train
Navigation he Witness
The feudal plight of all of the neighboring
Communities with a croat Serb or Muslim
Futile
Exactly was connected was a result of the oligarchs the austro-hungarian
Ecology met with a bunch of radicals and having witnessed the relative Freedom Sarajevo
Freezer homes from the Oscar
If we had now
Technology back
I think you would have a pretty solid podcast
I don't I don't
I don't support what he did I think assassinating a leader is still wrong
But it is fascinating to look at
Like you have one kid
From a small town who went got radicalized
Assassinated leader
Triggered World War
But ended up being still missing
Do a second World War
Holocaust that happened during that World War Rebels still to the present day
Right it's insane
Place by just
Oppressing
Population
I think I think
More interesting
Because
Clearly shows how
These massive McIntosh
Most likely going to wind up
Exploding
Right
It's not like
Everything's going on throws little wrench
Like he was
Yeah holyshit
It was just this one dude
Pixel
Successful
I'm in the first place
It was a free-for-all or people are just running around and that was
Assassinate a guy
6 people are all f***** up except him
Assassinate
Takeaways horrors of World War 1
There is a humorous aspect to the visual
Be exactly this
Gotta move a lot myself
Call Lisa
So
Speed right now
This is going to be a power
Play Nas.
World War 1
Super quick
Neither him nor Michael Kaufman ever prove
Specifically to
To get countries
Sent that in control.
Restaurant
Just assertive
Also if it was
Because of that idea that we put everybody into
Yeah we didn't have a World War 3
More likely because
We forgave so much debt
German
Japanese
Had a cruise over the time
And said you know what
You rebuilt
It turns out that if you want to not fight world you don't
Punish the people who
Opposite happen
Anyways
Our six-and-a-half
Is juice a fiber
It's just when the movie turn off hours
Rothschild control banks in Germany France England and Austria
20 million were killed in the war
Because of conflicts
People involved never fight again
They dubbed it the war to end all wars
Why do they want war what worthwhile is money and power
But secondly they want
The League of Nations
They had this in their plan
All along
Consequence
Once the war was over are about to be over that begin to formulate
This idea of a
Was never ever Harry.
I also just real quick
Committed in order to form
No citation
Just something that he deserting
The complex world that was going on
Pre-World War
And all the many factors that led to
Very unnecessary World War
Consulting
Cuz I wasn't that sucks
Also the citation
Empire behind puppet governments in Council
In the name of shopping all future conflicts
They propose the country
Sean Connery
President established
Woodrow Wilson
He was basically
Play college professor
Call system
F*** yourself
Look
Woodrow Wilson sucks
Is insulting
Because
Look
The things you can't take away from him
He was the professor is professor of political science
Princeton
Second
He was the president of Princeton which is a political position from 1902 to 1910
Further
He was a governor of New Jersey from 1911 to 1913 before becoming president
If the claim is that he's just a professor who got drafted to be the president
It doesn't it doesn't match
He has
A political background
Doubt with an apocryphal story about Woodrow Wilson
Campaign manager
You look like
President and that
Apocryphal story
Entire history of our government
Who has no experience
Serving in a publicly elected position
The lead convened in Paris in 1990
Many nations
Public publicly elected official or government military
And refuse to drink
Country saw the League of Nations
Refuse to join
The only countries that I can find the joint
Irrelevant
USSR in Germany
And none of them were because of threats.
Because of the prevailing attitude after World War 1
Isolationism
What's the word
Oceans away from you assholes so interested in European affairs
United States
Support this but you could do it I want to be a part of it
French
Do USSR Ginger
They would be added to the league later but we're kicked out
Spurge
The rest of the world
Restarting World War
Of course they weren't allowed to join the League Navy
When was formed after World War 1
They were in 1926 but Hitler withdrew in 1933 shortly after he became
Nowhere that work
So
So if you have like an authoritarian
Right
And he's like
What we need to do
Get away from all of these International
Call Avista
And we need to make sure that we are not
In any way
I responsible for their Acts
Directions or anything like that
Usually that's like
Power grab and then it will eventually
Scenario
Generally speaking
And then you start
Frustrated by the US Congress
Walking Dead
British intelligence
Rockefeller
Shut up the Council on Foreign Relations
In New York City
The council recruited the best and brightest
American Life
To support the growth
Lcfr State admission
In favor of an all-powerful
Where do they stick
They didn't
There's a purpose.
Bruise on their website is very clear
Council on Foreign Relations is an independent non-partisan
My membership organization
Some Think Tank and publisher dedicated
Government officials business executive journalist
Educators
Civic and religious leaders and other interested citizens in order to help them better understand the world
The foreign policy choices facing the United States
21c institutional
Including
Special program
Send develop expert
Next Generation
Affordance
The decal negotiate
Peace conference
A group of diplomats financier lawyers
Concluded that Americans needed to be better prepared
Responsibilities
World affairs
I'm stocked
That
There's also I'm not going to read this whole thing cuz
Super long
So where did they where do they say
No more.
It turns out that they
So I'll just want to be sure that
Really scares
Fiercely weirdos like Alex
About this like destroying borders
2006 op-ed
Website
Written by the president of the council himself
The basic argument
Is as follows
The world's Plus
Coexist
With a larger number of
Powerful
At least partly
Corporation
To non-governmental
From terrorist groups to drug cartels
From Regional and Global Institution
And private-equity
The sovereign state
God is influence
Buy them for better
As much as it is able to
Monopoly power wants
Enjoy by starburns
Is being eroded
Not by
Some sort of evil tooth fairy
Justified
Power out
Corporations
And inasmuch as we're able to communicate
Better there's literally everything across
The entire world and it's
Sway from
The power of states to
Which is why countries like
China and Russia
North Korea
To keep the outside
You start to see you around the world at what other people are doing
Or if you let your people control overseas and experience at themselves like like what happened with Gabriel open
Zachary
About this idea
Define what a lot of r
National
Ideas are
Our notion of sovereignty must therefore be
Conditional
Contractual
Estate sales to live up to its side of the bargain by sponsoring
Weapons
Mass destruction or conducting Janice
Forfeits the normal benefits of sovereignty
To attack removal
Patience
The Diplomatic challenge for this era is
Gained widespread
Support for principles of State
Conduct a
The procedure
For determining remedies
Wendy's Prince
Violated
The goal should be to redefine sovereign
Arrow globalization
To find balance
Queen the world is fully sovereign state
An international
System of either world government
The basic ideas
Still provides
Constraint on violin
Needs to be
Be preserved
But the concept needs to be adapt
World
What's the main challenges to order
Come from what Global Force
Do two states
And what governments do to their stupid
Rather than from what states do too
Each other
The very very reasonable
Opposition
Put out
Very clearly by the leader
Of the Council on Foreign Relations
Does not want to destroy State sovereignty
What's a greater understanding of the world we live in
I suppose the
The question to ask after that though would be
What is the logic
That
It is
Worldstar
I think it's World governance
To some extent
Brought enough
Concept that there really benign versions of it
There's really really
Non-intrusive
Sovereignty sovereignty of State
Within a world
Government
Cuz I mean but they're all kind of stupid
Maybe 500
I think it's time to Illinois.
Are f****** rightfully we walked from
Gary Indiana that motherfuker Gary stole our land immediately after he found
Doubt that Napoleon had lost it Waterloo time we took it back
The point night
I agree with you
Yeah it's not
Be merged
Confusion
Supposed
Conception is good I just don't trust any
People
Usually
You have a good idea
If you have people who don't know what they're doing
Diplomat
It doesn't
If you have people who know what they're doing usually
The problem is generally speaking
The people who know what they're doing
Usually trying to go the bad way
They're the ones who are you there with knowledge
And the people who want to help
Usually stoop
Or they're being held back by too many stupid people yelling is wrong
Ministered by a tiny
By 1930 the promoters of War Cinema
The Fabian socialists entered in London
And the fascist they stood
So if you understand what you just said
He said
Powerful World controlling group
It's split into the Fabian socialist
Some Europe
Poppycock you remember the the famous
No I don't miss this in my research
These things are still working together but it's a fake split
Publix
It was a
I can't be with my family
I got to go
Iraq
Alex's Citation for this point documentary
The Fabian socialists
A fascist
You keep saying
Guitar. It's crazy
So irresponsible
Graphic photos of Hitler
They came from the same place is so stupid
Knox Knox
Does the Fabian Society
Really interesting
Babe
Formed
Splinter Group out of this group called the founder of the fellowship of New Life
Alright that doesn't that sound
It is
The fellowship was an organization founded in 1883 that's not the cultivation
Character Annie Channel
They advocated for pacifism and vegetarian
From 1883 student go together so often
Give me the pacifism
Animals with faces
Articulating their goal
Quote
We recognizing the evils and Wrongs that must beset men so long as our social life is based upon selfish
Above All Things by a love based upon unselfishness
Love
Unite for the purpose of realizing the fire
Life among ourselves
Enabling others to do the same
And we now form ourselves into a society to be
Be called The Guild
Or Fellowship of the new life
Carry out this purpose
Might as well
The heavy stuff going on with them
Fellowship
Turtle transformation of the individual
External affairs
Decided to take me to start a new group to do that
And that was where the Fabian
Started
Threats ended up being the same
Italian fashion
Fascism started when Benito Mussolini was kicked out of the socialist society
Cuz he's too busy being a very very credibly National
Fascism
With that
Nazis grew out of the German Workers
Party
She's Metacritic
Nationalistic
They hated the Socialist Democratic Party
They thought they were fighting bolshevism and International jewelry
Liberal organization
Over Hitler Hitler
The party
National Socialist German
German Workers Party
Physically harder to trick left-wing workers and
Supporting them
Most of the rides
But people need some people are stupid or socialist
Yeah
That's
Amazing it still effective after all of the de bunking courses that has been done
But that's the point of these groups
Send the same socialism and that's not true at all
Got our perfect
Examples for why the
It still happen
Because
The
Smart people
Who are
Going all-out we're trying to
Transformers
Trying to make the world stadium
Did you see how many
F****** words they use to try and say that
Yeah quite a few
What are the Nazis describe themselves as
Herbalife
Communicate
Like why can't we started
Just like don't be a dick
Just two minute podcast
Here's my ears my mission
Statements
Before you do something
Stop think for 2 second
Don't do it was just put out an episode that Alex is lying
Yeah
National socialism
For establishing a new world order
Adolf Hitler
This is fun
Citation for a quote
Which they can't do cuz this is a fake quote
I looked into it is absolutely a Facebook
It's not a real quote Alex is just recording
This is a meme
Great
Supporters of
The fascist of the United States in England
Should be used to quickly transform
All the more sophisticated
Definition of socialism
Asserting that though that you're not watching this
Socialism
He might not be actually starting that he might just
Be using that
And you put it in the documentary he's definitely
Congressional Medal of Honor winner
An attempt by the robber Barrel to larger military open
Testify Congress
What's the most powerful man in the mirror
Socialism
United States
I appeared before the
Congressional committee
The highest representation
I was supposed to lead an organization of 500,000
Which would be able to take over the funk
So you want to do something fun
He smokes
Cigarettes a day
It appears that he wasn't lying
Laurel Street
May or may not have been telling the truth about the plot to f****** murder
And early Chipotle and put them in a ceremonial position
Actual
Gold standard
Gerald McGuire in bilge oil remembers of the American Legion
Who hated spr
They started by appealing to him because he was a veteran
American Legion convention
Mostly about how they needed to bring back the gold
Veteran
Wait what
Insisted on meeting the bank roller of their operation
Robert Sterling Clark
Who is the heir to be singer silver sewing machine
Fortune
Clark was concerned about the
Instructions
Is 30 million dollars to save the other
Good math
Let's not get mad
Is particularly impressed by the Italian
How are they
Mess with government
I get it. Took me a second to spell different
That's why that's why
So it was finally revealed to Butler
Seems unfair
The real reason they were approaching him was they wanted him to lead an attachment to 500,000 veterans
Washington to overthrow
Str
He did not go along with it
In their investigation the house found
Credible
But there was no evidence whatsoever that merited anything further than compelling Maguire to testify
At which point he denied everything
No one was charged in the house committee refused
Subpoena many of the other people
To be involved
Because their involvement was based on hearsay and second-hand information
So interesting in American history but the more you look at it the more it looks like
The opposite of what Alex
This wasn't
Recurred planned by Rich business interests
Specifically because they feared socialism and communism in the form of ser
The reporter quotes by the f****** globalist
Well
Fascist government of this country to save the nation from the communist
Do you want to tear it down and Rec built in America
In preparation
For their coup
They spread rumors that fer was death
Realty
Either pasta
Posing
All in all this supposed to mean
Is most Ramen
Alex Jones
A coup
The Patriots
To try and put Trump
But the power which puts him on
The exact wrong side of this
Is the Maguire of This Not That
I really find that. Like that
Really interesting
You know most times when you have a story like that
You know gets investigated and it turns out there's nothing
Congressional Medal of Honor he's not he's not coming out there like
Alex Jones
I mean Jesse Ventura was a governor of a state
Metals
He won the
The Hell in a Cell match
One time
I don't know if you did that
Fascist
Edward King of England
Was forced to abdicate
Because of his public support
For Hitler
This isn't because he wanted to marry
Losing American socialite has been previously divorced
That was not allowed no Edward was the Monarch is the official head of the Church of England
Policies that divorced people get remarried unless their spouse was
So it would have been bigamy if the two of them would have been married in the churches eyes
So everyone was against
The Prime Minister Stanley Baldwin told Edward that if he went against the public wishes Mary Wallace much of the government
Resign in protest
That's 1936 Edward abdicate the throne formally
On June
Third 1937
Her divorce was finalized married Wallis Simpson
Because you f****** loved her
They stayed married till he died
Is the queen or whatever it is
Windsor
After you'd actually at the
1937-d visited Germany and met Hitler at the obersalzberg resort
Buy Hitler the best interest
Decide with a knob
There's nothing to be gained by sitting out waiting for one side to destroy the other
It's clearly was never a quote
He took residence
In France and in 1940 when the Nazis
What was
You never roast
Pro-nazi
Inclination
Is horrible on its own
But it wasn't the reason he had to
To the cases because
Situation
Seems so bizarre
That's because they love
But
That's just a
That's the stupid
Which is
It's fascinating
Look back at it
Because we're not at all close to it
Like okay
He married to this girl
Right
Because
He was divorce
No she was she was divorced
She's divorced twice
That doesn't
King of England
Right
Who gives this
Is the king of England because
Technically
According to magical beliefs
The king is also the head of the church
About that
The king is the head of the church getting married
That's true
Oh my God I never thought about that
Circular
Wow
Yeah they would threaten with the government
Hold on I think you're working something at this moment
Furious because the
The reason
I want to hear that song
Is because he wanted to
Worst crimes
The king had to step down
Peace out of it which is a big
Problem
But
Is still a good actor that out now
Salt Lake
Decatur
Legitimately
Beautiful
Ideas
He did love her enough
That you like
Fine
I don't need you
Also
It's a smart idea
It seems like the role of being
Kingwood
Signing and personality was not Well Suited
So to speak
Swinger
Blind
Why did these people believe that
If he were a Nazi he would have to
Stepped out that's crazy because
If he was the king and he wasn't banging
Somebody who'd been divorced
Appoint
Like all of the all of the
British royalty related to all the other rich
Everywhere else royalty
Look up.
Control
What does Flushing
Believe the directions
Just as they had done was Napoleon
Oh yeah
The rise and fall of the Third Reich
True
Are Fulton mirror
Barbie roll
Public domain sea turtle
See that's what I'm talking about this so much filler once again the elite
Global governor
Could save Humanity from certain destruction
And this time
The elite
April 1945
San Francisco
United Nation was founded
You're right complex was built in New York City
On land donated by John D
Cuz that means nothing but it's fun
You and wanted to build their own City
Frazee
I told John D Rockefeller
Like a self-sustained
That was what their plan was next weekend
If we can't really do that
Hustle
Also like no laws apply because
International land or whatever in the compound is not really true
It's just that there's no sales
Kill some of the UN building
So I'm
This is actually just
That's something I discovered in my research
Second thing I discovered to my research
Is Batu the reason John D Rockefeller had this land
It's cuz it's on Nelson Rockefeller put an option
Because there was a guy named Williams
Why is it
People with regular name
It's weird I want crazy
Acres of land
I like zeckendorf try because a good movie
Dreyfus
So he under this land is 17 acres in Manhattan
You get a bill 200
In an enclosure
Like there's already a bad ideas and artist's rendering of it
Craziest things I've ever seen in my life you have all these buildings
They look like
Outside the building
Huge
Sing everything you need
Hospital
Entertainment all this so you never have to leave
And there was an airport on the roof
Airplanes taking off from the middle of Manhattan 200 feet above the ground
Do you have this plan this second or senior
And he was like
Is a good idea
Can't afford to do that
So the option on the landfill to Nelson Rockefeller was able to buy it for much less than it
It was worse because you could end up in like 8 million dollars
80 million
Dollars
The UN Charter
It's means nothing
Yeah
You your eyes are a bit bigger than your stomach
Great idea
I would say that maybe a having the airport on
On top
Can cause a lot of noise
I think there's
At the first town meeting
Go to Bistro
So I'll post a picture of the
Artist
Rendering it so crazy
F***** up
Shortly after
The incremental formation of Continental Subaru
Continental was the creation of the European Union
So you want to say really quick
The EU was founded in
That would have been it took
Years in order to
To get this thing going
At least started
Everyone would have been
To the sort of thing
The sword of unity of the coming together and
Pretty high
Heifer heifer WWII
Bruins
50 years
To put these plants
Define lateral plan of the globalist
Nonsense
The globalist
Using stealth
The Treaty of London claimed
North America
Intention was the formation
European superstate
You can't assert
Things like that
You can't know it's true insertive
I read the whole thing
It's a very completely benign document
Such Horrors
Is this
This is very scary
Every member of the Council of Europe must accept the principles of the rule of law
End of the enjoyment by all persons within its jurisdiction of Human Rights
Y'all just going to f****** terrify you
Does going to terrify you
The aim of the Council of Europe members
For the purpose of safeguarding and realizing the ideal
And principles which are their common heritage
Facilitating
Economic
Social progress
This will be pursued through the organs of the council by discussion
How questions
And by a non economic social cultural
Make America great again
Course I'm going to vote for the guy who says
Just about like we're going to create a forum where we can come together and talk about our shared
Kill Everybody
Pissed off whenever any
I think that's really all.
You f****** hate
Bad news
That's the inevitable
Next thing that has to happen or else
The other option is we all fight
I don't want that
Most people don't want that
Sure seems like it
Possible cycle
Get out of it this
A constant infighting
It's not if we collaborate
Collaborate
And then
Where the war
Far enough
Rabble Rouser
Or like all of those guys
Well you know what
To that other side of that f****** comp
And then after everybody done with that
Put together build something
Comfortable foramen UPS
And then what
Forgotten about those
It over again
Did you ever Junior High have to do like a class project with someone you didn't like
Couldn't get anything
Sing Don cuz you guys didn't like
With Legos and was like
You're good at this
Running
Can you start working together
You realize that you're getting
Something done together and
All of a sudden you realize you don't actually hate this person that you're in a group project with you drove through it
The world could be like that
I killed Danielle
She was from Russia
Here's another quote
We shall have World Government whether or not you like it
Conquest or bike
That does not sound real
Bibliography
Here Senate Foreign Relations
Committee 19th
Who is the Contessa
Progressive thing to say to the
World Government whether or not we like it
The question is only whether world government
Sensorcon
Very different
Whether or not
Is really
I read the entire speech
He gave testify in favor of resolution
Which if
Would make a peaceful
Transition of the United Nation
Into a World Federation of the United States
The passage of this resolution
First prerequisite towards the development of an affirmative
American policy which would lead us out of the Valley of Death
See his concern was that the way things were looking
The world's alliances were based on negative
Which is to say policies that exist
It's totally against
Something as opposed to affirmative policies
That would exist
To support some
And he says
Until we establish this goal
Continue to ask other people
To unite with us only in the negative purpose
Stopping Russia
Beer inspired negative action makes
Pour cement
That was kind of the big
Big contract
Resolution 56 goes on to the evil of the present
State of international Anarchy
It recognizes that there is no cure for this evil short of making the United Nations
Universal organization
Capable of enacting
Interpreting
And enforcing WWII
To the degree necessary
The Outlaw Force
As an instrument of foreign policy
It states the objective in unequivocal terms
Warburg goes on to say that the resolution requires literally no further steps
United States
It is a broad Declaration of
The purpose and nothing more
Later I use question
About to
The subject of disarmament
I enjoyed
It's a good way to look at it
I've never seen any hope disarmament or limitation of armaments by agreement between sovereign
A state
Because all of the treaties between the Sovereign Nations
Anyone can break
The result
The only result
Is that you give a head start
W gresser
Is fairly true
Well I kind of
Agree and disagree
Agree with his
Philosophy on disarm
I get where he's coming from interesting thought
I don't know if I would
The only way to disarm
It works
Ufirst
Exact core I-4
Exactly
If you want everybody to disarm themselves
You have to do it first you can't be like
Well we have now where is
Okay Russia
You get rid of get rid of
Because it's so slow leaves you open to a changing
The guard
And
The whole program
Exactly
System of government
Open till
Back to this question
Tearing
Under Secretary of State
Quality matters
Dean Rusk had this
When we turned to the United Nations and its
Charter we're conscious of the dominant role which
Support for the United Nation
Has played
In our foreign policy
Principal
To the Charter of the United Nations are
In essence
A summary of the foreign policy of the United American
We should not underestimate the importance
The fact that these principles
So congenial
Have been subscribed
58 other government
The world
Principles which are
Foreign policy
Is a tremendous asset
What's the United States
Careful
Today also
Something most people don't talk about a lot
Most of the UN foreign policy is our foreign policy
Anyway
The Senate Foreign Relations
Committee got together and they put out a report on
December 1st 90
Resolution
Or two
Report out
High resolution
Of its own
That still does make
Because if their foreign policy
Willie Hayes
No that's a fair point
Of the foreign
Create cooperation
He likes other
He likes that
What was the
Revolution
Which was supposed to
Declare that the United Nations
He's cool
Senate impasse
The Bilderberg Hotel
The Bilderberg Group
It's interesting.
Aforesaid
Mission
Steaks
40 earrings for men
Everyone should be afraid of
In the years since 1954 the Bilderberg Group met for the first time
Mostly what they talked about
Attitude
The prevailing attitudes of the business
Leader is in
Government officials
The Soviet Union
And then
So it's mostly about the
Three possible
Behind the Iron Curtain
Right
The minutes of
A North American Union
Form the core of the global government
Enforcement
The Bilderberg Group consists of the heads of all the countries
We're seeing a
With a bunch of
Build airbag
Should names of organizations and stuff
The United Kingdom
What US
Said us European interest
Really big
But it's also a sparsely populated by
Play organization
Chakra
I want to talk really quick about Bilderberg and one of the arguments that Alex
Is Central to his world
And that is what they insist on operating in
Secret
He has
The f****** articles
He brings up he's going to flash up a couple of articles
About them
Microfiche
And stuff like that
Where he went with Jim Tucker to Portugal
Stake out the building
Burger
Yeah Jim Tucker from the beginning about to come back even come back in a big way
So
Jon Ronson
Like followed by some
Black cars
It's all very very suspicious
Nothing ends up happening
Chickens out at the lab
So afterwards
What's the deal
He got in contact with
People from the Bilderberg
September
She ended up getting interviews with like two or three of them
Players in the Bilderberg Group who were at the meeting
Portugal
Explain to him very polite
Candidly
That the reason that they
Prefer secrecy
Don't want reporters to
Is because the p
People who were there would never speak freely
If they knew that things were going to be recorded or they were gone
Going to be released
Can't have a Frank
An open discussion about ideas some that might be bad
You might be embarrassed by the idea that like I really f***** up
Your own country or HP
You wouldn't be able to get anything done
That seems like a compelling
Yeah I imagine for secrecy
Apple
Steve Jobs in every one of those like
Planning meeting
Had the Press
We would not have as many cool Apple
Music you had into your
Career over
Have cooked ideas being reported as
Especially with people
Sure Cuts Round Rock
With reporters like Jim Tucker and Alex Jones
Hobby Airport
Yeah misrepresent
If they were able to go off
Spiraling down the drain of getting anything done
I'm comfortable with that explanation
The table are they probably also collaborating in May
Making deals
That are
Maybe exploitative I would assume Almost 100%
But it doesn't mean that they're trying
One World Government
That's a little bit of acid
Picture of the elite power structure of the world
As a giant pyramid
I get it only the elite of the elite
The group has been around until the mid-1980s rolled up in Coronavirus
Starbucks in my library
Into the late 1990s
So here's an article that's
Specifically
Bridge only consisted of rare one line mention
Put their articles about the Bilderberg Group
He's showing one line but it's so stupid
Alright he's talked about it I got a full 3-in
Used to do
Their Stranglehold on information Isbell into slip
On the outskirts of the national capital today Blacklist
Converged on Hotel
We're private security guards
Imposed
We're about to enter a really fun documentaries most Lively portion of it okay
Crazyshit
Out of the way up top
I'm glad that the last eight hours of our episode
This is Alex
This is where we will have to leave off
Alex Jones
Goes to Canada
What's going to be there when he shows up and what sort of trouble
Will he end up getting it
You tune in tomorrow.
Guys
This is
If you'd like to get to
Taste of the citation
For all of this
You've heard here today on the show
Please go to knowledge
Spike.com we have a bibliography
In progress there that
To cover everything
From today's
Episode
Astrology.com
The stuff is all that all sorts of goodies there
Click on that
We support the sort of stuff
After we do
You can also find us at knowledge site
Also
Knowledge underscore fight
Ron
Very much
You would die
Unsubscribe but leave us a review that sort of thing you can leave reviews on Facebook
As well
It's really going to help
Everybody
So tired
Still
It still has not recovered from the 9-hour recording
Of this
Endgame
So they're coming out over the
The course of the week
See you soon