Hello everybody welcome
Is part 2 of knowledge
I am here in a little bit
Is part two of our coverage
How's you're going to find
Accidentally
You can find that on our iTunes
Search for knowledge
Is there probably wouldn't recommend starting on episode 2
We last left off
What's Joan was
Heading to
Canada what was he going to do their spoiler alert for you going to check in
With the people of Bilderberg and wander around with a bullhorn
So
I hope you enjoy
Let's get into it
Yorgos
Alex Alex
Scary royalty political power Brokers
Add industrial Titan
To a secret meeting that will last all weekend
Is known as the Bilderberg Group cuz they're objecting be worlds
There was a time whenever every newscaster had to have that kind of Ted Koppel voice
What who talks like you
Alex Jones evidence
That the Bilderberg Group is
Looking for world domination all you have is a news reporter thing
Is it because assholes
Every four years Bilderberg Meats in North America
And in June of 2006
This is multiple articles for 2003 the last one was from 2015 hairstyle trends
The capital of Kenya
Push-up
A long history
A meeting of the minds Daniel estulin
Very excited to tell you about it
He's a he's almost as fun as Leo zagami
Not as fun
As our friend
Hammurabi
WhatsApp
Hamamoto
I jokingly reassure my cameraman
But the horror stories we read about
We're probably exaggerated
We do reporters get
Air Force people aren't let in
We do people get
Check the jail house in 34 hours
It happens every time
Well
Bilderberg
Pressure put on them
By the government
Security and that's why all this
If I was told that
If you like cocaine
I scoured all Wrecker
Yesterday an hours today
Trying to
Find something
It was just scary I'm in again I've been all over the world and I've never seen anything like
Hours
Nation what are you here for
Reenactment
In a while
Lifetime
I was answering all the questions
They told me earlier
You guys showed up
Everything
A plan
Jim Tucker
I want first
Not a good plan
So
The only thing I can find about Alex being
Detained biking
Costumes
Is an article 4
Written by Paul Joseph Watson
Prison Planet
And I want you to raise your hand
When you hear the point
Little bit out of place
In this report
Quote
Customs openly told Alex as soon as they brought him into custody that the Bilderberg Group of the wear of his arrival and that this was
The reason for his detainment
I forgot that there's multiple point
All three members of the team were instantly detained despite going through different immigration
Officials knew everything about Alex even the fact that George W bush once had him arrested in 1998
He yelled something at a press conference and police escorted them out
He pretends that he got a ride
So it wasn't like George W bush from his Ivory Tower said arrest that man it was like Alex
And they were like we can't have
Gotcha I was cussed at I was interrogated
Jail threats were issued his officials seized and searched
Through Alex's equipment for 15 hours
He was told that if any trace of pornography was found on his three computers that he would be arrested
Is that a thing that I wasn't wearing
No
I don't believe so don't you think
The little specific specific
Correctly
Canadian officials
No following
Nope
If you were
Memories
I think there is some sort
It's like the customs office
You don't want anybody bring it in the outside
Season p***
Immigrations officials seem to take a gleeful satisfaction in
Claiming they were Liars
Despite one admitting to having seen Alex Jones
Documentary
And he still said that he wasn't
Accusations of drugs and weapons smuggling were throwing around without recourse
You American s*** all over us Canadians and take you can do anything you want to US immigration
Acting like a drill sergeant
I don't believe the story at all
I think Alex Mista
Reply I don't know I think that's what happened
Showed up with a reason why I got
P****
It's ridiculous. That's possible to
Why he would make it that specific is they totally found support and he was like
Call call
Maybe catch some of the still arriving
Life is so hard for you
Play
Currently
The answer is 0 Elite
Pretty boring no Elites
Way more than once Alex is going to get into a conversation of where the property line
Start
I should warn you about that high drama
What's up
What's happening in there right now
This happening
Screaming a lot today
Call Palmer Lake
What about any everybody else
About 10
They can be fine
Later
Is it in that order
Typically big black cars
Bulletproof
That's a stupid cat
We're being kept Welbeck
From the building by
No idea who this guy is
Bmore security
Just a reminder
Want
This is going to be a bit of the next like 10 minutes A lot of them taking pictures of people
Serenity courage
Literally nothing
In the morning
Insole of course I complied with they wanted I wasn't happy about it because I have been tired I drove a quite a long way you know
McDonald's
Can I just saw a bunch of security here and I was wondering what was going on and I asked questions
They said they were having a wedding or they were having some sort of reception
So I decided to tackle couple more questions and I thought it was kind of weird
Flashlight off the trailer over right now
We're also in front Giselle
Coleman it look like Coleman the hotel so I left
Where is this morning
Well I didn't have to wait because there's a proof of people out here telling me everything that was going on
They're not fooling anyone any longer when you've got this
And detaining Alex Jones in the Border
What does help build perfect peach
He probably started
I Just Brittany people through closed windows
What's the drama here is the narrative going to be
I'm breaking into the Bilderberg and then he find out all the information and then
Good god no
Like what are we doing here it doesn't evolve
There's no further he doesn't get in
Alert
As well as the head of its steering
We look him up on
Google
The kemetic he has B
In the last decade
The reporters
These rich people have
Has been covering the 3rd
Cowboy hat
The 2006 list
Wearables 7:45
70s artists
7/2 more hours to go
Stop possible
Who is who is he
It's been 20 happy years with Metropolitan newspapers
All the wires are cricket nyyear
That could not happen without me knowing about it
Both
Was called
By the late fee Westbrook
This is fine cuz I was young once again has insert citation geography
More funny names
Dammit
I found out about the Bilderberg Group for breeding Westbrook
Some fun stuff about Westbrook
50s and 60s
If I
From what I can see right now just on the
In the fifties R6
See this was an older white man
The name Westbrook
So I assume he was very Progressive on racing
Pegler heated FDR's New Deal and was aggressively Auntie Union
Call pegler compared to Union advocates
Of the closed-shop to Hitler's Goose step
However pegler was showing some
Nostalgia for the Third Reich
His proposal for smashing the AF of L in the CIO was
Was for the state to take them over
Yes I would DS that would be fascism he wrote but I detest fascism
Such fascism
Which is great Advocate fascism
Arguing
End racism
Terrible idea
If the government were to take over
Funny bring a braces
In the Civil Rights Movement
Bigotry
That's weird
He embraced the label races
Quote a common but false for Nazi used by the bigots of New York
Which is something that'd be alright says now
Wait
That's that's an argument that the alt-right is co-opted now he was making that in 1950s
Only racist call you racist
He's a progenitor that ahead of the curve they also had
Because they hiss when they talk gulp down everything before them and fowl everything in their wake
I mean
That's
Hopefully not how
It's not good for a call him
You can just make
Got up so early no juice do hair
What are you trying to be starting a meal he's trying to be an iconoclast
Actually his anti-Semitism has a very easily traced back
Beginning
Vetted
50 semitism was based
Almost entirely on a 1949 libel case brought against Reynolds
Who accused of being immoral and a coward
Right
Use very much guilty of libel
And the court found him guilty
You lost the case along with 170
Largest settlement
Our largest punitive damage ever at that point
For libel
Phuc yea the lawyers the lawyers the case was guy named Louise on either
Stances that quote the Jewish World versus pegler
Reminder pegler was
Very guilty of life
So
Columnist
He Woodbrook the laws
Buy Hurst publishing
Well
He was fired by them in 1962 because he gave a speech that took the piss out of the Hearst Family
Are you started screaming about how they were a bunch of assholes and it was a Kitty toy and soda fountain company in all this
Play fired him for the American opinion
Go to put out by the John Birch
Society
If you say all those words together in a sentence
Beyond happy
Visiting to make you weirdly
Maybe
Just because it's so crazy
He was too crazy for the John Birch Society
Dealing with world-class stop writing
Sunwager
There's one quote that I found by this guy columnist Hayward drone
Who wrote about Westbrook pegler
This quote was really
The video of Jay Westbrook pegler
Consists of the fact that he is not the man he
He's infected Naughty by Nature
His sympathies are
When he's aroused about some
Wrong you can be more eloquent than any newspaper man I know
The point is that okay
It just reminds me of Allah
He's not the man any presents
Himself to be
Whenever he gets aroused by native superstitions and ancient wrong
He ends up being super eloquent having the great talent
That is just
I read that and I thought that's my boy Alexandra
Was an a******
Totally
History
Tracks with that about
I kept their horrendous I couldn't find any complete columns but I found a lot of excerpts of
You transformed over time
After that night
1849 lawsuit you got
Way worse
Before he even voted for the first time around
Inclination
Towards moderate
Rap battle
Weird
The end I
In WWII
Like you wrote columns
Allegorically talked about how like
Well yeah buddy we wasn't advocating against
How everybody was doing it
Like you can't be practicing that form of popular anti
He was the first guy was like dude I've been doing this the right way you guys f******
What is this
Pissy little bulshit
Is Teddy a strip
We're not going to
In the first place
That's a real anti-Semitism right that's good exactly
He was writing about the Bilderberg Group 1950 whatever doesn't really
True
To go on a 27-year crusade
To find out nothing and write fanfiction about them
Make me
Credibly sad
How's that makes me so bummed out how is Jim doing
No I've been well-liked okay at the time of this
He's smokey
Chain-smoking and red bunk half the time
Yeah I'm bored so the guy who just finished a cigarette so that's crack a beer
Roku Vista Collins
About how
L I didn't iFunny
His estate
We're meeting behind
Garth
Doors
Powerful Federal Reserve
Totally ignoring
Not a word
Total Blackout
D'lites
Since then
I've never stopped
Bilderberg
International
Led by Rockefellers near us
Play did you feel like the world for themselves
You haven't
Identify
Who is
Someone from Europe
A Cynthia machine
Without
So far haven't heard from
License plate there
Basic
Watching him get into the car
The Bilderberg Hotel
This little bit like fixtures as you like it
They said if you want call this book as you like it
That's so not true
True at all
It's very clear whatever You Like It Is
You just making up lore
It's so clear that
You're already making of everything else I can go For Broke
Play however you want
It's literally as you like it in the epilogue
Are you want
What is not a random night
Play
So that's how
The Bilderberg
Play back to the hotel
For half a century.
But they decide they have to be
Systemically every year
I will pay me today
Throughout the year
Is great footage
Something that looks like an episode of cops where everybody is just bored
Something I don't know if they cover is the fact that they always
Like the Bilderberg Group always
At a hotel that has a golf course
Golf is the metaphorical symbol for
That's why
Rory McIlroy
The devil
I think we proved that it Bilderberg 4:32 I remember
Tiger Woods
Get back
Central footage the riveting
Are you sure we're going in the right direction footage
I would have
Inside right now they're deciding
Whether or not there will be a citation needed
They are
You got one app
The Bible
Scrubs and learned nothing
His hand
Lighthouse State
People are selling the world agenda
Okay
The reason they want a Christian
They're doing evil evil is done under the cover of Darkness
Sunshine
Trite
Aphorism
Secret things are going private
Everybody good
Sure yet thank you
Again I need you to stay right on the sidewalk
Thank you
Also
Mustaches
Information
All we need
Your crisis
Spell becoming a pattern
A lot of that's a bad sign
There's a big crisis
Crisis doesn't sound like
We need to recognize
Problem reaction
You got that quote from David Rockefeller
That everything that Alex has said is true damn confirm that right now
So this is a quote that got around a bunch of
Conspiracy sites pretty much forever as long as
Part of a larger quote
Conspiracy sites
And it's the present window of opportunity
Order might be built will not be open for long we're on the verge of a global transformation
All we need is the right major crisis and the Nations will accept the New World Order
This is not real
Almost entirely fake quote
There is a video of David Rockefeller giving speech to the Business Council of the UN
This is the actual quote
This present window of opportunity with
During which a truly peaceful interdependent World Order might be built
Will not be open
For too long
Already there are powerful forces that work
At work that threatened to destroy all of our hopes
It's just feel like it's not the same
You know what's one of the funniest thing
Is that the end
Entire video
David Rockefeller speech which
Doesn't include this you can find it on
Infowars
No edited out
Is too good a damn selves
That would that would be like every like sweeping Zelma George
You're keeping mysterious this is a completely fictionalized fabricated quote
Alex Jones his own website
Debunk
His claims
Like I said in the bibliography
Because it does
Hilarious
This is this is a disaster
Like
There's like
Well is the disaster dance already disaster I think this is only going to last for another
Yeah probably
20 minutes
So you might not survive this no idea
One of my friend
Renee
I'm from don't be at the Bilderberg meeting
But I'm against the bilderbergers
Sister fight for my freedom site for my rights
Make sure the picture in a free country
I've been doing this for last
15 years ago because
Last year
It took me 14 and a half hours to get to Munich
I was pulled off the plane in the land was full of a plane and doing it could be interrogated
4 hours
On both lights
I was able to call a friend a journalist then
In Rome as a result of his presence than others
Calling report mystery farming in Italy it they'd back off and let me go
Everyone seems to have that story
Then they're background of like oh my God
None of it can be verified
I have not
Can't do it now
I would never even try
So Daniel estulin
Even
Call the wing Bilderberg 415 here
Tucker
How do you say
Feel about what
Very big
Everything else in my life is going horrible
But at least I have this
What they do is they do the same stuff that Alex data Ridge
Finally Rich was like is like Shield Survival Products
Stuff like that blog
Some stuff like that
Living off.
Just trying to create this book that are super Sensational like
Reportedly covering Bilderberg for 15 years yet so ridiculously never actually come out with any real information
Hard-to-get mostly just official sounding sentences speculation and every now and again
Princes of document
To make it seem legit
Heard about that you wrote a book called the true story of the Bilderberg Group in a review of the book for the Seattle Times
Bruce Ramsay said
Harry Potter
A special group of in-the-know
Mixing fact
With assertion
So the Casual readers won't tell them apart
Is the person you know you want it
Impeach and be is a known Wicked
It's all you're doing is speculating throwing around random
Being a Nazi is bad
But I agree with all the things that Nazis
But I don't feel bad so I'm going to call this guy
Who doesn't do all the things
I know not
I'm going to call him a Nazi
Even though
Really like me
Super cool
White supremacy that soup
But this Rockefeller guy
He is not
He's such a Nazi
Some of the sources quoted in his book The Truth About the Bilderberg Group
Include passages from the far-right anti-semitic American free press and the spectator
And also
Who's on his own website begins
Oh this is
Don't get ready for this
See happen about how Prince Barnard
A member of
This
Nazi
Organization
Basically just a writing
Korean Club
For really rich people to ride out the war
It was one of those things that you shouldn't have done that but after the war he did a lot of Auntie Nazi efforts and he was
He hasn't
How many of the worst part of your association with Nazis is riding horses I guess that
Comfortable with it but the idea but I guess if you're
Just riding horses
You still riding
In terms of like really benign things that happened during the Holocaust like
U-joint
Some organization
To give you stature in that people leave you alone
Right
I think it's not the right
Thing to do but it's not evil
And I think you have a pretty wide berth to people in the middle
World wars
His his plan was essentially like oh s***
The whole country is going
Two garbage
I am not
Anti-Semitic
But if I was post-war efforts has shown him to not
If I'm in that situation and I got the money
And somebody's like okay
You can either be part of the Nazi
And you can start doing the whole
Or I thought you were doing the post you could learn
But it's along those lines
Was I evil
Superintendent
Daniel estulin quotes him as a source
Georgio's
Biography
From his own website
Wrap it in
Commander-in-chief ambition
Flight Commander Intergalactic Federation Fleet ashtar command
Earth representative to the cosmic Council Intergalactic Federation Council on Earth transition
You may call me Hatton
Let there be no misunderstanding of who I am who I am in all capital letters
I come in this portion of the fourth-dimensional project commander in charge of Earth transition
It's goes on a long time
But it's all that
A f****** yes concept album is what that is that
The guy is using as a source about Prince Barnard
Is a theoretical.
Also fun little piece of trivia
Commander space command
I believe you forgot his full title
He is
Commander in Starfleet command Intergalactic flight
Federation fleet commander
He can fly something
Also was silver on his website
These guys are all the guy they're all the same guy that's the show all the same guy
Get away from it and go to like the crazy Project Camelot types of pain level
Shelby Spaniards
Weird a piece medical conferences world
Shity propagandist get together in Leo
Alright well yearly sales of colloidal black are still going strong
Manufacturing base that you guys are you so ugly
Used to because the FDA shutting down
So anyway
That
Is it is not a serious that and the ponytail
Is not
Mysterious purse
Call me 24 hours a day
EPPICard app
Are the 20 room 6 rocket by 3 by the CIA and Peabody
German secret service
Make a note
That's how I'm afraid there'll actually
May be able to review
Publicly about the
Build-A-Bear will have guns
And show up and killed
Because they almost certainly would
Look at these
20 languages
That's a great book that I just told you includes
The commander-in-chief Earth Project transition
Completes an Intergalactic Federation Council on Earth France
Yes
Drake
Let's be
Are you see the present
Of the CFR
What
Morass
You know what I wish
Wish
They could just do one thing
It would be the point out how all of
Evil looking dude
Also
Straight white
Feels like it's
With all of these pictures
It's a bunch of straight white dudes
Who look evil is fun
Also this guy
He misspelled his name is memorial
Alex vice-chairman of Rothschild Europe
Who is speaking with Henry
Getaway
From Alex ahead of shrimp arrives by Africa
You're the owner of the Washington Post Donald Grant escorts in renewing the head PepsiCo
Queen Beatrix of the Netherlands whose father Prince Bernhard
Found it
Is a leading figure in the group
Of course Global is King
Seen here with his bodyguard
Change Ford
Previous meetings
I'll still the deputy secretary of defense
A violation of the Logan Act
Do you know anybody who has violated the Logan Act
Dan Dan do know anybody was violated the Logan Act
Can't think of any but I know that if we
Did know some out to be really critical of non-existent law
Michael Flynn Texas I like the low tonight
Number one thing
Felony offense for any member of the federal
To meet with members
Without the express Authority an authorization
President or congress
But that's not all of it
Citizens not talk
It is illegal for members of the government
To meet secretly behind closed doors
What's the problem
Recovery
For this reason
Many prominent politicians attend
What their names do not appear
On the official list
The governor of New York
George Pataki
Does appear on the list
Governor isn't a federal
State position
Pretty much exactly the definition of
Head of the state government
You're not upset a real official
Crazy about
Their differ
The Federalist
They're different
You think Alex would that have a robust appreciation of that
David Rockefeller
Be careful
David Rockefeller at Brook Street
George Pataki walking across the carpet
Chevrolet
Arrived with police escorts passengers in the underground parking garage
Former World Bank president change
That's the only way to Sheraton Fort Worth
Cameras
I would be so sardonic
I'm sure they are a regular man with a hoodie I'm sure they are really hot
That's why we're here.
Do you think if they were angry there on the front page the local paper today think they're in there reading it right now Jim
Oh yes I don't think
You're happy about it
I don't think
They prefer
Absolute secrecy
Eiffel Tower
A slight variations my name and I don't know if I'll get it or not
Also
It could happen today
The last 3 years
I get back home
Hotels better half
I apologize
Sound effects
Inefficient
Oh my God they really going to attack Iran
They didn't
Fake laugh
I want to say that I did literally zero work
Into trying to come
Confirm whether or not these people are the people that claim to be taking pictures out
Because I felt like it just accepting all of them as
You got a picture
No
Could even then what's the what's the good if you're like oh and by the way that picture that they're showing you right now
That's of Dave in 80
I made the point of the Gabriella precede one because it's a
It's a drastic editing mistake
Harassment
It will never get too hard for us
The forces that we have inside
I thought my sources
Some sources include space command
People who are actually working for them the Secret Service the second layer
People in the Bill of Riverside the
VIR the clerk's the administrative office
There their day
They are our eyes and ears and every time
There's something else we always get into
Let's
It's not
Baptized
What does real
I thought you were saying that's why I
The best name so far
The staff The Kooks the shafts
When we actually get here what song is this
To make sure that we get information
What information of decorum system is unfair this documentary
Make sure that all information
Checks out a lot of the stuff ability
Information make sure that
Spell this dish information nullifies
Leavv accuracy
Reusing the exact same
He's going to go around that
Had to take the 20 seconds to replay that
Almost cry over that
These decisions are made and taken
Buy very elite group
People behind closed doors
This year the books
Suite hotel
We are not privy to
Talking about bad will definitely feel the concert
West Covina
1 events which apparently by accident seemed to happen
If I give your plan right here this year at brookstreet hotel
8 + 11
What does it do when you get 120 together to have meetings with government
Beneficial
That
That's amazing
Planning the cooperative
Planning the Democrat
Cumin
Mussolini
The definition is when the interest
Joshua
Bashas
Variety
Tickle what
Set a timer.
Drive to take
Complete
End of Watch
BMW
The irony of all this kind of talk
Is that when you actually go and read the doc
From like the club of Rome were there
Council on Foreign Relations
Is the idea of the need for it
Inform
And the need for public consent
And to do things
Despicable
He's in his Narrative of them
That's what they have to do the reason he can find it in the
Papers is because they have to let you know the rob you of it
To consent to that
Do you think they're trying to take away
That they have to have it
This is a schizophrenic game that's no fun exact
It's the definition of of poorly read documents and paranoia
The romance
Is that
Alex gets
To feel like he's living in his own
No
Daniel estulin
Is like
Like I'm writing a spy novel or Kerry Cassidy Project Camelot
Like that
Interesting concept
Other performance art concept interesting as anything that actually really damages
It's really really f***** up what else would you describe
For that reason
You remember whenever River Phoenix Joaquin
My man got a bullhorn
The article about having a megaphone
Jerked off to that
That his
Might be a prop
Is
Entirely made up of that article
Another one
Is like a week later
Blind
You're in Canada as our founders of Canada
1776 call upon God
Feel like he does not have a
Solid grasp
Without 1776 happen
So now
This is going to be a very big piece of Alex's cosmology
What he just said right
America
What do you think about Kissinger riding at 80% of the population should be killed in night
Kissinger would
The population of
Chance I think
He was smart enough
Not to write it
Refrigerator to do list
Kill 80% of the population
This is Alex Jones intentionally misrepresenting
Global biodiversity assassin
The 90s and referenced back to something that was written in the seventies Alex's
Bring up his dates entirely
In contrast dustrial world today in among the large middle classes of the developing World consumerism
Is all-pervasive
Andy Devine's what cost
The Good Life
Whitaker in Lykens in a report from 1975's
Estimated that an agricultural world
In which
How many words into that do the Galaxy
Contract
1975 Vandervoort they wrote it estimated that an agricultural
World in which most human beings are peasants
Should be able to support 5 to 7 billion people
Probably more at the large agriculture
Agricultural population
Were supported by an industry promoting
Agricultural activity
In contrast a reasonable estimate for an industrialized world society
At the present North American material standard of living would be 1 billion
European standard of living billion would be possible
These figures represent not just
Contrasting material demands
Of developed
And developing but also their contracted dietary habits
So Alex is misrepresenting
Intentionally
It was Kissinger making a reference to a study from 1975 that discusses
The two researchers
Even though
Really really wrong
If it's not it's not strictly
The point of it is still salient
Disgusting
The carrying capacity for dick
Modes of consumption
More than anything else the reference that was made
When's you to the proper context
Is more than anything a critique of modern
American levels
The consumption
More to the point the quotes that Alex constantly uses to make
Argument RJ
Made up
The idea that
But in no way in the biodiversity assessment does Kissinger or
Anybody else
You should kill 80% of the population
Just because
Capacity for the entire world
If the entire world were consuming at the rate that North Americans do
That would be 1 billion
Throwing everything away that run American
It's it's not
It look as much as I want everybody to die
Population is not the issue that we're facing
No I mean either or it's only an issue
How many koala
Because we have Nations that refused
To share anything
What if we f****** did anything
Anything along those lines
You find out that we have more than enough calories to support
12 billion
We don't f****** do it because some people got to be rich
Beer that is a that
That's one way of approaching the problem other people approach the problem in terms of
You know if there were
Much more
Caloric
Availability and trying to
To hoard
Riches and wealth
You would end up with
The massive booming population
Eventually you would get to the point where it wasn't
So
It's pretty
I think I think it is still reasonable to look at the population
An issue with a preemptive
But be that as it may
Neither did KISS
The point is
That the biodiversity one of those remains
If I can prove the Kissinger didn't
That's not what he was at 4
Yeah
Hey Alex
What you think about
The guy you think wants to kill 80% of the population of a meeting
We need to have like a clue style murder mystery
That's right
You invite your Kissinger
You get Dick Cheney he's invited to
You get Trump
And then at the end everybody's dead
I really don't care what happens in the middle or whether or not they all go to a house
I just want all of those people this is more of a reverse murder on the Orient Express
That's been noted
Make image in the paws of this the only part I really wanted to make is that Alex Jones
Intentionally misquoting
And misrepresenting
This report there was only discussing
Theoretical carrying capacities of different races
Consumption
And
In no way was it
Prescriptive
It was descriptive
In language
Talking about
Studies that existed 20 years prior not saying you should do any
Fair enough with mega haunted house
Yelling all of this hotel
He's got to keep his better up
Dad
The audio do I like
Call gyna megaphone
I wish
Tiger documentary through a megaphone
Water
You getting real specific
I think the reason he's doing this and why he had them
But take a picture of him with a megaphone
For the paper I just realized
Is probably because in Waking Life
He's riding around in the car with a megaphone
I think it's probably so to capitalize Monday
Nikki also screw
You should always be screaming
Quite frankly
The radio Studio takes away a lot in the capabilities of
Megaphone
God he thinks this is his I Have a Dream speech letter
From the Alamo Jesus
These people aren't even interested
Girl girl
But then I would still let slogan for the European you've made it on the show
Gravity Falls the protocol of the meeting list
Gustav affidavit it out there told exactly how they're supposed to
Behave themselves meaning of they can never address the attendees
Bergen ever speak to the Molester spoken to
The first they're going to look him in the eye
And needless to say all the information that is being spoken and doing a conferences
Is under no circumstances allowed to come out that's what they're told
The threatened
I'm not being
Able to find another job anyway the sector
Give the remote
Sector-17 beholder
Ambassador Richard Holbrooke
Stop the peasantry wouldn't recognize
Stroller
Rounds books
Maybe want to take a walk
I don't
Dude
I told him
See if you see a cackle
I don't see it
Talk to your attacker
I would have at least hope for a middle
He didn't even
A man ought to give him one big meal
We got them
He was walking really think they're proven something
Fantastic
And I shot a Galaxy got at the time moving lady jumping in that car
So they're trying to find a way in through the back
Nagashi at the people over here to
Golf Course
CIA
Especially
Region of the US Army
Debruce delegation
These latest usually are protected by the Mossad
That's why they would be Auto police
In this case
Working for the security
They are
They're little after they don't have anything
At all
Don't nobody say don't know why this matters
Doing all this
Dirty Works
Shooting Aldi in photographers
Bothering you
After she went off The Shield
September 5th
Approached
Ramjet speed I didn't know I still had
You Dad
Transport fired
Your father is leaving Bunker Hill Climb
Weather
Bilderberg was founded
I dated Rocky
Propeller
The Rothschild
Bruno Prince Barnard
Are there still
What about Prince Rogers
Many years
Russell
Is still revered
Did you see the Vanity Fair article
Quincy Jones came out
That's why
Shows
Lafortune okay
Course the Rockefellers
Have you all answers
Above
What word closely aligned with you
Bilderberg letter
Innocent timing
Smokin Cafe
Cafeterias
Nelly positively identified
What is the
Beautiful
Fernando Marron
Attended
No I think it is very difficult
Understanding
Small group of
125 minutes
Nephew women
Control a population base of
Billion people actually
Easier
How do I control all the hairs on my head
Slices Apple
Lots of very small
Slice of that apple pie each one of these pieces umno Moon
Trust
And by controlling this
Individual
Control entire organization
For example if you take laundry
Organizational control
What is this washer manual controls
Original Sin
Let all the numbers Coronavirus
Turn-based Western
Hemisphere
You need to call the American Union
Nasus to be
Bandit
Into every country in
This hemisphere
Musically Optics bad
The American Union
And only an educated inform the public
Stop them
Or
We wanted to downtown Auto
And talk to locals
This is great
This is good, Dee this is good comedy
Come on
Alex has no jobs
I just need to tell you that
I just met
Canada under control your sovereignty
Merging you with the US and Mexico
Tell you about this
This is deadly serious I'm just letting you know I'm telling you about it
As they say they're the guys that run the world
They make decisions
Wait and we just carried out
Leave them alone
Close to half of the people we randomly spoke to
My arm in between the doors and they wouldn't let me
Really overcast day
Batman
We don't want to happen
Because the Bilderberg Group runs the world
Do Canadians or Warriors
But most of this
Is public knowledge
Polite
Wikipedia
World leaders are re-elected
Circle
Address for a group in 2003
Because my
Center politics without becoming
A part of the Bilderberg Group
And then you find out that
Is the case that
Bill Clinton went there.
Blair
Who we think that we're electing
L
Our have already been
Whether it's liberal or a conservative
They're already part of the group
Salem horses
Diaries
It's two different
Party
How late is doing
Like Bill Clinton
The bushes
I imagine part of that is polite
Imagine another part of it is they have
Unique
Life experience
No one else can share
And that they were presidents of the United States
And the public
But can you imagine what kind of pressure that puts on a person
Like f****** George W bush had to go into weird
Therapy
Yeah that's what happened
Furious that we allowed him to keep his hands
But The Vig
I put the idea in some way is not
Suspicious to me at all
It should all stay
Dragon
Subterfuge Machiavellian backstabbing
And somehow The Lacs westerners
That the government's fine to do wrong
It's easy to me cheap
Makes it easier for everyone
What's your view on losing canvas Opera
You stay as it is
And I lost
United States to be there
Back in Austria capital of Texas
I like it but I also like that
Cuz it doesn't exist
Interesting
Was not aware that
I don't I don't know exactly what you mean so
I don't
Think there's going to be a merger
Supreme Nation
Oh you have heard about it
Everywhere
No
Alright well you're not
Potter's field
The Galaxy burn
Program
You don't need guys to North America
Super state is on the extreme FasTrak
Super State International agreements
We're just stepping stones in the formation of
Baylor University
Texas
On March 23rd 2005
Depressed
Maybe they will Schumer
Security and prosperity
September
From September 12th to September 14th
Appointed government leaders
Mexico state's
Medici
The front pages of newspapers
10 minutes of the secret assembly
Refused
Shining National Security
Thousands of pages of documents
Stein Mart
Already operating agreement
Manufacturing
All of it
From the people
Or their elected representatives
Important
The controllers also talked about exploding the public
World government get back to that in a little bit
Tis wouldn't also
Flag of our taxes but okay so stupid
Stupid North America has our taxes
Right
Susan are doing all right
Mexico has their taxes
Isn't there still doing alright
Why would you need a hole
Could we just do all the same taxonomic then just called like to a government
You need to
Fake government that you like the are all we all think this is our government
Okay then the other government
Property taxes pay for police
Pays for interdimensional
Dark program guide secret space program
We'll get back to the carbon tax stuff in a little bit cuz
Hugo's
Yes pretty hard on it
If they are meeting
Already
To talk about trade agreements and International
I mean like Rules of Engagement
Visit the lines
Why do they need to also have a
It's not all the same meeting
Yeah
I don't know that what he's saying is
I don't know how you proved the negation of a secret meeting
Like I can't prove a secret meeting didn't happen
Could I have a secret meeting
That's true
It's not
I don't I don't Endeavor to disp
Prove negative
It's impossible from a logical standpoint
Disprove
Negative
Will just be
Confirmative
What about negative
My my
Stration with a lot of these conspiracy theories always wind up being
People going so far out of their way
To do conspiracy looking s***
When you could just do it like regular
Do you mean those three countries
We're meeting whatever it would be
Totally within the regular meeting rules
To have that meeting
That maybe their work
Maybe a lot of these documents
It's were like
Public dock
You could still follow them but they weren't they weren't public documents
I see no real evidence
So we just proved they have 32
Robert pastor
Hi Robert Pastor cuz he's written by Jerome corsi
But he testified before Congress she pushed the idea of a continental security
North American Union
His ideas were
The best way to secure
The United States today is not at our two borders with Mexico and Canada but at the borders of North America
As a whole
In fact
Has openly discussed using Waze
US Army
Mexico
Eastern Europe
League City Police Department
Nationwide
This is
Incredibly disgraceful
Wolverines
Second
What's
Huh
Wait what
No
Danelle visit like
I'm not a person who super into the
The function of the military
But
Alex is rhetoric
Incredibly
Borders on nativist
Xenophobic
2 degree
The right now what we have in our service
This is 8% of the Navy's foreign-born 5% of all branch
Pictures of active-duty
Approximately
Immigrants serve in the armed forces and 37,000 250 you become naturalized citizen
Since 2001
Armed services include born in other countries and non-citizens
Often working towards
The rhetoric of Alex's putting forth here it is incredibly stressful
Have you heard of the police situation
Just read this
This time it's quote here
Ali noorani executive director of the national immigration
Operates to work in the United States
Has already undergone a thorough background check
And will undergo even more screening in police application
The security risk is a straw man he said
This is about people who've gone through criminal background checks were meeting the very high standards that we set as a country to
You want to serve and protect their community
All this boils down to
From Alex's mouth
Availed
Xenophobia white supremacy
EBay blatant disrespect for people who are serving in our armed services
Would I rather have somebody who is fought
And Claude
Struggled
To get to where they are
Joining
The police
Derek
The assholes that I knew from fourth
Derek sucks
Which one would I rather have in the police force
Eric was a dick
Maybe we better off if any undocumented immigrants that are
I would prefer undocumented immigrants
2BR police force
Cuz then I know
They're just as afraid as me
Justice
Interesting line I'm not agree with you
Domestic
But they're cool by stealth
Damage control mode
Security and prosperity partnership quickly
It is the only way that we can security and prosperity
4 people is through this Corporation
Omarosa physical
North America plants as foreign minister
To talk about
Protesters who were upset about losing their country
Arcada
Ever
Globalist publication
With their frustration
The population has not bought
She was here
Srbin non-disruptive
Dustbuster
She's kind of April 30th
The security and prosperity partnership
Secretive approach
Set alarm the pub
Show list
President Bush
German Chancellor Merkel
Commission president barroso
Chancellor
Yoshi very much for
Transatlantic
Economic integration plan
Important
Remind
I wish I could present on my way
Tubi app
Make it
The BBC reported that the
Us and EU
Alex is trying to present that is some sort of super nefarious thing
Trade Agreement
We watched American Union
You you
Are being created so they can be
Emerge
He's really f******
I'm stupid because it doesn't
Track at all
Literally every country that's in the EU
North America
Okay second we're going to discount
Secondly every single country that's in the EU
And would be in the North American you
Are already members of
So the idea that you have
You need to create even Luxembourg
Yep doody ideas
The idea that you need to create these two things you can merge them together
Cuz he's going to bring it
Yes
The idea that you need to create these things to bring them together when all of the countries are already together in a
Unified
Global body
It's goddamn like
No it's it just doesn't
Track and adding layers upon layers that don't need
To be there this idea of the single Market
Getting all that you actually read that article what it's talking about is the fact that
The United States in the United Kingdom have a bunch of regulations
Trade rules and laws
And you do need when you're going to have trade agreements
You need to discuss those things
Right and see what they decided to do was create
Bodywear in Lake
Could negotiate
The trade regulation
Both side have to come to
A harmonious
Balance
We're discussing the plot of
Star Wars episode 1
From the article
The Pact is designed to boost trade and investment by harmonizing regulatory staff
The two sides agreed to set up an economic Council to push ahead with regulatory convergence in nearly 40
Including intellectual property Financial Services business
And the motor in Des
Because those are
Yeah now the reality is over now it's probably it wouldn't be that in his Bonnet is that he doesn't forget anything
Things to be regular
I'm so he's actually trying to complain about that but he knows that that's not a realistic
Like he wants to say doesn't believe anything
Think should be regulated but whenever something is unreal run regulator
He's like somebody should regulate that
Does everybody was against regulations are f****** stupid
They were simply repeating what did they do
And the EU
Record states that the two blocks will aggressively push regulatory conversion
35 torque conversion education
All the planets
Regulate
We recognize that we have a problem
Greenhouse gas
The equator is a globe
We agree there is
You need to stop
Aw understood that
Pricing all
NFL
How can we translate this into a market economic
We have agreed to
Established
Hear USA
Can decide which one of them is wearing heavy
South Africa Brazil contoured montanita
Please
American Falls
Who's there
Bill's burgers on percentage of people work on together and for the position
Pictures of ultimate announcer the power destroying every cost
No matter how powerful the constant
So why are you against
Alex misspelled
Undermine
He said undermined
UK
Believe it up
He wrote undermined
That's beautiful little patio dirty but
That's so beautiful
Snooze.
People do
Undermine
African Union
African economic Granite early 1980s
Government shutdown
The African Union Army sir
Pro Controller
But that's really not
Nebulous concept of sovereign
Like what does that mean
Okay
They're going to dissolve sovereign
Now we're doing this breakdown of sovereignty now
Sovereignty
Yeah
What you don't you don't have any for your Stardust self-determination
Dissolving everybody sovereignty
What exactly is that okay
What Russia's sovereignty
Who gives a s*** Russian the Russian people don't have
No really have you and I right now why would I give a s*** if
If you dissolve
South America's f****** the entirety of South America is now just South America
And there's no sovereignty or whatever like what it what do I care
All of our problems the problem that I'm experiencing
It's in the government causes every single problem that we will ever have
By just being a government we need to defend against
Taking that government away from us
Subway
F*** the federal government but also don't
Darren crouch on their ability to
Exactly the argument really only works if you don't pay attention to that
Works if you believe that there is
Nefarious group behind the scenes
To get rid of the sovereignty so they can
Pull some sort of a scam and take over the world
And that's just
The reality is that the evidence
Is not there for that
You don't have borders
Stop
Being
Well it's the United States
Against
And it starts being
Is everybody who's not a globalist
Everybody who is this
And that's why
Rules
The globalist keep you focused
Against the global words like that
I don't know it's nonsense
So stupid
Make it make sense for the only way I can make it make sense to tell you that it's about something else
Four and a half of this and I've already lost my mind about something else it's not about
It's about
I just can't look at Tony Blair that wanted
I hate others
Set alarm
So if you were
So the only way to make sense of opportunity
It makes sense of all of these
Often contradictory and nonsensical idea
Is it
You cut through all of the
And you say
The people that you're against
Read
Non-white
You keep the people I see product
The people that you are for
Read white people
Within a certain
Space
Everybody else can go f*** themselves
Do you because you want a
White Nation
Of people
You know
Now back to this really quick about the Africa
Communion
Support globalist exploitation
Escape my brain immediately cuz that doesn't make any
Any f****** sense
Well the second plank of the charter of the African Union is quote
To defend the sovereignty and territorial integrity and Independence of its member states
Looking like a
Big priority
Also the African Union is it
It's not a perfect body
Certainly a lot of it has to do with the history of exploitation
Is perpetrated against African countries
Ignoring of atrocity
Should have happened
In Africa
Ignoring them or of course
Exacerbated
But the idea like the troops of the African Union or a tool for globalist
Exploitation
I think I
Africa
That was
Even
Hindered
Bye
Outside by America
We're only on the wrong
We're batting a thousand
I've got it
I have a couple of examples where the African Union
Did
Great though
Adama
The president
The Pogo died
Empower
Protests by the African Union that were saying this was a military coup
I've been under Togo's Constitution the speaker Parliament initiates new election
Election
Happy Hollow
The song ended up winning
But
It was able to
Cool back to Hunters
Into holding elections
Open 2017
By suspending the country's membership
In the African Union
They were able to use the international cooperation
And The Leverage that implied by that
To force military coup Hunters
Into accepting the Democratic process
Crazy
The afternoon was able able to force an election in Mali in
In 2013 after a 2012 military coup
There their work
There's there are
Plenty of examples of times when they aren't being used
Is globalist
Display Tatian tools
But actually to reinforce
Democratic principles
Africa
Reitz Union
Nearby
Globalist
Like it comes from a
The people are like
We got to stop these endless Wars guys maybe
Chilled
Comes cooperation
Because at that point you realize it's already too late
Also our children
Consisting of Asian and Pacific Nations
Having
A-Tech will become the agent
Pacific Union
And the world is to be divided
The three great regions
Administrative convenience
That's straight out of 1980 World Cup
Yeah he's given his specific
Like
Three nations that's literally straight out of night
But you understand and predict Aldous Huxley
You're just allowed to get that out there
But nonsense
Street Bob
Snopes.com
Monetary
They're trying to destroy Every Nation on Earth
Was trying to promote progress because
These people basically of their landowner
They don't need progress because they can
Control the land
If you take the most powerful man in London
The people who belong to lie
Tattoo the council
And the committee of 300
Belong to the bilderbergers
Near the bridge Royal to the Guelph leaving another black nobility of Venice
The black v
The New World Order is
The old world is just the names
Still
To bring them in.
Kicking and Screaming back to the Middle Ages
Fulton Industrial
Chick-fil-A
World Order
What are things that are in the post-apocalyptic
United Nations
Came out in 9
Clearly shows in order
We have to go back to feudal
Ashley
Said that in the
They didn't do crap
We talked about that already
Everybody knows
If you want a
Perfect societal blueprint for technological
Also utilize all of your resources properly
If you want somebody to invent something you make sure that 95% of
People are working under horrifically Edition
On a f****** Farm World War 1
You definitely don't want any sort of
Mobility going off
Cuz then people will be able to f****** discover things or change their position and they will be able to contribute in a way that otherwise they wouldn't be able to catch
Baba baba
The best form of world government
Serfdom
Me or the people that they pretend to be again
Because they're not real
Just imagined enemies
Modern feudal society
The globe
Standardized North America
I just want to be
It's like I want to show them what it would be like
Like I wanted more money plant
The New World Order
For good rapper
The physical
Of the North American
Desert highway
Martha Peter
Susie the trans-texas corridor
These Texans
Have a real bee in their Bonnet about it I realize I said that twice
Yeah and it also didn't
Belt
But it's supposed to
Internal retired army
My friend
Who died in World War 2
Turnover net gray
What are you doing
Would even consider confiscating land of farmers and Ranchers
And taking their homes away from
Yeah be terrible if foreign company
In Spain
Reflected
And they get the tolls on Texas land
52 years
Liverpool transfer
Text Allison
At least have been signed that would make Texas Highway 121 a toll road a private Spanish company
The Beto building Calexico
Capitalism bro
Airport
Critics say it's a threat to our national
Security
It's part of a plan for a North American integration being carried out by government and corporate Elites
Congressional or voter approval
They just found literally every clip of somebody saying Elite they could and then just try to handfasted in Chandler
All the coverage of this
Highway
History repeats itself
What is that
2000 years ago
That's an expression
Rome constructed and maintained more than 10,000 miles
Roman military power
Control concert tonight
Home also demanded tribute Roman subjects from Albion
Do Judy
We're forced to pay a tax to use the
Dominate
Father's Day Super Highway Sorrel
Powerful tool
Arson
I want to be clear
Alex
Pissed off about this highway
And I don't understand
Specifically yes and I have some complaints about the general highway system that will get into a little later
Specific one all of his
Plants fall flat
This trans-texas Corridor makes
No sense why he
He's mad about it
It's just that it's boring company
That's the only thing I can really imagine
Instead is
We should
Federalizing allow the federal government
Women the reality is clearly they had in that report there was open bidding and the Spanish company paid more than
You're willing to pay
American National
Company gets involved
But I'm not super thrilled because it's taking away my national sovereignty which is an abstract concept
The government
To get involved within a personal or something
Companies with more prosperity
In terms of the complaints about like this Mega Highway getting into people's
Go to stop I am very sympathetic
I do I do feel sympathy
Now granted your response is also
We're going to build this and it's going to go through your land and I put stuff
I think that's an issue that needs to be
I don't I don't think I'm not super comfortable with it but
Biggest question
Can the people anytime that is
Builta cuz you
And then I'll tell you
To go fuc yourself
Either there is a
Maybe it's
Cuz I'm like two beers deep but there's a certain part of it
This really attract
Do to me today
You should not be able to
To own land
Water are
You shouldn't be able to own any of the
The elements
Probably
Avatar Last Airbender
Bipartisan
If this super highway goes through all of these countries than their Birds
It's been some sort of
Interstate highways around National Highway
Ridiculous
Arguments for dick
Foreign governments and corporations infrastructure across North America
Nowhere
Copy your notes need to figure out what the point of this is
Greater than in Texas
Texas is the Frontline
Are being handed over
The government company
Foreign companies by the legislator
Turn over complete control
Government power
Illegally transferred
Unelected quasi-governmental regional board
The circumvent local governments and the will of the people
This point like a lot of I'm not coming in with a lot of like rebuttals
The stuff beginning
Magic
Roy just water off my back like a duck
Cuz in the bibliography so much of the stuff is just like
News reports about a road
Belt or articles on Infowars
I see a large group of a
Angry old white people
60% gray hair
If there is
Nothing
I know they're mad about this
Old white people look
Angry I feel like
Whatever it is they're mad about we need to do
It's interesting notes so far we have 95%
Through this documentary so far has been
Bizarre apps
Abstract shots of world war the opening
Alex Goes to Canada now
I'm at about a road so that's where we're at
We're in an hour and 8 minutes
We started with all here's how rich people have been f****** you over
Here's where rich people suck you up
Now there's a row
Is the road
Somebody got it
F****** stop this goddamn Road Texas
That it's that backstop
In case the globalists get too powerful
Right I know
Fitzwilliam
You'll have to cut it off for today
Tune in tomorrow
What about this stupid road
In Texas and how pissed off Alex Jones and Alta
Patriots are about it
Listening really appreciate
If you want to find out more about Austin go to knowledge fight.com
Also I know it's right. Cam is the bibliography for our coverage
Of Alex Jones is dumb dumb.
You can find citations for the things that we're talking about
Some short explainers about 7
He's throwing around willy-nilly and lying to everybody about
Also if you'd like to check that out tonight what it's their own knowledge buy.com
You can also follow us
Twitter at knowledge underscore fight
You can catch us on Facebook
We are there you can check us out
The review also going to leave a review on iTunes
Were there
You can I subscribe to show
Flower sticker
Continue to keep
Keep doing the things that we're doing
, click that button to show
Really appreciate it
And it helps a lot
But
We will
I know that we're leaving on a hot clips
Finger this road
I mean I know everyone's
Going to happen with this rude
I'm sorry to make you wait till tomorrow but
Such is life
Anyway