Hey welcome back to know tonight I am the other boys
In just a moment is Michael
Austin dear friend
You are joined us today for the third installment
Coverage of Alex Jones documentary
Garbage monster
Hazel looks like Junior High
History project
If Alex turn to say that I was a teacher
I would say
Incomplete
Needs work I probably give her the D
Reflecting effort
Effort
But in terms of proving any of the
Tell from the last
4 hours of coverage
So far leading up to par 3
He has failed to accurately cite a number of things of trend
Continue
Episode where we left off
Last time in that was Alex Jones is
Really pissed off
About a road
He is really mad about
The transtex
Quarter
So you know he he lies a little bit about it begin this
Is it a certain point cell
Enjoy
Alex
Now there's a row
Is the road somebody's got a f******
Stop this goddamn Road and it's going to be up to Texas
Is that the it's that backstop
In case the globalist get too powerful
I know it's William Travis
Got to get it
The next stage of this world government plan Transportation Control
And that is called the NAFTA superhighway or in Texas colortran Texas
The compass case
584 sounds
To be transferred into the control of a Spanish company
Which tunnels in Texas
Million-dollar is to ride on a road
There's no limit
Play the free market will ever create a limit on it
Cuz the free market doesn't exist
It's not like what he said
Describing isn't the direct product
Drive from Chicago to New York
And who knows where that money goes you hope it's to the state you're driving in
Could be Spain
More than eight
I've been designated as International art
Missouri
Start Steven side Mexico
And travels through the middle of the United States
Central Canada
Kansas City
Mexico
If I understand correctly
Kansas City
Is Mexico
It's Sovereign soil of Mexico
Question
If you are a
Who does not have full United States
Can you go to that Polly olly oxen free
You're a citizen of the port
This isn't true
This was evidenced by some emails by there was a guy named Chris Gutierrez
Where is the president of
Kansas City smartport
Mexican
Customs Office Space
We need to be designated as for in Mexico
Can Sovereign territory
Meet certain requirements
Under this plan what happened with this
Court in Kansas City
Actually really interesting
I disagree with a lot of
I'll be honest
But it's actually really interesting
And have you have this
That leads from Mexico a port in Mexico
The first stop that would make
Kansas City
Point there would be Mexican
American
Custer
So they could check
And the reason they would do this would be to streamline
Imports and X
In terms of shipping things
Out of Kansas City and into cancer
The reason is Kansas City
The city is the largest
Just Trucking Hub in the United States
Fruits that transverse the United States open
Buca's f****** dead center
Right so I'm I'm interested in
In terms of
All the Rail lines
Trucking lines meeting up here is some centralized place
Were you wouldn't have to take the time for American customs
The fish has to be in Mexico to check stuff
Any of that
But at the same time
That doesn't sound like a terrible idea I don't know probably can problems with the customs office would necessarily
Clearly need to be Sovereign soil of the country
Costumes that represents
It's no different than an embassy or something along the lines of emphysema
Backing behind them saying
You can't do that is
If you say that
Will start a war
Really interesting but
When you really look at the idea of why people were pitching this sort of thing
There is a lot of snow
Songs from it but you look at it they're like well if you just have the ports
Some place in America
Ship directly through a direct line to Kansas City in
Traverse from there
Would really be that much further than having
A Mexico
It's obviously they're trying to get around
Having to pay longshoreman
Like in California or somebody
All this does come down to really is
Some sort of
Simplicity and streamlining for these companies at the expense of America
Court jobs
There's a downside to this
When you streamline business you end up hurting workers
And this is not an accept
Yep you just end up
Screwing over people to work
The doc
Sometime it's
It's interesting on a level that is not at all without
Port isn't
Took in Sovereign territory it's just
I mean if you want to
Did you want to complain about that about every Embassy
Imaginary
Mexican soil it said
Bye
By being there America's like
That's Mexico so we're not going to say no to
Mexico is like
0% imaginary
You're cool work
Your benefit as America or these company
Is that you
Pay next to nothing for the longshoremen Mexican ports in order to offload stuff
Ships into trains
The end up going up to Kansas City as opposed to paying a living wage to people in
Los Angeles
California Los Angeles but whatever
You know what I'm saying
So you're cutting back your expenses on that and then return you have
It's all bulshit
All the reasons it's interesting to talk about have nothing to do with why Alex
Like that's all it is everything we talked about
Is all the downsides are going to
Heart
International
Predominant
Foreign companies are placing tolls
Documents show Robinson raised
The transportation infrastructure of Mexico
So far and made Prada
Mexico
Revenues rage
North American Union
Cracy
Citation
North American quarters are also
Suspiciously similar to timezone
Time zones in name
Time zones
Northern
Ridiculous
First of all the proposing in North America
Which would be so much what we have in chapter 11 of a nap
Which is Trump
By international law what is
She's the chairman for Nationals National eagle
That was founded by Phyllis Schlafly
Well then
Whatever she can go f****** but it's legal form was largely started as a
Organize
So so people who are
Whatever it showed up as a national Eagle Forum
That was like
She's an environmentalist
All the land is going to tear apart Schlafly
We're actually just blacks forum
Invalid
And what we would have is in North American Business Law but we have here in the United
Did the NAFTA headquarters
Is in Mexico and the United States trade
Andrew's against United States
And no one seemed to challenge it
North America
In court
Why what are you talking about
Supposed we want to keep her we want to keep our life is keeping
Bear arms
Will be security for being Court
Spanish
The Texas Department of Transportation
To erect toll roads on existing Road
Enter toll New Road
That were completely
$5
In Texas who don't know what the transmission
Those are girl for a turnover grew to like for tomorrow
Dominos.com
I don't even know what the foreign company
When the first came out
Newspapers across the state
Call for heads to roll political
Respond
Australian subsidiary
Make its first u.s. newspaper
So here is an interesting thing
Alex is making this case with a Spanish company
Macaray Australian company
Not true at all
Spanish
Spain on this Australian
What's Australia
Not true at all
The Australian Media Company mcaree media about 40 local papers around
Texas and Oklahoma
By purchasing
So was stated as they were trying to put together a portfolio of media
Operation
Sure
Alex and do that they did this
To silent
Critics of the trans-texas corridor
Also
Decide
Whenever people do that
Do you know who has done that
Provably have been said to have done that
Sinclair media
Stop it with a random
That weird cuz really
Bismack Ariba
Do companies
Yeah those two companies
Combined own
40 papers
Put on 40 which is an infuriating
It was also own forty,
This is very angry
Companies owned by Fairfax media Limited in Australia
New zealand-based Media.
Because
Cuz they're in Australia
A New Zealand
This road
Care about the road now
Frustrated
Westminster like one billionaire New Zealand is like
Got to kill this road
Looking Backward
Every newspaper they bought
Was a long branch has the trans-texas corridor
I've been critical of the toll roads
This is Justice or nothing
Compared to the profits little be made
State-by-state
Global panorama
A transnational company
Is aggressively cavato Public Finance
I don't want to be on that side with Bonnie and Corrado
Government simply actress facts
Stocking up for wealth and resources
And transferring
To Offshore Banking
Leaving behind a cultural and economic Wasteland
Easily managed
The North American
It's not about trade it's about control
Catherines even worse
Control Seafood
It's not about trade this subsidized trade with taxpayers funds
The New World Order
Right here in sex
The threat they got angry
R Ranch
Is part of the
I would literally still in from other people and I want
Want to make sure that it's not stolen from me
I don't want to give it back
Today held a major protest
Knock knock.
Texas County
A voltage or resistance
North American Union
The valve block
Structure
Abbott's infrastructure
Cool
United States Congress
I'm not going to carry in the driver's license
And I don't mean to General
If anybody
At a rally
Has
Cowboy hat on
I assume they are the bad
They get it
Cannot believe
You would ever trust anybody
With a cowboy hat
Trying to say something like they were wearing
I would completely different issues analysis
Also why are you
What is this
I refuse I refuse
You have
Bucking
It has a chip in it but
Another barcode on
What you already have one that I can swipe and has a barcode
Okay well just Market
But having a picture on your ID
It's just another identify
But they're principally against that to play how do you feel about that
Burn them off
WhatsApp
And that's why acid rain is good for you
Video of Cop
I don't want to be near this video
It was awful well-dressed for somebody who is afraid of computers
Action stick
Already
Population
No
Google
We started on the international
52 bakers that were running the world
Nathan Rothschild
Huge detour into there's this road I don't like
Was trying to use it as a
An example of like this is a Grassroots on the
The ground means
Control but it's not the arguments not being there makes sense
I still don't understand
The anger though
Behind inter
As long as that
Documentary was about this
Was never released
Easton
This is the blueprint for Global enslavement
Rhodes Rhodes Rhodes
We already have those right
Smart rope which is nothing more than an effort
Sebring control into
The cities
You have the rewilding of America in the in the wildlands project
The convention on biological
Diversity which is
Troll
R-real population
Toll roads
Nationwide
Walling off exit
The small town
Music
By Design
This trend is accelerating under the highway system
The country
All of these things are designed to bring more and more
Control to bureaucracies rather than to the independent individual
The sovereign individual this nation
What brought me into the whole story
In the 1980s
An early 1990s
Team aware of an agenda basically tulloch are at United States
What's called the wildlands project was also a key Cornerstone of the u.s. United maze
Convention on biological
It Will Rain that studying which I begin to realize
That
This was not an effort to
Protect the environment but an effort to
To control you and I
They were dividing United States up in the movement hours
So this map that Alex is flashing up here right now Verizon
It's it's actually really important cuz he talked about the wildlands
Project
Privately-owned of wildlands
Network
Federally owned
Yeah
Wildlife
Wildling
It's important here is all the claims that are being made by Michael Kaufman and Alex
Miss suction
There is like four straight
Finger insert here
And the maps in the B the bibliography
The key release
You really
Many if not all of the most
Explosive claims
Literally said to be unsubstantiated
And inserts and all of the quotes are basically
Like citations cuz they're not real
Also these Maps Alex conveniently forgets dementia
They were created by Michael cost
Gmade
Three baby babies maps maps
Interpretation of the UN biodiversity effects
The designations of land are not in the UN
Fear-mongering the map isn't even detecting a real plan according to Kaufman
Could have been
If he had not been there to fight do you win
These Maps show how 50% of America might have been used
Have been set aside in Wilderness reserve and buffer zone
If the biodiversity
The tree have been ratified
He made the map and he's in
Interpreting it
Interpreting it in a manner that only inflates
His own
So this is all just
Violated map
He was doing a
He caught it out multibillion-dollar project
Maybe he caught it out
In the language they've written something in
They could use this to do that
While he was working
I won't let them do
And then they did
He saved us
All the time
Wants to warn you that they still want
So I believe they would have done it if it weren't for you so they're still Michael Kaufman
Michael Kaufman wildlands project
Networking all that stuff and
Anything the really backs up at all the claims
What about the World Wildlife Foundation
But
The issue is that I can't find any non crazy Source talking about this stuff
Black weirdo blogs and stuff like that
Even the regular mainstream Outlets are like
We're going to pot
Do you guys have your fun
Michael Kaufman and whatever I don't care to
I don't think this is real
I don't trust the word of crazy
Stupid blog
What do they rip out whole community
Please put them in the back in the wilderness
The Federal Highway system was designed
The 1950s
The service deployment conduit
Otherwise good Highway
Smith also is
True
The highway system wasn't created
Specifically to deploy troops or anything like that
No it was because of the burgeoning
Suburb Bloom that was happening after the baby boom in the 50s
Destroying
Savory Park
Cumtown able to do Bible
Hey 1955 the Department of Commerce put out a document often referred to as
Autobook
If you look at the documents he's very clearly than plants her Highway
The plans of the highways are set
Create roads that we
Connect cities to
Suburbs
Joseph dimento
Another phone
Professor who co-wrote the book change
Gyros
He wrote the book changing lanes visions
Histories of urban
Open freeways
And I quote Highway Engineers dominated the decision
They were trained
Design without what
Consideration for how Highway might impact
Fabric
They were worried about the most
Efficient way of moving people from
Point eight
The yellow book formed the basis for
The federal-aid Highway Act
Create the interstate
At the time the bill required a lot of federal funding
Sound of a turtle sound
I had one of the only reasons
Eisenhower supported it for
But also for evacuation
Natural disaster
Or like a nuclear attack
This was the consideration but not the reason
Every president
Has been super
Rhodes
Going back to George Washington
George Washington
The credit the savings and convenience of this country all require that are great Road leading from one public place to another ship
Be straightened established by law
To me these things seem indispensable
They seem obvious
Also in 1990
Send Lieutenant Colonel Ivan
Country tours
The first world war could make it across the country
It was a study but also a military recruitment opportunity where they went out of town or like to join up
The roads sucked they destroyed cars
And that most bridges couldn't support the weight of most cars
That's not good for 1999
Stuck in his head is a very serious priority
So when Eisenhower was elected president
1850s
He ended up
Being like we we got to we got to finally get around to doing this right
Dima priority 30 years ago
Go back to Doctor Demento
An unmistakable part of the equation of highways
As a related
The highway was a federally-supported program of urban renewal
In which lower-income urban can
Mostly African-American were targeted for removal
The idea was close let's get rid of the blight
Says Demento
Nope
Recording a doctor tonight
That makes everything else sound very super villain
Places that is interesting multi-ethnic areas where view Justice
Play highways were 20 justifying with
Destruction of men
Predominantly black were wiped out and turned I threw surface parking and Highway
Noting a black bottom and Paradise Valley in
Detroit Historical neighborhoods down to make room for i-375
The same pattern was repeated over and over
Leaving two cities pockmarked with empty neighborhoods and destructive Highway
People displaced from destroyed areas move to others lead to overcrowded
Overcrowding in
Can increases in crime While most people with the means to play flight to the suburbs
Shooting on the new highways and siphoning money away from these cities very tax base
So this was at the same time that they would also have
Instituted the policy known as
Redline
Which
Kept
The people who were
Displaced from
Living anywhere where they would be okay
No iru
Focused attack let me know
Let me go somewhere no one else has
Okay
Are you saying that not only
This country inn
Infrastructure itself is racist
A lot of the motivation for the creation of a lot of his stuff was
Totally wrong in the idea with troop deployments Royal taxes Aurora
Thank God for racism
Pieces of s***
I've been there
The unconstitutional Northern command is now using the highway system as a force projection maker
The horse
Just innocent
County and city government
Are being quiet
Quietly quietly
Billions of dollars for Sydney
No matter how small or remote
License plate reading software
Read your lips
God dammit
Under the treasonous military commissions
American citizens
Orchard
Secretly
You're not good under Section 8 in the middle of you being wrong
About everything about a couple things along the way
Yes this is an issue
Why can't we work together on this why does it have to be
Movies centered around a lot because he's hoping because he's only
Right about these things
In service of the things that are bigger than wrong about
Evidenced by this
Misdemeanor
I agree Alex know he's lying
You know about
Not about
Call misdemeanor actor
Does cement some of the definitions
Terrorism
Has nothing to do with misdemeanors or anything like that
Destruction
The definition
Crimes that
Domestic terrorism section said
Assassination orchid
Kidnapping or Mass
Destruction
What
Notorious
Not want
Domestic terrorism
Mass
I don't know probably
I don't know
Something happened
In Oklahoma City
Could be
Federal police squad
Force America
The lineup and show their butts
In case you're wondering
Typo
But also
Alex is incredibly in support of what's being done by Ice
Right now if you want
Very temporary right very dude like you
It
Completely
It's b******* but also the article that he cited makes no mention
People being demanding that they show their papers
He cites like three articles none of them were irrelevant to that the only article
Kind of relevant
Is one about her New York
Subway
Train riders
Are being
Did I have a bags
The reason for that
It was the same week as we lunch
Wanted frames at bomb in 2005
Ifucking get it that week
Alright
Forever
It's not like it's today
People having
Wow
Outside the scope of this documentary
Everything that Alex is describing as
What could be done
By the global
It is stuff that he is describing
Are doing to everybody else right now the reason that he's
Like what this documentary scope
What does documentary imagine
You a regular wipers
Is treated like the way white people treat other
Happy terrible nightmare for Global enslavement
We would be treated the way we treat other people actually for Global enslavement at 12 weeks.
Interesting interesting
I think he's just read a history
Man
From the sidewalks
Paramilitary
I want to be clear about this really quick I have no idea what
This video is of Alex's
No context of it
Yeah probably
You have no idea what happened
Paper for Less on this newspaper
I hate being on the military's to you but if you're talking s*** to Alex Jones goes a long way
Oh man
This'll be so much a better movie if that guy just murdered Alex right there
Reality could be that these people in
Just went to go see a movie
Something like that
Completely benign reason that there on the streets
Vietnam
This footage
Any any like
This is where at this place there's a thing that there's a demonstration there's
People on the street
Anymore
Authoritarian state
If I if I'm reading this situation correct
Based on what has been said so far
This dude
Part of a
Some sort of military
So it's he's on the
And then Alex f****** Jones shows up
It says putting a camera in his face and asks him questions
Jobs
Yeah I know but kids come to school in there
Fatigues were in like r o t
DC and stuff like that other reasons
Look if I was working Veterans Day or Memorial Day
Alex Jones came to work
And he was like I got a camera in your face I'll be like get that f****** camera out of my face
Yeah
Long before 9/11
I have no idea what that affected by the federal
Coast to Coast
Appear out of nowhere
Principally I am against what Alex is it
Military to not be operating in the
The state
Whatever
What would butthole crossing of the Rubicon
The acclimation cell
The Kentucky Derby
As well as other
President Bush
Shadowgun
In the yak
Executive branch formal
Preparing for domestic insurrections
State government
Just trying to soften you up.
President Bush
And the presidency officially became
Fiat
Government
Has been shared
Legislative
Branches of government
Power resides with the president was a slick f****** graphic did you see that
Also Alex thinks that Donald Trump is the only weapon
Can save us
Executive because he thinks that the Judiciary
Congress is full
Afglobal at operative
So you need almost a fascist dictator much like the people
Smedley Butler
March against f.d.r.
Why does drives me crazy
And of course
Bush was which was a disaster
Terrible
Here's here's the
Through-line of ookie
Like
Washing myself
In the city
Right
As he says that
Kitty powers
F*** yeah that's wrong
And then I think and Obama expanded those Powers thinking
So f*** that f*** him that should be allowed
And then Trump is got these powers and thank God he's too stupid to figure out how to use them properly
Because
He's too busy on Petty squabbles here at the church
Like the more this presidency goes on the more grateful I am that Trump won
And none of the other eight
Because if
If anybody
Really can't cope with the level of intelligence
Like if evil Obama
We're president right now
We would be
Fox are you kidding me we being a caliphate I know I know Larry Nichols
Destroyed of a large group of people ever agreeing with their enemy
Right
The Republic
Yeah you're probably right we're dealing with people who say things like
I know it's wrong if you have somebody
Combining that level
Xenophobic Lunas
That Trump had that he he needed to get elect
Ruthless capability
Dude they could destroy America tomorrow but I don't think any of the candidates have that combination
So we just get the xenophobic lunacy and be abusive
W and chadian where W is
Dumb enough and silly enough to get elected and Cheney is evil enough to enact all of his plan
Lake George W it's still a billion times
And the trumpets
And I hate saying that but that's
He's got 3 more years
Motel
Time will tell
Until 2003 so
Well I mean he was bogged down by
A 911
He was the reason 9/11 happened
For the smallest of reasons including the documents
In the world regardless of location that affects population
Infrastructure economy
President
Total martial law
Total Marshall
It is important to add
The president is merely a pop
Assembly passed them on
Redwood future
Administration
Except for Trump
I'm transitioning from Road
I got a lot of abusive posts.
Really happening right now
Yeah I forgot that I should have given a warning
YES Prep rewrite
Show me
Rodney would help
Yes there are Benedict
You must teach
People
Love
Almost
Unconditionally
Why don't we
To the point where nothing matters
You got to teach people how to love their leaders find itself
Xenophobic
Predatorial always rational release under pressure
Pays off people Superior
Mazda
When all they really are
Parasitically feeding on the house population
Until they're cancerous movement causes the collapse
I'm here cuz he's just saying
Adamstown
Mystery
And less than
I don't know if he's rocklick
Broccoli
Hands of a state
This is where Alex get super anti-government
Lives of more than 60 million
Men women and children
Hitler's War killed
Great during mousy tongues rain Alo
More than 16 million peasant farmers
True
And the list goes on
Innocent civilians
Killed in Guatemala
More than two million Souls brutally murdered
By the government
1 million
500000 killed in Turkey
Turkish Ganda 100,000-plus hacked to death with machete
There are too many examples of innocent fan
Bee exterminator
By their governments
Industrial scale
All the
And that's why you should ask Oracle
Are you racist
Xenophobic mom
LobsterTube
Control the largest military
The only point that I want to make about this is Alex's trying to
Shock people with
These numbers
Terrible horrible thing
Woody's conflating a lot of things
Because some of those were intentional Jen
Besides some of them were
Terry NFL
Make a violin
That also
Ended up being genocide
And if some of them were
Droughts that were exacerbated by mismanagement of government like
The numbers that you have for math
That's not all brutal murders
A lot of that had to do with just like
They didn't know how they were running
His main issue was he killed all of the people who could have helped him run right those numbers are super
Inflated by virtue of
Cyclical pattern
Yeah
To do in
Everybody who knows anything is stupid it's almost like
Call Rolex
Is not a good foundation
No
Murdered by the government
This is all I'm saying
Complaining a lot
Thanks anyway
Number one cause of unnatural death
If you take the 150 million people
10 / 100,000
With 100,000 screaming of Robotics 1500
That's 1500 Sports
With 100,000 people
Greatness
Can't happen here
Won't happen to them
You have been warned
Write the Carnage with
In the last hundred years
Was only the Preparatory phase
Of the new world orders master plan
We've reached the point.
This is annoying racking up the highest death toll in history
We'll get to greener pastures here in a bit the mass murder and enslavement still going on today
And enjoys the full support and sanction
Of the new world
And the United States
I don't know but also
You don't want people's pillows actually being said
Because if you do it we will probably find out it sounds a lot like what Alex says
Later on
Open you just said that the China is the globalist
Testing ground for ideas
Depression
There's no
Bibliography
I need David Rockefeller
David Rockefeller
Try out different way
You're making claims like
You have to support them
What you're saying is embarrassing if you don't repress tinge
In different ways
Right
That's all he said
He's also trying to link back to something else is bigger narrative
Hey
Look at all the ways that people are being oppressed in China
Don't get a pretzel
You have to say that it's
Who is trying out all these different
Because if you just
The white listener
Have any concept of what it is that
Oppression really is
Because that's
That's what he's trying to describe their look at all the way
That the government in China has oppressed
It must be shattered globalist doing that
It can't be
People
Given the opportunity
Will f******
Horrifyingly treat other people as if it doesn't matter
Because if you just say that
If you just reveal that it's something that's within the heart of every single human being on the planet
Nobody
Just selling dump books in these documentary
Proving Ground
The 1.4 billion people live out their lives
Service Test
Us and British forces work
Close during World War II
They secretly back now
Driving out Jane Kai-shek in the next show
Bill Clinton's then Bill Clinton University
Tragedy and Hope
Back every brand of authoritarianism
Communism to Fascism to ensure that a centralized government
Dominick's the population
Autonomy
The only citation for this isn't Amazon
To buy Carroll Quigley's book
If I recall correctly
Play from my research
Search paper
1200 page
F****** way
It was going to watch this documentary I got to confirm 1,200 Pages Amazon
You should never start only other citation is a WorldNetDaily APA
Age is not like it is not
Professionally written
Style
Clear that they're just
Cherry-picking quotes because their quoting likes
Three words at a time that half a sentence what to make
That I can't get
The context of this.
Read a bunch
Two books in preparation for this
But I'm not going to buy Carroll Quigley book and read 1200 more pages
I apologize maybe I'll do that eventually
I think right now every one of our list
This was great
But now that I know Dan didn't read that
Talking book
Citations
You need to do better policy wonks I love you so much but you're going to have to turn this on
Dance
Jordan 45 minutes
Sorry I'm losing it
I got to get our
To create Monopoly
The elation
Through the barrel of a gun
Has continuously
Cheap price on the corrupt
Microfiche
Very exciting 1973
An article written by
The New York Times
Rockefeller
Celebrating their command-and-control system
So this is New York time
Verilux on a road called from a China
History
For context
Nixon adjust gone to China in 1972 year prior from this article
Previous
Between China and the United States have been
Very frosty
United States did not recognize the communist government of China but did retain relations
Communist government in Taiwan
Which largely made the US1
Your enemies in the world
After 1770
After 1776 1.08 took 68 years for China to accept formal Diplo
Romantic relationship
The United States
In 1844 the signing of the Treaty of
This treaty was only really brought up because
The fears that Britain would dominate
And we wanted a little bit of that taste
Also had dudes pesky Opium Wars that were going on with the first in
Actual armed engagements between
Which is a weird
It's a weird time for
Oh man
We might not get in there the British are going to dominate at the same time the Chinese
These British people are f****** murdering I need to get rid of that please
Rye River
Terrible like a
This is terrible push push
Yeah
People they're evil there that they're the ones who've been giving you open yet
We're not British
After that
After that things didn't get better
1882 Chester Arthur then-president
Chinese Exclusion Act
Prohibited all immigration of Chinese laborers
Reactivate the order permit in 1902 this is only repealed by the magnet
Act of 1940
A lot of Gold Rush
The immigrants were tolerated when gold is plentiful
Profound
But once it started to dry up the local started turning on
On the Chinese
Story of a
The foreign miners tax
Text with Pastor discourage Chinese from being involved
Costco
Foreign children
So they moved
Pick up working low-wage labor position
The only things that were available
The Exclusion Act
Specifically made it so skilled and unskilled laborers in Chinese
People engaged
Could not come
Even if they did they'd be put in jail or deported
This single act
Completely isolated the
Already existing Chinese population here in America
It's one of those things where it's just like
It's just like with this gets worse
Yeah before you go any further
It's just like
The
The opposite
The slavery
I would like
We can't have these people slaves
They're working for free
It's bad to inflate
Will be in house exact same people have different takes on it
Comfortable I know the problem is definitely has nothing to do with the system
That I've allowed myself to be worked under for this entire time
The other guy
The Chinese Exclusion Act of 1882 led to a. Known as the driving out. We're angry White Stripes
About existing Chinese population
Scrum up ways around them or otherwise
The Rock
Springs Massacre of 1885 occurred when white miners in Sweetwater County Wyoming got mad about job competition
Resorted to shooting stabbing and assaulting Chinese workers
But why terrorism
I tried to flee only to end up being burned alive in their homes and starve to death in hiding
At least 20 people
This was followed up by the Snake River
1887 were 34 Chinese miners were murdered
Chinatown in San Francisco would go on to be scapegoated for an outbreak
Most likely caused by a French merchant ship that arrived with a guy on it and it died of the plague
As Time wore on the
Never really got to a place you might cold good
Between the United
States in China
Toward the end of that 1800 Western businesses
Pinterest tried to get into the Chinese market but worst Boxer Rebellion
T99 where nationalist Chinese forces
Revolted against foreign influence
Open trade policy
Sikh religion and took
Mr. pelican
What are you talkin about
American relation
United State people with all we did was the same thing you did
This rebellion was released
12 European powers and the United
How dare these people live do the thing on their own land
Recognize the Republican
China we supplied them with
During the second Speedo Chinese
No Japanese war around or isolationist
Was declared do not get in the middle of that
We begin
China only item
Japan they were fighting
A little bit
As WWII workout Chiang Kai-shek was very helpful and
Making sure the China did not become a member of the ACT
Just powers
After the war in 1945 civil war broke out in China between the Nationalist Republic of China in the Communist people
United States support the Nationalist
But deep direct intervention to stop the Communists
As not being worth
The cost it wouldn't
Strange
That will be your allies
F****** Lega it's fascinating because
Immediately following the underworld
Really after
Those are the same
They're not the same
The point the point is that the way that we treated
China immediately
Of World War
Has dominated the
Entirety of our
Because we
Famously Eisenhower in
Churchill
F****** let's go to town let's finish Russia off while we got the chance
We need to
They're weak right now.
Take them down
In the same way China had just been decimated by the Japanese
Occupation
F******
Rudolph
Like the extent to which
Japanese Occupation was brutal
It's something that is not
Really quite as discussed in WWII literature is maybe it
It should be when you think about why we got North Korea and South Korea
Japanese Occupation
As well
Korean
Immediately following World War
How we didn't do any goddamn s*** there either
The other question of courses
What exactly are we supposed
To do are we the only people who are supposed
To do everything in these times
And then the other writer then we evaded around like
Cool long mess of things
And it was those
Small decision
Is made immediately at the end of World War II
Really
F******
Set the course for both
Russian and Chinese relation
Consider that at that point you already had Aid
Deep history
Literal beginning of our country being real shitheadsteve
The Chinese
After Roto-Rooter
Like you're you're saying
We've decided it wasn't worth
The effort to try and help
There are
The cost of an all-out effort to
See, his forces resisted and
Destroyed
To the result
We abandoned our allies who helped us
Avoid further complication World War
It's due back Ismael and the Communists took over the country in 1949
Recognize that
Which would be 6 years after Rockefeller road is very short
1971 us China relationship
Fossil
Cold War and Mao's cultural revolution almost completely isolated China from the rest of the world
For many years
Ryan from communist country
Nixon went to China after all what was North Korea before North
Nixon went to China after was known as the ping-pong diplomacy
Us in Chinese ping pong players getting along
Really racist Until you realize they're referring directly to ping-pong itself
It seems it seems very suspiciously like
The ching chong bing bong
Yes we ended up a created an opportunity word American
Ping pong player visit
Open.
This possibility of
Visiting
The opening of the u.s.
At the beginning of normalization of relations
At the point Rockefeller wrote his tiny op-ed article almost no access to China for deca
Probably a little naive or generous
Also taking into account
But he wanted to try and
Market now that it was open
Reading that op-ed in that context in my ears it falls a long way
Short of open support for Maui
Authoritarian rule the criticism made a Rockefeller statement is valid
Terrible Optics
Minimize the brutal authoritarianism
There's an argument to be made for
Infant mortality rates drop from
4012 adult mortality rates
Not necessarily China Heather life
Expectancy 35 years
B49
Which one of the sea
66 years by
19 seven
These stats are not enough Justified
But it would be easy to
To see those sort
Two things being
Persuasive signs
Someone who came in and just got the lay of the land as Ava
Taurus
So I'm saying is the Rockefeller I think you f***** up and make
This op-ed
It's a little hasty
Possibly but it's not all that sign of
Globalist
Being in favor of now's authoritarian rule
It needs to be taken in the
The proper
Existed in
Which was
Decades and decades
Terrible China relations
Only being opened up after
A very bizarre pink
And
Serval relations
Large
Not not like
Very much.
Like if you went to a conversation with
Any Chinese person
Every single grieving
The Chinese person
Yeah I know
We totally did
Absolutely
That was a good one
Now we're against
Yeah
Whatever the price of the Chinese Revolution
It is
The social experiment in China under Chairman Mao's leadership is one of the most important
David Rockefeller
New York Times August 10th 1973
All right did he really say that that is a real quote from the article but it's also taken out of context
Maybe five
Luigi said those words
Communist China is the model
For the New World Order
Shina
Has received more United Nations award
Form of government
Ignore
What award Awards
Noid
Authoritarian
Shina adorable
From a Consortium of eugenics organization
Which includes
Red flag
Throwing up in the air
So do you want me to go through this about the China so you can keep on eating the word forwards
Large population
Anyways this
The terrible history
History between
With eight
1828 salmon
Is recorded between 100 ABC and 9
Including the northern Chinese
1870s
19 to 13 million people.
3 Chinese
58 through 19
T2 led to the death of
50 through 8
60 million
119:42
243 kill 223 million
1 from 9
Killed approximately
5 million
Historically been in
In China because of the weather patterns at high incidence
However
All this has naturally been exacerbated Times by the Warring States.
General contractor
Getting in the way of distribution
Field and more recently by now government doing an absolute
Didn't do a great job
Weird way to describe mouth
Could not really find called of all of the ways to describe now I wouldn't be like
Okay
About this guy
Super wishy-washy about multiple children
To know if you look at history
You don't have her like a clear stance
There's no clear stance
Power you strongly in favor of larger population
Believing the more communists
More power
More amenable to birth
Control ideas even launching Family Planning
Slogan 122r just fine
The issue was that at the time
China was home to 1/4 of a cup
The Goldilocks and
Yeah yeah quarter of the world's population with access to
7% of the world
Usable land
Two-thirds of our population was under 30
Are the Baby Boomers are entering the
Stage of life where they would reproduce
This is all a
Complete disaster in the making for a country with a
History of salmon
Planned Parenthood was not involved
The creation of the one-child
But there is some concern that they have not done enough to stop it or mitigate the Cruller aspect of
Play a part of an organization called the international Planned Parenthood Federation
Remembers also include
The China Family Planning
So there's a parent group that right
There's been
Concern over the years whether or not these
Cfpa the
Family Planning associate
Has been complicit in the sterilization
For sabores
Did the Chinese government used to
Enforced
Hornets
Productive
Articles
Claims Planned Parenthood
Complicit consistently make
We target
Without being able to read Chinese or hop on a plane to investigate it's unclear what
Cooperation with the organization entails
Yeah there's a lot of like soft bulshit like
That's immensely fresh
Yeah absolutely
Because then because
Your argument that
Is
Anytime Family Planning
Of any sort
Comes about it is playing
But
I will only mention it whenever Family Planning does not go the way that I wanted
Take me to Richmond
Okay yes
Planned Parenthood has allowed so many women who otherwise would have been
Bog down by children and yada yada yada and all of this s***
Planned Parenthood
Whatever
This one group of people in China may be involved or maybe they weren't or maybe they couldn't bend or whatever
They had a thing and that did a thing
Planned Parenthood small
Totally
And I think a better argument you can make is that given the lack of evidence about rape
Participation ended
Disgusting facts
Definitely
And enforcing their one child policy
I possible that the international Planned Parenthood Federation was
Interested in operating
China is a way to offer
Self-directed birth control alternative
Do the horse oppressive ones offered by the state
The same goal can be reached by education
Or by force
Pastor forces always had too many consequence
Be worthwhile
Probably
But if
Effective nobody f****** tried
Well
It is one of those
Be careful what you wish for situation
Especially with the China's one-child Pollo
Your call surprised
Ismail children
Far above
And it has a one child policy
For a long long time
Turns out
One woman forever
Unintended consequence
Designated Nazi.
I brought up there was
Beginning of that
Disastrous
Famine found themselves into my baby boom
It's very understandable why those
Bike
Policies
Would be
Considered
What they did in response to them are unforgivable in and all that but also Planned Parenthood wasn't involved
And the only thing that
Any of the sites
He offers RN
Weirdo dumbass website
Improve
Is speculation
It's just nonsense where they want to
Car
Parenthood at being collaborators
They were there trying to make it like
We can do this better
Rather the Federal Way
Sterilizing
Condoms
That's the idea behind
But irregardless that is not
Legitimate criticism to Levy at planned
Just because even if it like
It is
You're going to their country
If you're going to talk about
Sovereignty
If your Planned Parenthood
Do you have a state
Not doing whatever you can
I mean ultimately what is the the gold Planned Parenthood
Giving women age
Nancy over themselves
So even if you're going to
One child policy
That doesn't change your
No actually makes it more important that you operate air
Of course
So it's actually like
Wasn't there trying to give
I think
Yeah
Women make their own decisions
Control their Healthcare
There's a place where its worst
F*** it leave it alone
Not our deal it's it's nonsense
Couples that have more than one child
Heavy fine
With the cultural desire.
Has plunged China
There are 30 million
The Chinese police state
Underground churches
Forced labor
Their blood and tissue types
Preparations organ parts
Send you have America
The Chinese government
Organs
Highest
Did not know that
Medusa Morgan
And the organs are in plants
I'm not sure if it's as organs are being flown out
Extraction
I don't like for the undercoating
I get that
I don't think he'll show
Disabled
Is merely following
The world
Ocean worldwide
So ironically enough to a Grand Hyatt Buckhead
Henry Kissinger
Was the fake quote
Of course
If you're Henry Kissinger look again
Henry Kissinger
He's the worst
But there's no way that you would allow anyone to
Here and then record you say
Depopulation should be the highest priority of foreign policy
Towards the third world
Even for Kissinger who may have said it in private
Would never say it in public
Do you want
Comes from an internet meme
Most likely
Most likely before that it was a message board meme attributing
Kissinger
Depopulation
Be the highest priority foreign policy
Towards the third world
Because the United States economy will require large
And increasing amounts of minerals from abroad especially from less-developed
This court cannot be authenticated
If you just try to sort
If you just try to Source the part of it the quote the US
The US economy would require large
Increasing amounts
The minerals for abroad from development
Is taken
From biodiversity
Talking about earlier
Whatever they feel like that Alex isn't
This part is the fake part of a quote
Completely made up
It's just that he's he's hacked off the real party and make it much more difficult to Google
We are trying to make it harder to find out that he's just fabricate quotes
He's lying on another level
What's here in Alex Jones documentary
Of the second part
Whatever may be done to guard against interruptions
New Supply in developed domestic alternative the US economy
Increasing amounts of minerals from abroad special
Developed countries
The fact that fact gives the US
Political economic and social
Stability of
Supplying
Whatever
Went wherever lessening the population pressure
Through the reduced
Birth rates
Can increase the prospects for such stability
Population policy
Becomes relevant to Resource Supply
Answer the economic interest
Of the United
So
There is a thin
Veneer of similarity in terms of
Dubai population
Issues
Population control should be
Our highest priority population
Kissinger so it could be that he is talking to
What's the researchers looked into the quote that Alex able to trace it back
The furthest back they can get
Instances of it
Aura of Louis Farrakhan
Interview with the
Anti-nuclear activists Lauren Monet
I am being the most likely public sources
Public sources of the misquoting
Both claim to be quoting the same source
But but
Sounds right
So I don't know I made this is just a fake quote
People
Who were faking the quote
Is in the Sacramento area
Heavy quotes
Yes
Before that
All of these quotes are fake
That's
That is
Easiest thing
As an editor
Or someone putting together a documentary
To figure out
Is this quote real
Can I find it in the public record
Is it in the text
Easiest f****** thing to do
And Alex didn't think
To do that
It's weird that
Within the definition of
Quote
Of the word quote
Direct
Word for word
That's why we have a separate word for when you're not doing that called paraphrase reaching for the
Spirit of what this guy's trying to say I'm not some summarizing it
I'm taking directly word-for-word so when I say
Quote
This man said this you can be sure
Word for word exactly what you said
When you are quoting somebody for Metairie
One thing you should
To get everywhere
Every single right otherwise a price
Otherwise
For admit you're lying
He would have a defensible case if he was saying he was paraphrasing
No you wouldn't cuz the spirit is still off but
White letters on a black background with ominous music behind him if he says
To paraphrase David Rockefeller
You be like
Alright well I found parts of this quotes
So here's where this really comes from
I know it's not a quote but
You know that kind of
Jordan
Those glasses
Versus Jim Tucker
Glasses
For sure I agree
None of this may succeed this. But this to me it sort of the Outline by which
In the next few years it's illusion
Where does this mindset
Why do the elites kill the largest mass
Feel like that
What ideology Drive
We're about to enter a section of this documentary
Is about eugenic
We're about to enter a cell
About Alex
Well that's what
What he says
What is
People think the way they do
What I hear is I'm about to tell you what makes
Easier Talkatone about eugenics
And this is the part of the documentary where I kind of have to take a step back
I got to have to be like
You're misleading people about what eugenics
Was as a broader picture he's not wrong in a lot of
Throw out eugenics
Even with bad information
You're closer to the truth and if you throw David Rockefeller is a Jew the idea of a scientist
That we hold up
Fairley High esteem
Long dalliances with Eugenics ideas
That is dead
True a guy who believe that
That's a caveat I'm going to make for the next
Benefits documentary
Well yeah I can't f****** arguing
Is real f****** popular for a while
Creatively explain the fact that you'll be
I might be a little bit
2400 years ago
Borders of openly proclaimed their desire
Again not before that
Plato's fault
Real-time traffic
Has always been a track
Because it creates a convenient excuse for treating your fellow man
Lower than that
Also there was nine
Traits was
The new
Explosion of Pop
Applications of it was
The new
So
Chronology
I don't want to hear Alex
Ever talk about reason
I don't want to hear him talk about how
Oh
This is why they demonized other people Alex you found
Plenty of reasons on your own
And a half
But I'm just trying to say that there is like
There's a pretty simple explanation for why eugenics
Vanguard
Realized
Call know when you mix intelligent people with
Super racist people
You're going to wind up getting
Super intelligent reason
Sims 4 being
Totally totally
Robert Thomas Malthus
Famous for saying
Collapse would be helpful
Because it would
You his fictional scenario would later be called
Email Susie and catastrophe
He wasn't insane
Because his ID
Led to the rise
New Scientist
The real quick about Malthus
Didn't want to wipe out the fact
He supported help
Videos about moral character
Essential to
Having a successful life anyway
Stop that was unnecessary
Catastrophe refers to a situation
In the mouth is warned about
Namely a situation where population in
Increase outpaced agricultural production
He warned that
Reply.
I'll choose is one source
Recitation
For this Andy doesn't specify
600-page book
I found this text
This is interesting
So we should facilitate instead of foolishly and Bailey endeavoring to impede the operations of nature
I'm producing this mortality
And if we dress
We should seditious we
Other forms of destructive nature to use
Instead of recommending we should encourage contrary
In other towns
We should make the street tomorrow work
Plague
In the country we should build our Villages near stagnant pools and forgot really like these
Settlements in Michigan unwholesome situation I don't think he's being serious
Specific remedies for ravaging diseases
Those those benevolent
But much mistaken men thought they were doing a service to mankind by projecting scheme
For the total extirpation of particular disorder
He is talking about Alex
Yeah basically literally and it's cut the Modest Proposal
He's clearly being
Facetious
He's making the point that like if you
You don't want
To be concerned about the
Potential for the poor to feed themselves
Right what are ultimate argument
To highlight how stupid it is that you don't
F****** support
People who were in it
Disastrous
Sarcasm
If that screwed up
We have never thought about it
We should actually be going out and explaining what
A tire
With Dominic
Course
Human hits
For the next 200-plus year
Charles.
Admirer
Alex is lying about Malfoy
So the idea that Darwin admired him
That's not
Suspicious or weird
Developed the theory of evolution
Chief
The survival of the fittest
With the help of
Known as Darwin's bulldog
Strong support of Darwin's theory
Darwin's theories were pushed into wide except
A monkey scientific circles
And then the world
Darwin's cousin Francis Galton credited as the father of eugenics saw an opportunity
Evolution Theory and applied social principles
Social darwinists
That's not
Huxley
That's not that that's not strictly speaking truth
If you look at their birth chart there is there's like people who
Intermarry
Other families
Because it's like
It seems very uncommon to us but inner marrying within your family like Mary
Your cousin or your second cousin
Was not on
Common in Britain
Alex saying that like these guys
They intermarried with each other that this
That was kind of a
Yeah
A lot of the time
We have places
Kentucky
There's so many reason
Do that
That was only a few Generations
They would produce Superman
The emerging pseudoscience was only codifying practice of
Already popular
Before families experiment was a disaster
Again piano collections on Legend
Guitar lessons
Seriously mentally all about retaining property
The moneyed class of the play
Particularly the royal families in the world
We're already at chef
Breeding
Build the predatory to stain for the underclass
Yeah but that makes sense
For them
The reason it makes sense is because
Nobody wants to admit
That they have their money
For no real reason
Nobody wants to MetLife
This is just random
Over there
Who doesn't have any money
If I was born I could have been the same person
Can't
Devastator
That was f****** Trump if you go back through his family of course they're f****** races
This eugenicist
Because none of them
I'm just as random as dude if I didn't have money
Reroute a couple
You can't allow yourself to admit that so of course
If you're a f******
Inbred
You're not going to be like well anybody could be
Well it's because of genetics
That's the reason my family has money
Because of genetics
Not just because we
F***** over everybody as ever gotten in our way because apparently maybe maybe it is genetic tan
Maybe
Sociopathy is something that you can transfer down through the line so you never have to deal with the fact that
Other human beings are also real
Evil people are f******
Evil because of money
Biometrics appears to be an ocean eye
Carlton
As a way to track
And as a way to decide
Would be licensed
Cold Springs Harbor research facilities in the United States
Eugenicist Charles Gavin
With the funding of Marin
Harbor is much bigger than the eugenics
That Alex is talking
But he's pretending
Fire research laboratory
Yeah there wasn't eugenics
Department
That was
Ignored
They found out about it and
F****** stop
Shut off
Cold Springs Harbor is this one
Unipolar
Just everybody's the same
Agricultural experiments for doing that I like
Animal husbandry
This
It's something
That I've been
Okay
So here's the hard part about you
When were talking about you
If you stop and think
What we did
Two dogs
What we turned wolves
And we now call.
That's huge
That is the concept of
Eugenics
If you
Find certain characteristic
Overtime
If you have complete control over there
You can breathe
Further enhancement of those
You then follow
Human beings are animals just like
So we can do the same thing
The problem comes
Because we control every part of a dog's
We can often see the
Changes that we want to breed in
In the dog get out
It's not that I want the dog to be smarter
Sing like that it's that this dog is much better at finding
Solana breeded with a dog that's better like that whole thing
I think that's a lot of the lessons that they started to learn
In the 1930s
Then you start throwing in
Does people have
Race
Standing
Class all of this
Like
Legitimately
If we were to x out
All of the other factors
And just
Like that the purest level
This guy has large feet
This lady has large
And then breed accordingly with no regards for no regard for anything else
Eventually you're going to get huge
That's how
Probabilistically yet
Kelly works for thirty or forty thousand
Everyone
That was my foot
Yeah maybe
Superman
What you're going to wind up doing
Is just going for the most dumb Surfer
Best level shift
Then you go go f*** yourself you're a lying piece of s*** I am so much of it comes down to
To like really am
Equated models of like morality based
I'm sort of a Genet
Genetics
Yeah you come into like Iowa what's
It's a it's a hot mess we could if you want to if you want to believe in eugenics
We could get big
I'm glad we were able to come around to that really frustrates me because I feel like
You you always wind up I like the more
I don't know
Like Eugenics isn't
A blanket negative word
The way that the word is always been applied is
Discriminatory
But like from a purely let's all step back
Before
And you hear these people saying you text me like
Well
Because
Look at what we did to dogs
We do math
That whole
My my problem with Eugenics is that
People often
Mistake it for the idea of something
Intrinsic like some sort of
Value of genetic
You know like
Morality
We can breed morality
You just how revolutionary
I might my chest is not my mind but my chest
It's so hard to explain eugenics
In such a way that
Satisfies both my
Inability to divorce Humanities idea of speciality from the rest
Of course you could work
Where in
Well the same time divorcing it from the evil of like
Well you know
Of course if you have a skull that's three and a half
4/3 in Long
You're much smarter than somebody else
You know that kind of
Using eugenics
On
Humans
Changeable
Advocates intrinsically immoral
You are a
Are the god emperor of Dune
Shut up
A grade
2210 station laws passed in the United States
Spoiler about to get to my
My favorite thing Alex lies about this
Citizens with mild deformity
Arlo test score
Four arrested
And forcibly sterilized
Yeah it's whatever.
So we're trying to help them out as a Hutu
They will take him to the hospital this afternoon
Be very careful watch this watch for a jump
How does it take this morning
Record necessary to
Prudential Sandy's case
Examination
They decided
Entire family
I don't know what you're talkin about
Operation so there won't be anymore
Now we take your brothers and institutions
I'm keeping my job I'm not going anywhere
Do you mean they're going to stop me from having children ever
Exactly
I won't go to the hospital
So for no reason I watch this movie
Alex is recycled
Alex is presenting it as a pro eugenic
Xmovies8
Exact opposite
You could tell just from that little sea turtles try to make this girl get
Paralyzed
So it's even more f***** up though
It's so bizarre
So that girl is what type of movie is going to have a cherub faced young beautiful girl they like
I don't want you to make sure you kill all these attractive
What are you talkin about young lady
So I
So she's part of this family right
She's got two younger brothers one
And the other is mental
Defective and you will only sit around playing with his dad's empty whiskey bottle
The mom
Apparently we've learned
The mom has a stillborn child right baby dies after one day the doctor comes over
Very awesome Hero characters
Doctor over to help you out and throw in the process of the
Coming over
They realize I like
This family sucks let's f***
Bunch of assistance money
If they will all get sterilized
I said the parents.
That's crazy that sounds like something that would never happen
Post
12 United States
The parents sign a waiver daughter T-shirt
Possible
Will get booked at the daughter to come and get her tubes
Don't ever have kids
Or whatever
Anyway
She's about to get married
Supposed to be like this really lovable character
He's driving her home
In the car vs turmeric
Character character for 1934
And that means he's like I want to marry you and she's like
I don't know if I'm ready like drive to suck you
Another most violent
The government comes in there like you got to go we got to get these tubes tied
Rum and the Doctor Who would come over and Italy is like a
She's working a job in
Supporting the family with the drunk parents
Muddles your argument just a little bit definitely don't know
Don't sterilize based on family sterilized based on person come on
So the argument that this good doctor is
Presenting throughout the
Tire thing
Is like
I understand where Daryl ization could work but the way we're doing it is
Precious the way we're doing it is
Completely unnecessary it's it's
It's been he's the voice of conscience in the f****** movie
Along the whole way
Trying to make sure they don't
Can sterilize her
It's not possible
Hospital
She's going to get
Sterilize how long
Like an hour
It's it's not all of this happens and it's not even watching the documentary
1/2 hours and I still don't know what's going on
Get through all of it
I will wait I will say jumps around a bit
Not euthanize sterilized
Here's the twist
What ends up happening
Super drunk
Mdiv fiance
Hesby
You got to do something to help her everything where the mom sterilize the dad
For Christmas I got you sterile
Drunk
Not even my daughter she's ugly
I'm so they called The Wait So now that's fine they call the judge and the judge called the hospital
Actually related
The end resolution of the movie is not good
So
Okay so
In this movie
Advocating
Maybe human beings shouldn't be categorized based on their Social Circle
At the end of it the movies like
Thank God she was categorized
The way out of the plot without being to subvert
The film system in 1934
We have to do it.
The plot of the movie is
The message of that doctor
And it's clearly the way we're doing this is not right we are
Cruel and inhuman right
F****** laughable
To make it look like that
More than it was saying
Anyway
Yeah well I mean Greenfield
Black people in that
Which is who they were doing all of the eugenics
Two criminals
Sterilized are both White
Ones like
Catatonic
Sterilization was used
Almost
Exclusively as a
They did make one really good salient
In the movie
Me for 1934 yeah which was when
The girl had to go to court
To be decided
She was going to be sterilized
Cuz they were like
Appealing her case
Another character was
Do to be in court
And it was this it was the son of the governor
Ain't like he's back in Chambers
And other than nurse there was like trying to keep him
Come together
Rips off her shirt
And the governor
Keep it together
And the lawyer comes over
Makeup to make it look like
I'm sorry for his actions in the past the governor in the judges like
Paralyzed
Class message like he's acting like
F****** Unleashed
Predator
There is that subversive message within
What are we talkin about tomorrow's children this
Like this is before all of those
Like you can't show this like all of those self
Regulating that the Hollywood
System did because realize I'd like
I think you genuinely do
I liked watching it in like realizing
Alex
Just like why would you
For him to
Only Alex
Consistent
Like this is a pattern of behavior
This isn't just like
Entirely to disprove his
The edited it specifically because it talked about eugenics
That was Charmed me about it
He's trying to find anything that disagrees with
And then cut it and put it in a way
To make it look like it agrees with him
One of course invalidating his own
But who cares his argument is invalid
Confusing whether or not anything he needs any
U.s. Eugenics record office with shut up
The first Network social worker
Expressly to serve as spies and
Enforcers
Citation needed
Cell
The social worker
Who would have their children taken
Who would be sterilized
Some cases
Murdered
That is from yesterday's children
Buy bankrolling the Kaiser Vallejo
Here we go
Phenomenon
Long predates
Kaiser Wilhelm
Existing in
Rape
So the
Connection between
Is not really
Concrete
At the same time there's a lot of question
Think about things
May or may not have
Ben studied at the Kaiser Wilhelm in
During the war
But drawing a causal and linear
Kinship there is not a pro
Central pillar
In the Third Reich
1912 East Conference in London
Eugenics
And games
Superstar status
Like the pet rock
Faith worldwide
Love you Jenna
Totally comes out knowledge
Everything I noticed you else's written
Has always come down hard on
We should
You want to know one more thing about him here
H.g. Wells lover
Margaret
Chapter promotion of eugenics in the United States
Alpaca Ranch
On the Rockefeller family
2019 23
When you say exciting ring
Got a lot of money and id22 from Rockefeller
What is it
Very unpopular flight to provide access to birth control and health
Services to women
Huh
Opera long time
She started a monthly newsletter called the women Rebel
The woman Rebel with the slogan no Gods no matter
Reproduce this newsletter antagonistically in large part because she wanted to create a legal challenge
For The Comstock Act of 1873 regarding
Information about contraception
Postal authorities of go on
Suppress the release
Five of the seven issue
Create
In August 1914 Sanger was indicted
For violating obscenity laws
On October 26th
Singer was arrested for operating a women's clinic in New York's Lower East Side
She was arrested
And when she was released
Tree reopened
Was arrested again
Reopen the clinic
Police responded by shutting
Clinic down for good
What you want to this charge is found guilty
The judge held that women do not have quotes the right to copulate with a feeling of
Security that there will be no resulting conception
Brilliant legal
The right to
F*** without getting pregnant
Army look
Right
Sounds right to me she was sentenced to 30 days in a workout
She appealed the Constitution
If you say women have the right to
The f*** you got to work for it
Csupo but in 1918 her appeal Was Heard
And the case set the precedent that
Except
Distribute distribution of contraception
Information to women provided it was
Scribe for medical
That was illegal up till that point
Are crazy
Stupid Forever always
Every time we find out one of Alex
You discover
How amazingly awesome they were
Okay here's crazy also
The thing about this
Like if Phyllis Schlafly
Should be lit on fire and then
When her soul is brought back from hell
Lit on fire again tossed out there again
And so on and so forth
Because I never want her to get comfortable any
I don't want her to be comfortable in her eternal torment
I want her to have to keep bouncing around
Basically
If Schlafly
Had a history as bad asses
That of life
Oh you're going to shut me down f*** you
I'm going to do it again
F*** you I'm going to do it again
To do this s***
F*** you I'm going to do it again I'm going to feel this s*** and at the end of that a precedent is set that said
Phyllis Schlafly
As monsters that she can still be a monster I'd be like
I disagree with you I have to respect goddamn hell out of that and he can't even
They can't be like look at what
And I disagree with her
Look at that badass
And there's no there's no point if it's like
Wholeheartedly believe in
Providing women
No it's cuz she's a demon
It's because she's a badass
It's not because
Kids are
It's cuz she's a demon
She anytime and time anybody who does something
That disagrees with what you do
So hard
So hopefully
So meaningful
It is not because
They experience at meeting
Talk that could come at you like that
Is if they're controlled by state
And Alex
You understand islamophobia apparently
And Alex's pretending along Tire Road shoes receiving money from these globalist rockfeller
Who else
Sucking wasn't
It's true John D Rockefeller Jr did Sports anchors work around that point
Everybody should have that's not telling the entire story The Alex chose that date
Specifically to bring up
Is it that the Tanger open the country
First legal birth
Control clinic
What is leaving out that around this time Sanger also married her second husband boiled
Noah h
He provided much of the funding for her effort
So the Rockefellers did start to come in
But you was running birth control
The all over the place
People were not helping her
She carried this Crusade for a very long time
Once it was legal
Some outside funding came in and
She got married to
This really rich dude
Which
Unfortunately
Seems a little bit for me because she's already
The problem is now
I've got it in my head
Poor people are never going to be able to do it on her own
Maybe he was woken
Again another crazy f******
The actors frontman
Sterilization program
Doesn't sound right
In 1994
End credits us eugenicist
As his inspiration that's true
Madison
Calling his race Facebook
Passing of the great race Bible that's true but Madison
He was a huge anti-semite into disaster mistaken regard for what
What are the rifle with the title of the passing of the great race
Not great
Got to be a great guy
Listen to regard for what are believed to be divine Laws In a Sentimental belief in the sanctity of human life tend to prevent both the Olympic
Defective infants
Sterilization of such adults
NOVA community
Human life is valuable only when it is of used to the community or race
I feel like he's
Gone a long ways off track you went on to say that the Nordic race
The Nordic race bemoaned its corruption byju's Negroes Slavs and others who did not possess
Blonde hair and blue eyes he's already on board
Don't use him as an
An example of like
Also know I think
I think it should go the other way around like look at how crazy this guy
Even Hitler got on board with his I think you probably was pre-loaded
To do so already Maybe
I don't know it's tough to say before Hitler
The passing of the great isolated
Mustang in 1930
Your your
Should be
Look at how crazy Madison Grant is
Hitler thought he was a genius totally
Mass extermination of the Jews
What he called other sub-races
As well as the handicapped from Grant
Part 27
The so-called science was aggressively pushed
Contest
Churches
State Fair
And that's why we can't have roads ended Concha
Big cash prizes
To see who could best
Implement
Major denominations then tell America
The Jesus is for you
So Alex is citation
For this
Is 1
From
Which covers major.
Written sermon that is
Clear of who it came from there's no
There's there's no like reference or anything which means it came from
Clear like it's incomplete
Like the pages aren't
Complete for the sermon so you don't know all the five pages out of
Who knows how many
Reference
Bismarck
Which says
The son of man
As it is written
But woe to that man by whom the son of man is betrayed
Good word for that man if he had never been born
Right
Using that good for him if you'd never been born. I get that moral characteristic
Or whatever
Right
Being doomed from birth because of bad genes
Extrapolate
You know what
That's not the craziest thing I've ever heard a preacher say
That's not the craziest thing I've heard a preacher say on Alex Jones Show
Easiest thing I've heard you say Reverend James David Manning on his show who says that the gays puts
Semen in Starbucks lattes
Because they like to have a good time
But also the other problem with that is
Is that like
Strictly speaking
An Oak Point
From
Potassium
Well it's not on
Like if you allow for the idea that they're already saying
It's not like that guy is crazy
No he's not like
He's not clearly under the influence of some Eugenics board applying a line of thought
Preexisting
Interpretation
Scripture it's not
Probably that's probably the major failing with scripture is that
That guy wrote it
One thing
A million whatever the thing that I wanted to meet
It's crazy to us
The Constitution
Looking building change
Grow don't
Just don't be like well
Jesus said in Mark 1 through I don't give a fuk
Yeah the past
Can suck my dick
Agreed
Except
Where it already did Rachel build on that
Pass for sterilization
And the Supreme Court rule
Favor
A brutal sterilization pod
Hitler came to power in 1933
One of his first Acts
What's the past National Eugenics laws
Unfortunately
Tomorrow's children
Rock
Operation
That's a good.
She's hardworking and have a good reputation
Do you know anything about her family background
Yes
One of the crippled 2020 classes
Ignoring all that you feel content but this girl should be allowed to bring
Ketone
Yoorana
She's not anything like the rest
Proportion is normal
Three generations of unfit
I think I'm not allowed
That judge is
Germany
For taking effective action movie where you wanted your good guy.
It says that kid to be sterilized
Good guys
Like in Eugene
Davenport
Laughlin go
4 dispatch
German
So here Alex says that Davenport lost Lennon ghost
Dispatch by The Rockefellers to help the Nazis
Eugenics
Davenport Laughlin
His
Citations on this are incredibly loud
To go with a
I don't know whether to go with like a
Lawyers Partners joke or like a Shadrach Meshach and Abednego
Like which way do I go
Here's where I'm going to go with it
Gertha
Go to pronounce his name
Alex Jones post as a citation
Yeah is that reporting to someone named Mister Eddie
About what he observed of the German
I'm collecting eugenic data
It has nothing to do with helping them or over at the hawk
It Was Written in 1937 before kristallnacht
Before the invasion of Poland Etc
That being said
Is gertha was a real bad too
And I use
Absolutely if I can race
Sonar Davenport
Alex has a citation that is another letter from the sky
This is from November 11th nineteen
22 a year before the beer hall push
Decidedly not in power
The letter of firms that there are Germans interested in the principles
Eugenics
Sterilization
What does not show that he was
At all
Davenport was a bad dude
He did write for some German scholarly journals much later than he should have gone up to 1939
Weirdly in 1938 he wrote a letter to the editor of the
The Time Magazine
It said about fpr in Joseph
Gerbils
Both quote LED revolutions
Aspire to dictatorships while burdening their country with heavy taxes
And reducing a
Its finances to
The chaos alright well smart nobody
Scholarly Journal
S*** on grbl
Before
Very confusing bad due to
Press clipping it out there's a press clipping to Alex Jones uses
The citation for Laughlin
Being 150th anniversary of the University of Heidelberg
But this is from 19
Even before gurthaz letter
The Olympics
So
That said
Laughlin also a bat
Look I'm not
The broad brush
If your name is mentioned
In 1930s
I'm going to leave with you probably not a good dude looks like.
So you know a guy's name from 1930s
What are the
Is it a hero or is it a bad dude
It's not a good percentage
Name from
Germany I'm going to be like
Lisa Rivera
Dispatch to germinate to help with
In 1930
Percentage-wise
Like if you're in America
Knock knock
Laughlin was described as quote among the most racist and anti-semitic of early-twentieth-century eugenicist
Biographer
There's little doubt that the f****** claim there's little doubt that
No evidence
But there's no provided he collaborated with
Them also you before he went to Germany review panel convened by the Carnegie
Concluded that the Eugenics record office which was
Charge of
Cold Springs
Harbor
Confirm
Pick any of the Eugenics record
They concluded that the research they were doing had no South America
And withdrew funding for it
And shut it the fuk down interesting Lee before that point they'd never audited the research they were doing so
So you present
With a pitch
You're going to find out
Then we looked into it
Turns out you're just erased
So that's not really science
And one
I don't
The right
Coming from
Bro I love you
Brought
Give me some sign
One of the big reasons that they didn't find out for so long as
Because these
Research
Planters
These huge
Knicks Records Office
The primary
Twista collect
Data
That takes a long time
Big window
Before someone's going to recognize
It's something is up and that what you're doing is meaning
There's an argument to be made that what they were doing was actually.
Rotting
These foundations they probably didn't mean to but
Alien to product is that's what they did
And that folks is where we will have to cut off
For today I feel really bad about that bad but
With
David's documentary is going into recovery is going
It's an impossible task for me to figure out an end
For this section of the the coverage
Play apologize for cutting things off
Hot Nazi talk
At the end of today's episode
Tomorrow at the beginning
Tomorrow's episode
But I'd like to find out more about OSHA
Go to knowledge feit.com we are on
Twitter at knowledge underscore fight
Can also find us on Facebook
We are there yet
Leave a review the show
Follow us tell your friend
All that good stuff we're also on
Subscribe if you wanted to leave review any of those things
Are really helpful and it would mean
A lot
But for now I got to get out of here cuz
This documentary sucks and it sucks to relive it as I edit our coverage
Putting you through it
You know what those listeners ask for it I've only apologizing halfway
All the best to you and yours
And we will catch you
Tomorrow
Alex