Everybody welcome back to knowledge
Four of our
Five-part coverage of Alec
To call it a documentary
We'll go ahead
What does the name
Convention he came up with
Film
Slick
Drew blank there for a second
Nothing
But researching
Recording and editing about this documentary for the last 3 weeks
Anyway guys where we last
On episode 23 we were in the middle of
And as promised at the end of
Continues
At the beginning of this episode but
There's not too much left of it look forward to us
To get into some other b******* Alex's lying about
Couple of quotes that he's faking
Couple more quotes
I'll be honest
This is where I think I got a little bit mad in the middle
Self decently but set
Be some cracks starting to show here in
What would be
H 7 of me and Jordan sitting around and recording
This
Nonsense
Anyway
Enjoy
Just enjoy
Alex
There's there's an argument to be made that what they were doing was actually
Rotting
These foundations they probably didn't mean to but
Alien producteurs that's what they did
I didn't start off as a scam
With the strong support of the US and England
Germany
The end of the war
The Allies protected
Prosecution
Nazi scientist
The tortured thousands of people to death I wonder why I have to assume
Yeah that's not true they didn't
Yusuke
Mengele escape to South America
No that's not
It's untrue protector
There were many scientists
At a high-level who and who put a lot of a lot of them we're not involved
Crimes against humanity
That would be nice
Will do you know any other name
Yeah David's parking
Citation needed
Citations needed
Franklin
That was his brother
Okay what has me making fun of
The German language
Is possibly true but you're not proving it
Because you don't have any
Okay fine
I know about like naive to think that the American government did not protect
Genocide
Jenna ciders
As well as our desire for knowledge and the
It meant meet at the time
To defeat the Russians in developing whatever
Of course they projected there's a there's a bunch of
Bottles that I would have to that a number of them involved
The idea that a lot of people who had access to Teresa
Being done
And the results of it we're not involved
With
The crimes against
And so a lot of people
From prosecution
Commit War crime
The United States could have swallowed them up
Most of the people who were involved in Project Paperclip
Lot of the Nazi scientist who came over like 1 or van Braun unrelated areas involved
Relations and crack
Nuremberg trials were specifically set up in such a way
2 only
Prosecute for a couple different
That were within the
Spectrum of the Court view of the Court jurisdiction
And
I don't
100% accuracy but
I don't think
Did someone like Mengele would have escaped prosecution
Alex
Alex Jones said
Specifically
Singular
Scientist
Not playing
Yes he's talking about Mengele
It was history's f****** amazing though like realistically to be a Nazi is this evil
Margaret Sanger situation were like no no but I'm Amazed
Like V the fact
He had the foresight to know like
It's going down
Escaped
10 days
Before the camps were liberated
Did get captured
And they used his name
But because of
Some sort of stuck up with record-keeping
They're like oh you're not one of the people we are looking for a out released and ended up escaping to South America
Lakeville lucky that he had
In terms of that it's just
It's unbelievable
Maybe it's mind control
So he did Escape sup American-owned really protect
Alex Jones
Making that claim
Requires far more
Citation
The Nazi brand
The Allies literally fought each other over who would get top-notch
Wow
They were free
The angel of death Josef Mengele
Is Bosch otmar Von vershire
We're not prosecute
Even continued his work in Germany
After the war
Ne8 brain
Mangala did not Escape prosecution
At the Nuremberg Trial because he is
Escaped to South America
Escaping
To be metaphorical
Most people weren't tried In Absentia
They're only a couple people who are gone
Something like that
But here's the thing
The Nuremberg trials were incredibly
The first thing to keep in mind when you talk about the Nuremberg trials is there's a jurisdictional issue that it was only limited to work
Crimes against humanity waging Wars of aggression
A crime of that
Variety
Considered under those guidelines
There's no reason to think that otmar Von verschuer would have been found guilty
Was even deserving of the Courts at 10
What he did
We rightly can look back on his grotesque
An awful now
But it didn't rank with the Nuremberg trials
At the time there was the appearance
That he was just a scientist who benefited from receiving
Some samples from Angela in Austin
But not anyways and active
Participant
History calls that into question a little
So here's the thing Von verschuer was
Mangalore
Doctoral advisor whatever coming up
Completely separate
Research in
Institute nemeia received some samples from Angela
He was not involved in the camps and anyway
Well there's plausible deniability in terms of like that if there's no way you're going
To prove that he
Committed crimes against humanity war crimes
Crimes of aggression
Things are not going to prove that
If you could do that would make a great if you bring them up on trials in the
Those crimes
No so there's no reason why he ever would have been brought up now
In hindsight we can look back
Probably probably not
He's probably way more guilty than we know
It's kind of like
So
I look at it
Kind of like the way people look
Catania Harding
Look at the time for a while people saw her is just
The victim then she had no involvement with the Gallipoli
And his actions but she was involved
There's no doubt she was involved
So there's something like that it's too-little-too-late can't do anything about it
Pennywise
Wait which
I didn't see the movie
Jeff gillooly was her husband who hit Nancy
Nancy was the one who was he
The Nuremberg trials there were the doctor trials in 1946 to 90
B-47
Which would not
We've been locked up in
Nazis for a while now
Not as long as the road as far as
As far as
Tonya Harding
And Aunt
That was on TV right like I don't remember
No not the nothing
Like on TV
On the day
People were like
This Olympic athlete had her husband beat the s*** out of her competitor
Sounds about right
That was like 10 when I know I was remember that and I remember like
Steven the videos in my head of that
Crying like
It's amazing to live through though
That is a real thing that happened to
No big deal I was a guy
And if I refuse
Tonya Harding is a monster but abuse
I feel sorry for her but also
She's really good one of the only people to hit a triple axel
Competition but it wasn't
Nancy Kerrigan was also really good Tonya Harding was really good she was running
The triple axel
Rarity
Nancy Kerrigan was probably going to make the Olympic team
There's only
So much room on that team
Dude he has beat mob ties
Really
Lead pipe problem
I don't see how you have a friend
Good
Situation
46 + 47
Yeah up Nazi sign
This would also not guilty of any of the charges that were in the
Jurisdiction of that Court
Charges they were able to make war crimes against humanity
Performing medical experience
Experiments without the subject's consent
All prisoners of war and civilians of occupied countries
In the course of which the experiments of the defendants committed murders
Brutalities cruelties tortures atrocities
Nicki Minaj
Also planning performing to mass murder prisoners
Warren civilians of occupied countries
Mattias does
Buy gas refill injection
And diverse other means and nursing homes hospitals and asylums during the euthanasia program
Are participating in the mass murder of concentration camp in
And
The other crime they could have charged them with with membership in the SS
None of these would have applied Devon vergere
It would have been applied to mangala but you had already escaped stuff and
Known as protecting anybody it was just a waste
Waste of time
Prosecutor
He was clean
Got to wait cleaning
All of his Witnesses though it been
Hitman
In the leg with a lead pipe
You just got the samples from Angela I think
Hanging out with Mussolini
Angry exposed
Text scrambled camouflage
Eugenics quarterly
Social biology
The American birth control
Became Planned Parenthood
New terms like transhumanism
Population control
Sustainability
Conservation
Replace
Racial hygiene
And social Darwinism
What's going on here at all previous.
Crypto eugenics
Purposely
Taking their Eugenics beliefs Underground
They became highly respected anthropologist
The postwar world
All of those things are eugenics
I don't think that's what that
Thing is.
Let that drawing
Project Paperclip
Military-industrial
The founder of
Roosevelt
That is a little icky
Perhaps
Thomas Watson was given a medal by Hitler
You also returned it later
I don't know if we can find evidence
But he was a dedicated follower of him
He was
A boy that's a problem
Yeah
Thomas J Watson and Supply his punch card computers
Technician
IDM human identification number
This is
This is true but I don't know if
Launch Car Technology work.
Computer
That the problem that I come to visit all of the citation
For this Art Online
Taking. I've no idea what he's
Trying to sight
But
Thomas Watson and IBM
Did have involvement with giving Punch Cards
Technology to the Nazis were able to use
That made the camps more efficient
Right now the f*****-up piece of the ovens were made by a company name
Siemens
And semen get all of your s*** now to Leggett
It is like that IBM
They did
Provide punch project
Computing
But the real problem is not
Sports attic
Stop
Supporting the Germans when the Holocaust happen
The business relationship between Germany
And IBM a company that it was before which was a German company
Predated the rise of Hitler by 20
3 years
They were already doing all this business in Germany
Stop at parties
Credibly f*****-up
Should be deeply ashamed of himself
Because the the
The histories
All that that I bread
I have been so
Overflowing with this concept
Well we just couldn't believe
Like that kind of that kind of excuse kept coming up over and over and over again
Then where you talk about
The people who developed
The technology
That they use
When you ask them like
Well
We were told what it was being used for
This year
But we could not believe
And then two years later is like oh s*** that's real
Like the Holocaust the Holocaust now
The Holocaust deniers
During the war even right up to the end think about year-by-year the dishes
Between like
36 and 37 37 and 38 38 and 39 39 40
Like the difference between those gears and terms
The perspective what was publicly available information
Even even very difficult to wrestle with
Even soldiers in the
In like 44 were saying
Well we didn't believe that the Holocaust was real until we saw it
Yeah because how could
Possibly
What what kind of conception
If it weren't for the Holocaust
You wouldn't be able to conceive of a holocaust
Like it's impossible to imagine
Well I know there's another kind of right now
I meant
I think there is some sort of responsibility I believe that exist for likely
He's business people who were doing business with them
To have some sort of oversight of like
Whoo-wee contributing
But maybe I'm being idealistic
I'm not entirely sure
That's where we start talking about unregulated
Actual capital
Because unregulated
Corporations have no respond
All they are is machines
Money
Well yeah but
They're people who are machines built
To make money
I can't find any documentation or evidence
That size.
The numbers that were tattooed on people were used
With w and Arabia
Continue
Similar punch-card systems as early as 1928
The first real computers
We're literally infinite
Biogenesis
He said literally technically the first computer was created
You could say that an abaca
Was technically a computer won't start let's just grab the name that he
As in electronics
Computing the
Decorative
That's why I got
Water claims there
In the formation of all done
Injustice
This government will be controlled by a scientific
Huxley creator
Former SS officer Prince Bernhard
Again
The SS
Group he was in
It was a largely equestrian Social Club
To believe otherwise is to believe that space command guy that candle
Excellent oxtails
And Prince
In the event
I would like to return
In order to contribute something to solve overpopulation
Reported by Deutsche presse-agentur DPA
August
Well we're at 43 now this is quotient
Number 7
Statistics
It's a paraphrasing of something
He did say
Is a paraphrasing of the introduction hero to a book called Animal by fluke Howell
Here's the actual quote
I just wonder what it'd be like to be reincarnated in an animal numbers that it would endanger
Extinction
What would be its feelings towards the human species
He's a population explosion hits
Denied it somewhere to exist
I must confess that I'm tempted to ask for reincarnation as a particularly deadly virus
The book itself is just a compilation of famous people answering the question I am the title if I were an animal
What would I be
All right so this is kind of a its misleading use of this
Yeah burst of like explanation
It wasn't
Hey I got a question
What if
Songs
Green
I'm going to ask famous people we got a book
There is a cottage industry for that we all written by like
Publicist
You're right you're absolutely right
We got to go to Duke
This is a vaguely correct quote which is
A new a new high for Alex if you are up
To answer a banal question we will be writing a book
If I was a moose what kind of
The knowledge fight
That's damn
Surly moose
Aldous Huxley author of Brave New World
Shortly before his death
Best-selling book
New world
Implement
He didn't admit that this is about a half an hour long speech
I would have q-and-a session afterwards you can find it on YouTube there be a link on knowledge fight.com
Awesome speech Aldous Huxley
Very Charming order
Alex is going to
You play clip
That are selectively edited to make sound
Like you saying that there is an actual plan
Talking about but it's not if you wasn't the entire we don't have the time to listen
I recommend everyone Coronavirus
Quick question
The context
Within which
Admitted
Would make sense
Are you torturing all the time
To get him to admit this information that he has been fighting against
Admitting this whole time you giving a Charming speech
Oh well then he finally admitted killer
The guilty
Knowing I wrote this amazing best selling books
That was actually stealing the plans of the wealthy and now finally in this charming speech
I can say
I admit it
That was it
How do you does that tire sometimes
Strictly speaking
Brave New World in 1984 or both
Technically better
Is it May 1st
To program a little context
Hear about the the speech itself
He's giving
Speech to
Student lecture
Berkeley
Screengrab you have up
Hurting me
Twinkle looks like
Sorry to get off the screen
Thank you very much
Discussion
The fears about the form of 3 like what form authoritarianism
Could possibly take and of course
I have primary point is whether or not be Brave New World model or the 1984 model is more likely
And of course he's like
Oh yeah I wrote it about how like
Well when I wrote that
Came up with
The drug that wasn't real
Yellow course you would never want to have an authoritarian regime that's a boot on someone's face all the time
That's way less efficient than making
Someone loved their slavery
Exactly how you talked mostly about how
I was right or well was wrong for what he's talking about
Write a little professional dick
Yeah I think better than the
Right
All still just in the realm of like
He's could happen
I would actually probably stay the night
I think it's easier to get people fight again
You know
Okay how you're going from harder to break free of the all the
Then the 1984 dystopia
Is my conception of dystopia
Get out well then you would rather live
No I'd rather live in the 90
Before 1
Fight against
But you're probably going to die
I'd rather die than live in
Either of the
Well I think there's a hypothetical
Fighting against
That woodworking
How long to the bottom of Wyatt is
You feel this way about our two
Death would be preferable to
Drug
Desperate
That's where everyone's
Genetic
Woody
I don't know I mean let's talk about the major
Alright alright
Comparable
The parable of Brave New World
We said another parable
Maurice's
George
1980s for the British
The scientific
Will be probably
Eventually
1984 pet
They will be
Cousin
Nhu minutes
If you can
Forget people
The nature of the ultimate Revolution
We are in process of developing
He made a cut there
He didn't call
Okay
He made for me to let this whole Alex Jones
Things go time to start
Alex made a cut right
Before you said
To me what we talked about with the revolution
The reason he calls it the ultimate Revolution is
Because it's the revolution where we will be able to
Change ourselves opposed to external forces change
But
Now running through my
Paper is about
Brave New World in 1984 comparison
Papers recreationally white Neighbors
Then later on I will
They have cancer
There's a slight pettiness in this beach I'll be honest
What cuz the the resolution of 1980
4 is the main character
To love his
Play
So that
Kind of the
The
Description that Elvis's pudding
Towards
84 is
Look at how a 1980
All of these horrible things happen
And there's a result
The same what other something that the person has to endure
Right
Brave New World
All of the bad things that happen or something
Where is what the main characters in
During
Brave New World is nothing but
But pleasure like that kind of
So the difference there and if you're all this Huxley I I suppose that
His his main difference
Between the two of them would be
With all the text Lee is writing Brave New
New world
He believes that human beings are capable
A break
Through
Taking off of that
That's kind of like
Blind
Drugged out blissed-out love
And find something better in the future
Whereas Orwell is like
People
If you beat
Enough they're going to love you no matter what
His
Like I get why
All this and no I've left Alex
Way of the path Alex and Alex
Alice Alex
God this is there's nothing there I'm just take on it is that
King Junior High paper on the two of them in my head improv Isley
I'll just his take on 1984 is that it was a product of the time it was written
And that the authoritarians pollotarian
Beers of the time informed
His version of the scary state
Supposed to hit
Perversion
I didn't expect
But
It's not
Technique
Will enable
Exist
Presume
That people can be made
To enjoy state
Do you need
Decent standard
Your assignment
Except
7th Street
This was one of the things
I talked about you in Brave New World
The results would be either
How to make people
The literal end of the speech is him saying that
Now that we have all these capabilities
Great task
To make sure that
All this technology is used to make sure and get a dignity
Blah blah blah
Some sort of dystopia
All the ways in which you can be
It's our responsibility for you now knowing how to f*** people over with us
Have left a massive wave of Destruction behind
As if we
A stream of congressional investigations as uncovered more than
Between 1910 and 2000
I bet that number is
Individual
Or like
There's no Citation for this but I have no idea
2 gauge this
I would I would bet that number is accurate or low
But I would also bet I would also bet everything I own
The bulk of those
We're closer to 1910s
Then they were 2,000
That's a wide swath of time
Where medical ethics was very
What he's doing there is cheating
Time in Seattle
Yeah
With a point
Alex you're not allowed
You
Personal are you not allowed to talk
Mini
Still others died
Radiation experiments
Hundreds of hospitals in the US
Men women and children
And plutonium
Dosage levels
Call Elsie
Medical ethics was really f***** up
Pregnant vitamins
Uranium
And the death of them
Soldiers Sailors and Marines were used as guinea pig
Atomic and hydrogen bomb test
Patriotic American
Shiny Bisharp
Oh man
This is really f***** I mean it's f***** up this this part of our history
This also goes to like they didn't know what the effects
Be good you would hope but they didn't
US Army Health Ministry
3 million lira
Israel
Government-run Public School
The medical check-up
Mini of Wichita
More than 110,000 of the darker skin shoes
No
The maximum
All of them lost their hair
Alex is a f****** liar
Here's what he's talking about
So the only the offers for this are too late
To a documentary
Children
I've ever heard of that you're turning the ringworms at all
Which is used by Mizrahi Jews
Jews they were descended from the Middle East
As evidence of Injustice as they suffered immigrating to Israel in the night
They're almost definitely very severe issues
Is there integration in
Israelis
The film claims at least
100000 Mizrahi Jews were subjected to radiation level X beyond the maximum recommended dose
For treatment of ringworm
That's not good
However the documented dosage
Just given to Israeli children were similar to if not less than those about 2,000 children treated for
At New York University Hospital between 1940 and
So it's very different
That's not this
No it's a it's a misrepresentation
Is the thing that
Is the documents show
I feel comfortable in this territory
Is really weird I was doing great right up until you said
Actually the real interesting
Definitely more
Real
4-wheel parts investigative
First name to live with
Pretty good
Shipper ship Arts it slows off the tongue
This piece of history and found something pretty interesting
It turns out that the protocols that were used in treating immigrants for ringworm in Israel in the night
Which is what all of these things were
They were called the cause of the use of Zion
Alex was
I did I got that reference
I was just presenting there's like these kids were sent to their
At the school
Nurse
And got radiant not one that's not what even the documentary
Keysight
Is about
About
Fear-mongering documentary sites is like
So that it was about using radiation
Worm
Immigrant
In the 1950s
In Israel and that protocol was based on a campaign from 90
8:39
Among Jews and
Eastern Europe
That is mostly among Ashkenazi
In course of which
27000 Eastern European
Children were irradiated
In part to allow their families to emigrate
Ringworm
Grounds for occlusion
For immigrants to
States and elsewhere
The folks running the program
1950s
That previous campaign
Headbands
Successful
And wanted to offer the treatment to the Mizrahi
As well as others were coming into Israel
Does Israel
What's a large proportion
Who were irradiated in the initial campaign has been killed in the Holocaust
They didn't know they didn't know my god dammit
These kids died in the Holocaust
And didn't live to the point where they would have head and neck
Tumors like they would have had they have survived
Terrified
But it's heartbreaking
It was a possible they could have learned
From the previous campaign
It's not like that
Like the head and neck Schumer's happen to everybody
So some of the people who survived may have not
And even if they did they might have thought it was a side effect of living through whatever irate
Radiation or test
That we're done to them in the Holocaust
I don't know what it is about that story somehow
Even more heartbreaking
That x-ray treatment
Was incredibly infected effective at treating ringworm
And would not be it was never invented until 90
Most of the world in
Employed the radiation
Not knowing the damage they were doing
Generally speaking ringworms
Radioactive
Usher Yeah
If you would your brush your teeth and be like look at makes your teeth Club
For was much more prevalent among immigrant populations in the early 1900s
Because the means of transportation
Rotation were so cumbersome
They ended up traveling and being held in really cramped quarters and hygiene was terrible back then
As Israel was the
It's forming in 1948 that led to
Waves of immigration
And this increased radiation treatment
You can see the tragic end result Bad Medicine
I'm here but not a coordinated
Attack on anybody
We had tons of immigrants that came to Ellis Island
They didn't get a raise
Results because
You were found to have ringworm which they would check for
Looking at people
Scalpicin what have you ate
To wherever you came from
This is just a really tragic piece of like
One of the few non-racist
Yes terrible immigration history
It's just a tragic
Alex Jones
To try and score some sort of weird points
And it is not working
It's one of the few situations
Where it's same
Literally everybody
Was rooting
For good things to happen
Through
Just a bunch of oversights
Mistakes
The worst
God
The cover test
Chemical biological
Radiological population
More than 2,000 with deadly chemicals
Blake Personnel in local hospital
Is f***** up that was in 19
There's a lot of things that have happened
Since then but all of them are like
Who's better really
It's not
It's not like anything that is
Actually damaging it'll be affected if there were an attack
So f***** up I'm uncomfortable with it but
Currently testing pesticide
Highly toxic experimental drug
On tens of thousands of
Prisons Across the Nation
Force inmates to participate in experiment
Silverbacks graduate
Do it
Against the practice of eating mutton Bertrand Russell
So real quick understand Bertrand Russell
Coming back and bite me
Some prisoners
Absolutely
That's so true that it's true
The argument that he should be making
King really is more about
Well there's that
Racing class
Certainly
But also
UB about the system
Prism
We have where we have
Exploitative
Entire
Do the point where your body is inflamed
Anyway
This Bertrand Russell
Yeah that sucks
Let's get into it sucks
Let's go on down and
Sucking
Quoting Bertrand Russell
God dammit
Actually real
I know this I know this
I do Coke
Look like
He has a lot of very smart things
Load him
Because most of what he says wind up coming back to bite yourself in the ass
Liz Ramona book Iraq called the impact of science
Open Society
Russell is describing to come into the World War I used to have one world
He's clearly and very
Sickly talking negatively about how things
Could become a dystopia very quickly
If it's a solitary and state where to apply
Some context
A totalitarian government with government with scientific bent light do things
These are more scientific than the price
Rulers of Russia
Ever more inclined toward the sort of atrocities that I have in mind
Probably
Does selective breeding
Animation which adopts best practice will within a generation
Insecure great military advantage
Assistant one may surmise
Will be something like this
Except possibly in the governor
Governing aristocracy
The males
Females will be sterilized
The 30% of females will be expected to
Spent the years
From 18 to 40 and
In order to secure adequate
And father
As a rule artificial insemination will be preferred to the naturalness
Method
Gradually by selective breeding
Congenital differences between router
Until they become almost difference
A Revolt of the plebs become
As an organized insurrection
Cheap again
Practice of eating
There's a club
Such possibilities on
But I firmly believe that if the Nazis had won the last war and if in the end they required worlds
To see if they would before long
Have established
The system as I have been to just
Prevent these scientific
As I've been suggesting
To prevent be scientific or as democracy is necessary but not
Sufficient
There must also be that kind of respect for the individual that
Inspired the doctrine of the rights of
So the Flash Forward a little bit
There's a tendency which is inevitable unless consciously combated for organizations
Sekolah
And so true increase in size
Until ultimately almost all become Birds
A scientific oligarchy
Accordingly
Is bound to become what it is called what is called totalitarian
Expect
I only important form
A power will become a monopoly of the
This model is system has sufficient Merit
Be attractive to many people.
Are far greater than its
I think the evils that have grown up in the Soviet Russia will exist
In a greater or lesser degree wherever there is scientific government
Which is securely established and is not the
Depended on popular support
Afford to pay
55in concrete fact
When it is when does pretended that the state as
A good difference
Oh a good different from that of its citizens
What is really meant is that the good of the government
Or of the ruling class is more important than that of other people
Such a Buchan have no basis except arbitrary power
I think that's so long as powerful democracies exist
Democracy will in the long run be victorious over.
I allow myself
Immoderate optimism
Into the future
F*** you Alex
But also
Fuckyoubaker
Yeah yeah
You are so wrong on all of that all of it
Well
That's why I get comes down to practical application and how shity people are
Anyway
H g wagon 5.3
And hundreds of
Constantly
Look at those pants
Another word compound
Develop a survival zombie
But the authorities
Possible
This is the exact same book just the same context
Yeah Bertrand Russell
Yep
Over how many years ago
Bye 2007
U.s. population
Oran sometime
Prescription antidepressant
But in the case of foster children
Are forced to take a cocktail
Feel like that's not true
Prepositions
Testified before the State House Select Committee hearing on psychotropic drugs in foster care
Republic
When he said that foster children in Texas
I've been placed on psychiatric drugs
Because they were
Very very sick
The kids come from Bad gene pool
They don't have stable parents making good decisions
Besides the gene pools that lemon traumatized by abuse neglect and problems and then they've been traumatized
First of all the gene pool stuff
I've been stuck Alex
The end of that guy what he was talking about
So
That's such a
A guy
Raised
In a place where they say the n-word all the time trying to do his
Nice like
Look I'm just saying that the cultural pressures these it and then he just keeps using the n-word
He's never
Keep saying the n-word bungee like
Breakage paragraph
Heartbreak paragraphs at you
Always going to be bad I don't know who this is about the big
Bigger picture
Statistically speaking children in foster homes are more likely to have experienced severe trauma
Manufacturer in the definite separation
Experience from their family
More likely require pharmacological intervention
This is not an unexpected
It's like Institute
Literature on the mental health issues of Children and Youth
In foster care review children
Approximately 80%
I'm having psychological social and developmental delays at compared to children
The general population
Approximately 8
20%
The regularity and severity of emotional problems
Strongly related to their history of deprivation neglect and abuse
And the lack of security in
And any of their life
Rate that you see in children
After care Express
Pacific mental issue
Make some of this
Clearer
When you look at post-traumatic stress disorder
21.5%
And foster children as opposed to 4.5% in
In the general population
Panic disorder
11.4%
3.6
Anxiety disorder generally
9.4 vs 5.1
Drug dependence
3.6% versus
These are the sorts of things you would expect to see in elevated levels
Compared to the general population
Seeing as most people are not put into foster care unless there's something traumatic
It happened in their young child
Hood answer ptsb Spike
Correlation
What
Okay
Haha
Frequently change living situations would give anyone tremendous anxiety not knowing
We should be moving all around hold on
Here's where here's another study that I found those really interesting
A 2012 study by the national
Survey of Children's Health
Summit children living in non-parental care
Actually more likely to experience quote
Adverse family experiences
Childhood
They found that 70% of children living with two biological parents
The household experience
0 such events
Compare to 18.7
Children living in household
With zero Biolage
There's a difference of
30% compared to
281 point
3%
Children who experience
One such
So there's that
But the big difference comes
When you look at children who experience
Multiple event
Children living with two biological parents
Headache Point 9% incidence of experiencing
Compared to 29.9%
For children living with no biological
That's an almost three thousand percent
What do you separate out kids in foster care
So you exclude people who were living with their grandparents
Something like that
You find a 48.3% incident
A four or more adverse
Family events
80 young childhood
And a 15.7% of
Deckhand
This is
So statistically relevant
Yes such nonsense it's so cruel
To imagine look now we're just trying to drug these kids up
Just trying to drop these kids off now no one's taking care of them
But
Now
That's it
Yes
We know all of those
And yes they all make perfect
But have you considered blaming the only people who are trying to help
Yeah we could do that okay
Do you know what it is
Millennials millennials
Traumatic event like
Are you still cool with Lavoy finicum the guy who got shot
The Wildlife Preserve
When he had a child Farm
Raised
Money by having foster children
He wasn't taking great care of them
I imagine not all of them stay there for all that long you would probably a part of
The problem Alex is thrilled
To just ignore that
And point a finger at the
The aftermath
That's embarrassing Alex's plan
As far as I can understand
Is
Blame the victim
If you can't blame the victim
Play
Blame the people trying to help
Yes
Everything
And everything we reach Prosperity are we go
Very sorry about that
I had a friend
It makes it a very
Personal issue
Now your f***
Nailed it
The Western World Is Now implementing eugenics
Fetuses are now being priest
From Portland Oregon
London England
Protective Services
Criminal databases at Birth
Forcing them to attend
Probation hearings
It's not true at all
The source
This already has on this is one article out of the Guardian I believe
UK
Auto Telegraph
Really f***** up because it is
Very much
About
Doing visit
The children who are high-risk
Their parents are drug addicts
And the way I was reading it was like
We can do some therapeutic interventions
We're going to track them
Yeah that sucks
UK
I've no idea what he's talking about in Portland
Visits for two-year-olds
He has no backing for that no other
The overlords of scientific dictatorship
Are ruthlessly Prosecuting a war
Are most offensive
In December of 1974
The US
World population reduction
Central National Security issue
National Security studies
Chandelier regurgitation of the British Commission on population
King George the sixth of England
What's third world nation
There's nothing to do with what he's talking about the National Security study memorandum was
Written by Kissinger and
April 1974
President Nixon wanted
Effects of rising population
This study should focus on the international political and economic implications of population growth
The memo internally even shows that it's possible the end result
Quotes
If any
New initiatives by the US are needed to focus International tent
Problems
Correctly
Kissinger was like
Hey
You guys want to find out if we should do something
The most further goes on to edit
The study should take into account the presidents
Concerned the population policy is a human concern intimately related to the Dignity of the individual
And be objective of the United States
Is the work closely with others
Rather than to seek to impose our views on others
Whether or not we're actually reached by this this document itself is not evidence
Of what Alex is talking about
To do far more work
If you wants to prove his point nothing nefarious and nothing evil in this
The f****** a******
You are mad
I'm sorry but Kissinger offered us plan
It's a fun-filled mad at you
I don't know Kissinger recommended tumescent World Bank
Nations initiate aggressive population control program
Russian sterilization
Kissinger
Reducing population
Nixon White House
Also implement
Which was George Walker Bush
Bush advised China
The formulation
Forcibly sterilized
40%
Native American women on reservation
Nothing in this house citations at all
Now I believe
I believe it's possible to the natives
Directly said
Sterilize 40% of the Native American
Women Poppy
I believe that possible
Is anything beyond the pale I definitely want a citation though if you say that
George h.w.
So legitimate lead the only citation the offers in the bibliography is
The transcript of Nixon nominating Bush to be the ambassador
December of 19
70 nothing to do with China directly it has nothing to do with the natives
Wasn't into one child policy
Searching for any backup on this plane is burnt
All of the references are
Like Bush stepped out of the agency
Father's role in international investment banker
Who chaired the First International Bank of Houston
Then directed The First International Bank
Ventures Limited London
Drag boats
The largest bank in Texas
Bush travel bag
The family's permanent place
In the British Imperial financial and political in
Middle East Asia
Africa and Latin America
During this period China adopted the brutal eugenicist one child
So wild doing all kinds of other changes their policy in their life
Even the f****** claims that are made of these
Crazy blogs
That I tried to find a support that
Is a paragraph out of one of it
Is it
Got to do better than
You have to prove your claim
Do you know his documents been watched by more people tonight doesn't even work
Documentary about us watching his death
Little bit
Club of Rome
Advocated environmental it takes 6 hours to break out of nowhere on 9
What is a band
20 more minutes
You're just going to hear
The background
Isabel
Are we going to get back to the Texas pipeline or whatever we actually might
Are we going to get Debbie did they build the road
Spoiler alert so this is about
I don't want to get into it,
Artificial scarcity
Club around creative you waited almost
Yeah I was newly created
Not true
Rome was founded in 1968 by geologist
Time is Sheldon Hubbard's assessment was
Not really all that accurate
But available information Technologies were not what they are today
1836 on the underlying principle
Warning people about
Might not be materially in Korea
Well it may be true that tie we keep developing new ways to extract oil from
The new methods we develop all come with some form of diminishing returns
At this point most
Expert
Except
Discovered pretty much all of the available
Easily extractable oil on the plane
There's not much more to fight
From this point forward at the countdown till the liquid oil Reserves
Start running out it which point we'll have to take on some addition
No burdens along with the oil leaks
Some of that comes out before
Extraction of oil for
From Shale is more expensive because
Way less effective as an energy
Resource required to achieve
Similarly creating a lot of garbage
I is
Possible but it's incredibly
A barrel of oil cost Saudi Arabia proxy
Play $9
He's currently opposed to about $45 for the United Kingdom
Do the same using waste products
To do it cost about $80 a barrel
Beyond the much higher cost of these Alternatives there also
Much more difficult
Their expenses in the form of pollution
Along with the
Surprises
Have some of these
The fracking that's are required to access a lot of the more difficult oil Reserves
They were fighting now has been shown to increase Airborne emissions
Significant danger to contaminate
Adam call seismic activity
A further problem the complicates things
Is there today found in the past of the people are
The motivation to do so is pretty clear seeing is that it
Inflate their busy
There's no formal process
Place to audit reserves of
In January 9th of 2004 shell announced that it had overestimated its proven oil and gas
Gas reserves by 20%
Or fruits high 3.9 billion Barrel
At seems really high instances like this make it increasingly difficult to get an accurate estimate of how much
Easily available oil is really out there right now
And how close we are to having to rely on the diminishing returns
Right bottom line is
Club of Rome did not come up with
Further
People making definite predictions about people are kind of dumb
Generally rabideau
But
There will come a time
When we have
We it's all going to be downhill
It's just another day
Right because of
Good methods it'll be needed to
Extract the oil
It'll be too expensive
It we can't charge people that much for it no no by it those are
Argument
Simple
Prepare for that now
It's not worth it to prepare them
That's going to be a disaster
We can do it now
Z-CoiL might have been misleading
You already understand the problem and realize we're being dumb and not fixing it
Exactly
Aggressively pushing
Planetary government
Nations Global biodiversity
It states
Very clearly that the human population
For what current level
Billion
He just repeated the same thing from a different angle he's wide angle
Calendar
Subsequently
This is not
The idea of a race specific bioweapon comes from the 1942 Robert
The sixth column
DNA sequences
Theoretically possible
Which is kind of scary
Desiree specific bioweapon
There's a paper called the Sunday Times
I posted an article in November of 1998
But this is likely to complete misreading
Fiction
In the aftermath of the release of the article
Vulcan
The Sunday Times
Planned a follow-up article but most likely due to
Embarrassing backlash never wrote part 2
I also the articles of the authors of the article
Never have speaking about it spoken about it publicly
So the article
That tie was the source for the coverage there's coverage on like wired
Inform report
Of this
That that's where Alex gets this idea those are the two authors from the Sunday time
Never spoken about this ever again
The Forum report and rent
Dot-com reported that they sold the
Or it came from South Africa
As an apartheid weapon
It's all a lot of bulshit
God dammit
There's no there's no support for this anywhere in any credible
What what what is there that because
No it's not a thing
Theoretical
Just like there's no better there's no better proof of like well there's no difference in races or anything like
Here's the best way to prove
That there's no difference between white or black or Asian
Like that train build a bomb just to kill one of
People trying
I know and they're not suggest that there's no real genetic difference they would have
Already done
Aunt f****** Sabrina
Publix
Useful
Now I will say that I
I want to change the channel
This is
Incredibly taken
Out of town
The idea of a Dick Cheney
You saying that
I don't want to I don't want to
Ever I'll just
He's talking about
Change in the future
Using drones
Technology
She's going to advance
Here's the actual
Advanced forms of biological warfare that can Target specific genotype
Transform biological warfare from The Realm of Terror
Three political useful tool
This is this is merely a glimpse of
Possibilities
Processor
The transformation not
Precise
Prediction
So what are you saying is that along the way
As these things that we
Don't necessarily want evolve into
The Warfare may start using
Biological warfare as a political tool
Whereas before it was just in the realm of terrorism
Context
Will eventually be the
People running come
He's not
He's not saying that like
That's a very
Infection but that's unfair
Well
Why would they want to reduce the human population
Thereafter power
The overlords of the New World Order
Are now aggressively pushing
For a worldwide
One child policy.
They're not
It's pretty simple
I have a really long explanation would look at what
Ended its one-child policy
Right
If
Yours
And you see that
What possible way could you be like that's a great idea
No way that that's possible I was going to skip past this but I'm going to read anyway cuz you need a little Leo zagami
Senior Life
It's a one-to-one
We tried an experiment
Here's how the experiment worked out
It didn't work let's not do it what kind of in
Even if you're imagining an enemy
That would do that
Leo zagami writes in his book confessions of an Illuminati the time of Revenue
Tribulation leading up to 2020
His information perhaps not surprisingly a source to an article written by Paul Joseph Watson on Infowars
Brooke
His assertion that Bill Gates and George Soros and all The Usual Suspects are trying to kill off everybody is immediately followed by this
Quote
Is a trendsetter among the false philanthropic Monsters of the elite
From ancient times to appease the gods of the astral plane they offered animal and sometimes even human sacrifices
As I often heard personally during my time in the sects within the networks of the Illuminati
From this point of view the plan to eliminate to limit birth
And forced abortions certainly has a magical significance to the astral plane
Hey Gibby considered as a human sacrifice when done intentionally
At the end of March 2015 a drone pilot made a shocking discovery
I was flying my Quadcopter over the Georgia Guidestones
And found these crazies stains that look like blood
At the top
Are the Georgia Guidestones
These are
Cited sources
The Drone pilot to I was
That look like one who works for phenomenal place.com
Very intriguing
Because you don't see any stains from the ground at all these Stones look completely normal for
From the ground up
Think of it but it does look like blood
So I guess what he's suggesting is that they're sacrificing people or animals on top
This is the sort of place where you get this
Rhetoric have one child policy
Again
Leo zagami put this in his book
Citing Paul Joseph Watson and then immediately got into
So there we are
The Shining
Only later
They imprisoned.
Are being made
England in Europe
I want to promise you this
The end of this is very
Having large families
Frowned upon
Estimator in the same way
Gordon Summers new corporate
I think tank in the UK says
Too many kids
What's Megan Planet worse
Panthers
I taking long trips overseas
Families in our rich country shouldn't have more than two kids
Place to get more than 1 billion
For the United Nation
Implementation of population reduction policy Planet why
Quote
Isle of Ted Turner's quotes
I love him
Can we get a whole can we get ahold
Can we get a ramble
This quote right here a total world population of 252
5% reduction
Compressor be ideal
Discarded as being from an interview in Audubon
Beef in that magazine
The actual quote from the magazine from November 1991 was dug up
Panda it is screenshotted online
We got to do it all together that's going to do away with the word foreign
We've got to think of each other as Neighbors
Instead of word foreign we need to use international
Whether we like it or not we're going to swim together or sink
Together we all five billion of us here on this little Earth swimming around in space
There's too many of us
And most of us are living in correct
If we had a much smaller population over time we could
Heaven
Where we only had one child and maybe over 300 400 years we could cut back to 250
250 300 million people
We can replant or cities
Where there's a Central Area you could walk or ride your bike to work so you don't have to drive 30 miles to work like do in LA
Bets
That's where we stopped being into this is a quote it's your Rambler
Traffic in LA
So logout
300 400 years
The people just had less kids you would get the number down
Unacceptable not talked about
Whatever we would actually work out pretty well in terms of the amount of people who just died ever
Everyday
Accident
No you wouldn't you just have to wait a long
People have an epic where you just have left
He's right about like the numbers
And stuff like that
A lot of stuff
He's crazy
Like a complete
Sweet Nut Job WCW
All you need to know about it
The billionaire
Duke Phillip Phillips
Which is the best which is the best reasoning for why you shouldn't add him and your documentary if
The globalist did exist
And it was all these billionaires
They would allow Ted Turner anywhere Focus
Like legitimately is the world's largest owner of bison
Largely because he has a restaurant that serves bison and doesn't want other people to be able to have us
Mary conservation
Either weird dude
Source this quote but I remember it from an episode of
Jordan Jesse go
Yeah Jesse Thorn was talking about
Seeing him speak at a conference
He's like that he was asked about how he'd been married a bunch of
He's like
You know what
Say what you want
I didn't do anything with any kids
That is why you do not laugh
No absolutely not so he gave an interview to fortune in the 2013 that included the following
Say what you want
What does that mean
So you give this interview to fortune in 2030
What's your prescription for how to manage population that doesn't manage the environment
Well we need that list
Needs to be volunteer
There's been tremendous progress
In 1950 not one single country has a stable population
They're all growing all 200 country
Now I think forty or so countries have negative or stable population
Japan is losing population rapidly
And quite a few other countries are too
The problem is at the rate that it's going losing out on the population
In order to have a really healthy long-term future we need to
Two and a half billion
Compared to
Reply reply
We've got seven seven and a half billion right now that's two and a half that two and a half billion goal came from Paul are like
Who wrote population bomb 50 years of
The good news is that it's able he's around the world choose to have one child starting right away
We move back toward the two and a half billion without any abortions
Population
Control all we need to do is use Family Planning
Look I had five children okay but when I had those five children 50 years ago the world population
The world population was 3 billion
Less than half of what it is today
I don't know anyway
Uno
Oldest idea of him being a aunt
Depopulation
Reducing the population but only through voluntary mean
At again
Because if
You get the kind of answer of
I didn't do anything with any kids
Come at me
Say something like that and I was going to be like well I didn't kill anybody
Like what like attributed to Ted Turner and Ted Turner I'll be like I probably
He's actually into
Activity population in one child policy being enforced
Mostly,
Songs from an article to call Jose
Squats in Rotonda
This website called active
Sources back to an article in the globe
We're at Ted Turner Spokane
National Center for Atmos
Spheric research
Potato
Reflect that
There is no real Citation for everything only
Writer says
As if we're going to be here as a species
5000 years from now we're not going to do with 7 billion
Anyway
We're going to do with other far more far less
I imagine far more comfortable
Population fund
Other population reduction
Almost exclusive
The population control
Here's a spot about Bill and Melinda Gates
They have a website they have all of their taxes
Information on it that's publicly-accessible all of their tax return
You can find everything that they've ever done everything they contributed
Every president acting like
For full Transparency International a transparency initiative Alex is totally wrong
Unless you think literally everything counts as population
Control freaks
Between 2009 and 20
50 - 5.6 billion dollars to infection
Disease Control programs population
Digital 1.4 billion to combat malaria
Love that
1.3 billion towards programs
STD and AIDS prevention
11 billion towards tuberculosis release
Coming in at number five doesn't need relief
Believe that to be
Coming in at number five on their giving
Productive
That's their fifth Sia
Giving thing
At all
Which isn't really
Listening population
Control really
900 million
Reproductive Health Care
End up with about 1 points
6 billion quarts
375ml
Towards
Amongst so many f****** other causes
221 billion dollars in Alaska
6 years they've given
How much
Has Alex given
What I would be
Mike Mike
How much would it take
For Alex
Like legit
You're giving out billions of dollars
Alex
How much does it cost to get you to go away you know it would be an awesome
And be like
I will give you
10 billion dollars
To shut the fuk up
And record the call
Sao Op
And maybe like
No way
Now you've talked him out your release the tape
No no
I think I think you would have to follow through
Know if you reveal that he wanted to go for it and you're pumping and
Like that
Because if I'm out since whatever work like you
If we had Bill Gates money
The way to go
Because if you if you come to Alex I'll give you a
Say yes
He's got to
10 billion
Keep talking
Nothing
You'll never buy me
You'll never find
Billy
Now I do not interested
I took you down by 1000%
No you haven't really cuz if you have the tape
Matter if you follow through all that matters is getting it from your end
Cuz he's never going to say yes until he has the money
The preliminary negotiations are going to be like I will give you 10 million dollars through shot
I will say yes when I do have money enough though
Well let's get back
The controlled corporate press cynically report
To help
Third-world children
What is the world's most generous philanthropist
When their friend
Population reduction
Warren Buffett
37 Billie
Defending Army
Population control
The headline says that he gave 37 billion
Charity
Play that at all
There's no ref
No citation
Forgiving at the population
What's what's on license
Which
We all know.
Yeah but just all population
Does he currently only has
39 billion dollars
So he gave $37 to charity in 2006
Maybe who knows
The Susan Thompson Buffett Foundation donated
The organization
Dedicated to contraception
Women's Health
Specifically the development
Accessibility of inter uterine device
UD
According to Bloomberg
In 2013 the foundation gave away nearly half a billion dollars to organization
Supporting reproductive
Really cool about the
They did it all
For the nookie
Come on
That's a reference
I got 75
So they did it secret
I went through a bunch of different companies didn't want to bring it back to
Necessarily
Funding all this
Massive Research into
The people would be f*****
Yeah and there was an article on Jezebel even though
Like if you have an IUD
Warren Buffett
The lot of the funding for the development of them
Was I able to be
Happened because of his funding
Judith disarno former director of domestic programs
Berkshire Hathaway
Lawrence
Fun said for economic
He thinks that unless women can
Control their fertility and that it's basically their rights
Control their fertility
Are you sore ear sort of wasting more than half of the brain power the United
Includes the contraception program in Colorado
Which provided women with free iuds and resulted in a
40%
Declining birth rates
Teen Mom
And a forty two percent
Santa Claus
Abortions over the course of
Five f****** gears the New York Times reported without the f****** and realizing
So a lot of these initiatives
Incredibly effective rate of abortion
Pull a f****** utilitarian argument
Well then actually in arguments from all of your racism and bigotry in your life
Oh yeah well women are equal in
If you want to pull some sort of like well women
Get rid of that b*******
If you want
To make the most
If you want to be the most productive
Recognize that you're wasting a half of a woman's light for whatever it is
Or your f****** destroying all of this s***
Just a petty
Dumb sexist misogynist and then you finally made his unfortunately
Post-capitalist
Know this guy's evil because he hates women
What's your f****** stupid
I'm still mad.
I've been dealing with some sort of weird roller coaster up and down anger ride
From Bianca
Didn't come through the audio it actually much better
There's only 10 or 20% of us
Dr. Eric Pianka
The dubious quote
Receiving an award from the Texas Academy of Science
The world
It's too slow
Because it would kill 90% of the world population quickly
Traverse
His graduate students
Most frightening
Local newspaper
Bianca sustained standing ovation
Groves
So here's what I want to say about Eric
Pianca
Based on what
He called
For the extermination
I think you might've actually but I think he's one of these
I honestly take you and Eric Pianka probably have a lot in common because I think that there is a common noun
Terms of like behind that are inflammatory in order to sort of provoke
I think that's kind of his style
Cuz I looked into him bed scene like some of the position
He's taken
Watch some of the interviews that
I don't know I'm not sure isn't spoken on that list.
Kind of like an a****** but also like my professors like heaven my time to colleges
He's trying to provoke people into critical thinking
Right typically answer
He ends up getting trotted out on shows like Tucker Carlson and had him on and stuff like that
Back to life throws quotes in his face and be like
You're not really that's not really what I said
Destroy Humanity
Well
Whatever
This isn't going to work
I bet he looks like that giant bearded everyone's like the crazy guy
IHOP
For them
To want to do that with
The right-wing would totally invite me on because they be like all he's going to say some s*** about white genocide
You goddamn right I'm going to say some s*** about score
Kill all white people
You I'm just going to if I was in studio
High Point to everybody in there and then me and then I'd kill myself
The new Lauren Duca Tucker Carlson
From the transcript of the 1999 speech that
Susan reference
To hear some of the
That I was able to find
But here's what's going to happen
Population collapse is there's going to be a lot fewer of us
Who's going to be diminished
Solutions going to go down which will be good
But that is not going to be much to recover from
Our descendants are going to curse us for the party we took
The party we had that I recommend Richard heinberg book
The party's over oil war in the state of industrial society
This man is thought about these things deeply
The end of oil is good to but it's not anywhere as good as the party's over
Why is people for a long time
John Stuart Mill in 1858 took issue with the whole business of grow grow grow
And he said he thought stationary cyst
Made sense
Stable system
Where you don't have bubbles that are going to burst and you're going to go Bank
He said he didn't think people had to elbows
The top two fight struggle with each other to
Just to get resource
But if we could just live in a stable world
Continue to grow and work based on this grow grow grow
Then we could work on The Art of Living become better
Being foreign
And these are some of the things that John alametos that is in the end of limits
To grow
And this is the end
In the sixties when I started
Starting ecology there was a lot of sand
At the top of the hourglass
Remind short stint of 4050 years as an ecologist
There's not much time left that you can get on an airplane go to Madagascar and study something while you can
Thank you
That's great
I like this guy
I like this guy I think he's wrong about John Stuart Mill but I like those guys kind of an extreme
Speaker in terms of bikes
Sensationalism
I think he says these things
Provoca intellectual conversation in a wreck
He's also a geology
Just threw his concern
So cute he's kind of worried about the
Sister more than he is about Humanity
F*** your feelings your feelings
F*** your feelings bro
Jersey Shore Ben Shapiro
For the day tomorrow
You know we will jump right back in the after
Jordan
Spiritual kin
Dr. Eric Pianka
Not entirely sure if that's fully track
But
I will be back tomorrow with
Conclusion
To the end the game coverage where we have completely lost interest in doing this for
Spoiler alerts for tomorrow we get into climate change
A little bit about that
Super fun stuff so I'll check out that will be back with that
Tomorrow
But in the meantime
Go to knowledge fight, that is our website
We also are on Twitter underscore fight
We're on Facebook
You can check us out there
Also we just have a we just opened up a new Facebook
We're people can get together and have messages and maybe I don't know Workshop a meme
Whenever people do
I have no idea anyway it's good place to have some conversations with like-minded policy wonk
If you'd like to go over there and join up the name of the group is going to
Go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
If you go I just searched for that you can find it request to join and we'll collect
To be a member
Also we're on our scribe download past episodes
Leave us a review all those sorts of things
Very helpful do appreciate it
But I guess other than that
This is exhausting and if you all have stuck around for all of this
End game coverage we appreciate it and it will be done after tomorrow
So
Thanks again and we'll catch you on the flip side
Babe
Alex