Everybody welcome back to knowledge fight I'm the voice you will hear shortly
Is my co-host into your friend
This is our final AR-15 final installment
In our ongoing coverage of Alex Jones is very very stupid
Sophomoric
Amateurish
You come up with a number of other
Not very complimentary words to describe documentary
This is the end this is the final chunk
You may note that at this point Jordan and I are a little buzzed
A little
Fed up with the b*******
There's another there's an endurance aspect that comes to into this when you're 7 hours into stopping and starting a
Very bad documentary to point out
Also this isn't true
It gets it weighs on you and you may sense that a little bit here in this final installment
But not a good stuff to look forward to there's a couple of my favorite thing certainly
How's that we run into and
The final shot of this documentary
Is in hindsight
Incredibly funny piece of History
Or Alex Jones
I want I want to give it away
Anyway I hope you guys enjoyed this
Really
Conclusion
To our coverage of Alex Jones
The game
Oh oh so I'm not going to come back at the end of the episode because the you know the episode has a natural end
I don't know if we give any plugs at the end so I can know you can check us out at knowledge plate.com knowledge underscore fight on Twitter
We're on Facebook
You can find us we have a special private group called go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
To conjoin up and hang out and
And I'll just mix it up with the other policy walks out there it's on Facebook
We're on iTunes so much
Thanks to everyone who made this possible
And I apologize that there's still two more hours left to this
Alright
Enjoy
Holding
Alex
So cute
He's kind of worried about the ecosystem
The more than he is about Humanity
F*** your feeling feeling
F*** your feelings bro
Jersey Shore Ben Shapiro
We're on our way
Just trying to make him
Immigration
Because they have a police car.
Probably said it but who gives
Much of its Nazi baggage
As usual
Most people don't
Like you'd want to breathe clean air
Have a good one
And parlay it
The support
Global policy
Let's further destabilize the third world
Okay
He
Flashes up on screen here
The Sierra Club and the nature cat
Conservancy
Phony conservation
Groups of the largest private landowners in the world
Funny
The owner of Charter Communications
Coming in at number 1
Germs
The private landowners
In the United States
That's the number one is the guy from Charter
Charter Communications
Like I needed another reason to want the guy from
My boy 1 billion Acres
The 90s
Still Turner these conservation groups that are listed aren't even in the top hundred of the private
Who was all billionaires
1.9 billion Acres of
Usable land
Lower 48
Of that 139 million of those acres are considered to be
Developed Urban or rural residential
349 million acres are
747 million Acres Ark
Consider forests
788 million are range or pasture land
Where animals can graze
Alex plates an article gear that asserts that nature conservation Conservancy there
Million preserve Acres announced
2 million
But that does not
Tell the whole story
For instance
15.5 / 15500 of the Acres that they own
Are part of Palmyra atoll a series of acres and Lagoon
1000 miles south
Hawaii
Don't really seem like he's talking about in terms of
Controlling America
You own something out in the water
William reiff land
Yeah I would want to control that at all
It doesn't really seem like what he's talkin about
Bunches
The bought this thing called
100 thousands of Acres that they own
Finish up the land was required for the Great Sand Dunes National Park
Plus they have offices
30 different countries
So there's no reason
Think of it all
Conserve
Are in the United
States
What's really is
Are in the job of
Conserving
Yeah that's kind of what they do I'm sorry I think I said that John Malone and Ted Turner
Billions you did the million
I apologize to catch myself there
Up to when you look at those
Still way too much
Scarier
How do you know how big
Response to Eddie
How big is that
Can you take it outside of America and go to private landowners in the world
It becomes a really interesting because Alex is even more
The largest
Kevin King Abdullah
He comes in at number two with 547 million acre
Number one
The Queen of England come-and-get-it 6.6 billion Acres Way far above everybody else
Because the monarch of England retained the royal title over the entire British Commonwealth
Sochi technically own
The entirety of all British lamb
Okay it's the same thing with talk about Edward the 8th
Technically being the king of the Roman British Church
Britain
I get where I get what you put up with his formalities
You got to get her name off that s***
Drop it off
Don't leave it we all know that now but there's
People don't get her name off the lease
What if she's late on her bills
The pope is number 3 because you technically owns all land owned by the Catholic Church + Vatican City
About 177 million Acres worldwide
King
Different countries
I really think about like a authoritarian countries like Russia and China technically the heads of state
All of the land
Rights are all the stuff these people like so when you start to look at it
Nothing
What you really see when you start to talk
About
How much land these individual
People own
And how silly it is for them
You start to realize well
People can't really own land
It's like who owns land
Like what are you doing with it
In Russia
You are all of Russia
Right
Peoples
What are you doing with it
People playing pool
The real England take the Queen off the lease
Do it
Libra on the money
She's cute
That can't be
Population
True
U.s. military dumps millions of gallons of nerve gas
On the east coast of the US
They don't say a word
Thousands of companies
Should I worry about chimeras animal
How do we get to chimeras we were women allowed to vote he's pissed off that these fake cancer
Service design
Conservation groups
I'm mad and there is being released into the wild
He had legitimately no Citation for Hannah
Chimeras being released into the wild
Even for our show
With our history
To go from a living hold on let me start it again
This is about Bilderberg
Very got to do about Texas roads
No it's
No cuz first it was about World War II
But I guess up
Railroad
I'll enroll in China population control
And then I got mad
Spider-Girl
AR
I get the sense within which Theory
But I felt like
We spent the good first hour and 25 minutes on the first two
Bilderberg
Creepy roads
Don't worry and now
Mirror
We're heading around the final Corner we're still close to home
But yeah
Being released into the wild true
Turn mic that you can buy
Something I want to tell you something Jordan
He's going to leave
Cheesecake
Do you ever see likes to come together in the end of Comedy Central
What is this guy talking about
This guy is brilliant altogether
That's what he's about to
He's not going to do that
Because I've seen other people try to do that
Far more often
The end of this
Is so f****** funny
I keep building it up it's going to be a disappointment
But I love the end of
This documentary
Speed at which we're going we're going
See that ended
About 2 weeks
Large environmental organizations
The corporate
Of the planet
Intensify
Hysteria
Hell yeah organizing principle
As the planets new religion
First of all the planets
Nature is
Not a new real
Anyway
Goes back probably
Probably is the oldest
So old
Also I'll never forget how disappointed I was when
Watching this Live Earth cons
The middle of Athens
I like I just got done rocking to somebody I don't know who it was
UB40
Comes out
What
UB40
Alright
When Metallica came out
Forgot to mention this immediately followed by
Wizard
S*** the ones you did I'm blue Eiffel 65
BMO
Metallica came out in James Hetfield
Lead singer
Comes out
Cuz it went to another country
A bunch of country
E-40 did like
3 songs
There's too many for UB40
The red red wine that might be it right
Don't know if this is the order of it but then the other thing I remember is Metallica
Metallica gets on
Before they can even play a note
For do that song
Make some noise
Paw Patrol
So like
Your heart's in the right place at failed so fake Rebellion
Limited
Oh I don't even
AFI
That's all
Anyway
A Fire Inside
Emoji
I think so I don't know
They claim
What's killing the Earth
Adult
Countries across the world
Marc's
And raising taxes on
Electricity
It is a scientific fact
But the shot
Scientific fact
Large
Consensus that it's greenhouse gases
Believe
That the car going on in that
All of it is a hoax
Is because he really miss understands
Two emails got hacked
From the climate research
And they were all taking everybody
It was super taken out of
Also I mean
Do you want to talk about that a little bit so I don't have to read this paragraph
Has been reading f****** paragraphs at you and I feel very guilty
Know if I remember it cuz it cuz I remember my my dad was
My dad my older brother were all up in this
If you read the climate emails it actually shows
The whole time that we were actually to Cooling.
And all these grafter bullshittin
And then of course 6 months later ever
Nobody forgets about it until you start
Talk about it
Climate
He's always been
The same
They took a bunch of
Text messages with the
Hey
Trump's a f****** lunatic in the like
It's okay to say what is true
Via the big email
The big email jerks
It was an email from the
The climate Research Unit head Phil Jones
Hide the decline
Private Client became
Buzzword
As if this climate scientists were flippantly talkin
Who's co-workers about cheating data
The reality is what he's talking about
Was a reference
Just something that is well-known part of
In scientific
The tree-ring Divergence prob
As it turns out for a long ways
Where we have data for it
Tree-ring
Run
Consistent path
With observable temp
However
And the data is gathered from
Does not match
The documented temperature
That we know are the case
From time
Those tree-ring Sam
So
We're not entirely sure
Why that's okay
Phil was discussing using Mike's nature
In order to present the data
Completely consist
With scientific
Cisco ethical practices
Scientists are not sure
Reservable temp
It's due to be discovered
Aspheric
Variable that is probably in play
But was not
Before 1950
Other scientists speculate that it could be due to
The sensitivity
And maybe a byproduct of
Seasonality that we are experiencing
Increased levels of aerosol
Send the air that are also causing global dimming
Could also
It could be vaccine
Absolutely
So did the reality is
Coax
Invested about 50 million dollars over the last 50 years to spread
So doubt about
And that's not even including what ExxonMobil is
The carbon freeze sound at nine out of 10 of the most prolific writers were climbing
Mobile
Including I don't know
Yeah
Directly
And I don't seems like they should have to
Declare that flows
Rochelle company
Yeah exactly
He's not one of the top 10
Alex's buddy Lord monckton who's his climate change
Expert absolutely
ExxonMobil
Here's the chief policy adviser for the science and
Policy and
Think Bank operated by frontiers of
Foundation
Four years were available from 2,000
1 million
337 thousand
For what
Probably
Also
Crazy Loom
Justice
They're just all about
Sprites being supported
ExxonMobil
The science
Supported
Inhabit
Bulshit
The signs of made-up bulshit
Is deported
Debatable
Is of course supported
It seems crazy
Also
The Sun
The sun being the
Driver climate change
Very much
It's very much addressed by climate scientist
It's going to look into any of it
That's why you can't
Psych
10000 books about the thermal output
Call Warren
Scientific facts
Are the British
We spoke
When I called Rothschild
He just laughs
Thinking Leon
Population
The globe
How did
This is his big gotcha from the energy
Is good personals
Global warming
Ablution base tax system
Principal
I think he said the planets in the wrong order not you say
F*** you your money changing and set up the clip wrong
Friends and we know
We know what happens which is what David Rockefeller that David roster
Rothschild
Give the order of the planets
You and I know that there's no that you made a mistake
Alex set this up
You're like oh he's going to play the clip
We have to deal with this bulshit it was an obvious Miss baking
If I were Fallon I'd be like
Play the clip
You cute up the wrong quit baby
Still doesn't seem like a mistake it seems like what he
He's a nut
It hurts me
It's like that seems like such an easy slam dunk
You set the clip Up
We move on five minutes down the road we all get to have a good time.
The rest of the time no one has to know I got jebaited
Classic Connect the beginning of the documentary to the end he was talking 82 Medics about Nathan
Rothschild the beginning
So now he's going to talk to his ancestor if they accept Medicare
Why is the I got your morning
If you don't hit that home instead it just you being a dick
To multiple Generations
Of everybody I think you might actually play
Rothschild later it's inexcusable
I think she does play it
I recall he does but I'm just weirded out
And he even gets the orders
The planets round
Jirachi
Unbelievable
Level of mistakes that were made in editing
AR
Outrageous goddamnit sperms of fact checking in terms of the bibliography
Terms of just like
If I were the guy who is task
But having to like
Put this together
It's two and a half hours long or so
Time to put together all the video in the audio
It would be like
It's taking us 10 hours just to watch it
We're going to get through this
We're causing it mainly
Vast majority of it
The consequences are bad
And will be
We Act
Polar ice caps
Faster than ours
Now I know where is David
Rothschild
My friend
Attacks is the best way
Cap-and-trade can also do it
If there were
Carbon-based tax
Would there be a need for
Economy-wide
Cap-and-trade
They are not either or
We can do both I am in favor
Both
I want to talk a little bit about Al Gore and his
Carbon tax
Connection but Alex Jones lies about a lot
Cuz I actually
Incredibly fast
The stuff is
Amazing
How much Alex
Texas lying about
All of it
Especially outdoor
So knowing his personal
Hatred of Al Gore
I believe he would lie to I read
I read this one
Blog
Deserve a citation
Asian but they're like
Climate change
Coasting along strictly on the Charisma of algor
Stereotypical
Vici
Every like what I didn't host SNL and every skit was just about how boring he was
He's just been portrayed on.snl is the most
Boring guy forever
Inflated things
I want talk about Carpenter
Just going to give you a rat
Example
So
This year
Singapore is about to implement
Right and they've lost property
Text effects
At all
This this write-up about it and here's a car
The tax will affect 3240 large emitters
Define disposed admit 25,000 tonnes of greenhouse gases
Is annually
The government is looking at charging between
And $20 per ton of greenhouse gases
The goal is to incentivize
And create a Level Playing Field
Field for the development of
Stainable energy sources
They're being held down by being left out of large subsidies offered
Tacoland
Fuel industry
Baby look at that it's 32
240 business
Is there only going
Affected by
In Singapore
Just be a number
Businesses
Thousand
In America that would be a
The reality is that
The bunch of
Countries have imposed
Carbon tax
Susan the past
Have they reduced
Because you get there
Based on what I know
If you implement a carbon tax
Any kind
The entirety of the world will collapse so tell me Dan that that has happened
Many times over
Impose one in 2013 Ireland
In 1990s country Sun near immediate results
Decrease CO2 emissions
With minimal impact on the economy and no energy outages
Australia
Cassie of carbon taxation
They enacted a carbon tax and
12 in 2014
The weirdness in the other government
Things got weird and
It was not the voice of the people being heard it was
2014 till further
Strongly urge
Graphs of emissions from the time. Between
What you see is
Consistently
From July 2012 to July
Dropping over
Team million ton
Visions drop
Very precipitous
Right
Immediately after the repeal in July 2014
Trend turns around
In 5 months
Pentagon backup app rocks
85 million
So
There is a very clear-cut example of
This works
Is effective in terms of cutting down a mission
Using the examples of countries that have
Race car
You can't relist
Weekly claim that they don't work to reduce
The only argument you can make
Go out there that's also true and Australia is involved
Wade and there's not going to be as many
Bulshit Dan
Where's the science the water water Bertrand
So you can really make is it emissions don't affect climate
Reply I'm just a thoroughly address
The case money is somehow being
Wendell B
Climatech
That's the only thing that you can possibly do
The ladder
Is a matter of
Really
If that's the case then
That's not really a climate changes that's a government corruption issue
Seems like you should get rid of those people
Yeah so
This idea that people with these fat cats
The New World Order
It's interesting because
There's these people who are really strong
Proponents pushing for
For the carbon tax
The carbon tax
They include this
As a integral part of their proposal
Quote
To avoid kill whitey
That's in there that slower
To avoid burning low and moderate-income household
Periodic prorated
Dividends
Or dedicated to reducing the tax burden of regressive tax
Such as the federal payroll tax
And state sales tax
Depending on whether the tax
Is imposed on the federal or state level
There is a precedent for this sort of thing like the Alaska Permanent Fund
For the state of Alaska send every citizen to check for the same amount as payment for the earnings
Of Investments made from the state's northslope oil royalty
Canada announced carbon pricing
In Florissant
And this is what the plan
Included
British Columbia system is designed to be Revenue neutral
Meaning of the government will take
No extra money for
And instead returned it
Tax credit
Alberta sister
Some of the costs
To lower-income can
Consumers in the form of
Small business
Taxes have been reduced
From 3% of 2
Offset coffee
So a lot of the money
That is being brought by climate carbon taxes
In countries that are using it
Is legitimately being funneled directly back
Into the people
You are paying for energy
Now
Let me tell you why
That is
And why it will never work
Do you know what is more likely to work here
I hesitate to answer
Is if the government implemented a carbon tax
Said we're using it to give back to rich people and then
Ended the, however one is expected to being along with it
America
Go crazy
We are more comfortable with you if you were like
Okay so
On Exxon Mobil
That
All of the proceeds of which
Will go to subsidize exxonmobil's
New home
Which we have
Hired exhibit
You don't like it
You know you guys are going
Feel weird about any news
Stop screaming at me about the estate tax I wish I hadn't brought that up
I apologize be state tax only affects that I really I should have stopped should not talk about this conversation
Alright you making a point
Hold on
Calm down
The money waste
Your children
Back to you because you need it and your children need it
We just
Your children are dying because of the
People not only are we not taking money away from them
We're just taking away the subset
We already get them
Do you know what's crazy we don't even need to enact attack
That's because right now you are paying
For those Rich oil company
To murder your children
So what we're going to do
Going to make that better
I get what you're saying but I completely lost track of
The role-play I don't know what to do
I was going to ask for a binky
This one is going to do
Is except I want
Motorworks
For the attempted
-5 points for the break-even
This is a carbon tax that will be applied to the business
But there's no law that
Affect them
Consumers which I think is really what should be done
Instead of charging everybody more the money
That's collected from the text
Redistributed to the people have to pay more for
What is
That if you
On mobile are those
They're just going to then pass that text
Onto you
Tire prices that's what I just said
That's what I'm talking about
And I say f*** that there should be something plays that says you can't
How would you not do
Eat the Pack b**** that's what I would say
Eat the text
Either tax bet you can't pass it along that seems like it seems like
Should be able to happen because otherwise how because otherwise there's no way for the government or
Society
Restrained
Penalty
Are there
Alright
Products are a little more expensive everyone's going to buy them anyway they have
Right but that that is the
The point of it though is that if you are going to suck
Well yeah capitalism sucks but if you are going to do that
That if you are going
You text like an Exxon
You have to go to remove the oil subsidy
In the first place
So what you're really doing is making
Making it so expensive
Those
That they are
That you are fostering a market chain
For somebody to do something
Like what's the highest growing
Creator knows Alternative Energy
Give the subject take all the oil and gas subsidies away from Exxon and those guys to
Today
Give it to Alternative Energy
You want me to Carpenter
You will go away on their own because it turns out
Built almost entirely around f****** people over there's actually some good arguments
Wouldn't work
But I can't remember exactly what they are
But there are some compelling arguments about why
That's like a
Jordan 6
No that's not a quick
But even like subsidies for the renewable energy
Clearly be a
I don't know exactly what it was
Right now
Invested Millions upon millions of dollars in it exploded miserable because it turns out
Renewable energy is hard
Which is almost like
Sometimes it go down the wrong road it's almost like maybe one time on saving the universe
You shouldn't
Quit
So speaking of that let's go
Yeah well Jones like to pretend
That this whole tax credit
Is carbon tax thing
Carbon tax credits
Bunch of texts
Carbon credits that you secretly going to be making billions of dollars off of it
Will a Galaxy Note about Bitcoin
So the accusation is just making stuff up so you can get super rich on
Sustainable energy is ridiculously
We flimsy
Thousands and thousands of scientists and researchers academics
Some politicians beeline support his scam
Reviewed studies would have to be false
Slide
You know
For no reason
Just in order to prop up his game
I know a guy
The reality of this is that Al Gore started a business called generation investment
4 as a means of investing in and
Open before word renewable green
Technology
The Firm has been
Is very
Because it turns out sustainable resources can be
Quotes
The message she hopes Generations record will call attention
Is one that the world's investors Canton
Ignore that they can make more money if they change their practices in a way that will at the same time
Environmental and social damage
Modern capitalism
That's from the profile in
The Atlantic
Like
If you look at it
His investment firm only working with
Sustainable business models
Has outperformed
Like a cross
The board almost
Every other
Investment firm
Makes me angry it does matter
It does matter
Angry
It's not
Good for him
I don't know I don't know who to root for
I don't I don't root for him implicitly
But I root for him in
Is that what his model isn't trying to get people to
Be selfish
No I think that is a good thing
And the fact that
Everyone has thought about this idea that what he's of what
He's doing that's not possible
Anyone f***** around and did it
Example of
A lot of money in this
He wasn't even any got a triple double
Good day come on
Anyway
The Architects of the New World Order
Are going to race to complete the structure of World Cup
Technology
Threaten their Monopoly of power
Not much longer
The Architects chart
But Alexa
No
He's mixing up a lot of things
The first Global Revolution as a reference
The club of Rome the ultimate Revolution is the name of
The speech that I actually gave
Vinyl Revolution is nothing
And Society itself
Is a construct
Control the civilization Within
Just as a child maintains the environment
What does Miralax
Living out on a tire
Never questioning
What's a scientist
New World Order
Is controllers
The closely study human behavior
For more than 100
Export control
Using amiibo for socks
I'll be able to control a chunk conscious person suddenly show up in the right after Lohan
Towers of b*******
Here's another
By 2020 there will be a one-world government Ray Kurzweil
Yay
Real but it's actually misquoting
Miss quoted by 2020 there will be a new world
This is from his book age of intelligence
The sound interesting but not really based on anything
Other than speculation
Ray Kurzweil has a terrible track record with predictions including the such like this
So this is this was from his book in 1999 season predictions
A 2000
Yes people use personal computer is the size of ring pens credit cards in books
The typical hormone
I'll give him
What are you talking about
Phillies personal computers the size of books
That's one
Credit cards credit cards
Credit card credit when smaller
Fine
The typical home has over 100 computers in it many of which are embedded in Appliance
What is the computer and yes he is.
Don't go back the Abacus argument
Cybernetic chauffeurs can drive cars for humans and be retrofitted into existing cars
Call them people that we don't talk to
Uber they work by communicating with other vehicles
The roads don't feel like Uber drivers
He's made a number of like sort of solid prediction
Most musical be distributed electronically and most
Transactions will be made on the internet
Lego sort of prediction
It's not just pretty solid guesswork it's not really that
Crazy that is
Just sort of having a good idea about where to
Technology is going
What is other stuff is pretty crazy
It's really wild like one of us
By 2009
Musicians will jam with robot man
Robots movie capable of the creativity
And then when he started on it
Guitar Hero
2009 through to be like today
You never heard of Herbie Hancock
Robots already
The important thing is he is a futurist and a technologist
The only things you really cares about when you make
Make predictions to talk about
Not politics
Any other consideration
His argument that he's making in this text
Ray Kurzweil what does he do
Music futuristic also work for Google he's a
He's a very prominent
Futurist is a f****** dick
You know what you can do you know how like Alan Watts has all those f****** videos that people have online with
Swelling music behind him giving lectures
Yeah that's the same thing
Yeah have we not
That maybe our issues that we just have put
Swelling music behind
Documentary certainly has a lot of it
F***
Citric with regular while also was like use a consultant to Google what have you like
Victoria what do you think about the future
Presenting about this new world government not one world government is Alex
Misquoting
Is this
It's about technology
He's making is this
The advances in technology that are going to
What happened like the proliferation of internet and space travel and that's who it's going to
Collaboration to avoid the end result
Complete segregation
Between nations or destruct
Right as it looks now with China and Russia
Existing in there
Currency
Stroking up
American nationalism
There's literally zero reason to
United government's going to happen in
2 years there's zero reason to think
Yep so this production is pretty s*** misquoted it by using
Air but otherwise
Also Breakers Wells prediction
What's Spirit metastasized
Into the fields of genetics
And Robotics
From their Inception all 3 discs
Dominated by eugenicist
Billionaire founder of sun Microsystems
Courageously went public in 2000
And if worst
Mass extermination of everyone
I took so much courage for him to say
He wrote this article doesn't need us
Alex is completely misrepresenting it
F****** really long boring thing to go through it is
Already already abandoned by whole thing
Already like the show is going to enjoy this
The fuc
I'm realizing that now really f****** funny things that are coming up still I promise you
So self-conscious
Oh my God this 2:13 documentary I'm losing it I'm done I'm done
My emotional state is still fly
I feel so I feel so guilty that I've kept you here this long
Look we agreed
We agreed
Common Law Courts
Castle summer for 7 hours are common law married
Admiralty law
Go read
You can find why the future doesn't need us
You can find this online
Actually really interesting
Already talked about
F****** also heavily featured it
Elizabeth more interesting stuff for us to cover members
Angry we are both going to be for different reasons
Write a tender both going to be pissed off
Annihilation
Orgasmic orgiastic pleasure
She only the beneficial aspect
Bring
So what
Is one thing
People do not agree with
Community
Help
They all f****** fight with each other all the time
Society fighting with each other meaning of your name is trans
Human
Yeah he's beginning beyond what human is of course
Getting along with other people trying to get you at the same time
Any important posthumanism I was what transhumanism grew out of
This community actually even agrees that that's true
Some people think it's like it is possible they grew out of posthumanism but
That's not a consensus they all have argue
The prophet Alex runs if he was treating a large diverse group as one individual thing
Pretending
Humanists believe in the singularity
No
About anyting
Humanism
They're mostly interested in watching a bird
Technology
Speculating about how those Technologies
Could be used in the advancement
If you Mandy and what the implications
Of those
Could be
The history of transhumanism has been
Predictions
Most of which have been wrong
They 1999 in a different book Ray Kurzweil
Spiritual machines
You couldn't number predictions
For 2009
Some of these are also failed
This goes back to the this is where the
Humans with cybernetics
Music
Translating telephone
Speech to speech language translation
Are commonly used
Language
Absolutely
Not even close
Decade or so that technology will be refined but now
It's not even close to
Good
You can do it but whatever is going to come out is going to be real f****** clunky translation
I'll give him one that's no
Most routine business transactions
This travel reservations take place
Between a human and a virtual personality
Often the virtual presentation includes an animated visual presents that will look like a human face
He's just watched anime
We got high and looked at Clippy
Yeah that's what happened
Ante leswing the majority of 10
Some help with that prediction
Text is created using
Continuous speech recognition
So
Further up
Other two
Animated
Hanging around with us as we buy shift they don't want we don't want to
Cuz you can just buy things through interfaces on my damn.
I'm talking to a robot on the
Screen
Transhumanism drawers in that same area as motivational
Most people never ever hear about them or flowy speeches
At all this fun stuff about human futures
More diverse much less exciting and
Debates about the
The ethical implications
Possible future technology
Pretending it's all like
We worship the singularity
Events of our time
Has been a dude injecting him
Himself with what he thinks is
Is a herp
Osher
On
Stage
In front of everybody else at the transceiver
Wait wait are you telling me that he had the Lord boxman's
These guys who make themselves cyborgs by like half of that
Implanting little thing
Fingers in this guy is like
I got herpes and he just shoved it right up his ass
Freddie Gray
Deranged is the syringes in the Chica wasn't straight up there but you know
You can take
Basic license however you like it
Whatever you need at this late hour
Let's
But many of them don't know
Is it master eugenicist
Transhumanism
And the societies control
Openly admit
What's a new system is
Progression to Absolute Terror
Julian Huxley is
Sometimes credited as having
Bulshit
Realistically
Considered
You could go back to any
World story about the conquest
Anytime
Hunt for the Fountain of Youth
These impulses that humans have
What is deeply rooted
External input
Little Grantham longer Library
Immortality
Even Alex Jones his own product DNA Force
Comes from that mentality it markets Itself by
There's damage to the
The telomeres of your DNA but legally can't will improve your body's longevity
He even sells products
Dr. Wallach
Whose name evokes nothing is not the longevity
And Young Jeezy
Yeah that's true also that those are the only two things the second
Absolutely an accident
Julian Huxley did coin transhumanism the term if you ask some people who are wrong
Article you wrote
But the truth
19 years earlier
None of these ideas about transhumanism new and Huxley was around it's just that he was a high-profile biology
Fox Lake and a technology
Technological advances were much greater in 1957
40 or 19 20
Introduced
Proto transhumanists Ideas Book Guide Dallas
Or science and the future
See-through invention
But
We do not also evolve our ethics along the way
Do all these ideas exist
For f****** 30 years by the time album
So what you're saying is
Nobody ain't never heard of Steampunk Buffet
Right
That's what you just said
Hyundai
Definition for the transformative movement in general which means that all trance
Do not agree with either
You're not stuck with all of this
A bun straight past those
Minutes you're like okay
Look we need to a hacker
Need to change this entire Earth is destroying as this human body is not functional anymore
What I need to do
Mastiff
Need to find a way
Augment my body so I can
Are you telling me that I'm just going to get caught up with all this b******* with other people with magnets in my hands
F*** that
I want to get into a fight I want to be a trinity 1 hour to put more magnets away
The wrong Missy
The bottom line is even though
Two things out really boils down to is always
Throughout their entire house
Possible technology
It's been an essential part of transhumanism
And probably one of our that makes
Exit the most boring
Boats that technological advancement
A live forever
Most won't be able to
Keep up with the new Master
Prime for World governor
It's now all about
Google control
Access to
Life extension systems
Margaret Thatcher's house
Dare
Biological evolution
Is too slow for the human species
Over the neck
It's going to be left in the dust
Okay
That actually sounds
I'd like to humble myself
For you
I've no idea
This quote is real
At this point in the documentary I've given up on trying to prove his clothes are all stove
I don't give a fuk with Lakers last days is whatever
We found dance break
Ray Criswell
Decades ago
No longer be able to get jobs
Sounds like
Before we get to this thing about Mexican
My workers have a Good Vibration
Computer chip sausage
Is that to make sure that access
Sensitive information
Contain
Second they have nowhere else to put
These goddamn microchip
The largest issue with Mexican law enforcement at they face outside of the cartels
Police corruption
Use of RFID chips
Complain to the police officers allows much greater
Air control
Restricted information
Chips implanted in arms cannot be faked
Unique RFID code for
Breech birth
Allows a record of who is access
What pieces of evidence
Doctor stuff all that s***
This could not be itchy
Can you be using the device planted
Standard ID card
ID card could we
Stolen
The ID cards
Corrupt officer
Like that they're not giving them to rank
Can file employees
Federal top top
Traffic
The others
Didn't know you can't do that because they are so fragile
These these things
Take them out of someone's arm
What if you can't walk into a government building
With an arm
I think someone to be like
A guide to die
Even in the most terrible parts of Mexico I think someone
Someone be like what's up
Alright
Are you going to a bassinet
Babushka
Alright
Anybody order
Okay
Get me into that evidence Locker
That my work would it be strange for the Subway delivery guy to Michael wander around
Weird
8 hours documentary a little bit drunk
Yeah you can probably Rippetoe
Mexico City
Ryobi ocean7
I could do it
To the other reason
6 would be
The other reason that they do this
It's cuz there's a lot of
In Mexico getting chip in order to
Mexico Rex
Incredibly high in terms of kidnapping
Statistics
40% between 2000 for 2007 and Mexico according to official
Mexico Rex
Columbia is the worst countries for
Interested in that I'm tripping for that
Clear whether or not that
For that but
You understand
So fragile where you going to put the
And to this dumbass
I can probably kidnapped
Here's a dumb quote
Digital reality
Are suicidal nihilist
Suicide
No there is no broker
They would always prefer to go on willing
They can
So that was a quote from Arthur croker
I looked at the citation that Alex gives
He gives a citation
Wired Magazine
It's not it's not in there at all
To a publication called
What does a cyberpunk Maga
Awesome story
Well was it is it though
Houses
Play Kow.
A little bit. I'm just saying Arthur Kroger because I read the way new
Leftist article and Wired Magazine
He's a hunter restaurant
He speaks with these
Flourishes of lichen
Extremism
Interims
He's actually talking about
He sometimes speaks
Riddles
If you read other other air other interviews
You come to the conclusion that like I like what this guy is putting down but I don't believe
If you
So here's the quote
This one about the suicidal nihilist
Are these people at the top
Of the digital reality
I come from a Cisco cyberpunk
It was run by a very serious group
Drug addict
They start the magazine
Then change the name to reality
Thousand
The 1989
Why would that be the one you said along because reality hackers they found
That they couldn't get distribution
Because people thought that they were like cutting people up or do some sort of
They're their images of covers
And stuff was a little bit ago
Stream and set like that to the name reality hackers ever thought it was kind of like they thought it was okay
Gourmet magazine
This guy
Nom de plume
Was are you serious
Fun I was watching
He was watching TV
Save I didn't make that up
So he came out he was watching TV news like everything is
2000 Audis
Got these weird
The products are all 2000
It's a queen
The other person involved
Another - 5.
I wasn't there I didn't do that
So she came up with this
She's great I don't know
House refuses to give interviews.
She came up with Mando as the beginning to 2000
Seems like it should be harder
Shiplap
She have gotten
That was what was running the magazine
So her inheritance was Mondo
Exactly
I appreciate that
Regarding the nature all about
An issue number 5 in 1992 Nagel editors
Accidentally transpose the names of avant-garde musicians
Glenn branca and Elliot sharp cover
Rendering them Glenn Sharpe and Elliot Broncho
Send sharpen Bronco for household name
Pure readers notice
But Mondo obviously owed an explanation
Rather than backward
Rather than apologize Mondo proclaimed the snafu intentional
Greasy hands archive composed an essay about post-postmodern modernism
And deliberate art damage or rather they scribbled notes on a napkin while I'm having drinks
The outline was passed around the concept ended up as a collaborative two-piece Manifesto
Called what do you say after Popo
Half the time we were trying to battle people into thinking we were deep
Says who
Waffle wagon
It was parrot
Paradise Brown
Okay we got these two names wrong
Instead of saying we got these two names wrong
Let's
Device around why
What's the exact correct thing to do
I'd love them all right Honda 2000 for twenty thousand more years
Bucket higher s*** on designer drugs and like weird experimental chemical,
Compounds and s*** like that
They have
No serious pretense
Kickstarter and they coming back
I think we got the
Editorial policy to where it's at
Like if you interview somebody you can fight him if you want
If you don't like what they're saying
You can argue with them
No other Publications
We pretended they were scored early in magazines would never come out
Ford to put out that magazine so give me a large inheritance
I will make you a way better
So Armando party might
Is the quote from that article about the
About time travel expert being interviewed
Others others experimenting with weird mental line simulation game
Spiritual Whisperer
Or Bart Nagel
And future virtual reality theorist Brenda Laurel
360 turn without falling down
Japanese animation videos flickered on monitors
Speakers performed
Frottage
Antique sofa
Adiraj that's when you put your dick in it
Journalist mgq might have been taking a piss on the front lawn
One creature that would trap people for entire evening
And conversations about Francis Bacon was actually William shakes
I've heard those
Before
It's everyone's looking tired of their mind the editor of the magazine and some weird theorist
Trying to spin around and make a 360 without falling down
Derrick Derrick describing this
This is f******
This is so boring
But
Approved by
So the guys behind Mondo we're really big on just making
Shut up 1993 Bardenay Eagle rattle disappears with an n
Tutorial inspired by artists Jeffrey Koons
Theory of image appropriation
Either steal it and manipulated wrote Nagel or use it blatantly under the fair-use.
Nagel practice editorial preached
With a cover of issue number 10
In which he superimposed a photo against the background stolen from the cover of another magazine
Niger was immediately Savaged in trade journals
He retaliated with an editorial an issue number 11 which is where this Arthur Corker quote comes from
About a new technology that works on
Works on the DNA level 2 detector microscopic recognizable patterns and images
He asserted the technology in
Coated patterns that are invisible to the naked eye but detectable no matter how much an image was used
He further claimed
That in what
Year hence
All scanners and copy machines with
Contain a built-in chips
To protect these codes and notify and National computer image Bank
Every duplication by modem
The computer with an automatically debit your Visa at
I tried to make it more and more absurd by saying these scanners would be hooked up
Computer could actually detect if you were scanning some buns Style
I'm in a lot of photographers were actually excited about this
Richard Avedon already offered
Come on they were already offering to donate their proceeds from the style set to a photo assistance group called
Creative
Dammit
You just made all that s*** off course he did
Eric Ebron started writing the message
And this guy Avedon wrote messages like
You look like you was she was tricking people they were tricking everybody they were trolling like
Razee
Amazing I love
The other thing
I can't remember what the name of the band is and I feel really bad about this
There was a band
You too soon
I can't remember what it at that exact Circle
Constanza Salvadoran
This band
Actually babe
Like a local punkish band or whatever
They ripped off some of you to stuff
So there album was actually called you too
Hey Ben The Edge and YouTube
And they almost destroyed them
Like you think
Aggressive
Litigation
I'm so
As Mondo 2000
Popular YouTube requested
To be interviewed by
Oh no
That was a bad idea Bono f****** Edge come on guys
Run into a merry tricksters band without getting your ass kicked
When are you serious was friends with the band
D2
He set up the interview
And without Edge
The Edge knowing
The guys from the band interview him
About how they had stolen various elements of the videos that used on stage live performance
Talking about
Heaven halfway through the interview you came in like
Hey this is the band that you sued
What the f*** is this
Financial
She refused to publish the article or said that we don't want to do this
Right
Definitely what he would quit over yes they're run
That's delightful
I love finding stuff like this that I had no idea existed
There's like
But I wish I was hip to that when I was younger
No s*** every so much cooler now if I had grown up with that but
I live in Missouri
Sorry structure
Free Humanity
Cannot afford to let psychopathic
With delusions of grandeur
Repeat the mistakes of their for mattress because it is highly probable this time they may destroy you
Salinas shell in their mad rush for godhood
In this film we have chronicled Overlord
Is that
Which already claimed the lives of more than 150 million
In the 20th century
I'm Invincible tyranny
It will dwarf there
They were Sovereign nations in Parma
Skippers final solution
Once world government is in place
No one
Able to stop
New World Order
Global population
Hundreds
I get it
Their Quest
Production
So there's a bunch of FEMA camps that's not
There are FEMA camps
Yes I know so the proponents of the people can't believe generally basic
Concerns on house resolutions
6:45
Isabel about that by the homeless
Establishing
Center style population
Provide humanitarian Aid
If you want to speculate wildly and let paranoia run the actual text of the resolution
Stated intent
Benign
And something that word
Horrible
Didn't
Same dumbass Patriots
Provide somewhere for us
Also the only role that FEMA even hasn't all this
The country is broken down into
Covers
So there is no because
Like why would you have a FEMA Center in every
When there aren't really
As many
Like
Emergency
Risk
It's not evenly distributed among states
Earthquake
There's no flood control.
No it's not important. It's not important it's about
It just at fault lines
Coast have a very high
We need to put all of our hurricane specialist
In Idaho
The only the only reality there is to it
Internment camps
In America is that is incarcerated minorities
Rent based on their ethnicity
Japanese
And World War II
Tears
The long walk
There's a lot of info
Remember no certainly not
Beyond that there's only one in
That's Rex 84 G
Short for Readiness exercise
Before
The plan was put together by Reagan and Oliver North
And then
Director John
Trustworthy plan calls for pudding
Chester Civil Right
Union
Supporters and minority immigrants
Some camps because of
The disruptive effect
Their perceived
Have on the right lane
Political status quo
Capillus
The plan was never put into action
The only example
Outside of those
F****** racist
I just brought up
Any president
Has ever put together
Pictures of an actual plan of putting
Dissenters in
And
Keeping scores
Somewhat I mean there are other minorities and immigrants involved but it's also about Union organizing it so it's all
Activism
If you get rid of all of those people
What
Are the people yet
But I am
Before
One of the triggering event
Who's going to be mad if we invade cell phone
Like
Until was literally directed at
Liberals anti-war people always been annoying
Well also
Yeah
It's it's
You know it's interesting that
There's no documentation there's nothing
In the world
Liberals trying to create these
When was America and unilaterally the Opera
It seems that way
But that means but that's what you get so much mileage out of crying the victim
Maybe we should
We consider of rounding up all the white National
I think you're starting to
Probably a bad idea anyway
Is it all messy
These dark Builder
String of man-made bio-weapon
Each one
Worse than
There's no Citation for this
You decide what they're going to do that
There's literally no reason to believe it
Follow the same time expanding the police
Extermination of the population
Fighting invisible chair
Chaos
And the Georgia Guidestones and as a cold test
The elite sacred mesh active Georgia
Why
Georgia
How big is a class system
Masterforce deliver slate
While the elite enjoy the land of the Earth
Evolve into superhumans
Weird way to Andrews house
Give it to the intermittent
The New World Order
And the agenda
Of the Bilderberg
Goddamn
We should have done this into chunks
Documentary is not good
What is that
What is the post-credits sequence is working or whatever
Expose the globalist by traveling to disassemble turkey
Psycho Bilderberg
Dalton shall not break in
Bagon music
Call
We were at the Ritz Carlton
It looks like a typical
Bilberry praderio they had the armed guards all around the place had with tunes of
Formation Wayfair
They also had
Cops all the way around the building
And they had all this
Hi-Tech things baby
Member can
I hear whatever spoken Indian language
Instantly translated
Language
What the f*** is he talkin about this he just read The Hitchhiker's Guide and thinks of Babel Fish is real
No it's not the battle fish is
What you're saying then
No I did a bunch of research on this cuz I was fast
Possibly with the big things in their ears no cuz there's
You know that translator
Look at it
This technology can never
It was darker
What we have in front of us
Too many languages sound book
Similar issue
Just cognates
That exists as false cognate words that sound very similar but aren't the same
There are like bear bear and bear what you going to do with that
Will you do that with a weird translator get contacts
Closed now you need artificial intelligence
So the other problem the other problem then it comes down to
Idioms translate idioms
Do you have like this week
This CFR is going to have trouble with that I get you
So I looked into this and it's really fascinating
Because there's a couple of startups
That exists out there that they're trying to make this acknowledge
Did you real I'm sure none as a Babylon
The one that I watched
Video of actually don't have a name. They don't f****** deserve a plug
Frankly I don't support what they do
Technology
It's a handheld device
Until like in Japan
You're like
Where is a karaoke bar
And then you hold it up to somebody else where is the karaoke bar in Japanese
It's a whole video of Japanese people being freaked out.
That's a little weird but here's the problem
The video doesn't show any moment
Sounds like
Then responding
All because it doesn't translate the other way
Work right but it's just so you can be heard not
Do you have to listen to their f****** Japanese bulshit
It's such nonsense
Disgraceful
Pretend you're immersing into a world
Bob disrespecting it
I don't know I think it actually is
Denigrating
The idea of travel
But also a lot of these businesses that are like. Just this one I found a bunch
There's a bunch
Apps like startups that are trying to
Work this out
A lot of them are crowdfunded
And I
We all know
Most ideas
Crowdfunding
Some of them are real
Summer like here's an idea give me money and then you never get the product
So there's a bunch of stuff like that but like sound too good to be true
Anyway with Jim Tucker's describing doesn't exist
He's making this up
But
It might have been the light
So they cannot keep up with it
Really great dane Ahmad
I'm done with my notes
Hilarious
I hope so
Recipe
Rest in power
I would have cut a lot of this
Call me hear that f****** weird machine good old man
Walking across the street Fort Lee
Proving nothing Bilderberg meeting her this weekend
New camera
We had my two personal cops following me today
Deleterious
Those guys are up
Go follow you
There's a car for this out to the
Hotel
So for it
I would fall in Rochester
John Elway
Owner of Fiat
A fellow Builder
Thought they could take a stroll
That Garfunkel
This Bilderberg attendees sneered at our camera
That's not a snake
This car load of kingpins gave the media
A murderous look
And seemed shocked
There's a wreck Harlow
Now
Anything more than two is a Carlo
Yeah you got them guys they just drove away
What a boring f****** n2007 the Bilderberg Group
Receive the heaviest Global coverage
Jim Tucker witness press conference is attended by hundreds of
The members of the media
The new generation of info
Where are those at
Attract
No matter where they are
There's more crazy
Her explanation
Bilderberg
Harry
At least he's a potential Fresno
Even if they obscure Governor parking
Bill Clinton
Lost his virginity at the Bilderberg meeting in Baden-Baden Germany 1991
The present the following
Is that
Little ruffian
They do that often
Officially
Goldberg versus Governor Rick Perry a potential president United
Yes
Violation of the Logan Act
Bill Clinton's White House
5 $300,000
Recent text.
When Perry returned to Texas for Miss.
We were determined
McCown
Orchestra
Am I beautiful
This is still going
This end is so funny
Did you have the end you would already
Define now
This is so funny
What are rules
Super jump on it dark enough to look like tonight
So real quick just also this is edited by Russ
Rob Jacobson
Rob you should never work again ever
Object is called out
Abandoned
The real true, the end of that is
First of all just be cut to Alex off alone with a bullhorn
F****** hilarious but then with a context that we have
Now it's a little more funny
I love that I love him being Trump's secretary
Never memorize goddamn stupid
Whatever Alex
Spelling is Meaningful everything is
But shout out to grill f****** Charles Graham Reynolds and Reynolds brush set
I would put this up there
Strunk's
Church
Golden Globe
Michael McWhorter and Glendale never heard of them
G killas
Audio for this I don't know now I'm back
Except
Editing
Yeah
His fault it's all out
Asphalt additional music
Douche
Also voice-over recorded and edited by Rob that's not great
Camera operators Lotto
Elastolin
Michael Kaufman research
That's great I love to see this violet
Joan
Who is that that is
Wife Kelly
She goes by the name
That might come up
Later
Special
Mcwhirter Glendale
Mst3k
Oh yeah but they've been supporting sexual
Blueprint for Global enslavement
Jordan never going to believe this
We are about to finish
Clock
The clock in time right now
What are we at hours 11 minutes
It's only fitting
Sportatorium
This is brutal.
Most of it
And has been
For you
Like I feel mostly guilty about making you do
Cuz for me I could
I could
Sit here and
Like a voice-over of
Hey this is a lie
Gillislee but
I think you one cuz you're
Bayou
Close
How do I solve u4
From any guilt
Of
Oh that's your prize
Appreciate that very nice
You got a lot of wrong
References
Both of us know something
Is
Sinbad about about it
How to read paragraphs to Gerald McGuire into a Jerry Maguire
Reference
I feel like
Keanu intro
I know what effect you know how to turn Gerald Sherry
Disabled
Are you in at 1:30 in the morning I cannot get my hair cuz f****** agree
Be with me at all and now that don't look at it in the f****** camera on
Furious
Jordan we got to wrap this up
Jiminy okay
About end game cuz I think I think I think
I get I think I get what your take on it is
And that is that
It really amounted
To nothing
Like a diamond 9 and a half hours when this is over I guess
Like I've nothing
You learned nothing
Learn about Mondo 2000
No I think
More Woods
Inexplicable documentary why it exists
Bananas
Exist
He's crazy
Is this the way it does is even more insane
Because it doesn't
It doesn't have a through-line veritably
Stowe in Crofton
Like
Just have
Like a guy
Under desk
Do f****** hour on the roads
I'm sure he could
But what's really interesting story that story has a start
Have a narrative
And if they don't build it then you get that.
Like you start we're okay well we need this because of all the
Building in your life
Before you wanted all those roads to be there but now this
Please try to open it
Congratulations
Edmond roads and then
Quotes
By the way
Cynthia Rick Perry
Like I don't I don't want nothing there's nothing I mean the only point of it is
Exist
As a time capsule of what Alex Jones
Put out as
The foundation of his career in
Canal 11 years later we can look back like you've betrayed
Literally everything ever hear about
You have no moral Center
There's absolutely nothing
That you don't contradict
On a f****** daily basis
Nothing is real even that
Being sad
I mean
My big takeaway
Is that like
Brew doing the research
Of course I expected
Find stuff about life
You know that the foster kids
About xy&z different thing
What I didn't expect when I couldn't
Never have predicted
When I started doing this
This research
Was that
He wouldn't
Cover his bases
I never would have expected it would all be in Carta and
Psych reference here
Like I never thought that the bibliography with myself are
15 * at least and I
Still lose my s*** ever
How do you say the word
Encarta it
Absolutely crazy to me
This documentary
Quotes
It exists
It's been viewed by millions of people
I'm against that bunch of people believe what he
He's saying
And hardly ever check
And look at the bibliography
That's a problem
That is not that is not an acceptable list because everyone who's watching
Psych
It's all just nonsense claims
Alex Jones documentary
I assume most of it
You are a policy
I would like to donate
1000 million more dollars for us to do another
Commiserate
Please
Keep it
Do not
Give your money anywhere deer make me do this again please let me out I'm
Please somebody help me
Get me out of here
I never I never
And none of these
Daniel estulin
Book that he made about the Bilderberg Group
Sites
This guy who talks to aliens
Earth Defense Force
And he's taking his word about
Whether or not print Barnard is a Nazi
Also
This guy writes a bunch of books about aliens
That's the small-scale version
Alex Jones
Problem with source
Like all of this is just things
He's claiming
All being assertive
And it has no Foundation
Wakes up from stuff that is
About Lake
Eugenics
Being f***** up
It is a mess
That a lot of our history intersect with Nazi
Like
That stuff is
True
But no one
Hiding that
It's uncomfortable to
Talk about so maybe people don't bring it up all the time
Sources exist where you can find all that information
What I'm saying is f*** Alex Jones I mean like
Legitimately
I would say 100 hours
Probably
Researching
In this documentary
And now
Plus
Recording this
Right
So officially you have been paid
91 cents on the dollar
Lady that
Cuz I'm low-balling and terms
The research stuff
And it's valuable to me because of all the sides
Stuff I've learned
I value that I've learned
A lot of these
Statistics about like foster children
Kind nuvet in my head that hurts
Get a better picture of it or you know what I do know whole lot about Serbia
I didn't know a lot about the 1990s
Serbia situation
Really know about the beginning of World War
Excuse to research that stuff
Is really valuable to me I appreciate that and to Alex
I appreciate you
Opportunity
To do that now is not the time to be magnanimous
Thought
F*** you you lie about everything about 6 hours ago
It's clearly intent
There is no way that this is an
There's no way that you can
You are making a documentary
Were you use a fake quote by Hitler
Or use a fake quote by David Rockefeller there's no way it makes it too
The Final Cut of your documentary
Whitby citation
Filter simulator
There's no f****** way that passes muster
Are you making a documentary unless you're like I know I can't prove this no one's going to check on
The same way that Ron Paul there's no way that's right that research newsletters
That's the point of a trying to get to
Anyway this is tough to some up but there's a lot of feelings that I have
Have
That
For me like
Really f******
Hammered at home
Just like just
The conversation of isca
Stupid or is he
You doing this
If you're stupid
You can get away with putting this documentary up there
You're dumb
If you are putting
Quotes
On screen
Hanging them as like
This is a big f****** deal
Knowing full well these were not anybody related to what's going on here
Goes over from being your dumb to being this is on purpose
There wasn't a f****** release date on this
There wasn't a deadline this wasn't
This wasn't like
Talk about that this might have been part of one of his money bombs
Like that there might have been
Something where he actually did have some artificial pressure to put it out
But that still artificial pressure still don't care Google
Google all that could have been helpful
Exist in 2007
First
To anybody
Making a documentary
For anybody can I give my advice first
My Facebook
A lot of people try it on this
Not all of them did
Whoever came up with
Tried the rest of them fuksa.
Anyway Jordan
Mortmort point
Oh absolutely
But more than anything else like
Appreciate you so much for doing this
I know I dragged you in
This is the thing
This is probably
Like a
It'll probably go down in history as a
Classic example
And I appreciate
The ordering pizza being a friend
Next episode it's going to be called don't record for a week
Oh my God
Episode
This episode continues cuz Jordan doesn't know how to edit
Next episode just
Repeating over
For 2 hours
He made up quotes about bilderberg's
Next episode the only man who can
Can replace Dan Friesen
That's right
In studio we have Alex Jones everybody
I'm an idiot
Great episode
We've come to the end of nine hours of this b******* and
For about nine and a half
It only seems fair since you
I think you took this the hardest
Then
Everybody before you
Self
Deprecate any further
Around hours
But I came out of it
But that was that was a low point for me but the only person that I
It's not me
The Listener
City of Oregon
Dan who does
The research and
I pity you.
The editor
You poor poor bastard had a lot of work ahead
So sorry for you if I failed a f******
I'm over it tomorrow as I do it
Love you too but
Before we get out of here
I must have
Who
From all of the weirdo characters
Would you like to choose to tell them to go f*** themselves
Now let me rub you down let me run your mouth
Smedley Butler
His dream was just so crazy let me run you down some names
Yes
Jim Tucker
Daniel like his hat
Great ponytail Michael Kaufman
Michael Kaufman he's a piece of s***
Alex Jones
That other guy in
The kid or the older guy
Well there's the other guy then the kid
What about the older guy who's really Bernard the security guard
Cool dude
Smedley Butler in my head again cuz you brought him up
Like to add you to the list of FrontRunner
Let's say you're estulin
Michael Kaufman
Obviously
He's a she can go f*** himself
I agree f*** that guy
Thank you all for listening
Sorry
Holding
Alex