Alexandra Thurston color
Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
Is there a hook
There is I know a lot about our job
What seems like forever
You can find
All I know is that alright
Monument to looking up
Whether or not a guy said
Right there's a lot of that
The Show by just doing a little bit of a house clean
Because
I I think I did
Do a good enough job
Thursday on Thursday night you were all up in my business and I got something wrong
Well
First of all malphus might have been a worse dude than we gave him credit for
Whoeasy
Other than the other thing was in the first
The first episode the beginning the first thing we stopped for it
That h.g. Wells quote
I misread my notes
About the quote
There was accurate
But also the specific
Part of the quote that
He takes out
He doesn't even put an ellipsis into note that he was you know
The quotas using AP Style
The quote that he says is like many people will resist the new world order a Dye resist
Nothing at all in the middle of those
Two sentences there's a list of like
Millionaires and Maharaja
The specific people he's talking about in that quote I forgot to point this out
Where to find them and solve the New World Order problems about the people who will resist
The New World Order of taking care of people will be these millionaire
Angelica
I just wanted to clear that up because I'm very self-conscious
And all that
I just didn't make the point strongly enough it was even worse than this house
You can check out on our ography Wichita
You can also follow up with a lot of machine
You can find
Episodes of over today as are welcome back
To reality but before we going to be all about Cotter
Friday
Poconos
Before we give a shout out to a couple of new donors what's going on out there
What's going on up there Pete be
Thank you so much for joining up with the show
The next was actually very special
Special shout-out to someone who is
Bumped up their donation but at the same time has also become the moderator of our new group
On Facebook is the encouragement for us actually creating that group you sent me a message and said
People can post stuff and
Joke around and
And all that stuff do we have
Groupon Facebook
It's called go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
Find it and if you request to be remember we will let you in the group there's a lot of fun stuff going on
You remember
Pics of those eight words in order to buy the group
People clowning around it so it's a great time
Stupid
Inspiring and encouraging us to open it up it's really cool it's so fun looking at
And myself jumping in and clowning with
Absolute real nice
Inspiring that
And bumping up donation
Keegan you're officially a technocrat
Someone sodomites Italy a bucket of poop
Jesus Christ
So thank you very much Keegan
Think about it you might have already been a technocrat
God bless you
You're the best
So it took a long time
To do that endgame cover
There's a ton of research
Very weird
But his bibliography suck
There were loose ends there were
His research at the dry what the f*** is
She talking about there's a guy with a cowboy hat
Oh God.
Cowboy hat cowboy hat
His cowboy hat was of course made by a globalist undercutting his
Entire argument either figure out why wasn't also wearing a bolo tie these requests
He's dead so I had to have a seance
Define doubtful took a lot of time
So I took weeks of research
And then we recorded
Turn for us
Taken by the way we are turn of the century spiritualists apparently
I'm The Reincarnation of David Wilcock
David David Wilcox claims to be The Reincarnation of
Who is that guy is called the sleeping
Sweeping mist
What was his f****** name
Edgar Cayce
Claims to be The Reincarnation of Edgar Cayce
About reincarnation on Project Camelot
Point of the future
You know we recorded that there was a hot 9 hours
And then the editing of its posting
They're putting together our bibliography that took up most of last week
We haven't had an episode
Unfortunately or fortunately
Matley it's debatable
In that time a lot of stuff that hits
Home for Alex
Has happened we had these
Did the shooting in Parkland
Which
I think that you and I have discussed we have no in
I'm talking about at least at this point out of respect
Those affected
And rage
There's that the argument
That are made a really stupid
Exact same arguments that have been made
Over and over and over again every time there's a tragedy
So if you want to know about it go listen to us talk about Alex
Pretty much pretty much the same f****** thing
And there was that that town hall meeting with CNN
About that
Too much
Smarticle started
It's come out about how he was
In trouble with YouTube standards
Yes
So it was a big
He's got two strikes
Straight to laughter
I was talking on the group go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
Some folks my position on it is quite frankly
These sorts of articles are really just
Reinforcing
Victim status
His narrative
Think it does nobody any help
Do I to tell this order bulshit
Think about how many f****** strikes he has whenever he's okay
Exactly
Single f****** articles
And here's why is a monster and here's why
Alex Jones
Noted ridiculous
It is quite frankly like I think it's stupid
I think the strikes there was room
Two are non-specific
How much baseball has
Influencer
Exactly
Baseball's not arbitrary
You can make it two strikes strikes
Technicalities in baseball
But not in YouTube
If you guys are going to play that game and that's what you want to do
Hit me up
I can find you some more strikes
I know if you think I know a few places where he vaguely threatened
Chris Cuomo's children
If you want we can get some stuff
But that's not a reject
Sincerely think that
Kind of nauru
Anybody who's pushing for likes
Some sort of a
On the merits
Content
I think is barking up a really bad
Tree
An approach to take
Because
Up to a certain
Point he is
Protected under
Piano priest
Guidelines
Write better there
Specifically 2 /
Protect
Speech but it's
Disgusting
Doleful
You play a losing
Game when you're like
Yrz-a the more reasonable thing to do is
The crime
Certainly deal with those usually
To allow
His listeners to see him within the proper con
Things like
Show people his bibliography for m
Thing that I think
Could a road
Public confidence
Warriors
But again we talked about this he would just say
Of course I don't have anything in a bibliography all my sources are secret
You know like
I have top
I'm getting off on a terrible
Absolutely
It's been a big week
Did you know there's a secret and Carter page
You can find on the dark web
You know what's weird
It has all of
Encarta
Encapsulate on Tor Browser
I want I think we did a really terrible job of
A couple things
Thinking about a little more
We didn't know like I think that it Bears mention
Alex made that that came out in like
Mention George Soros in that documentary once
That's true you know there's also
Things like that that are like
Call George Soros wasn't involved in building the trans-texas pipeline or whatever
Do you use involved in everything
According to Ali
I think it's interesting that his narrative hadn't developed to that point yet
You're doing a great job globalizing
This Texas
This thing out
That way Alex can talk
The trilateral commission
The timezone
He's Alex Jones big Boogeyman
Anyway
Alright we're coming back
We got it. Check in
With the present
I was like
Dewey
I think we do out of like a decent completeness
That's true that's why I was looking around
I was like
That's weird
Milo yiannopoulos was on
Every day last week
I saw that are really trying to forge an alliance
Really why I believe so
Milo is reached
A premature point in his career Rhino 11
When that happens
Generally people go to Infowars so
He's going to Infowars and he's really
He's be the potent tool for Alex right now
But I think he'll I would say his wealth
Pretty quick
As he's done
Literally everywhere else
I don't mean this in any homophobic sense
But I think that Alex is audience
Assume
So much of what drives
Is Infowars at
Misplaced
Version of masculinity
Yeah and that's why they like this
Testosterone coffin
Owen Shroyer shooting hoops
In a commercial for Vitamin B or whatever
You know there's there's a there's a weird
Testosterone-driven masculinity
That is at the
Score of Infowars homosexual
Most likely turn off his
Very masculine base
Awful awful
I think it's only a matter of time
Before they
The charm wears off
For them
Alex is trying to give him instead make them feel
Enlighten
You can't call us racist or homophobic we listen to a gay man
It's possible but I think that I think
I think the alternative is
Who's more likely
Play Just based on what I like
Johnny like these guys all of the Olympics they've been listening to Johnny where they're crying at figure skating all the time that's something
That we know about infowarrior I don't know I'm just guessing
But
Who knows
I don't know I don't know it's it's
But so far it's been a really good press
Gambit for the two of them
Everyone
Why have you so
Right
Infowars change
They'll write up a boring
Milo is saying bulshit on him
A monstrosity is never come
Heart
Do you think about the bottleneck
Alex Jones
Infowars related material at generally come from
You know right wing watch
Or
Clips from right wing watch
And the reason is
F****** takes forever to go through all the
This b*******
Rightwingwatch does it for you
Video of XYZ thing
I think is interesting
Alex Jones
The show Media Matters
I'm not saying anything bad about Media Matters or any of these shows
Jose they pick up the thing that rightwingwatch put out because of
For them already
Where is we cover
Paris
No I don't want to do that
I want to be a part of any of those Institution
Like I thought about that I could apply for a job at Media Matters
Probably get one
Like based on the work that I've done already a lot of those things I've written
A demonstrated track record of being on that side
Hypothetically I don't know what there is more to that side that I don't know
But I would assume
The competences I've displayed probably would get me at least an entry-level jobs
And I've no interest
So
My point is everyone just covers
This piano clip
Milo being
Yeah it's because it's the thing that someone's already pre-packaged
Push it out I just wish the people
Like you were saying look at the bigger picture
Anyway
I checked in
On Friday
I wanted to see
What was half a
So I watched a bit of it
I have a couple Clips I want to play for you
In his first one Alex
And he explains how he feels
About this perceived
What's going on
With YouTube
France is a Wall Street Journal article
30 flashes up on
And it doesn't
To your apartment
Mansion
All your stuff
Add
Whoever was in your house
Goldentot can a russian agent
Bulimic
I am allowed to
Translation of a narcissistic
75 IQ
Brother
Authoritarian
Can you celebrate
Picking on you constantly
All these other idiots
Boron
Rush Limbaugh $300,000 to show off
First Amendment
I wonder which of those considerations was more important
I wonder if he was more like also the first
Tire sale on app
300 Grand and he gave me services in response
Normal transaction that we all make all the time was I making a good deal
But also
The First Amendment
Maybe put also the First Amendment
Tell him hey guess what you're feeling and I'm the one who saving you
Maybe entirely bossa
My cake YouTube
Operation
That's right
Rush Limbaugh
Because
They could shut him down they're going to shut us down people hang together
Monetized on YouTube
We're going to shut everybody down
YouTube is private company right moron
Love it
She's doing good
Yeah
Amateur comedy of it is like Milo being on now
Because he f******
Wouldn't touch
Milo
Right after all the s*** went down
You've got out
$300,000 Milo
Because his net worth
He need some juice was it because oh he's in a desperate position cuz that'll f****** lawsuit
Workout anniversary stop giving the money
Maybe because I
1st of August 1st Amendment
Sodus Point
I mean
It's all like
Hello Alex.
The deals with this fake idea that he's being censored you just
Get mad at
His normal enemies YouTube
Well I've got this Wall Street Journal article
No
The First Amendment covers
What the government can do
A private company can still just do whatever you have to agree to their terms and condition
Clearly say
You know we can f*** you over if we want right right now
Every company
Movie theater
Every ticket was
Was printed weekend
Refuse service to anyone for any reason
It's the same thing with most black
Do that
Most
Right now
Yeah we'll see how the Supreme Court rules before we
Go there and then you know every almost there
Murray State has at-will employee
For any reason or no reason
It's just what businesses do to an extent mad about that is like well you have a lot more.
Journal article here in front of me that has YouTube 6 a.m.
Conspiracies propaganda
3D account, property
And I was really little bit here
YouTube kids planning
Give users more context for videos promoting conspiracy
Theories are state-sponsored
Stafford buying internet Giants
Clean up its platform
Make criticism over its role in spreading listen
Information
YouTube said starting Friday would label all videos come
Did identify this Sunday broadcast
The category that would include even the United States
Public Broadcasting Service or PBS
The step is significant in part because
Has been a major conduit for our
State News organization that us intelligence
Officials called
The Kremlin principal
Spell propaganda
So I looked through this entire article it doesn't say anything about censoring a Infowars
Only one referee
Prince to Alex Jones
At all in it
That's oblique
It's the
YouTube first pooped its search results for breaking news in October after his criticized for surf
Conspiracy theories about a mass shooting
I killed 59 people during concert in Las Vegas
The change appearance
The search results for some key news events that have attracted
2 conspiracy
Three days after the Las Vegas shooting
The results for a search on YouTube
About the attacks with a video titled quote
Las Vegas shooting was a false flag attack shooter on the fourth floor
But on Thursday night the results were all made
Stream news source
The policy hasn't always worked though on Wednesday after a train carrying some Republican lawmakers
Is chloride with a truck
Searches for grp crash on YouTube returned at the first result
A livestream from Alex Jones
The founder of conspiracy
Recite Infowars
As the third
The third video title train crash attempt
Assassination
GOP Congress members?
YouTube said its algorithm
Recognize the search
Quickly enough
As a news related to Gary
So
It's talking about
I mean Alex Jones is reference their butt
Part of it
Yeah
Dangerous territory whenever you say like
Just cuz you're saying
Stupid s*** we're going to block you
Floor jack
About how the kids are crisis actors
Difference in saying stupid s***
And I don't take the piss
This is tantamount to
Again
The large part of the coast
Private company
I don't consider this
Some sort of racket
Steering sensor
No that's a good question
Platforms
Republic
Like would be a good idea if YouTube has publicly owned
I kind of think I'm not sure
Right I haven't even sat around and thought about it enough to have a informed
Either I just thought of it right now let's get into it and I think it would probably create
New and interesting problem
I don't know
Cuz it's it's kind of like a Publix
No everybody puts
But they don't have to
Like the reader at the reason electricity and telephone
Some s*** like that weird
Deems Public Utilities
Because
Without
Monopoly over them
That's different than a hey if you don't use YouTube
You can't put your review of black
A up
That's not the same
Yes
Are you sure it's very different how can you survive if somebody can't get ahold of you
Just like what the long distance phone call
Just emailing you they're very different
Not letting us put
Stop it wouldn't make it so we can
Operation
And my response though be there's so many ways you can host
Video online and if you have a website where you can embed those videos
You have a good reputation and
People start to like what you're doing
Shouldn't matter if YouTube is on board with you.
I mean you're just kind of being
Petty
I mean
That's another
And always because that's the second click
You know what I'm saying
Like if you're on YouTube looking
Confer Alex Jones videos
That's very different than if you're on YouTube and you
Steve and Alex
You know I'm saying yeah
In terms of problem of theirs
Suggestion
Just like that
Which much has been written about especially over at BuzzFeed
Missing articles you can
Read about
The algorithm
Used to
Suggest videos on
People end up with people going down really f***** up road
That leaves
Toolots
Misinformation
Beyond the right
To be on the conservative side
They just got rid of
They can just do that right
But they wouldn't
Scores
It would reduce their traffic
Traffic
Racing stuff
Alex Jones in the next clip
I was going to scream but CNN and it's
It was a picture on his rug
This this borders on funny
But it's it's still not
There's something weird about every major CNN host I don't know where they grow these people
I just realized our demons Milos Bellaire
Photos
Screen is a picture of him at an adult swim party it's just clearly like a Getty Images
Anyway
No no no no no no
We got to go on the ride
Looks like it
Still not named hit the Quan
Uncle you really impressive and what happening right now
Photos
One thing that you should watch
And this is the true comedy of this
Steve pieczenik is on the phone
Bear on the phone
He'll show up at the end of this clip
It's just funny to know that he's silently there this whole time
I don't look at it
It sounds like Alex is tickling
Sexual harass
Cooper
Sorry there
Psychiatrist or as a psychiatrist
He's asking for 10:00
He's not relevan
Choir
But at the same time to Alex still always charm
To tickle yeah big but unfortunately it turns bad
Steve pieczenik says
Sandy Hook
Parkland
And when should looking at is the nonsense of the
Vestiges of the
Depressed trying to be relevant
How long does it go
Let's go on
It just like where this place
He went on the run on Owen Shroyer
Flower Angel Parkway
And all this s***
It's it's unacceptable answer
This is level of s*** I don't want to deal with
There was a
Take me away
Take me away to a better place
What's this I hear
What's this I hear in the distance
I got the trees
Play the song are you just playing this by yourself
Sometimes when you're really frustrated about a right-wing propaganda
When you're frustrated about a right-wing propaganda
Would you put on a time travel
Mellow out a little bit
Like flashback song
Alright we find ourselves now time-traveled back 2006
2 points
Real quick
First off
Let me make a point real quick you're a bit killer
Let's try to do a b**** you f****** walked all over it
Look better about time
I'm sorry
I will do it on the next time travel
Alright
Why is it
But these guys are always
Liberals are such but they're all triggered all this
And the way they describe everybody's appearance is like
It makes me shudder in
Is Brian stelter
To make you curl up into a ball like a little
A little baby that's interesting but since I am in 2006 right now
I have no idea
So he was certainly not on CNN
There's a method to my madness
Yeah we're now in 2006
Don't make me
LOL baby so we're now back in 2000
Thanks for very specific reason the 2006 for whatever reason
David Lynch
Infowars
Very nice let's do this
Let's do this
Smooth
Wouldn't have gone back to Brian stelter
David Lynch
Would putting out
Inland Empire
I don't
I never will understand
Anybody
The exception invitation
From Alex to come on because
You kind of have to know that there's a reason
Like if you're going on and you're not one of The Wack Pack
Chaddock
Matt Bracken
These type of guys
Gerald Celente
Look if you're not one of these guys
And he's calling you like if you're David Rothschild come on
You got to know there's an agenda
And David Lynch.
I don't think he realizes that there's a
Legenda 2y hour
Alex wants to have him on
And you could never know what this address
Now it's surprising people who come on
And have their own agenda the Takeover
Like
Christopher Walken
Salon
It's interesting that you bring that up cuz generally
Whenever Alex does something like
Like this
You end up with
The world's worst
Interview
He's a terrible because you have Alex who has his agenda
M4m
Who has their agenda
And they're working across purposes
They can never get quite on the same page
Quite frankly
Adapters right
Because there
We're clearly told beforehand you can come on to promote your XYZ thing
Yes that's what those interviews except some questions and what have you but
David Rothschild even said as much I'm here to talk about my book and Let Live Earth concert
Sins that are like hey what are you and then your next question is
So you got a new movie coming out right all goes here's the introduction analysis
I think he is with Lynch
The Elephant Man
The TV show
Great mover
Barnes & Noble
North Ogden
Right now
Talk to you Alex
What the f***
He's lifting credits he likes
I even like
Right I mean it does seem like
Where do Taco holder
Alex has some theories about Lost Highway wants to run at
Now before we get to that Alex really want
To know what Inland Empire is about
David Lynch
When in 20
I don't understand
Who was Bob
Alex really wants to know right off the bat
What Inland Empire is about
David Lynch
Surprised by this
Isn't thrilled with that sort of question
Peconic buttheads a tiny bit
Well I say about it is it's a story of a woman in trouble
Pretty complex
Well you know Alex I love
Stories
Chicken early
Alright one level
Concrete
That hold abstract
And abstraction
Things that Cinema can
AR
You know we experience in life
Cinema can
Play them so it's Anna
Experience B Ford
Cinema 10
Stupid questions
And I sitting
It's a beautiful language
Film
And
Speak American
Say Inland Empire
Kohl's
Some of this
What Alex is saying there is
My audience is stupid
How to do a thing
Alright that'll break
There's a lot of
Music
Abstract
My heart that I need to ask
Express at the same time
I have to deal with reality and I think
Text the two together
But seriously
What the f***
Is the movie about a little depression drifted to Ventura
Jaybird music
Inland Empire
Bless your heart man it's
Story of a woman in trouble
And I'm
And Annette
You know
So he's not going to get that plot synopsis
I think I think it might go up there we see the first indication of
Do men not seeing eye-to-eye on what
Conversation
Because
A decent interviewer would have heard that
Lymphocyte answer and maybe ask the question about film
Do you know where would have like a follow-up on that that sort of thing
And Alex is like
Tell me the plot
A book report
Your guest has already indicated I'm not interested
Telling
The plot of the
You know there's
There's a guy in Silicon
Your your next question is like
You're just going for another lap
Around the same thing
To go into a movie not know
Too much cuz nothing you enter a world
In front of Bebop
Nothing to say at this point to Alex
Pictures of theory about Lost Highway
I'm intrigued
You called out
Any comments on from the director of
Call Paulding
You know I've been
Back on unlocked Highway
I wrote the screenplay with Barry Gifford
Screenplay together
We've never really talked
About this
It was
At a time when the o.j. Simpson trial is going on
And you know
Similar things with the character Fred Madison
Human being can do a thing
So horrible
And keep on living in
Smiling and as O'Jays
Golf
So
There is a thing that we've discovered a
Psychogenic
Fugue for the mine
Self to
Hi the horror of
Something done
What you thought
Yeah and Alex
Heard psychogenic
Yuga
And I got the word wrong asking
Very weird
Embark song
Well it's in OU
You can I won't say anymore but
The thing is this
More often than not
In the long run
Nothing stays hidden
So
There you go
Cuz I'm trying to control myself be honorable
Good for you out it
That's that's bad
I'm having a psychogenic
Because I want to be honorable
What is the psychogenic
I am struggling right there when he's laughing and all that it's the two parts of him that's like
I want I love this guy
Cuz I think he is a fan
I think it feels like he is David Lynch fan
But at the same time there's something he wants
To ask him
That he can't directly ask him
That's inside Alex
There's something that like
He's hoping he can just
Pivot Point that'll get him to
The topic
Vicky wants the interview to be about and so far it's kind of about creativity
Probably a metaphor
At this point Alex retreat
I was like all right you came on to talk about your book
Ask about you
Okay
Catching the big fish
Meditate
Consciousness
Creativity
And it's
Facebook
You know of
You know
Lights
33 years of
Meditation
And
A works with
Sketching ideas
Because I
You know ideas are like fish
And we can we can catch the side
Ideas
Cleaner of conch
We can pitch ideas
Deeper in
Creativity
Bowling
By learning
Contacting that
Founded infinitode
Inside every
Human being
And it feeds the creativity
And it feeds the joy of doing things
Wisdom
Confirm Mark Frost
I don't even I don't really
You know I'm
No
Okay
You never mind
Some sort of pagan
I don't know cuz it's a non-sequitur to him talking about his book which
Is just pimping Transcendental Meditation
Bad news about Trump
Colt
Yeah
It's a giant
Giants
Wasn't the guy who popularized by his jokes
Before
Rape charge
I don't know about that I don't know a whole lot about his personal history
I don't think it's
Well I mean I'm sure it's terrible but I don't think it's relevant
To like the David Lynch
Appearance here
Nor the the nature of
Transcendental Meditation
I would have you
It being on par with Scientology
Without the horror stories
The public house
Stories
Without the history of blackmail and private investor
It sound
It's it's
Some really crazy stuff
Why once you once
You start to look into it
I think it's
But pretty
Generally
Evil thing
That is
Blackmailed Mark Frost
Putting owls
I don't know I don't know I don't want to jump in half-cocked on the
Quite frankly
Can I
From all the research that I've done
Intuit
I think what they do is they take something
Very positive
That is meditation
And they've made
I very dangerous
It's called around
So you
The positive benefits
You are
You achieve through meditation
Bye
Buy gradual
Indoctrination
Can you associate them with this
Group
I am
I don't know
I've read I read a bunch of stuff about
About the practices they have and it's good
Traditional
Meditation
And start going into like a autobiography of a yogi and floating and
So fly
I'll just go ahead and jump into the
ATM stuff might as well we've already broached the subject
What David Lynch
She is going to
Didn't do a little bit here on this episode
Does who who sells
Do you know people like
Jim Carrey
Google list
Celebrity practice
The Amazon
The mile-long
It's really good for you
But
They claim and their the hook
Is that it's a relaxation Bass
I like you
You know that's how you open the door
But
You have to you have to get in
You have to pay for class
I generally speaking they're about $1,000
Or more
Unless you get them through your school
Cuz a lot of schools have meditation program
Moms that are done through
Transcendental Meditation
I did not know that they do those the students don't really have
To pay for those but of course not
Going to subsidize Transcendental Meditation.
I don't know I don't know
I haven't done enough Research into that too
Like say where the schools are that are doing it but I'm a little uncomfortable with it because of its Brandon
Worry just
Can kidsmeditation I be totally into
A+
And I am School Transcendental Meditation
You pay for these classes
URI undergo a ritual
Call Sachi
I called the Puja I don't like Rachel's at the end
A mantra
That's supposed to be your personal Mantra and met in the idea of it is sort of that if you tell anyone what your Mantra is
Then it stops working
Which is a way that they
That way they can just give out the same mantra.
Because of the nature of this
Puja ceremony
They're trying to present this idea that they're creating a personalized mantra
It's leaks then
Documents
The show that how they choose the mantras
That's the only thing that's based on
And so they get around that
Now
Disappointing like
Even a good
Comment along those lines
I can do some cold reading
Is a little bit of intuitive like seeing if you're falling for this
You need to push harder or if you're going along
People who have been
Charles Manson
Well here's the interesting thing I wanted
Demontra thing
Is
Arbitrary
Words what is your mom
Well t.i. I actually fooled around with this a little bit in the past
Speak to
Affect
Let's say
Video of years ago from a guy who used to be a
Teacher of Transcendental Meditation
The group speaking out again
Practices of
How it is essentially
Like the Puja ritual that you go in
It's basically induct
It's putting you in a trance like
Giving you this mantra
And then there's a bunch of follow-up
S*** you have these like procession
You have to go to today
If you're doing it right with the reflex
Hammer of that transfer
Teaching YouTube
Get into the trance
State yourself
The Mantra that they give you is super unimportant
It's just the act of repeating this thing
And so the guy was explaining
Yeah the guy was explains all you have to do is basically choose a slightly long thing
Really have a necessary meaning
To much of a meaning
Your brain will like about the meaning
And so I came up with something and I tried it and like
If you if you do put in like a good
20 minutes half hour
Couple times doing that
Like I did reach some
I'm sort of a state that I would describe as all
Like it was a
My body felt
Entirely different my brain felt like I was going to different plates it was incredibly powerful
Like I felt it felt great
Especially devoid of the teachings of
Outside of their grasp or whatever I think that the method of
Induct inducing a
Transcend yourself
Susie's pretty effect
Kit from from my
Admittedly Limited
Exploration
But now if you were doing that answer on with the Zen Buddhism in the pasture
With Zen Buddhism
You just kind of get there and you shut the fuk up
Bright
I meant
There's a hundred schools of meditation
Another better than
Any other they're all just different routes to quiet
Or whatever
State that I got in
I imagine
Achieving that state
In the presence of people who are trained
To induce that
State
I think it would be
Incredibly vulnerable thing
Scares the s*** out of me the idea that this
Millions of dollar organization
The charges people tons of money and has a bunch of celebrity pimping it
Is sort of based around that
Like the reports that I've read of the ceremony
Is are like
They're manipulative
F***
Lake DDS Central tees
The essential pieces of it are basically undergoing
Like ritualize thing
Is where the instructor tells you to do things
Which is tacitly you submitting
Then you get put in a trance state
You're taught this
Mantra
And then you're able to read
France
Yourself
And I don't think I don't think it any worse than giving you the Holy Ghost
I don't think that you said something about it that I own
Not for my church
Of course not
Either of us if you have those those like really
Wildly Evangelical Church
Is with me you like
Touching
Pan beat up like that a lot of those do also
Do you know Susie like chanting and the jumping around with your trying to do is make you lose your breath a little bit
There are those
What are the
I but II we're not talkin about them today because they aren't the guest on Infowars
The issue that you come to is that like the
You get into it
The more the turtle
It's revealed to you
The idea that it's relaxation
Clearing your head and creativity
Sort of Fades away in the later stages
If you keep going
You end up learning all kinds
Good things about life
Spiritual Purity moral perfection
Getting in touch with
With the cosmic consciousness
Eventually their weekend
Retreats that explain like
Communing with
God consciousness
Oh that's great personalized you can get in touch with
She's really f***** up
Considering they're charging
Tons of money for all the
I don't I don't like anything.
Eventually
Level right if you just
If you just give us more money you're going to get to reach the next level
Speaking of which
You can become a policy wonk
So I think I think
You can use the technique
Transcendental
Meditation teaches
2 as a conduit
Too good meditation
I sincerely think that's okay
Of
Church
I think you can do that but
I have
I have some very serious misgivings
About
Transcendental Meditation
As an organ
Innovation
And then further I think
That
Careful
With this sort of method
Inducing a transfer meditation
Because
There is a slight
Dissociation
Comes along with
And again I can
Can speak to that
In terms of the
The experience that I had when I was using the
There was a semi
Detachment from my body
Detachment from my brain
Have to get off this
It wasn't that full but I do worry like
There are tons and tons of stories of people who have had
Psychotic break
Because
Of the implicit Association
They can reinforce
Dangerous ideas that
You may have about like things not being real
The stories you can find about
That's not good
Did have to go to rehab or Hospital
Not know you could do that
Dissociation and trance stuff which can exacerbate underlying can
It's not something that should be undertaken
Lightly
And I don't
I don't know that
From what I can find
I don't think
The Transcendental Meditation
Organization is
Careful
With with
Power of the
Did not realize
Yeah
Take to see if you're healthy enough for
Active sex life
I think this meditation last longer than 4 hours
Pretty long at Stanford
I think they're like if you're just doing like mindfulness meditation or something like that
Real Bass
Your earring
In the clear
Other other techniques
Rite Aid
Can be I can be a little little much
I think I think it would be the same thing with
Do you know if you look at
Almost any cultures
Yoga practice
You know I think you do end up with
You know what the whirling dervishes
Hey dude
Dissociate
To a certain extent
Advice
Write a lot of culture
Truth have
The idea of the
Communion with God
Implicit within it is dissociation from yourself
And that's not always
I don't know
Can a fine line here
The real bottom of it
Ultimately consciousness
Everybody realizes implicitly at the very like base level
Being aware sucks
Like don't you wish you were unaware don't you wish you weren't
I think I think
Just a bundle of instincts and hurt your love
You using a Tango where is the wrong word I think
I think it's more are you tired of being yourself
41 a little break
From
Normal
Whatever
Anyway
I just think
It's interesting
Play coffin
Alex Jones
Mtume I think David Lynch
Is a little bit more of a villa
Because he has
The David Lynch Foundation
Transcendental Meditation
Have you selling a flex because they casted Kyle McLaughlin
But to assume that should never have
It look
I don't I want to get into casting decision
Either
I love
Fan
He's on here to pimp this book
Can the big fish and that's just a book that
Extolling the virtues
Transcendental Meditation
Automatically
Ebooks
Transcendental Meditation don't tell you the techniques
Or anything like that
To go to the classes right that's part of it
Thousand dollars
The people who are the
The teachers have to sign an oath
Includes the following Passage
I acknowledge the prior to receiving the training I had no prior knowledge of such a system of teaching
That there is no other available Source where the knowledge
Such teaching may be obtained
That such training is secret unique
I'm a link in the chain of organization
Seems that you have founded
Purity of the teaching and movement
You have laid down the wise rule that should I ever cease to teach at
I'm feeling the blank
Organization
Or any other organization founded by you for the purpose of teaching Transcendental Meditation
I may be restrained by appropriate process from using the secret teaching
Transcendental Meditation imparted to me
It's probably the law
I mean the way I read that is that an implied gag order
Copyright
Occidental
Meditation techniques
I think that's what that
Essentially a contract we're like I won't respect this a secret at unique
And if I ever leave I wouldn't tell these secrets
Conditions
Think it's like a differently worded non-disclosure agreement
A lot of
People
Maybe
I've held to it
2018 plenty of people who come out
Explained exactly what is going on
But David Lynch's book The catching a big fish is not going to be like here's the techniques
You can use at the end
Out the Workshop near you or whatever
And so is his appearance
Infowars
But
We know
Have
Established
Do you want to talk about
He wants to talk about his book that is selling fan
Transcendental Meditation
Alex still has a different goal
We haven't established yet
After he is
Been butting his
His head up against the wall with the stupid question that have nothing to do with David Lynch just said
I don't think
Appointment next clip but
Evil is a strain
Think about
There's plenty of it
Especially just on the
Surface of our world
And and
You know what's in a ball with
Negativity
And negativity is like a
Who sings float Nana's
And we got it a big
And if you want to blow that
Negativity away
All you have to
Is wearing
Died within
Everyone
U-GRO that light up
And a side effect of that is negativity
D2 enlightenment
The full potential of the human being is there
And the keto
Peace On Earth Is there
Very very beautiful
Ryder
Any of your latest films are works
Is there any archetype
World War II
No
Direct
Throat again no again Lynch's going off on this
Like
You know
Can see the ocean
Three stars
You specifically like
Advocating the Bennett
Transcendental Meditation World TV
No big deal if you don't Transcendental Meditation all I'm saying is that you're the reason Wars happen
Instead goes to the
It seems like he was really close to being like
Stop talking about this whole motion
Well so at this point Alex is like
Come out with it and ask you a question
Like dipping his
Towing
Movies filmed
Let's mix it up on the erect
Clip
David Lynch Noah's what Alex wants to ask
Alex
Keeps being like
I want you to bring this up
I don't want to be an a****** you bring this up
But sooner or later I'm going to be an a****** David a where
No
You know what they say that
Reflects our world
And I think that ideas come out of
You know her
Are feeling the world in
The ideas themselves that I get our separate
Message
Me to you know do anything at this time
Ideas that you get
You fall in love with them
You see the way Cinema
Translate those ideas
David Lynch's explained
Creativity
Right
The creative process really good job so far
And then you're rolling
And a whole thing comes out
And only later as more and more of it comes out.
Simard UCF
You know like that
You don't set out to
Calamansi
You commented
Hellboy
Just commented on the film loose change
Yeah you wanna.
Do you want on Dutch television in the interviewer asked him about that
Glue strain
I don't know
It's very weird but
He's sitting there anyways like I have a lot of questions about 9/11
He talks about 9/11
Well
Not really Alex's
David Lynch's just confused
So on
In the
Where is New York
Say anything in the clip I watched
You didn't say anything negative about
Lustre
She doesn't say anything
Let's to say like they're right
About their conclusion
These sorts of questions
Make you look
At what you see
You think you experienced in a different way and I have questions that I don't I don't understand
Like the Pentagon
The hole in the building
Is too small for a plane I don't understand what happened
These questions haven't been answered
And then the host is like I
What about the ideas that the
He's like those sorts of ideas are too big
For people to think
Like your brain can't handle those sorts of ideas
The ram
He's implying that the
Kyle McLaughlin
Antebellum
So
Alex wants
They can get the horse
I want to talk 911
Dubrow
That's all he wanted to get to
You know what now that I go back
Can think about it
Did
I don't think
I don't think Alex gave him the Mulholland Drive credit
Alex doesn't like Mulholland Drive
Fire walk with me
This leads to the two of them talking about
Deal
Why why
You know I knew they were going to bring it up
And
What I said
Yeah we're we're all you know like
Detectives human beings are
Detective
Like-for-like
Even for context clues I can't figure out if he was saying the light detector was or we are
Similar to detective I have no idea
It's within character to say either
Immediately after Transit
Meditation
We were like
Do he's going to talk about light and darkness
Add about how like
The answer to Darkness
Is adding more light
Sorry I do think you might be saying we're like Detectives
I have no idea
Look at our world
And we keep looking at it
Can we get these
Feeling
There's more going on than
CI
And you know this is a
It's a world of Clues the world of
Mystery but the mystery can get you know
Can get salt
And
You can
Find these answers
You know
A lot of these things
Within
As far as 9/11 goes
What bears
You know
There's things that
Esau
The Conjuring
Question
And wondering
And some
He doesn't seem
Quite right
So it makes us
Wonder
We need
That's all
Before 911
Was just trying to brag that he predicted 9/11
Infowars 2000
Before you
Call Dad
America
Hell
Exposing
You have concerning my love
I have the same
They were brought up in all this
You mentioned
And I just don't have the
Turism
Is there like there's a lot of really weird stuff
But the explanations given
I meant I think this is what he saying
Because in the end
And it any of these 9/11 documentaries that you're going to watch
My reason quotes
What you're going
To find
If you're going to find
Answers
You know what I mean they provide an answer and if you if you are David Lynch
And you have
Leesville
And you're coming away from it saying like
I got I got questions about a lot of this stuff
And you don't have answers that means you're rejecting the answers that are given in documentary
Implied
Did you like this is unsatisfactory as an explanation but I'm still an option
Right
You know what I think especially as we are people who do a
Podcast about it
Propagandistic
Theorist
I think there is a pressure to have an answer and I appreciate David Lynch coming down here being like
Panthers
I have no idea
By weird things
Questions answers
Can ask me that question
Ship documentary.
That's a good one
Check out their bibliography
I don't know actually cuz it wasn't so just ask
G Blake
Produced it
So they might actually
Have an article
Anyway
Lynch's Inc
Questions not answers
Leads into this
Which I think is
Fanciful bulshit
Unless there were a controlled demolition
I understand Alex
Do you know
Are there spirits
This question
The rising from each of the events that day
I don't have the
I just have the
The you know
Instinct means I'm hungry I want
Is 4011
When you learn to dive with him
Which is so
Beautiful image
Experience
Human
Human neck
Experience the new understand 9/11
Impact the ocean of
Knowing that
Your vibrant
Intuition growth
Intuition is like
It's an ocean of solute
You get this is going
You know it
You know
Call Art
Processes and
Call creative process
Nothing we do is
Man
Doesn't you know start with
It starts
Idea
Catching those ideas
Being away
I'm going away.
Translate.
And make it feel correct based on the eye
Idea
It just goes like
Fat
At this point I think what he's essentially pushing is
911 is solvable
Through transcendental
Ninety-nine percent sure that
What he's telling out
That's a weird thing for him to say
Considering he doesn't have any answers
All the time
Complete enlighten me
Understand where the 9/11 questions are
That's where the answers are
You have to be calling
About 9/11
There's a hundred bucks a month
You can't wait to hear the audio drop for that way
I'll tell you that right
I think there is a p
Piece of this Theory self-contradictory
You just brought up
Which is that idea that like answers are within
I am one of the world's most leading transcendental meditators
And I'm telling you I don't have an
Which leads me to believe just using
Haven BB then see
I even sort of argument you don't
Dancers aren't with it
But I'm going to take away
23 Pages released
Intuition going when we
See things
Powerball
Handle
WhatsApp contact
At what will what did you just say in the beginning
F****** talking about
That brain of ours
He say we only use five or 10% of it
Nobody says that
Show you that when you
Oriental deepest level of life
Full brain
He is engaged
And it's the only Xperia
Brings the whole
Brain
Into you know quotes
Brainstorming
Thinking you know.
Do it
So Alex
Super brainstorming is what he's talking about
But because David Lynch hasn't used
Specific languages
It's really going to set off the buzzers
He's allowing like what he said very like
Transcending
Allows you to use all of your brain
These RTM talkin
Scarlett Johansson
Great Neck trying to indoctrinate Alex's audio
He's trying to use this appearance
From Christ
Oh boy
That's why David Lynch one on info
That's not off brand
Kind of does that in almost every interview
I'm not going for the Transcendental Meditation
No I bet
Seducing
Everyone
That's not what I'm talking about the other side of this bridge
I think you understood a word I've said this in
They come back
From break and then at this point
It just sort of turns into
Sales pitch
Subway
Olympian ass Heather
Refinishing
Fusion more 21
You know Alex it's it's
Something we just don't
Hear so much about in the western
So much misunderstanding about meditation
There's so many
Kinds of meditation
But there truly is
A Within
And if you think about it so many steps
Since we've heard have the word with him
Within within within the fence
Wizard of Oz
The Kingdom of Heaven which lies within
And all else
Will be added unto
Experiencing that deep
Problems on the surface
Know thyself
Strfkr
And once things get better
Shirley
He has his gold
Christopher Walken interview to rehab in it
And for him to just randomly be like
We cooked
I love this salad
9/11 was an inside job
And these tomatoes that he made
F****** incredible
Put pepper on them
He really got
Some butter in their kind of baked it a little bit 9/11 was an inside job
I made the chicken with also had steak
Because we're hey we're very rich I think walk-ins crazy like a
Enough to not do that
Akira probably I imagined to be in the middle of talking about that salad they were making
Say something crazy and walk away just knowing that I'm not here
Continental
Crazy
Well I don't want to talk to him about that
But David Lynch I could take his credit
He knows that like I'm not going to talk 911 with you I'm going
How to use your questions in your repeated badgering
Chamoy
As a way to like hey 9/11 just one of the problems on this Physical Realm surface
When in reality all religions
Have been talking about the within that only we can really give you access to worship
Exactly
So here's the last clip of it takes us out of the interview and again
Strathmore
It's Lynch
Shillingford
Call Vicky Quest Power Switch
Because you know all I ever ask me questions
You know
It is when you see that
Make you wonder about
Theme
Pictures of the building question
I like those pronunciation
Steel
There's so much
Mini problem
In our world
So much
Negativity
Don't worry about the dark
Turn on the light
Darkness
Automatically goes
Help do that for yourself
Activity one of the selling points on Transcendental Meditation
Website
In terms of like there
Can 24 in other countries in Institution
Like that is a dramatically decreased into
Dental terrorism
Sure
Even part of the eyes
It's hard to sell on their website it's like
Transcendental Meditation it's hard give you a mantra and that Mantra will be
Studies about Transcendental Meditation is really difficult to tell how much of it
Should be trusted
I am quite frankly I don't have the key
Kind of time to go pour over all the
Details for just one episode 339
Cuz a lot of it a lot of the research has been done by proponents
Transcendental Meditation
It looks like their methodology is good but it's really tough to say they may have a dog
In the fighter.
Right I mean like statistical studies generally are not accepted and left.
Through independent
I don't know I don't know enough
To say
A pun
On studies about
Transcendental Meditation
But if it is just going through being made about like relaxation
Increase happiness
Get that with all sorts of meditation
It stopped
It's tough to take the
The practice and the organization
And deal with them separate
Related to practice does have been
But the organization
Is a manipulative
Squirrely
Call religion
That's fair enough
And then we remembered really doing
Something
Bring bring that light of unity
All diversity
Is appreciated in the light
Of unity
It will be so beautiful so easy
All power is the creator of the universe
Auto problem
Petexec
YouMail best charity starts at home
Barnes & Noble
Anytime Barnes & Nobles
Thought it was a good speaking refers
You know what people BFF people
You know have
Question
They have the right in this can
Country by golly 2 in
Raise the question
Absolutely
Dino II support
Enlivening Unity
Potentially human being by doing that everyone
I have that but you know ability
And then let's start working on real
Dynamic
For the world
All these other problems
You know
Mostly a ridiculous
Certainties
You know we
Parting shot with
I'm trying one more time
Hey Google
This is a classic Alex Jones interview with someone he admires
Their work
And that like
If you can't be a dick to them
Strfkr
The other person has a goal
It's a terrible interview conversation
Course at least trying to engage with the things Alex says
And weave them into what he wants to talk about where's Alex
Just keep talking.
Now
I think it's
Disgraceful that Alex Jones
Even if
If I put myself in the head of someone who believes
This world
I think it's disgraceful that he had David Lynch on
Because David Lynch
Is a big
Big
Part of the Transcendental Meditation
Movement
Right now
Who is Alex Jones's big anime
Global
Liberal
The globalist work
Towards
You know what this point I really don't know like everything was big fear
Mind control
World
In 1976 the followers of Maharishi Mahesh Yogi
Started the world government of the age of enlighten
Spread the teachings of Transcendental Meditation globally
Well there you go in 2001 they established Global country of World Peace
Quote
It's not a good name for a country
The global country of world peace was founded by Maharishi Mahesh Yogi
As a Consortium of educational organizations in more than 100 countries working
Create a new era of Peace progress and prosperity in our world family
The global country of world peace is a quote Nation Without Borders
Promoting Unity Consciousness in the reduction of narrow nationalism
That divides Humanity from Humanity
A peace-loving people
Everett
Loving people everywhere
Alex Jones also has some ideas
About believing in
Deflating the currency you what have you
Look up what country for World Peace has their own currency
Call Dora
What is equivalent to $10
Music
Gold standard
For a long time
Global country of world
Switch is a organization within the transcendental movement
In Yogi's Without Borders I believe yeah it's better than friends
Are part of the larger organization that all
Strong force out of Maharishi Mahesh Yogi
Country
From a 2001 article in the independent
Quote
Disciples of Maharishi Mahesh Yogi the Beatles
60 water found a Sovereign Nation in South America
They've offered the government of Suriname 1.3 billion dollars over 3 years
At least 35 Hundred Acres
For a year or Utopia 20 miles
Northeast of the capital.
Paramaribo
The proposed
Global country of world peace wood minted
Currency
Maintain the central bank
And have its own legal
Enough money to spend 1.2 billion dollars
Set alarm money
Of the celebrities who are apart of the organization 8
So many more than psychology
Liking people just don't talk about it because it's not as scary and they don't have all that gay black male
But you don't have don't have like
Like Tom Cruise John Travolta are
Massive star
He's a big star but he's probably one of the most
Famous vocal proponent
Nearly on the level of Tom Cruise
And that kind of helped Scientology they got a bigger guy
But so they can trying to start their own country
The country in Costa Rica
And I quote
You can't lease
You get leased land and then say your country
In in mid June of this year this is
Some Costa Ricans were contacted by delegates of the religious organization
Global country of world
From then on the indigenous sector of the Central American
Country was immersed
In confrontation
The even on almost reached
Communal divisions in
Physical fight
It happened that the global country is an organization born in India but with a Dutch
Legalization
Supposedly you know they don't believe in
And now supposedly
Its main objective is to reach a single world country Without Borders
With a single currency
A single thought in
In a single ruler
King Maharishi Mahesh Yogi
I want no
I would like Global country World Peace
You guys have a good old time
I don't like having a king
Even came
Costa Rica to a point
The king's Minister the dentist appointment Costa Rica on the margin
And ignoring the Costa Rican state
Aiden
Has owned the currency ROM
Equivalent
Quizlet according to them to $10 on the unit
The indigenous leader leader Lisandro Mendez under the charge of Kik
Of Rica shanty rostra
As Costa Rica was baptized
As in Costa Rica he was baptized
Received from the central
Bank of Netherland the sum of 4 million dollars
He begins to administer this new state
Name his ministers and
Receive a salary of $1,000
This situation
I think there's some translation
The Situation's filled the page
Imagine me
Try the patience or whatever
Exhausted the page
Of the other indigenous
Miss people's in area and their
Send it was a disrespectful indigenous ancestral customs
Ignorance of the country's reality
The community's almost
Confronted each other
Summit favor and others again
The cause was knowing that the global country was trying to acquire 7,000 hectares
The plant organic bananas
In addition to 7,000 hectares to establish the capital of the global country
All of this in indigenous territory
Finally they've learned something from the white
From colonialism
Thanks guys you took the right thing for
Finally
Costa Rican president
The members of the sect to leave the country in the shortest time possible
Integrity of the company
Hey guys
You can't have your own country go away so let's just look at these
Little Things
But I've brought up here at the end of this episode
This
Global country for World
Which is a part of the transcendental organization
Crazy guy you know what I want to say that there's a possibility that there's something Lost in Translation there to like
The single ruler being King Maharishi Mahesh Yogi
That might be translated correctly as possible but it might also be a thing where I like that single thought ruler
Ideological ruler good but
Right
He was also
Dead by 2000
I'm to be there as it may
Like what you have here is a a rank history
Here in Costa Rica and Suriname
Of them trying to buy land
Impugn the territorial sovereignty of these countries
Do you like
Would be super again
You have their larger goal this would just be the beginning of
To create a one world government with one world
You're being
You want to create a nation Without Borders
Narrow nationalism that divides
Humanity
You have things that are principally against with Alex Jones stands for
When you talk about Lynch got to listen to talk about the global
Alex Jones throws darts at all the f******
Time as we discussed in the end game coverage
Like you look at a hoss
The leader of the council
Council on Foreign Relations
In his essay that he wrote about globalization and sovereignty
He discusses the need to retain Sabra
But to have the definition
Being adjusted
To reflect
The fact that we live in a global world
Right things that happen in other countries affect
What happened
To you and your sovereign country
And
Non-national organization
Are affecting everybody
That currently we have economies with outboard
There is
Nothing
The stuff
I've read from Alex Jones Boogeyman globalist
Weather actually saying
We want a One World Government
Vade
Yeah but
Come on they made Mulholland Drive
You didn't seem to like that one like that one
Eraserhead
Alex you're so blinded by your strfkr either you accidentally had somebody on your show
Who's promoting ideals of an organization that actually wants a One World Government
Congratulations you dumb f***
Goddamnit he never fails to surprise me
He's dumb
He's so dumb
Go suck it Alex
You want more of the show you
What the f***
God we've got
We still got the Easter sale going on Budu Blount run Twitter at knowledge underscore fight
You can find us on Facebook
New group
Check us out go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
I got to show I'm doing a show at the Improv in Schaumburg
March 4th
I can come out and see that
Improv Schaumburg
If you are still available
Flights are cheap right now you
Stay in Schaumburg
Beautiful
Boring suburb
Say it I'm thrilled by a lot of these International we've been way out for a while
We've interacted you probably haven't but I've interacted with her online
I'm thrilled by a lot of these new internationalist
Coming out of the like the woodwork
Like I receive semesters when people then
London
Other parts of England
Finland
Just in the last week it's crazy Denmark
It's not theirs that I don't know what the
I don't have her finding this but
It's awesome
It's awesome I hope inventurex with these folks
Also to everybody out there who's emailed me about The Avengers in
Initiative
I appreciate that I will get back to you because of the endgame stuff I throw to put
Responding
Emails on hold
But I will be getting back to you and I appreciate
Your post
Soundbite
Is coming
You get your own private soundbite
Bombshell
That's not private
It'll just
Also if you did email me if you did email me about that that stuff
Please email me again
With you you want to be from Little Caesars
At this point Rocket Raccoon
Everyone else is still in airplane
Are the West Coast Avengers Marvel
All the Marvel characters in the eventual TT
Yeah everybody who's
Iteration
This is stupid Star Wars
Listening
Yeah you got
I would like to say
Maharishi Mahesh Yogi
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work