Hey buddy
This is podcast
Do beverages
Talk a little bit
About Alex
Coming in with a little introduction for a little Minnesota today
What we've got for you is excerpt that we did on Monday night
With the rest of the episode of decided
To chop off a bunch
Cuz
Tried to cover a little bit of Alex Jones is rhetoric
Viva viva
Parkland shooting
And what it turned into was kind of a repetitive
I didn't I didn't feel like that at the end of the day when I look back at it but it
How much does
Conversation
The larger country
Nation of the world
And I felt like we were just retread
Old territory that was gone over over and over and over again
About how I
Alex Jones
Then tragedy
Situations
We talked a little bit about
The
Patient with YouTube
Applying to Alex's
Channel
And already when we recorded it on Monday and now
Here on Wednesday
Evolved
To the point where I think
We have a different point
That we'd like to make
Which hopefully we'll talk about 4
Next episode
From all that there was a piece
What we cover that
I think is very
And I think it is relevant
In relation
Shooting
I'm suffice
How to say Alex
Acting way out of line
That
The victim
We just got in and I was very standard for him
He's throwing around rhetoric about
This is the globalist
Just hoping he says every time
Feels a little bit cornered and sales have dipped a little bit icy
It's kind of
That's a lot of the stuff that we covered it
Beginning
Episode
Talk about a very bizarre
That happens the day after the shooting
Marjorie
Douglas
It's cool and that was that Alex Jones
Students
Gentleman by the name of Jalen Martin
I on the show
And
That is something that is worth looking at
Daiso
That will be what we covered today I hope you all enjoyed
Can have a good one
I will be back tonight with another episode
There's a whole lot to go over Alex
This world is falling
The part right in front of his eyes
Through all of it
The triumphs emphasizing episode
But I will do my best
Enjoyed
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
We heard that Alex Jones reference
That
There was a kid from the
School on his show
Yeah
By the name of Jalen Martin
The internet has gone up in a flutter of beabull
The governor
Needs to protect him cuz
He's going to get killed
For the things that he has said
And then another side of the internet
He's not real
Or he wasn't a high school student there wasn't
At the school
All of them are pretty crazy
I was able to
Find the argument that he's not a high schooler
I posted a link to this
Website called sex
Cecc
Cedar Point
It's like a conservative
News blog of some sort
New should never be anywhere near the
Conservative conservative
Blog
Some sort
He was a writer or is the writer perhaps
But he wasn't
The high schooler but if you read his bio
Clearly
Vindicate
She's still in school and plans to go to college this fall
But interesting Lee his name is taken off the writers page
The other website
So use the Wayback machine cuz I wanted to see like if this was some internet
But I pulled up from August 23rd 2017 but with less articles
Cuz I hadn't been written at the time
I have the same bio and
You know the only thing that I wanted
Take away from it is
Jalen has been expanding his knowledge of the political world
For nearly three years
Specifically since June 16th
Husband
So he is at his libertarian and conservative views that were called
From studying the history of Barry Goldwater
And that's not wrong to have conservative views or anything like that it doesn't
Add some sort of a monster
Amazing already and Infowars guy
Yeah you're not upset
At at least
He's not there yet
He's a trump supporter who writes for a
Yeah
Eno
What are you going to do
When can you do that's how I feel about
Isabel
He has as much
License
To speak about his experience
Is literally anybody else in the world
He has every right
To do that wherever he wants to
Hey I feel as bad for him
As I do for the other
Sewer being assaulted
Attacked online
By the people saying he's not a high schooler
Confirm everything that's available everything I can see he is
He was a student at
School
The same crisis actor attack
Coming from the other side
And it makes me really sad
It make it bums me out
There's a further problem
Oh no
When you when you have that long pause that means
It's a pretty big problem I'm not going to be stoked about it a mi into the inner
Review and I'll get to the problem as it comes up
The first problem is that Alex Jones repeatedly says the name of the school drawing
Which is
Even if you're going to misspeak one
But if you're going to consistently call it and majority Stoneman
You don't know if you don't have a grasp on the issue
Consistently saying the name of the school wrong
I'm not going to take your in-depth
Information with as much
You know
Credibility the research you don't know the name of the goddamn School
Anyway
John Martin
A senior
Stoneman Douglas
High School North
Miami
But the context here
Is the background KHOU
Florida summer baseball tryouts
He's a top sports reporter
I hope they talk about the Xbox
Going on
Just like
The top
Animals
Wasn't God Runner
So what he's done already is
Jaylen Barker
Is Our Guest
Acting like he's going to go to him
Yeah right before he does
Set up
Did what he wants to do
And that is
He brings up this other Narrative of a mass shooting is already
False flag
He has no evidence of that
He's established
While also saying this you got the baseball aspect
But this reporter who is there who talked to that girl who we've already rest
Too sad that she ran in
The shooter
On the way out
So he's already contextualized where he wants this to go
If this is a subtle memory
This is a thing that you can do to try and get people
To remember things
Things differently
Even if it's like what investigators during an ethical when they're questioning saucepan
It's how you
Tell you frantic if you did this in court
Be there
Just like where
Just go into things and Shay
Get to Gail's Flags just for fun
No
This is Frank man
I was fake
Sometimes.
Reports say that I said no one shot that's a hoax they always put out
Blame the victim
No such statements
MSNBC
Other online
So
In this rambling introduction
To his
Oh s*** yeah
I did not expect that
Yeah it's weird
Alex
Introducing his gas
He is laid out
The stuff we've already talked about
CNN is going to lie about us
We are victims we were we are maligned by everybody and so is Trump
Two longer
Too long of an introduction
Show
Joining us
Give him my condolences for any friends
Talk about white
Empathy for real my condolences now now is a great time
When you f***
That's unreal
I cannot hear that
Stuff
Really f****** bad stuff
The Secret Service
SWAT drill
I told you you know where ever talk to
Lone gunman
AKA Tim McVeigh AKA Lee Harvey Oswald
Hi. Did you know this
Alex
I'd like to start off with saying I don't know
Okay
Beginning of eclipse
Pea-size to set up to set up an AKA
Sing this video of a girl saying that she heard shots
When she was in the presence of the shooter
Rahmani Rambles through all this other b******* about how Infowars it lied about all the time and Las Vegas with us
Volkswagen we know all this information sources
Then
Give
One further punch
Did Lee Harvey Oswald and Timothy McVeigh
Are fake lone wolves
Cool Nikolas Cruz is exactly like
View
Is you
Who is a student there
To be my prop
I need someone from the inside
Who I can throw around with as much credibility is the end is doing
With these kids version of that
I need from you is I need you
To validate that there were multiple shooters
And Alex
I mean
You know in our episode about David Lynch
Let me put out on Monday
Episode
Alex Kapp
Badgering him cuz he wanted to talk about 9/11
He does the same thing
This kid
About wanting him to say that there are multiple shooter
I think it's a little bit different
Saying that to a grown man
Directed
Yeah
Mulholland Drive
Little bit different varied if
This is the making a murderer type s*** right here
It's it's
Like I told you the top of the episode
It's incredibly disgraceful
You have no idea how disgraceful
Before we get to that I had an interview with Alex old one
Lawyer press
To pick give me Council on whether or not to
I would want a lawyer who screams
Escrima lawyer
Are you in love you got to pass the bar I have not done that yet but
Pretty easy in Illinois
Think about his experience
Because
I think
You know it Bears hearing
And also I think that Alex is probably going to
To use it
Poorly
But I an explanation
He brings up
Fast forward again to later in the day we hear the fire alarm
Everyone was confused because we already had a fire drill today
Why was the fire alarm going off
So we all just went outside
Easter there for like one minute within one minute
Fire drill
Okay let's go
I mean there's like 3,000
School
So what then like the next three minutes there hasn't been like at least 50 cars there
Not anything serious until I see a helicopter
And within a few more minutes I ended up being a helicopter but
I got reports from people around me
This is a Code Black which means
Elearn
And you could cause mom cuz he didn't have his phone fire drill
There's an active shooter here
Can you like shut up
Teacher walked up
Play I believe it's probably accurate
Or real ale
Came out of nowhere
Noticed
You probably don't want people
Spreading
Erroneous information that hasn't been
Confirm
Don't don't spread that we don't know what the
The situation is
That seems like
The behavior of
Someone who's probably pretty stressed out
Doesn't know what's going on and is responsible for a large massive kid
Yeah like I don't think that to me doesn't sound like
Some sort of cover-up
And I don't think that your first thought is
Okay now you have 3,000 kids
Calling their parents
Can you have
3000 cars
On their way
And there's an act
Yeah you end up with real real bottleneck problem
I don't know exactly like
Hour and a half later than that they caught him
I didn't have a perimeter
Concern
What you going to do
I think that experience is probably sincere and real but I also think that
This teacher trying to enforce a cover-up of some
So also he Jalen goes on to say that
Secret Service
Had a drill at the school a month
Prior
And that just doesn't make sense
Even if you're a conspiracy
Hear it
Cuz the Secret Service is Secret Service
The Secret Service is engaged protecting people like the president and other dignitaries
Treasury
Exactly it's not a it's not like a
Is shoot-'em-up kind of organization in the
You would want the 80s
ATF or DEA or something like that other combination of letters
Nothing to do with this sort of thing
To the idea that he's coming on
It's being that the Secret Service had a drill there a month prior leads me to believe that he got some faulty information about
Who was doing the drill who's the sheriff
Department Iowa
I believe it if it was
SWAT team even or something like that with the terrible world we live in now but the Secret Service aspect
Dove this is
I just heard him say
Tate's hottest codes
The thought of coats
Play Black that's a bomb I remember that
Experience
School
The shelter-in-place kind of drills
But I work at Groupon truck in office
A couple times
Shooter exercise
Cuz they were concerned that someone might be able to come in and shoot up the office
Station treat their workers better
Crossed my mind
Cross my mind while I was sitting in the office
Yeah if I go I hope I thought
Groupon
Next clip we get Alex
Guy doing his first volley
I'm trying to get Jalen
Disabled
I will see how it goes
Michelle Martin
Laying on a recap
The Secret Service had a drill there
I just other place I was asking you what are your friends
Wanted people you're talking to
Autistic
Thought
I was because you obviously had some serious
Cut-out like Sirhan Sirhan
Behind
At what point
When using
Just like Vegas
We got new video on top the other videos where to play as well
Definition
Please elaborate
Yeah I talked to a guy who had a class with him
And he said he was just
Really weird
Did everything people told him to do it was like
I'm just waiting friend
Obviously mental issues
This guy
It was like
When you told me that I kind of like
Makes sense in a way you know
Spanish flag
Compliant like that
There's so many things that they could do just from someone telling them to do it
So he doesn't he doesn't say any doesn't confirm the multiple shooters
Was
Influenceable bread and so
Maybe Annie
Yeah
Like the best Alex can do with that is that
Supports that it's
Somebody controlling
As opposed to
Purely speculative
Someone might be able to tell him to do a thing
Turn around and he doesn't have any knowledge
Picture of the shooter he's basing this on something he heard from someone else
This is second hand information at Beth
Alex
Tried to get him to say
But there was multiple shooters
I'm sorry didn't get what you needed
So
He goes back to the well little bit later
Girl
At the high school
Interesting thing about that is
You know he dropped the gun and Blended in with all the crowd
I just went to Starbucks and it's right there
I would have been walking beside him
Literally on my street
And that's the thing about that is
I heard
There's no way because you would not
I know exactly how long it takes to walk
To my house
He is again asking him to just say that there were multiple shooters
But he goes just far enough that Alex brings him in for a war
Verbal hug
With the you know
The official story is just like everything else
But he knows that he needs more
He needs needs
I think there were multiple shooters
He needs it
A real quote as opposed to his endgame like a conditional
Heard from somebody else I heard that there was
Shooting later it is that
Then of course he couldn't have been anybody with a thinking Blake a functional brain would be able to tell
But that's just like if it's that simple
So Alex goes back to The Well of thirds
And
This is not good
It's going to really make you mad and also probably make you laugh a little bit at the end
But it's this is from one to the other
My friend
Then almost disconcerting ability
This
Is Alex Jones to a T
Badgering a child
In order to use them as a prop for their propaganda argument
That are based in reality and then you'll see what happens
Anyone in your own words the last break
We're getting in your friends coming out as well
Trying to finish
When you talk about people
Coming up
What specifically do your friends and classmates say they thought
Okay so after the school
This is
Third hand basically other girl girl in that video
Who ran into the shooter in the hallway
The girl told my friend who then told
Right
I know you're busy
You got in a windy spot on your walk around outside so we put you on hold of you 25 more minutes
I come back like that
MPerks
Ml Smiler
How to get to a spot where the wind is not blowing up receiver
I'm going to get to Annex
The clips on the front the back of more people
Computers
That's all
That's all coming up we come back or not going to be here
Turkey point that out to me
We got
Shut off all of Shikamaru
Fluoride-free
Toothpaste
Again ladies and gentlemen
We have
50% off super high quality
Fluoride free toothpaste
And it's 425 a coil silver is fortified by quality iodine
Firms in a contradiction some of the top line
But I can tell you right now that some of the top line we're going to FaceTime about
50 Cent
We play
Up to
$3 putting on the Run 2 Step cause different each run
And then
At 7:47 at 15% off right now
It basically lost leader for us but I want to see how great it is
How far are you from the ads over yet so brave
It's available
Additional 10% off is on a auto ship
Each month
Had to get additional 10% off
You get it in your mail
Every 1534
Infowars store
Dot-com
Infowars
When she upgraded as she'll Force Plus
Fifty-three percent office
Why would I buy it now
That will cover the news
So
At 1
F******
You don't do you realize that he had gotten as much out of it as he's going to get out of it
I know you got all right
To talk to her and may have also heard something I think at the same time
He may have said that they still heard shots I think I think
It's possible
Yeah there's wind and Alex is like
Sweet add break
Get the f*** out
Yeah that's it
It's embarrassing it's a disgusting lack of
Optics is what I want to say but this is the game this is
I mean it's the day after the shooting
He has a kid from the school on there badgers in to try and confirm
The multiple shooter narrative the he wants to push
And when he gets close enough he's like your phone's to Wendy I got to do a 2-minute
That's what he does
Does nonsense
He's an illiterate man who also is
Into a weird pill
Multi-level marketing scheme Ray desperately afraid he's going to lose because he got in bed
With the f****** people who were committing treason
Everyone gets
That's what ends up happening that's just the end result that's in the cautionary Tale
You know what I have to say to that
What you going to do
Immediately thought about
Whenever he did that a pivot is all that is is a more brazen
Cable news
It is
It is something that
Should be
That is disgraceful and embarrassing is that is
How much difference is there between
That
And CNN running all of this live coverage and then we're going to have to go to break
Well they're selling toothpaste
How much of a difference really is there
It's different
Because after that 2 minutes
He went to commercial
Oh
That's what's
I mean that's a little that's another level of disgrace
You're right
People disagree with you there be agreement that we have societal gotten into with entertainment
Is someone's got a fund
This entertainment that we water watch
And so we put up with these commercials cuz they pay for it
The entertainment in the shows that we want to watch
In the same way that you do I got to watch a little ad before YouTube video sometimes
Trailers in commercials at the movies
It's just the agreed-upon situation
Alex breaks the social contract by doing commercials in the middle of the show
If he does it
So
Brazenly with the like
I am going
I'm going to do something
Get some Bowman
Intensity and then
Can throw to the commercial cuz I know I put you in a suggest
Edible state right
That's what he's doing
I just don't think
At the end of the day
I don't think there's any
Reason
To engage with him
About
The
The stuff that he's doing right
I do I think that
Vintage
This is not
This is stopped being like
Awful
And this is now
Truly
Pathetic
It's just
What are you
Doing what are you doing
Part of it that's like that
No
All right hope you all got something from the hope we learned a little bit
We saw
I'm very kind of the
The main goal for Alex
The primary goal of course
To say that there were multiple
You believe that
Be the case
The actual
That that is in service
Sing a nice hot
2 minutes
Sales pitch
And right before going
No this is
This is Alex
Heartless pile of garbage
Anyway you want more of our show you can find us
Knowledge
Cam you can check us out at knowledge underscore fight on
On Twitter
You can check us out there
We are on iTunes
That is knowledge fight on iTunes
Probably got a search
The entire thing
We don't know how to make the most of algorithm
Yes we will see you soon