Alexandra Thurston color
A little bit
That is what we do I like the gravelly voice hair
Is there another reason to listen to us besides
Wonderful
Gravelly voice
I know a lot about Alexander
I'm not a serial killer and you are
Apparently
Serial killer
Things to do really quick
Wild episode to go over today
Any is too much
That's probably true owners
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you we appreciate it so much
I also like
What's going on up there Adam
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much thank you very much Adam
Salad biblical names
If that's what we like on knowledge fight we love the Bible here if you believe it's Mary spelled
Maria though Bible
Yourself
New Hope bible
Compulsive walking Guitar website and join up
The new international version of the urban dictionary version of the Bible
Incredibly desperate
Alex Jones did a very depressing and
Ultimately very desperate 34 hour marathon
News from what I heard he had the best
There's so much to talk about so much to go over so much
So I started watching at 11
When the Alex Jones Show
The kickoff of the marathon
Fortnite
Time
I would have done what I 30
4 Hour
Marathon
I would have stopped
In order
If I look at her
Please give us some
We talked about recording on Thursday
In preparation mode for that and it turned out you were busy
I would like endurance challenges
So I started at 11 without looking like a little
So Alex Jones on right out of the gate it's most
Kind of normal I've been being very defensive about the people who are suing him for creating an abusive workplace
There's a lot of that
I have no doubt
You view license but you're not far off
I've never heard anyone
Look into my eyes
He was getting really weird and going on and on about how like
My ex-wife's
Mom is Jewish that means
I like whoa hold on
Technically speaking matrilineal descent
What is why I hate my kids
3 years
These anti-semitic critics
Sopes
Music
Cowley his ex-wife of
Secretly working for Israel through her or something like that
Yeah
Totally
A member of the Jewish community
I'm not entirely sure it's not my business I don't really care
Vehemently
And now because it serves his purposes he's like
Ratatouille that my ex-wife is doing I can't hate them
He has no idea where to go around about this
Dashiki
How do I how do I
This next quote is even worse and this is a direct quote
She has a noble nose but she's not Jewish
That is a very interested
Fruition
Alright
She is
From the Acropolis
Knoxville
Propolis where the Jews
Weird
And then Alex brings in his first guest
And it's that assignment Roche
The sweet slander from South Africa
At one point Alex is like the
Leave like why don't you just go and let the blacks kill each other
He was on the show
Barbarism
What
Is going here
So he receives to have like a couple of
A couple more
White dude
I don't even remember who they are
The the
The fake Twitter where all the white supremacist going to get kicked off Twitter
Comes in
The shop
Wicked
We get to the war room
A giant 28 might as well have been a giant pile of cocaine
With Owen Shroyer
Diversity
Into the proceedings
He allows a woman somewhere in The Other Woman
Indian guy on who's running for office
He's trying to take Elizabeth Warren
It's pretty uncomfortable because they keep saying only a real Indian can be two-faced
A very very
Play that like it'll really appeal to some part of
The base
So that interview
Actually think beyond the racism that guy was kind of making
Couple good points
About
Problems being bigger than just looking at one problem
You stalking a lot about likes
Systematics.
And how like when you look at like
Poverty you got to look at a bigger
Pictures of Rome
Subway about is like
He works like system
And stuff like that
In his
Expertise to real-world issues
Beyond the real Indian beats fake Indian
Like I'm not into
The rest of the stuff you saying is like our right
Just kind of bored you're fine
Are you know you're running for work cuz of that slogan
Boardman Rodger Stone
He's wearing it.
Shirt and a tie
Already know he's not at carnival this week tomorrow
Name to Jacob pangle
Who is that is a journalist
List of sorts
Who is on CNN
Debate after the Florida
Shooting
News pro gun
Of course I am
His appearance was anything too awful either at side of like
I just disagree with stuffy saying
But I looked into any rights for a publication or I've come to find out now he owns this publication
Their slogan includes
I looked into it was called Rodger Stone
Struggle for America
A little puppy
As soon as he gets off
Alright
Decided not to engage cuz I don't really have anything
Again I really have any skin in the game outside of like
I tried to take that was a puff PC feels like it wasn't
What kind of
We could just agree to disagree preemptive
Superfly
Boring and then afterwards
We get three hours
Have a guy
Who I watch
All of it
I don't know what is
I just
I just waited to just
I know he has Jerome corsi coming at some point with me
But I just kept referring to him as the boring intern
Because he's a young guy and you just
So dogshit boring
I need something
Couple his great quotes
Sorry like there's
Racism doesn't
Exist anymore
They're like
15 people who hate
Hate Mexicans
In the world
Chad Davis
F****** hate Davis
Right
Papa Roach
Their dad
You got that
I've sewed like I was just sitting there like I am
I'm having
Rubble
Like not even staying awake cuz it's still before 8
Yam
I don't know I'm a bit off more than I can
Then
Alex Jones
All right you get a breath of fresh air
About
But just to give a little bit more
Contact
Text what happened
After Alex Jones finish
It's another f****** boring
And I watch
I've been drinking
Little bit along the way
About for a sec
Slam dunk videos
For a couple hours is what
Don't
A lot of lot of metaphors
Undercurrent
Yep.
When I come back
Boring intern
Bruises
Running another 3-hour ship
I remember his name
Smith
Well he's also
Who found those
FIFA contract on 4chan
Sign contract
Any member of antique immediately
Tucson
Yes that hoax
Great
I'm really bored
I need I'm flagging
And then it becomes too late for Infowars to broadcast
Anymore
And so they go to the London office
It's probably about like
In the morning here to go to London because they're on Greenwich Mean Time
Until you got Paul Joseph Watson
And Tommy Robinson
We're going to be brought
Sing from London while everyone else in Austin
Takes a nap
And so Tommy Robinson
Is just
Howling
Apocryphal stories
About Muslim violence
I had no likes like
Citations for any openings
Eric
I like this
I like that broadcast
The old-time Grandpa tell stories level terrible
And like I'm watching the viewer
On like I was on the Infowars
Maine live
Stringent
300 people watch
Or something like that
I have to assume
He knows those numbers you can stick it in his performance was just like
Cuz he gets done
Then comes on I like turkey
For however long he's on
Then get to David Knight
Advanta maybe get another
3 hours of Alex
No I gave up at 6 a.m.
Paul Joseph Watson
Sunset these words
The Sargon of asgaard
What
I'm out
That's the only time I would have started listening
National
With these guys
I know what they say
You say
Okay I'm not
Sure why his
Like
Maybe he just had a YouTube channel that people like and that's the beginning of it I don't know
I don't care about his history
With somebody who thinks he is the cousin of
Thor
Card or something
I turned it off I went to bed
Guilty about it
Yes
Guilt is the feeling that you should have been experiencing that moment
Half hour nap
Then come back
And I didn't wake up until like 11
We're all good and everything was fine
World world
It turns out you could have not listened to any of it
It was worth
Anyting
Was that second
Swing shift from Alex Jones
Listening to right now
I want to give a shout out to my friend
He was riding shotgun with me and chatting over Facebook
For some portion of it he started trolling the Infowars chat room
About that a little bit
We learned a lot
I learned I learned a great deal about
Being forward
Text from
I'm exhausted because I feel so good
Alright
You might detect a little bit of booze on his breath
I'm exhausted cuz I feel so good
He kept getting callers or like you can see how tired you are
He is quite drunk
Which course
Alex's experience
Some exhaust
Exhaust
Repeat stroke
Yeah I know we start off our adventure with Alex
In this first clip he is just talk
Larry Pratt
Who's the guy who runs the organization called the gunownersofamerica which we would look at as a
Extreme NRA
That's not good
No it's not the Gun Owners of America
Because he's
There's nothing really in
Everything happens and Alex
Keeping it together
Cuz Larry pride is respect
Old man
He's got about his best behavior but
Once he leaves
Larry Pratt interview
Creating straw ban version
Of the accusation
Scott said on the other
EEOC complaints filed against m in thousands of newspapers today
They say I
In a video we were shooting on a computer
This is how crazy they are
President
Prices of a Nazi with no proof
That's why I'm telling you the lister's
There's a shoot that's that's supposed to climb out there
I'm asking you the lizard understand that I'm not complaining at you I'm not asking for more from you
I'm saying you
You're the reason we're here
You're the Reason we've had success
You're the reason we are defending all of your frames
So give us a credit
Got them financially support Infowars today
24-hour broadcast to point that out
Give me the flavor of almost all of the night
Is just him
Episode as one of our lives
Art listeners would die
Cuz of the iPad
Yeah everytime there's an app
Do with this wood
Be not good
I want to get nobody said he was grooming men for gay sex
Sex in a plane
Is that Alex was grooming man for gay sex
Because I had that I have both of their legal complaints
It's here in front of me I actually do know that he hugged
Ashley Beckford
Wait
That's right under the pretenses of the heart
Complained
Because I don't want
And I don't want there to be any bones
About this I don't want it to be like Alex
Cuz fake version of accusation
In 2014 the CEO of the company allowed his friend Shane Steiner into my office
Computer with images of gay
Twinkle light
Bodybuilder
And I don't know if that is right or if Rob Jacob
Explain that it was actually a pornography
So leave that aside for a second
2014 CO2 company Alex Jones Jones allowed at my office
To display on my computer images of gay pornography
I believe this action was a continuation of the intimidation and sexual harassment
That he was grooming me for homosexual sex
I made a formal complaint to
To the human resource
Department
So that complaint
Should be on their files
Unless
They have
Sensitive
Deleted them
He
He also makes this claim cuz he says
Continuation
From the years 2008 to 2012
The CEO of the company called me beef
Referring to male pornstars
Intimidating and harassing
And a form of sexual harassment
And he was grooming me
A homosexual sex
So that claim is being made
This side this idea that
He may have
It might have been a bodybuilder
Intimidating
Addressing the actual issue at hand
He's creating a fake version of it to respond to
Houses
Erased
Align perfectly with what I know of
Cuz I don't want to read like four paragraphs
She was sent out when she get first just started
The cover a democratic
Party for the first presidential debate
Not used to it
Infowars for Gears
Compared compared to my lesson
Three months
Consistently pressured me to engage with the Hillary Clinton
Supporters as a black
Trump supporter
I was subsequently
Subject to multiple people hurling insults and racial slurs at me including Uncle Tom
By one of the gay white male
Another Clinton supporter a white lesbian woman told me that she knew more about black issues than I did
Because she's married to a black woman who is also Prime
So this is all captured on video now
Just at that night
Not be uploaded to YouTube channel
Because of the interact
Newsworthy and had no political value
Rob Dewey
At lady
It to exploit the racial attack on me
Play for Infowars
Prophet
The existence of these clips is still hurting my professional reputation
Mutation is a journey
Chloe working at Ward
It's Dave still behave
Horribly bad for her
You should not work at Infowars if you want credibility
It's not going to work
So she she says I went back to the Infowars office
Tears
Incredulous at how I was being racially attacked because of my support for a political
And Alex Jones
Force me to share what it happened to me on air for YouTube
Another social media that same night
Feigning his own tears of M
Answer the broadcast I was with Alex Jones robbed in several other staff members and Rob dues office
I was talking about
How I didn't agree with the white one
Said that she knows
About black
Community board than I do
Because she has a black wife
Alex Jones was still pretending
Feel sympathy for my plate is a black female Trump
Supporter and he put his arm around my shoulder to initiate a side hug
After he pulled me into his side
Instead of removing his arm from my shoulder
He allowed his arm to slide down my back
He grabbed my butt with his right hand
Simultaneously use commenting to those in the room quote
Who wouldn't wanna have a black wife
In response to
I felt embarrassed in Derby
Pacifically touch my behind at that moment is
Come on
That other people might not notice
So she goes on
Not
A good way to react
No situation
Of all the things to hear
When Ashley is talking about that and
He's like that's no good
In the office as usual
Alex
Come to find out quote what I like to do for fun outside of work
It's my opinion that it wasn't
Is intention
To see if you could groom me for sexual exploitation
Because he also mentioned that I had a quote good body that look like I worked out a lot
I was concerned that these unwanted sexual
This would eventually result in a request for sexual favors
In exchange for promotion
In the office it was rumored that
He may have had inappropriate
Some chips with other female production
Instaff employees
In addition Alex Jones himself has alluded to the fact that he loves
Worcester grab women's backside
A videos of
And that's fair
I come to about all this
Is like
I take these allegations
I believe her as much as I believe anybody who makes
Claims and it certainly waiting line without
Public behavior and what we know about you
I think
If I had $100
$7 on shoes
And $3 on she's wrong
But even then that $3 is like
Penny's I don't want that $3 back
Because the odds are so high
Set Alex's where all your money back
Money if the $3 is right but
Some of them will get you in a minute
I really want to
Make very clear is that
I'm making a judgment
In the court of public opinion
Think her
Claims sound credible
Based on
Things other people have claimed in the past
What his ex-wife says
The fact that all of his responses are
Strawman versions of the accusation
Actually dealing with the
I'm accused of grabbing her but you like
I touched her back
You know me memes
You're defending yourself a gum
Against the false charge
Probably
Hey I remember what nights
She's talking about situation
I felt that this was what was going on and she felt that this was what was going on
Story that's a conversation
Subway
I don't know I believe that it's up to court
To decide
A complaint has been made and hopefully the process goes as it should
At this point
Can't believe it
But I also know that your
You're innocent until proven guilty
Alex
Is doing a bad job.
Publicly
How this goes in the future
I Will Never Surrender I will never and I will have settled that lawsuit with Ashley 41
Also I mean really need to come
These claims were filed
At the beginning of February or lights
The second week of February
Coming
Course that's the only reason he's doing this
That's why he did one in April last year
Either one in November I'm not entirely sure why you did that one end of the fiscal year
I could have not accept
Chamber 2000
15 because of his
Divorce because
Eonline
That's why you doing
If you getting sued by two former employees
He probably knows
There's a decent chance some other employees are going to come out of the woodwork
We can only hope
I don't know. Some people be like
Yeah B
This isn't covered in my MBA
Or something like that you know
Converse still not protected
With the same spirit that I am approaching this we'll see what happens
We'll see what happens
34 hour marathon
Let's get to it
What's the best move forward
Just because Alex Jones burps in the middle of the worst Nigeria
Forsyth
Christian fighting radical Islam
Antenna or tonight
Jerriann
You're a lot of media hype a lot of stuff
Delivered
Everybody watching
Realize when you go buy a book or video or some supplements are water filtration are you will make a $10 donation
That's how we built this this was not easy to build
Copper plating
Here we want sweetheart
I'm a victim
But I'm not complaining
So are also
If you are going to reference
That's good Chris
Do not talk about the ones in Kenya and Nigeria
AR
The worse they are the worst
Admittedly
Raping lesbian women all over the place because they're too gay and God wants them to
Those are the ones that I want
Dimension
When I'm talking about
People fighting
For freedom
Big shout out
Great dude
To this Marathon
Is Alex Jones knows he's being sued
Yeah but what he could never have expected
Is also the day before
Donald Trump would come out and say I want to take people's guns
Real trouble place
So
It doesn't
Affect his main broadcast that much
Literally watching Macbeth
This is exactly
Line by line was he visited by three witches
Division of storage place
So
Dino Alex
Struggling with his maybe turning on them
Turn on
So in this
Evening shift
Adidas
Right right
In the evening shift he's got to find a way
He spent most of the day trying to
Figure out
Suspenders
And like as usual he came up with
Great ideas
No
I think he doesn't figure it out until maybe like
I don't know
Half an hour
Real f*****-up thing that he said about Trump
I want to go ahead the air again
Dianne Feinstein
Winthrop and fuel each other close to get 45 emoji
Just because he's better than Hillary
Understand we were told our sources last week that he's being turned
Blackmail
Biceps operatives in the White House
We didn't put that out.
Now
We got no pics leaving today
Melania Trump and Stormy Daniels just looks like it's time to wash your succulent
Gorgeous female
She's in there
Yes the word is that's been going on
Sideways
I want to thank this is Art of the deal stuff but
I got to be honest with you cuz that's all that matters
Trump starting a magazine job I was right to endorsing
Warriors
Aluminum in trouble
But
I had torches off Erin on Airway segoe Sandeep
Text eoin
I just didn't touch it
That is best friend feels like that is why
She looks little thinner
Stipend
Just that quote
Look straight up
She's a luscious succulent
Beautiful woman
I just wanted to add my name
Jesus Christ
Succulents
Succulent
Also I tweeted out that quote and Ashley Beckford
I have a lot of Correction with
Infowars
Adjacent personalities
Oh boy
This is so pathetic
Because
Never do any of that stuff
Do all those women accusing him of
They're crazy they're out of that.
The Russian P story
That's all
He's Beyond reproach
Beyond is the most
Moral man is
Sure
We heard that he's f****** hopex and that's why she resigned and we can never trust him again because of it
That all that other Russian stuff
Still crazy
Yes he's f****** hopex all the time
David was God
Or whatever
Brought up King David music
That's right religion
Joe talked about you got to throw some of that
Goldsboro little bit
Trump at Ali's wives
We didn't say suddenly
Evangelicals just want somebody that will leave
I would love to get them
They're not hypocrisy.
Bible
OSHA real Christians have already been down the road of evil
Sex or drugs whatever they get there. Democrats
President
The judge
They judge the heart
My God does
And everybody else
I'm never going to sit here and steer you wrong
Yes you will
I'll give you this Blanche
Nobody's buying me off
Yeah right
Probably break time's over aren't true in a row and then you say
But I'll tell you something that is
It's also not true right situation
You can just be like
I never said that you did
He never did that
But I'll tell you this
I'm definitely doing this I'm real
Machine-gun lies that expect me to believe the last part
The thing that you say I kind of agree with him a lot of them
Some have been around
The block and one of the reasons is because
Addiction work
Is generally you have to replace one addiction with another
That's what a lot of people do aren't treated
Can you end up having a lot of people
Exercise
Who are born again
I may find Jesus
Eminem Jesus
It becomes everyday
Community absolutely is been around the block
That's not good
Vegetable art
Again
Painting with a broad brush I don't mean everybody certainly but there is
From my experience growing up
There's a lot of people who are just mainlining
Pretty much and that's not a healthy way to look at
Maybe we can have a discussion
The other one
All up in everybody else's business about acting moral
Those are the ones who are being Hypocrites you know the ones who are like hey
Gay people can't get married because marriage is sacred
Those are the ones who look over it Trump sham marriages
Mail order brides
And they're like
That's good marriage
But all of those gay people God hates you
Yeah sorry this makes clip Alex speculates that he's going to
The whole time
Most of my life
Speculate
Live long is also
I'm 44
Stop doing this
But I have to keep on cuz they're trying to push me out
That makes sense
Also
Well no it's just his weird
Kind of thing
But also there's another motif of this
Keeps talking about wanting to quit
I understand totally acquitted
Don't work
Outside of like
Fascist regime
People are really
You can't be your it's really worked out super well for him until people started paying attention
He got hooked up with Trump and everyone like hold
TalkBack threatened that's a
The problem he can fly under the radar making millions of dollars every year
Easter is profile is too high
And it's really becoming a problem
You should quit
Butter how hard do matter how bad it gets I'm going on again
Jackson Give Up on Humanity
Right I'd watch
72 president
Without you my sexy
Pressure
Exactly
I'll be honest with you makes me sometimes just want to
Have it all over with
Jordan
I know
I got to get my soul in line
God
All you fools don't believe in God you've never
Tasted a tire thing
Somebody put that on no papers tomorrow morning
I want you to experience what I seen
Mere glimpses of the mind of God
Unspeakable understanding unspeakable Grace
Unspeakable will a speakable Beauty unspeakable
Unspeakable power
Unspeakable fidgets
Unspeakable bread
Speakable
Give three horses
The followers app
I got my time zones messed up
Speakable
Basketball
And
And Bone Thugs-N-Harmony was there
I don't know why they were there
Crossroads
He's got
32 hour marathon
This is at 8 p.m. Austin
Guinness drunk I just mean this is a conversation of a man who's like
It's about closing time at the barn is like
I don't know what I'm going to do with my life I don't know what's going on right now
Our twenty-four of marathon he's been screaming the whole time
In a cigarette in front of them
Speakable vistas of anger
Or whatever that is
Space is in
YouTube videos normal show for 3 hours
So in this next everybody has lawyers apologized
Before I play this next
Because we're going to include
The clipse
So Trump talking about gun
Control
Because it's
Crazy that Alex
Actually playing those clips
It's nuts
Normally you would just ignore this or something like that
Keep playing these clips included
Says
We're going to get this
To work with you on this
And then you'll see how many hours before
What are you
20 minutes
Listen to these clips
And then listen to what how Alex
Deals with it immediately
I think it's very
Dianne Feinstein
And then we're going to go
The trouble I like taking the guns early
Then due process just a horrible statement
On the biggest family Honore lawmakers are Friday and I really like a double sided meaning
Your phone calls
It is Thursday night is 9:43 Central
That would be great also
Number States
Firearms first and then go to court
Musicfirst depositors I can just point out like this
It sounds like
Progress or something
I guess
It's not you still crazy
Only thing I want
It is like
Obama's never said
Anythink
Even remotely close to
Let's circumvent the courts and take people's guns and metal go to court
These people are stupid
Not
He's crazy like
Did none of you see this coming sooner or later he's
Oh s*** that's a good idea
Al Green
I hate domestic violence
Would that apply to me that part of it is actually real
Really important
That is a lot of the domestic violence guideline
A lot of states only relate to like
Husbands and wives exactly
Your girlfriend and still get a gun
Better things
Those are the sort of loopholes that
About including
A million times over is one of these
It's probably the number one
Vindicator
The sort of behavior
Procedures
Crazy man's case
No bigger fan
It doesn't make sense that I have to wait till
A lot of people are afraid of
Dianne Feinstein of California
Behind herself
She's beside herself like she's entered Heaven There
She can't believe you sound just like DACA
You always said during a campaign
Zodiac
Anime
Common cold
Bigelow
So that was really interesting
Expressing
Some people
Enough
He never said that you didn't hate Mexican
I think there's a lot of people
Play the places
Message boards
You got story
Yeah he even plays this long
Collection of clips
Very clearly
I'm going to help get this built
I agree
What you can't even how stupid is it
Even Trump
No that doesn't make sense and then that's how stupid the NRA and then
Disagrees with you
Quit please like hey why haven't you guys made any
Any progress on this you're afraid of the NRA
Talking about in the Middle where it's hilarious and that's why is it Heaven it's not be
Because she thinks this matters
Right now because she's going to get her bill pass or anything like that it's because
F****** hilarious to be in the room
Brother getting dunked on but the same time
I feel like there is a part of her that
Things like maybe we can make progress on this
Probably she's a horrible horrible.
I'm not but I also think
Irrelevant conversation
Listen
He's not about how she's smiling
Because otherwise
I got to wrestle with
Holyshit
This is worse
And you just like I had to guess I would say that during that like
2 minutes is probably when he was chugging
Some Jameson
I imagine he was a group because it
The video is off Hamilton playing a video of trump
It's a good opportunity for him to get a little booze and
A bit more f***** up
Pretty quick after that
Cuz I was watching it and I like this is a roller coaster a booze
Zenith pretty Gravely drunk there at the beginning
And then pretty quick here
Ends up getting to like this
The drunk esoteric Alex we know and then by the time it's over it's
Angry crashed
The Angry Birds
Alex
What's up
This quote
To condemning Trump
This close
But he gets sidetracked by what
Who's more in it
Is Mooyah
As a journalist
You just watched Dianne Feinstein
Let me see giant
I like all that he's Afro-American
Populist
Not.
Ignatov
Don't you get it president
They're not going to let you be the pragmatist it's all
A big joke
Wizard of Oz
Funny plays
Dianne Feinstein
Holy crap together and spiraling on a loop intersperses video of the Wicked Witch of the West
Definitely not deal with the fact that we elected a crazy like we should have known he was always going
The simplest
Point vet
Furiated the right literally
Well yeah
I mean if it if you have to wait until 21 to get a handgun
Shouldn't have to wait until 21 to get all done well
Because the easiest argument to make is the exact argument
Justin reverse is like we should make
All of them 18 cuz you could
Just using the same information and make that argument
You know what it's like it's like
Hiring like a wolverine
There's nothing like that just because of Wolverine is like
Tidy up sometime or whatever
All of a sudden it f****** attack you while you sleep or whatever you like
Great analogy to your house
The Wolverine
I lost a metaphor
Is where I picked up
You judge me by Trish
Fry said that in my life I learned
You judge a restaurant
Put on table take care of his wife
Beautiful
G.
Popping babies out of a 5 Seconds
How many miscarriages
I got 20
You get what I'm saying
So that's what I'm saying here is
Nobody's going to turn on Trump harder than me
That's
That clip
Okay
Fox
But the f*****-up are you thinking about anything now hold on
No it's not what it is
The first part of it
Totally
Restaurant by what they serve you as food
Find a better 4/1
Think about their service
But at the same time
Food is good enough baby you don't care baby like exactly
Odo
Cuz Rose really just like humans are only as good as their reproductive
Look if a woman can't Berry kids
Not saying she's a bad person
I'm just saying
She doesn't count as a human being right now the problem is of no Worth to the rest of the speech problem
He's like
If if it was devoid of Conte
He was just saying if it was
She's not fertile
Yes
It's surrounded by is the quality of a thing
Yep
420 baby
One miscarriage
Look still a goddess I'm not saying music
Nobody going to turn on Trump harder than
Perfect metaphor even further into
The Trump is popping out babies every 5 minutes or whatever
My response to
That is not long enough gestational.
18 popping out on viable baby
Analogy
Quality of babies
That's a large
There
Yeah and I don't care. Packet I just think that that is
Incredibly incredibly
Buck job that's a weird way of thinking
The weird way of thinking about
Yes all of those things he said weird
What's crazy is there weird and different
None of it is like uniform crazy
You judge a man by what he can put on the table
And how many babies he can put in you
That makes sense right
That's exactly how we should judge human
Stop
So weird
That would make sense maybe or like a farmer
Chinese farmer would be like from The Orphan Train
Living in like a subsistence economy where you have to grow your food
Tend the livestock
Reproduce in order to run your life
Lucky children are free labor is what Alex just said that are free labor
One of the only rationalization
The only real world example where it's like
I do what you're saying
Wild
But to be like in Austin
Right-wing radio host
And hold those views
It smacks of just like you don't see people as people
You see people at breathing machine
Pretty f*****-up
When is the next clip
Route to talking about how like I believe he's still on the line
Buy cuz of course
If he does
F****** vets
He starts talking about a signature
Spoiler alert for what's happening
And during the long pauses he's got the document cam
On the piece of paper in front of him
And if you'd like
If Trump signs at
I didn't realize that the cameras on it
Bonnie Wright
Besides Donald Trump
Name underneath it
As he's talking
And then
Just starts make
Can a line of.
They're not
I'm such a purist I wouldn't do that
That's why I'm not surprised
There's a lot of race do not president
Shoebill
He puts his name
He takes Bell
The ban all semi-automatic rifles of Dianne Feinstein sign
He's playing it out
Donald J Trump
He's going to be some big problems
That crazy signature
Guarantee this thing
Never Back Down
Pointed back to his own signature
Over enunciate incontinence
Form of drama
Never compromise
Audi
I'm not sitting here saying I'm a greater man
Disney problem
I'm not like other man in my life better than a real man
That's what I see my better relationship one
Yeah you're totally
I'm a big man
Because he says It'll recognize a better man on the pizza I want to see
Judged I want to go to him like the Oracle of Delphi want to go to
Also
I made all these so I'm definitely better than you great man
Lary over there he was a miscarriage
But I carry him around and toe and memory
I'm so Alex realizes he doesn't have enough content
To do his late night shift
To-do at 34 hour marathon
Besides to go to Kohl's
Howdy
Go to Costco
New York
Hell yeah
Here and Harvard
Brenda Radford man right now but
I'm the type of person that
When I am which I usually am
You're usually right
Emergency usually with our sales ocean
Ships on the blood in our heart blood veins
It's paradox
Cuz I do these promos under these sales raise money
50% off rolling like 10 bucks on Friday night always paradoxes of financial
Squeeze
Make less money
It's just Bad Manners
Play Foreigner.
Why do donation lines and millions of dollars on donations every year
Thalia donation button on a word., prisonplanet.com
They're only about
Support sectioning
Sunrise like $10,000 a day on that
Couple
VoIP discount
Hard thousand dollars profit
You should not be
Telling people your business model
Very bad
If you're getting $100,000 in profit
You're crushing it
No
Not for what Jeep
Pretences audio
I just meant
1/3 pocketbooks pretty good
Ballpark
Goodnight baby
But still $300,000 worth of products
Forgotten like 10,000
Donations
When he gets off of errors that will be 12 hours
The marathon
You got to assume you're not making any money with it
Do you work out overnight
Shift right with the Harrison Smith
Boring everyone to sleep
Like legitimately that's
Really bad
It's a lot of money but that's really bad based on what
He expect
Text to Macon what he pretends.
You should not be saying these things are there
Probably.
Witchduck Bay products
Lawyers in the lawyer's wife
Paperwhite
Global Corporation
Globalist grocery
So close to car
You're crazy
If you don't go to Infowars store.com
Angle
Proud of shutdown
Her Facebook or Twitter
CC there he's using the YouTube
Situation
We're going to need you because they're going to get us
That's a big part of my
Is not a winning strategy
Interpret
And I
Sexual assault
Well and I'm touched her on the back
Yes I'm blaming the women
Exactly
That you have a gun
Are though really like it like her wanting
Concealed carry class
There whatever is irrelevant
Like even if she's saying that she
She felt intimidated by everyone carrying guns
At the office
Like
That doesn't
Just because she wanted
Classes on it that doesn't invalidate the
Intimidated by
I wouldn't want to work in an office where everyone was also wearing gun
I've gone
To the shooting range and number of times in my life and I understand the enjoyment
Shooting a gun recreationally I can get it
And I don't I'm not again
Exploding guns
As a ruler
But if I was in an office
Like when I worked at Groupon if everyone was packing
I would be
So scared
Any small into a very
Brought
Mexican standoff
Very quick especially when you consider like the
Hair trigger
Party supply of people like Alex like him going from crying too
Screaming updated performatively
Like you're feeling these things breaking stuff
And commercial breaks and he's even
That kind of thing is
Like
That's not a good environment
I booked into this
At the beginning of the
His first
Shift when he's talking about this allegation
He's like open carry the legal
I looked it up
It's not
Open carry is very much allowed
And if you
Is it illegal to have open carry or
Concealed carry in an office
Do you have to have is you can't have one of those signs
That says no guns
Your whatever
You can have
You can have guns in private property
Assuming Alex Jones
Broadcast
Cast from private property there's no reason why I couldn't open carry in your office
Mean something
Open carry legal in Texas
Means he's not even aware of the gun laws in his state
Which is troubling
Anyway there's a little more
It's just like
It's just like Trump and the sexual assault allegations were he's like
No I never did that you can't prove anything
How many listen to the clip of himself
The exact
I don't have guns out
Well let's go back to this show whenever you said
I won't carry guns all over the place
Play Bedford like that
Well let's go back to when you called a woman succulent just a minute ago
Innocent until proven guilty
But if you've already
I'm going to go on your guilt
Call Jordan
Trump said that that was Locker
Right
Incidentally
It's the same kind of a
Excuse that's coming out of Infowars
HR
Current which is run by Alex
David Jones runs the HR department
Yeah yeah that's
Number one
Most likely
When I was reading from the EEOC complaint
You said he filed
New did it with this f******
I think I remember reading in that
Complaint was that
I can't can't remember if she said she filed
Complaints while she work there or not
Because she didn't know who was in charge of
So that is
That's far more likely
File complaint
Again
Talking to your mom because the elementary school bully beat you up and she calls his dad and his dad is
Clearly like the a****** who's the reason the kids
Take care of this mini
The kid that bully comes to you the next day and is likely to told me you told on me if you ever do that again
Yeah
Anytime you anytime your boss does something bad you tell his dad on
Here's the quote for the statement that they made to the Daily Mail
Jones's father dr. David the company's head of Human Resources
Give me the daily mail
Head
That's crazy
Raise your email that the Infowars office environment
Can often be like that of a locker room
Some had made complaints
It's HR about certain issues but insisting on writing
Call Hema p****
And told him to get on with his
Yeah
Standard
Great band
The Beast
Really
Not good
Zero tolerance
For ethnic discrimination
Conair
Wow
Kind of
Junior said the company is made up of
Equal opportunity offenders adding
Yeasty environment
Enrique of everybody crap
I'm just being brutally honest here
From your HR head
Admission of guilt
Okay
I did do that
Come on man
It's not totally fine
If the seventies
Hey bro
Doesn't work
I feel like that quote Mike
Come up in court
In terms of it being like
Now
Kind of admitted these allegation
Foundationally true how do you respond
Now we're looking at things
Yes I did that
I did that too
And I
I totally did.
Do you think these statements reflect poorly upon you as
Yeasty
This is just an incredibly weird ramble
The Gibson to like
Sales pitch in the middle but on committal about it cuz want to talk about
Spiritual issues
A little bit more than he wants to talk about sales
But those spiritual issues are in service of trying to make more sense
Just like Jesus said
Exactly
Church 50% off
Apparel
Tiring
Going through all this
Reach plateaus in Community Theater or whatever
If I hadn't been on this Quest so
I'm blessed Beyond this Quest
Either rhyme Smith
My friend is very stressed
I am Subway's relate to what he saying
Because I too have got it's been a lot of work over the last year and a half or so
But I've learned so much
And I feel very thrilled to have learned
To be on this Quest Alex let's see where you go from there
I'm not complaining but
I'm seriously a lot older most Realty
I know
Sure
I remember things I see people doing I used to do
10 years ago 20 years ago
I remember back
I was like damn
Humanity's gone
Because Maddie Maddie so strong
But
I've done this so long I don't warn people I've done it so long
Become removed from it now
I'm far away from it now
Brando solimine
Learn to anesthetize you from pain
He's like 10,000 years ago now
No it's current
Completion
Ordinariness final decision of the species
I just want you to make the right decision
Decision you want to make
Try to get you to some
I just know Christ cereal there waiting for you
I'm not even strong enough to make sure my kids
Have I ever parent knows how that is
I know the charges are Caruso's I'm not sitting there saying that all the answers
All I'm telling you
There's a real devil
He wants to take you with me forever and you don't want to go there
That's all I'm saying
And so
Part of me
Netgear support your help
That's not sick
You do realize that
We are on the very front lines
The information and spiritual war
I keep looking for somebody to come along
Somebody
I'm ready to put all my energy behind somebody else
Cheap-looking
And I keep looking my zebra
Real quick
I don't
Hire good people
Quality recruit
Call these people in Limon
But only people
David Knight
Work here
He's the best of God
My dad said no one not make my dad
Owen Shroyer terrible
Rodger Stone keeps walking with me I don't know what he's up to
Of course he's a bob
Jerome corsi
Is b*******
Lost my shirt dry to Biomat office what am I doing
All these people are scam artists
Hanging out with Milo yiannopoulos now what am I doing
God help me
And don't even get me started on that prick Watson he's also saying like I keep
Looking for someone to take over in all ice
Sbu's you in audience
He saying is like I feel like
Sick part of me that doesn't want to come beg for your money which
That's probably your smart-ass
Part of your body Alex
But in that case
The way he's framing it is
I don't want to convince you to give me money
You should already get it I understand he was very close to being like if you haven't already
You're not one of us
Well it's what I
Flashback to is when I was in church one of the things they would always tell us
In the youth group is like
If you don't if you don't feel close to God
You should pray to feel close to God
If you don't want to feel close to God you should
Pray to want to feel close
What's the god
Alright
Giving the money you should want to give us money
If you don't want to give us money you should want to want to give us money
The woman Inside the woman side
Exactly it's a load of
This girl got a little left
Get it all of us
Individuals are going to change the world
It's all the little things we do
It's not one Heroes going to do it
It's all of us together
Little things like buying
We can have a fix of this at Justice
My son and my three daughters
Who are Jewish
Don't have to go to the tribulation
She loved my gut tells me
Humanity's going to have to pay for what we've done to unborn children
My shoulder so I can be laughing all this happen
A real heart
We're going to face Satan on the Earth
AI
Robots
Everything
Because
Or Shake
Mountain
Bash your head
Hoping you can die and you're not going to be able to die
Thought is that a i
And you're going to beg for God to tell you
God's not going to kill you
Because you served
Seems like a weirdo
Seems like a weird
Darkness
Pray for God
Achillea
But no
Was full of love
He's more about torturing you
Fraternity
How to pay for multiple abortions
Calm down
Also like
It's the feeling that I get from that is
The ceiling to it
Through certain extent
People think this is funny
I think it's because he has an awareness that like people laughing
Because he went
Right there is like
Robot
Everything all you think that's funny and you're like
Exist
Like I don't want
To hifalutin
I'm here but
The fact that multiple Infowars
Employees started like
Retweet not retweeting but like saving tweets that I adore that uncle's guy responding to one of my
Jon rappoport followed us the other day so I think that there's some sort of an awareness
There might be
I can't say for sure
Explain why Alex
Like self-aware enough to know that
Some people
But also that could just be normal human self-awareness
AI robots
Everything that covers it
It looks just a couple months ago he was saying the chimeras are
That's the biggest thing
He's moved on to a i
Anyway
The Bold
Declaration
I don't believe
And all I say is buckle up
My soul
Headspace
Down just a little ways
This is going
Did you take a look
Lowe's
Dresses
You don't want to go there
Okay
You know where it's going
Hell
You don't want to go there
We are going there
Apparently yeah.
Like
Where did the space jump
Are we talking about
Time and space
Right I don't know he's just a crazy person created an einstein-rosen Bridge
You sold your soul time Jump
Coronavirus
If you'd like
Profound
Now why is it
Don't worry about it
Forgotten but you said he was going to go to Kohl's
So here's the beginning of rats
New York
Personal betrayal
Really humbling to see
I can tell you're you're you're a nice man and you hate it when people
Take advantage of you and do things
Are honorable
And you're just trying to help people
Well I appreciate that
It hurts me that there she'll phone
You p****
He had to because
He can't
Allow other people to feel bad for him
Actually
He listened to that and he heard somebody
Play listener
You all right
I feel bad
For you Alex Adele
You can't feel bad for me I feel great I always feel great I feel bad
So don't you feel bad for me hundred percent
For the bad guys
Fallen
Cowardly
Right that's what's underneath
I was watching this
In lifetime and then when I went back and watched it
To cut the clips and what have you
There's two things they're running parallel with the collars that are really into
There's a sale
Piece of it and I'll talk about that a little bit further down the road
But there's a b storyline
Can cry on air
You can feel it in him that like
There's so much that voice
He wants to go to a collar that says something that allows him to Launch
Into a rant that will make him
Can cry
Great television
But unfortunately Raptor man comes in with a pity party and he knows that if he cries from
He's weak
Week
He can't show asked his audience and then there's another caller later
Who does the same thing and you can tell
You and I will see it in his face looks like
Deepfake emotion
And you are only giving me a motion that is weak
Frustrating for him
Takes a turn for the
Realize
It's not good
Well we know
We know there
Good people with every race color creed when others bloodlines
To focus on
Because the enemy fears those Bloodlines if those people were
Actually stand up and do what they were
Full potential
What is 1
Help for Humanity.
I think those those people are targeted
Because of their potential
And it's a very very sad things we have to grieve
We have to grieve for them and I'm just understand that
What they see in US is a projection of themselves
What the f***
They're afraid of certain bloodline
The Illuminati I guess or the powers-that-be the new world order
Car gets hurt
Bloodline
Because they're afraid of their potential
Like what
We're going
That's what we're talking about here
Save setting that up
There's good people in all Races
His collars
Bloodline
Flip
Clear
Buy bloodline
Talking about
Race
Ethnic origin and that sort of thing
He's talking about
Nailed it
I don't think
I just think
Certain races are better
Races are so good they have been held down by my imaginary enemy exactly
Yeah like mine
I
Confederate royalty
There's no doubt about that
They have
Held my bloodline
All my dad is is a dentist
Bullion qualified
Bhr
What is this is nepotism
Hibbett
Head of HR is not like an entry-level position
What are you doing
You just a head of HR
I'll probably just there to take cover
Cover for action
Did all the crimes every good run
To come to an end
For a while
4 guys
Alex Jones.
I feel bad when I see people little kids trash cans in Venezuela
I know they've got thousands every week Donna starvation
You think I'll go look at those Hispanic people down there
CDOT traffic another Venezuela
I'm Alex Jones I'm a big guy
This is so close to Andy Daly's Dom dimello
Like this kind of voice
Gross
The girls
Sparrows
It's damn close
Better than
She told me that satanic let me tell you
The people
Go to the people that run those countries
I drop by their limousine to their helicopter
See those families eating their garbage it makes them feel real bad
Makes me want to do
Throat
Going to kill those kids
0 crops
Sure about pre-market
Renaissance
Years ago with his riches of us per capita the average
Venezuelan citizen
Was making as much as a US citizen
Look it up
They were on par
In the 1970s and 60s or the US
I guess it was about the US and Venezuela it was Argentina
Sad big slick New York bags come in
Addition on a run stuff can teach you how to be socialist
The be slick New York Banks socialism
Socialism
Don't talk to you a little bit about Goldman Sachs
Nobody is bigger into socialism than them
I want to talk to you a little bit about Venezuela because I think the way that Alex Jones speaks about
Situation there is really disgusting and degraded
He was
Was he trying to talk about how in Venezuela they shared foil
Subway
That was later
What's the
Nationalized
That was after like
This is from the website called the Venezuela analysis
Lot of research into
Cultural
Historical aspects of Venezuela
Going to read some of this as a quote
Venezuelan Allison
That's a good that I could do
Portmanteau
It was not until 1912 that the first oil well was drilled
Shortly thereafter first
First Royal Dutch Shell and then
Standard Oil became major producers of oil in Venezuela
Within a few years by 1929 Venezuela was the world's second-largest oil producer after the United States
At world's largest oil exporter
Between 1920 and 1935 oil
Percent
To 91.2%
This of course had an immediate and dramatic impact on the country
Economy
Known among Economist as
The Dutch disease
The most important consequence of these was the agricultural
The agricultural production
Decline to almost nothing
The country fell behind in industrialized
American country
By the definition of
Disease explanation
An economic disease
Get this economic disease
Just caught whenever commodities
One sector of the economy
Which is not match
Despite increased
Incoming other sect
What happened
Is Addison sectoral
Increase
Causes several products
Any other side
The increase sectoral income causes
Distorted growth and services
And other non-tradable
Balls which cannot be imported while discouraging the
Tradable
The reason for this disparity
Is that the great economic greater
The greater income rapidly raises the
The demand for imports
Since domestic production
Father demands quickly enough
It also raises the demand for services
Which of the domestic Market has to
The increased demand for imported goods and domestic service
Call Danny
Increase in prices
With articles domestic production
Increase
Because the flow of Foreign Exchange into the economy has caused a greater in
Inflation of wages and pray
Itzy
What is it
Douglas Adams it was the the shoe point
Right you have
An economy suddenly starts making a lot of shoes everybody wants shoes all the time so then people start making more shoes
Everybody starts their own shoe store
Then you forget
We don't have groceries
And their agricultural production
It becomes almost nothing
Exactly
We continually increasing oil in
Reliance
In Venezuela
On this source of income
In lieu of individual income tax
Mystery Begins
Began to feel the effects of the oversupply
Especially following the increase production of oil in the Middle East
And the imposition of import quotas on the United States
The consequence
Tropically low oil price
In 1973 there was a middle east oil embargo
Which lights are the revenues of Venezuela's oil sales quadrupling from 1970s
Newly elected president Carlos and
Andrea Perez
Intended to use the vast explosion of money
I need to fight poverty
And diversify the economy through
Import Subs
Kitchen
This had a good effect for a while but in the midnight
80s price.of.oil crashed
$3.19 a barrel
Well agricultural production made up 1/3 of Venezuela GDP in the 1920s than 110
10th by the 1950
Jesus hurt agriculture makes up about
6%
Venezuela
In addition to the Dutch disease problem
The sudden increase of oil revenues in Venezuela caused
The Furious problem in the
Fiscal
That is the new revenues called the illusion that the oil income could be used industrialized the country via massive
Infrastructure projects
Do so the oil
As the president
At the time of the oil boom Carlos Andres Perez
What happened
Was that the quadrupled government income cause government spending to quickly increase it even surpass the new-found revenue
When the oil income
It was not a z
Easy to reduce government spending as it had been to increase
The result was the government
Yeah the result was that the government gradually went deeper and deeper into debt
Between 1970 and 1990 for foreign debt Rose from 9% to
3% of
So what
The reason that Venezuela is devastated
Is partially mismanagement
Partially
Like
You know some problems
Necessarily
But the cause of all of it
Is
Well you can you can still fight that way if you want
But it is this Dutch disease idea
Where their economy
Was solely reliant on oil is solely reliant on the fluctuations in
Price of one particular commodity
Is also going to
Just as
Fluctuated
He's going to as you can see from the way the Venezuela has
I had so many f******
Coups and Revolutions in all this stuff over and over again is because
Ultimately your economy is
It's going well it's really just masking how f***** it
That's what was happening in the six
Quadrupling of income from oil
The average
GDP being
The people who were making a shitload of money
Loyal
Inflate the appearance of the economy
Would you look at it
I think that the situation is far more complicated than even I person
It's still trying to work it out
Is because
Of that.
This is what happened
It's there's much more complicated ecosystem
That's what happens with
Capitalism
Literally right score
Capitals win and destroyed
Bright
The free market
Alex
2 Stoopid
And once again we see indications
AR
How old is Darren
Nevada coming up
Break
Maybe we're not meant to be
You know what
We got 50% off
Baby Bop
Baby cats
Bathwater
I'm going to chew on a lot
So I thought I might roll over my eyes go up
Call me racist
I don't want to die
Is that why I want to die
Kill you
Anytime
I realize they're dead already
Join us won't kill you.
You're dead already
Sleeping
No that's okay my ancestor your dad I'm not yet
So
Okay
That I'm creating in my head
Understand the mindset of the people he thinks he's talking about in the mindset
I understand the mindset of the people
Are his enemies his fake enemies because it's the mindset of
Many classical Victaulic villains
From film tropes of literature
I get that I seen
But like
The guy understand the mind
He's just describing plot holes
Tired
If you don't scream
It's weird
Idea it is much more difficult to try and wrestle with like
What is the mindset of the
The person who created
Just so you can make money
I guess
I don't end that's why they called braces
The caller
And I
Never
I have never
Heard a caller
Whose voice
More matches what they say they're up to
Then this guy this is crazy
Taylor call thank you Robert California.
Hello sir my name is Robert Bentley and I'm on the ballot
Running for congress in a 36 District of California brother Dam
Yes sir
Member of the NRA and I support Trump 100% however like you I am very
Very concerned he shouldn't be so nice all these people to treat him so badly
Bright trucks
Wow
Or 22
High school bully raise up right now
Feel like I'd lunch money has lunch money so bad right now
He loves the NRA
Member of the NRA
He's on
He's on the same side as you
Yeah but come on man
Teaches you about Moneyball
Helps you talk a ball game
Some
I called that perfectly though
Always clear
Immediately clear
Is that not a proton voice he's just created for himself
That guy was born to run for Congress as a Republican
That guy was a chimera
Is living is true
I want you to not talk over really quick
It's not
But I want it I want you to listen to Robert
The guys running for congress
I thought he was going to go away real quick
But I just want I want to interrupt
It's interesting to listen to him say he doesn't categorized
People
Categorize people
It's an invalid
It's fascinating within the same thing
Yeah
It's hard to
Polite about it
It is so
Disgusting
I deal with people of every color of
We always get along
I recently went to the
March in Palm Springs
The mayor
Palm Spring
Is a
Pansexual person
Category
Now
This person lived
March
Address
It's it's
It's like no just stop it
Like some
Jokes I appreciate your call
Brake Grey
It it does sound like that because sounds like it was written as a joke
It sounds like
The women's March
Was a transexual
Navigate to hack you back around like
Oh yeah
Running for congress
I just picked along with everybody
Name
Anybody
Every person you ever got along with
Do not know anything about this guy and I would never get along with
Just by listening to him you got to go like I hear that boys would like
We're never really had
It comes from nerd voices like that but I do have like avoid avoid
Adult
You should not do that and you know you don't have
He like I don't categorize people person
Category
Which way was he going to be categorized
Anthony's just
Transphobic
I just got his hair
Important
What's going on
Also what is
He think
He thinks she's actually saying
Whenever he's talking about
Transsexual woman
Leading the women
Text
That's the Pied Piper thing for him I think
Bright
By removing his own
Wow
Weather
Yeah well that's true
Scenario Alex
From what I understand
That is insane
Because the man is
He would be a trans exclusionary feminist
If you was effeminate
Either
Trans exclusionary misogynist
I guess
I don't know
I thought
But what are you saying is
Really stupid
I want
Alex is really getting
UTech Saturn
It's the point where he's at
Can't get drunk enough
I want to go forward
I'm scared we're not going to make it
We gone so far how far we got
Please join me
We've come so far if you just believe in God
You have everything together
Tell Scotty all this thousand years from now
Alpha Centauri
The new to me
Black panther sound
Stars
I'm done I got to go I'm going to bed
I'm out here
I just love this
I got to go to bed
6 Cozumel
We're going to go to the Stars
It's written
On our flag
Rob to call me an Uber
Who wrote it on the flag tell me who wrote
He's just at this point today I think manifesting and intense
Frustration that none of these callers
They're giving him what he needs
Just cry
It goes onto another call
Does not succeed in making it look
Because it would make him look weak
The way she's presenting
Normally should get you into an emotional state emotion
Start with Judy in Florida
Girly everything for all the go-ahead
Hey Alex
It's good to talk to you again are you looking at you earlier on
And I never seen you look so sad and tired and I know you're very tired
With all the work that you're doing
First off I love you products
Because of the attack
Sure at this point far out was
At this point far out was trolling the chat room
He's not tired he's drunk
I met a couple people were like no he's really tired
But a lot of people
Started jumping in
And what I realized there's one or two options because I did this later in the
I was bored so I started
I was during Harris
Some Smith's part as like this
So boring
Write a bunch of accounts started
Chiming in like you doing
Alex is trying to put us to sleep
And I got a lot of people to jump on board with
And the same thing happened when far-right was doing lead this guy is drunk
Check it made me realize one of two things
X1
Is people listening there's a lot of people who are watching it in the same Spirit watching
Just waiting for a leader to jump in
Aunt be like
A lot of people are Bots
Mirroring whatever what they,
Just reiterating
Or like using
Using the idea
And making simple sentences
Is based on it in
Forget be like chatbot
Or they could just be in for listeners who are
Matagorda follow literally any leader see that's the other thing I thought about it and it's like everyone is so f******
Malleable
Or it's
It was a sort of thing that I could see definite
Yeah but that is not
Disqualifier for irregular Infowars
I don't know the other thing I was crazy was it's like
People engaging with like he's drunk no he's not like a little bit of that
Writing a essay about gnosticism
Project Camelot
I better go over to this one
Write about gnosticism
At this point Alex
Isn't such a bad head
Headspace
I told you already
Wherever God doesn't hear me
That's why
But I'm not perfect I love problem just please
Just don't let them get me I don't want to be with them please
What's your choice
But I don't think you have anything to fear I mean my son and I are staying and I have a daughter that lives
McDonald's
I love her husband
He's very much a
Trapanese
Scottish guy because he is but he's like a silly boy
And I'm not going to be the one to reach her but you know I've got does
The people praying for her because I really believe
What was happening in Israel I believe
Like
Behold on the world
It's intense
Sublime
Like your son-in-law
I'm so I don't know if we ever really talked about it
Paul Joseph Watson made a video like a couple months back where he was misusing science
For feminizing
Outerstuff so
He drew a bunch of
Conclusions bad like
Soy latte
Story latte that's why they're such
Feminized dork
Or whatever and it just became a meme on the internet
And it probably actually he probably ripped it off of some message board
But he made a video about it kind of
Throwing around isn't
Cancel
The thing is it's not as fun as cuck
To say that so they're going to get to keep it
It's never guess I'm never going to throw soyboy back at Villa
So they get to just have it and it's going to linger in the alt-right world for a long time
Sadly could cook we reclaim does like ice hilarious
So the other thing is that boring intern whose name I can't remember
Baked a couple times they played a video of him
Going out to the University of Texas at
His name is soy seed
He goes out and he claims he's trying to get political discourse going or whatever people with
Signs and they just block him
It's the end of trying to walk around and they just block her
As like
The only thing that's actually in the video is whoever the cameraman is literally pushes a woman
The video of you guys doing
I bring it up
Is
VI
Wendy's being blocked by a sign he's actually this guy looks like a silly boy
He looks
Really weird
What Alex is productivity sales on your website have soy in them
There's a lot of Google Soriano's products
Exodus guys responses like
Pickle meme what I like that's a shity defense
We reached a new level of incompetence layout
You have got to figure this out being out in the field and recognize
Really something we believe it is just trying to make people mad
We're trying to provoke people in all of Alex's
Make the subtext text
Every time
Does next caller gets us back to the the other
They are going to make him cry
Side and then this is the other side
Alex
Wants
Your money
That's really bizarre because in this call
The caller
Literally offers to split Alex
Could you please buy some
Let's see what happen
I can tell
Weight of the world on your shoulders my friend
I'm an old friend
God works in mysterious ways my friend
That's why I'm calling tonight
First off
You have a lot of friends that are with you and behind you
Specifically
Folks that are self-made people that own their own businesses
The do their own thing and great job cetera
Around this world I know that I'm right on Campbell
It it's it's God's been
And I haven't talked to
2 + years
Just remember that you do have a lot of support and lot of friends behind you
Number two
There's a lot of stuff here working through with
Employee problems and all that crap
Grand Rapids
I'll put my money where my mouth is I don't have the millions that Gary has
However
I've got a fantastic labor law attorney and if you ever need any help
What's Bill with you you're awesome
Black people have done nothing to but help
Like one of them ever sick I let them on plus 4 months old pay them in the shop it's like
It's like the weakest people
But we still can't be evil it's about like the album
And they're like
Put your faith in humanity
Got my contact information
So you can talk to you
We don't talk
Later that's fine
But I I mean what I say in this
Haha yep once again we get back to
Dubai money
Do you not get the game yet
This leads me to my next
And that is that there was a
Much higher incidence
Of 425c
Supply commercials during the
The marathon
Then there ever is on his show
I think there's a reason
That is
I do I don't know
I don't I'm not a lawyer but I like the guy
A lot of self-made people
I make a lot of great jobs for a lot of people
I have a labor attorney on retainer
It's 8
Crazy to me that they keep stealing one of the best
No idea why my employees
But you understand
Is freaked out is vide recognizes
I'm not going to take these two court
He just knows he needs a certain amount
So he just wants to make
As much
Cuz he can
He's already budgeted out what these lawsuits are going to cost him
I'm sure
What's coming to like
I don't want you to give me a lawyer I want your money
This money
Understand me
You are offering to solve what is ostensibly the problem
Add to me that means
That's not the real problem
Course not
Or some other problem
To take this to court
Right
I will lose
I want to pay these people go away I have a lawyer who's just
Good enough
To threaten the people who are suing me with
Exposing information about them
To make it lower
He's able to apology
That's what's going to end up happening he knows that
Like that
It's got to be something else I don't know exactly what it is
That that leads me to believe like
These lawsuits
Are f****** him up emotional
Because he knows he's built
That's what
Driving the the performance in the emotion
And the feelings screwed
Do that service.
But it's not the financial
I think he's just using like okay
These people are suing me
YouTube is coming after me in quote
Perfect opportunity
For me to put on a marathon
I raised a whole shitload of money
Ostensibly
Hey what's weird
During this 34 hour marathon
We got one
Huge donation
Also telling
Crazy
This one
Massive
Hundred million dollar donation from an anonymous donor
He's clearly an Infowars listener
It loves it loves it through this business I am running illegally
This point
Alex decides to say some stuff
You should not have
At this point
He gets into
I can't imagine this not coming up in
Not quite frankly he starts talking about Rob Jacobs
And ways that he doesn't
He doesn't need to say these things
His lawyers
Should have told him to say nothing
I would advise them that
Give good advice
Alex
Shut up
Billable hours
Locked up
I knew Rob Jacobson
I had a video letter one at a few other editors
Show Homeland so alone
And don't ever treat him well he couldn't believe he got a paycheck and he works all these free liberal things and
Please stop
Bob likes giving and I was nice to English
Black Trump
Do it well that's okay.
And
I like that and say all that
It's like
Defeating him which we will
Like I would walk around the office calling people any Semitic names I mean not looking play
No he was just telling you
Call people names
Powerful
I told Noah
Stuff for him
They know what to say they know
To invert
Misrepresent
Like I would sit there and say oh
Like I said things they say why
I walk into the room and
Scream
Apple Jacks at black people
Shoes
That's not the complaint either
Droid telling us what it is he's doing
Well then
The complaint but it is totally out of context
For some it's just another creating a straw man of the complaint
Here in Ashley beckford's EEOC
Complaints
Barry mcbreen receive two gifts of fitness shoes
Which was Laden with swastika
Donald Trump
Would you probably display to me
Prince's that's great
Hostile work
He was one of the pairs and then in parentheses it specifically States
Without the swap
So Alex Lange
Other pair
But showed me the swastika shoes
It's it's fine
They don't wear nothing shoes
Display them proudly in their offices like your bronze baby shoes
I think I would rather have them
That's kind of like
I'm very torn about it cuz like
Torn about it because on the one hand like if someone
That's not see shoes I would be like
Imagine if we had such a f*****-up body and puts it looks like us use of swastika
Like I would be blown away and if I worked at a workplace I. Can you believe how f*****-up
And I probably would show them to people
Or something like that
The fact that it's in a cup
Complaint leads me to believe that the
The presentation of it was very different
For real
Maybe we're the bad guys here
Swastika shoes
Indication that like
Maybe we're not
Cruising the best
Just another instance
Creating strawberry
About
The claim
She's just saying that the claims are different that they are with
Leads me to believe that the real claim
Or the reality is at the claims of paleo
Oh absolutely
And we do all this
Doesn't hurt me attack
It hurts me that they've got people
So given over to the lies that they believe it
Is that something
Well
I'm Hitler
I don't think George Soros
They believe someone
Is fighting the Hitler energy
Supplement
Argue in debate
David Duke
David Duke point out that
We had an unprecedented amount of time for an interview with Alex
Do you love David
Seemed like he wanted to appear tonight
It seems like they just had a word
Seems like they just had Samantha
Check differences about their beliefs
Send it
Complained
They references David Duke interview because
David Duke
Jewish India
Individual
And the resident Jew
And stuff like that
Police harassment
Environment
That's very interesting
Singers like Alex
Again is making a straw man
In the complaint
That's not
And the inversion
They always total flip
We're fighting satanism
Dover
Look at someone whose soul
Has been overrun
JoJo oh my God
Grab somebody
And just talk into hell
They said about you
You're thinking about them like
What dimension do they hang in like
Scarlett Johansson age
Mansion
What happened to lullwater in the memo get naked
Real men win
To be killed
Ritualistically the movie
The movie with
The movie
Angler fish
Light
That beautiful woman was a lie
Cool.
It's like what the
The hell and you realize Hollywood powers like that black
You're finally going to be
Apparel
Hi-C
Would that the metaphor
What am I
And then you see a response
Yep
It was gay grooming
So that becomes Jones is having a grooming in
Women
Don't think so man hug
Also the shuttle
She hugged me
A woman hugged
Les Schwab
So he's being satanic cuz he's flipping thing pretty much
Baclofen 100 is
Exhausting
Like when I heard that I was like I
I
I mean
Empathy is tough
At this point for him like in the middle of that telling of a Scarlett Johansson movies plot for 10
I like
I worry for him
There's still a part of me that's like
I am
Deeply concerned about what's going on in that head
Doesn't know that all of his list
Is there Nazis
Yeah we're at least eight the die-hard one
Let's get to this next week cuz that's actually
Super
Mentalist
At the beginning of this quote
Themes delusional
At the end of it
Is
Is delusional
Powerful
Michael Jackson lawyer
The Democrats
Every time I defeat them
It's not like a power trip
I keep beating the globe
You have narrowly avoided people following through with lawsuit
How do you make multiple public apologies
And basically just
You mean
You are the one who settled
You know like you are the one
Right
But you didn't
You lost a lawsuit
Custody case with his wife
Because apparently he's been dragging it out then
I would like to injunction
Globalstar real beatings the globalist
She's losing lawsuits to people he slandered and mistreated
But then narrowly getting through
Out of a pickle
These people
So f****** good
Bad games
That's a troubling
Way to look at reality
Favorite
Did not see things
It's like God why did they join me
Like will be him
Will be there
Will be gem
Over but the listeners
The activist they just keep
The word activity
Have what they want
Over and over and over and over and over again
Third time he said he wants to quit
Play roll over like a dead whale
South African Farmers that produce 70% there's
Nobody
Aberdeen population
Is 40
Thousand Farms
Baby
130,000 people on
Little Farms
No way leave.
Under communist rule they don't even know
Today
Interracial brainwashing
Patroon Asia activity they don't even know
They just want to kill
And that's with reach me up
Freaked out by that if that were real
South Africa
Department
They voted 240 1283 to confiscate the white on land without
Population at own approximately 72% of the farm
Colonization
And apartheid
Distributed as the white minority possession about
Three-quarters of usable land
In South Africa
Controls
They were massive will they own it dance
Power imbalance
That's how that works
Even this Marxist guy that Alex is railing a bad was like we're not
Talking about slaughtering White
People
But here's where the quote goes bad
At least not yet
Went bad
I feel like that was the right thing it's bad Optics
The situation
That's funny
And also
I hope he means it I didn't
Hear it said so it could have been in jest I don't know
Like what this situation we're looking at now is just
People trying to make right what wasn't made right at the end
Because
Control of the land is power
Even though the formal system of apartheid went away you live in a place where people can
Possibly live Equitable live
Three-quarters of the land is owned by less than 8% of the people
State-sponsored apartheid doesn't mean it's still not economic
Apartheid
Ironically
Lot of the afrikaners
This Brewing by Parliament
Which is really funny
Considering everything
Also the opponents of this move and claimed
Zimbabwe
A 2000
Atlanta Mass
But most experts would be quick to point out that the reason that happened was rampant Corruption of
Maybe one of history modern history is great villain
Has more to do with that then
The corruption aspirin
More Equitable state
Is that I told you
Alex Jones is first section
The 11th
Before
Section during the day
He had Simon wrote
The flying Burger
He was on
How to promote a fundraiser
Like a go fund
Of course
Because we're not be allowed on any
Mainstream
If I went to check on it
Periodically
Play throughout the day
It's just one of those things
He's on there
He was on the show is $85
So I wanted to check back later little bit later in the night maybe likes
Six seven hours later I checked back and they were like
$400 or so
But I was looking through it
And one of them was an anonymous donation
For $100
And the commented
Was just
The 14 words
We must have
I'm sure the future of white children blah blah blah
Just verbatim
I like
Yep
You guys get it
Yeah.
And I when I woke up in the morning I went back to check
To see how their fundraiser was doing
And that comment
You know
Did the cause
B b
Pushed
Clearly very popular
I'm on white nationalist white supremacist
Right arm and Alex's
Clearly helping that cause Ride Along
Really weird
Also the the farmer murder stuff as we went over on a wreath
Contextualize
So it's
Is it
Hippie
They would almost be something to talk about if they would admit like
They're taking
Our land back
Is racist against white people and they're taking our land if they were like
They're taking our land back
Then you would have a conversation of
Well is that is that a good way of doing things
There's a conversation is that the best
Like moral standpoint but just from like a general stability
Do that
Now mainly it was horrific
But it's possible that that policy
Decision
Did have something to do with
So maybe let's have a conversation about the best way to take your land
Conversation about
You think we're just stealing your land
Yeah
Yeah you know I agree
Peaceful transition of power as opposed to
We're just taking it
And it is
It brings to the state
Should have been in
Exactly were a crime not too long ago
8 stops
Blake if you stole
A very valuable painting
And then whatever the museum was like hey could you work we're going to take
You were like
This is your
Do you like my art
Clothesline
So
Besom
Signal I think
The issue is far more complicated than even our
Analysis of it
Morally it is right to take their land
Like practically
How you do that is a very different conversation
Is more real than Alex's
We're even like some
Let alone
True true
Alex Jones plays
I'm out I don't want to work
Olivia Olivia
Feel like I could turn it around
It's the Frank
Call Zin
Isaac Alex I am sick
Tired of you
Cleaning all the time about how people are trying to shut you down
Bright I need your help Frank
Spencer Shay
And so it's an ad commercial
I'm seriously that he's being shut down
I took the entire night in the Infowars
Everyone was calling each other Frank
Like it wasn't meme
Can Franklin
Ralph
Sprite
For this
Next clip
I was just another caller
Later in the Brock
Yeah it's about midnight where I'm at and I'm wondering how Frank
What one time
What real quick I'm going to scroll this back a tiny bit cuz even I misrepresented
Actual commercial the same
Complaining all the time
He says I'm tired of you bragging all the time
Kind of
I'm super important
Steven A misrepresentation
Presentation I apologize that I I slept up
Plug one time
I'm being shut down everybody went bought products
Boost
That would be so upset
He's an interesting fellow
He called them and said all but you want to get your ass also stuff
He probably can't find
I'm just trying to restore stuff
And Frank's betcha that I'm saying I'm under attack
What do I do just not
I really am attacking people not seen
Wow
And this time I am
At least I have the little now
Yeah that's that's f***** up
The game man I have to say I'm under attack to get funding
Remembering
Yeah so is not good
Particularly pissed off that he's being sued for like racial
Harassment
The healthy work environment
Because he's
Everybody
Man
And if you do what
Sometimes
Prizes liberal
Leftist
Minorities and women I don't care
What color you are are German woman
Listening to music
Black white
Not a good analogy
If that's
True
It works
Because everyone in front of the camera is a white dude
If he does have a completely diverse staff
But surprises leftist media that comes and shows up
That means he's intentionally holding some people.
Which is which is that good
You working
Do you realize all of our listeners are not allow people I call
I didn't watch the entire man
Yes I'm sorry
Break for a little while
Envy I would put it.
I would put it at
18 hours of it that I watch
Bully 2
Way too much
Way too much fat Indian dude who's running for congress did he win
I don't know
He's legitimately the only non-white
I saw in the entire time
Who's playing videos of Ashley Beckford shooting a gun
That's be only like
I admit I might have missed somebody
Don't think I did they keep all of their diverse people on the other 18
That was the plan the whole time night Chaka block with all these ethnic
Can gender minorities
Like I don't know man cuz I'm alright
South a
Slander
Guy who runs Gab
Anthony cumia
Gerald Celente
Jerome corsi
Owen Shroyer
This jacob angles guy
Rodger Stone
Tommy Robinson
Lipizzaner to believe Alec but if he is telling the truth
That's worse
That's very bizarre position
To be unlike
If you are this much of a open
I like
And it should drive home the fact that Alex
Just really wants your f******
Sick and tired of this video
I appreciate you out and only be clear
How to say this
It's real
Check my
Fred like pay for mine
Coffee at the gas station
All your gas you paid for the copies on me and I'm like
I don't deserve coffee but I'll tell you this
If you want to find the operator you want to buy the product they're trying to shut us down
What is that
I don't deserve for you to buy me a coffee
Spoken by a product
Look I don't want you to pay for half of my legal fees
F****** website
I am rich
My business is in trouble
I think more of it is like I don't want to barter
Money talks b******* walks
Buy a bra.
Except the only stretch of the show that was worth watching
Predictable ads all over the place in
Boring
Alex Jones these people the Ashley beckford's and the
Rob Jacobson
If they keep up this lawsuit
You're in real trouble
I think if they don't settle
You are in trouble
Man it'll be fun
But the other people come out
I really like to hear about like what other people's experiences were like working there
Gucciardi avechi
About to Alex I bet
Car he's probably got some stories
Patel
Has been fun Jordan
Knowledge
Follow us on Twitter
You can
You can download you can leave a review
We got the special Facebook group if you want to join then go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
Direct direct people are finding it
Also
But made a big decision
WhatsApp
With the Avengers Initiative
Right
I'm not going to make people a really long time ago
I'm going to do something that I think they'll like
Even more
All right I don't should I spoil it now I don't know
Should I
Okay
You just decided not to do it
No.
Not that I realized what I could do
Cuz I could make
A super long
Ridiculous soundbite
Play it for people
Haha
What I could do
I've decided to do
Create a 16 seed bracket
I'm f***** up things Alex Jones
March Madness
Dover what's the most
Alright I people can vote once we start doing the next episode
Real start pretty soon and then the voting will be in the Facebook group
Muhammad Ali
I might have to rethink this
I won't renege on a really long sound bite if this is not
Some people like butt
I think we will like it
Everybody loves the bracket
That's true
Alex is mad
Anyway guys thank you so much for listening
George Wendt
Racism in South
Except for the right
Quick to sue
You're very racist towards white people
Alexandra Thurston color