Alexandra first in color with huge fan of your work.
Sit around and talk a little bit about Alex
Jones
Something to do with my matinee Idol good looks
I know a lot about Alex is delightfully fun for people
Isolate
And this is the first time I've ever said man
This water is garbage
Garbage water say that about my good friends over at ice mount
I like the Ice Mountain line of sparkling water
Because there is a tartan
There's no sweetness like a lot of these other fizzy Waters
It's just a straight-up
Water
Straight up water
European
And that's why you are dumb
Jordan I've got a really fun show playing that for you here tonight for you and the listeners
Defeating the entire purpose
The show for me to know any
About
Can't wait
Sometimes I stumble
Whenever I hadn't seen the movie Moana
Can you just would not let up about
Never happen
Supper for me
Sometimes the stars align
In such a way
That I know this
Something along the way here is going to blow your f****** mind
It's going to be.
Okay I am just very excited to bring that to you but first couple of new daughters on the podcast
First Electric
I'm a policy wonk
Congratulations
It's not April O'Neil from Ninja Turtles
I was going to make
Review
April Ludgate from Parks and Recreation
Define Farrah.
I also like to give a shout out to Mike. Thank you so much for joining up
If you'd like to come aboard Mighty or as I would call you April O'Neil
Very elaborate
Knowledge fight.com
And helping us keep this going we appreciate everyone who donates so
Amazingly much
It's absurd to level of support
Interesting people reaching out to us makes this all its cradle possible as opposed to you and I
Losing our minds
I'm talking about this dumbass hole in Texas
Anybody listening
Like when we first started this I think it was going to be like
And what happened
Do that
Nice
T just s***
Crazy
It's not
Check back in with Alex Jones post-marathon
Of course because over the weekend
He was lying about YouTube shutting down his channel
Is accounted been Frozen and YouTube.
Videos of
Which kind of flew in the face of the idea that he was frozen
BuzzFeed reached out to YouTube and apps penny that was true and they said shut up
End
And I realized I realized the reason why is it because
He didn't make enough money at the marathon
Needs to really
Get people excited
The fear back in them
So I checked I looked at the
Ashok you're on Monday as we're recording
On Monday
And
Owen Shroyer without a lawyer
There's nothing here
Sunday's child
Refund
His lawyers
For real you did this s*** I don't know how to help
Pronounce just
It's the timer is that
I want to be there
You're screwed
Whiskey
That'll work
Watch Sunday it was really boring
Goddamn is nothing we can do
I guess I could go back to
Time travel episode
Which was September 1st
Until I went back never forget
September 1st
2012 13 and 14 I'm sorry 13 14 and 15 we're all best of shows
Jesus
Put packages
He's doing clips
Yeah basically it's nuts
September 1st on a food that I had in front of me we're all untenable as I can
Do a f****** clip show
But one of the clip shows
Included his interview with Russell Brand
Here we go
That can't
It's going to be great
He's a dumbass New Age Guru or whatever it was it was just boring
Really boring interview
There's some comedy in the fact
Exit like
Russell Brand is pushing
A revolution
And when asked what his Revolution
Oud galuteria socialist
Alex
There's some comedy to that but I realized it wasn't f****** worth
So I started looking
Is Russell Brand
I know that his Booky wook
Is a great literature
No I don't know a couple things from Russell Brand
Past
But I don't think he's great
He's not terrible I guess and here's the one thing I do want to say for all of like his
Overly scarf
Words like people who live in Beverly Hills and are worth 15 million dollars talking about Revolution
Posh lifestyle Drive
For all of that
Stuff that is valid criticism of him
Certain very annoying
He's not somebody if you look at his actual life in his actual career
He's not somebody who's just been all lip serve
Cuz he's really active in like
Union fundraising and stuff like that
Even trying to help people
And stuff like that
You can't take that away from
And I won't
And the fact that he grew up in was a horrible drug addict
And then has been trying to
People to
Deal with drug addiction as a disease
I tried to take that more seriously I think there's a lot to respect there even if you did
Doing all right
Even bright
Give me the poor ones who can't say anything and no one will listen to them
Just getting the job done he does a lot to help people and isn't all talk
But
He wrote a book called mybookie
S'more
I got to find another fuc
Celebrity interview
I got one of these it's got to be good
So then I listen to his interview with Jonathan Davis
Yes
Alright one there's a guy in corn name
Jonathan Davis
J devil this didn't come up in the interview
Irrelevant Alex
That's got to be the only thing
Yes I am the devil
Thank you
It was a really boring interview because Jonathan Davis
I don't really know much about politics and I don't want to sound stupid but Obama's trying to be a dick
Kind of sucking his dick
Because he's a Starbucks celebrity so much
The in the beginning of the interview that's the only clip I really regret not cutting
I've been a long-lived room all the time
Okay so now I imagine Alex
Just driving around in his Escalade listening to
Something
Listening to
Bullet with butterfly
Dude I got nothing
I'll let you know any cornbread
Alex loves new metal
I listen to that like this is not usable either
I would remind
Chart success
I do
Strolling around another day
Because this is too weird
I couldn't unpack it new too long
Actually listen to the whole thing by
Look for this in the future
Alex Jones
What
Alright
I had no time to like
Do you live that appropriately
It's like I got to put on the back burner
I heard that all the time girl
I found
Something that would work
Something fitting
And that is
Time that Alex Jones
Had a preacher on his show name Steven
Anderson
Are you aware of Steven Anderson
No
He he runs
Is a church
That is described as
Something that makes the Westboro Baptist Church
Look like God
An intense Church
Yeah we'll get into some of the specifics about him
But
I listen to their entire interview
Man it's really all about
Just arguing about
Free or post-tribulation rapture
Alright
I've been I've been wondering when we're going to get into
Tribulation timeline
Pre-tribulation rapture
I have done this strategically in terms of the clips that I have
We don't have a whole lot from that episode
Because it's really boring
But you'll see what I mean you'll see where we're going about Alex giving a little bit of an introduction
Steve Anderson
And then
Talking about a book
That is a part
Of his foundation
The foundation
Of his a philosophy I'll explain on the other side of this
You stupid
Capacitor
Who's here in studio
Pastor Anderson
What is
This carol
The real quick
The caller before they said brought up by Carol Quigley's book tragedy and Hope
Alex
Hands up
Just pretty funny
Do that but disaster
You're going to have to take away their guns take away their web
And overcome them
Housing Warren
Obviously
He's going to put us in a in a in a
And it's a ciety where we have no Freedom we're completely controlled completely
We're not going to be able to defend ourselves
And that's why the Bible tells us that Christians are going to be beheaded on Mass
Because the government Enterprise
Tribulation
The tribulation is about
Starship Enterprise
I could have come up with a
Am I in my research for the
For both referee
In my in my preparation for this episode of the sermon that this guy gave
About
You're really close
But Star Wars Star Wars in relation to the Bible
To the dark side and it's like anger
To whatever right
Hateley
To the dark side
That's not how
Yeah
He doesn't know s***
All right I move on to the next
I don't want to spend an hour listening to this guy
Critically deconstruction the reality of
Of that Star Wars
Eyeballs
I want to know I don't know how he feels about so many things
Okay
In the biblical metaphor
Did Han shoot first
That's the first question.
Absolutely
Like when King David
Killed his best friend
So here's the next
Where Alex begins to start reading
And
You get some some
Real stupid s***
Feel so pretty quick
Colorado
Bowers Elementary School read out loud
He's just making sure
And neither are you
What
Heath
Alex
The 1990s 2001
Small Arms
The treaty that they made that in the UN
I was about to
I just want to read you hear from
Was put out
Do you want about Miss
Do you have
Myth
This conference is being convened to draft a global treaty to ban ownership of firearm
The review conference is not about banning small-arms are prohibited from owning legal weapon
Be negotiating any treaty to prohibit citizens of any country
From possessing firearms interfere with illegal trade
In small arms are light weapons
The United Nations programme of action on small arms does not purr
Prescribed or suggest any action against the legal trade
Manufacture possession or ownership of web
Each sovereign state determines its own laws
And regulation
For the manufacture sale and possession
The firearm by its citizens
The United Nation
Has no jurisdiction over such Matt
The UN program of action is focused on
In Small Arms
Weapon
The program was
There is no illicit trade.
No regulation belly regulations
The program was agreed to in 2001 by the 191 member states of the general assembly
Including Parliament members members of the
The security Council
They committed to collect
Destroying illegal weapons
Adopting and improving National legislation
That would help criminalize the illicit trade in small arm
Regulators
Activities of brokers
And setting strict
Import and Export
It's not about saying people can't have guns or trying
It is just a matter of
Eagle International gun running
And then you're coming for the illegal weapons
Obvious
That's not even
Plateau
So Alex also there was reading
Carroll Quigley
Editorializing
Crazy
I'll give you some contacts after we get to this next
Clip where
He reads like a hunting pack
Archetypus
That's how we eat it's scattershot adding stuff
That just isn't
In the texts at all
Really makes it sound like Carol quickly just wrote down like
We're going to go after ever
Everybody
We're going to destabilize
Everyone
Right here
With such an amateur
Conditions
Affordable
Well forget
Certainly I can spend all day on that
No
So he's using a little sky
He's using a little passage from page 12,000
When weapons are of the amateur type of 1880 as they were in Greece
In the 5th Century BC
Power
Similarly disperse
And no minority can repel the majority
Yield to its will
But on the contrary to buy complex
Inexpensive
Can afford to possess
Or can we have a situation
Who control such specialist weapon
Dominate
The majority rule
So what this is actually talking about has nothing
Things to do with taking people's guns or anything like that
Quickly wrote This Book
Sixties has to do with the Cold War
Status quo systems between
The United States and the Soviet Union
Just on the page before this on page 1199
He says forecasting can be attempted only by
Extrapolating recent changes
Into the future
But this is risky business since there is never any certainty the present directions will be Maine
He goes on to really lay out that what he's talking about
In terms of
This stuff is
Back in Early Times
You had
Really rudimentary weapons
Absolutely
In those times
You had
Armies that were made up of
Citizens
It so you would have people
I would be
Driven to War mostly by overarching reasons to go to war like
Encroachment from
Someone's going to wipe us out
Stealing our drugs
The reasons
High-end philosophical reason
Things to go to war
Likes self-sustaining
Comes to go to war
Where is in the future
Going to become more complex
And more expensive in that requires
Professionalization of the army
In those cases what you would see is likely
A reduction
All out War
Because Endo circum
You would have
Professional Army
To go to war
Necessarily for the same reason
That you could whenever on head sores
And she'd like that they are willing
Alfred
That smaller
Right base
It's your job
Because Obama said like
Unpaid 1201
Professionalization of the armed services caused by increasing
Complexity of whack
Weapons
We may look for with some assurances
Unless demand for Total War
Using total weapons of mass destruction
Unconditional surrender
An unlimited goal
So he goes on to talk about the situation between the United States and the Soviet Union and how
The idea that we're getting worse and worst nuclear weapons
Makes everything much scarier
But also makes the likelihood of any of those things happening
Less likely
Because they're so scary
And because there are is not about
Interested
About internet
Operation
Minority and majority
Conversations within that quote that Alex use about like a government
Necessarily oppressor
Its citizens and taken away it's gone
Now he's talking about this wave at America and the Soviet Union right
Because of their specialized
You know you can't just go to war with America right cuz we're going to
We can blow you
That's what he said that's a big part of it
Keep coming back today
It's a text Fitz.
Descriptive not prescriptive
He is a historian
Who's talking about the
Friends that have existed
Throughout history
And civilizations and talking about
What is life
To come from these
Befriend
To do X Y or Z could come from
That I thought was actually very interested
There's still another element of this complex picture
This is this is also related to weapon
The large part of History over thousands of years shows that the reason political units
Grown larger insert.
Has been because of the increased power of the
Offensive
In the diamond
Weapon system
Any periods in which defensive weapon
Become dominant
Have been those in which political units remain small and area or even became smaller
The Growing Power of
Canceled
The. Of about
1100 BC to about
8900 maple
Power units so small
The all power became private power
Imma State disappeared as a common form of
Political organization
The cerose the so-called dark
So
Good thing I'm bringing up here
Is that Alex would probably really like the decentralisation of power
And making power units
Smaller he doesn't like
Federal government you like
The state government so if you really wanted to
Why don't you f****** tell everyone to get a castle
But you know what I'm saying like
Even in there he's not
Carroll Quigley Castle
But this is one of the effects
If you study history of offensive vs. defense
Anyway
Because of course
If you are defensive weapon based you
Are going to
Stronger
Smaller tighter nit
That's that's the whole point if you're
You're circling the wagons
Everybody's getting his closest pasta
So they can protect each
Everybody spread out cuz you wanted
Take as much as
Element exact offense
Yeah that's really fascinating
I found a copy of Carol Quigley's tragedian open
Nrm game coverage I said f*** this
1300 pages but I've started reading
Actually really fascinating so far
I'm about to
Love gun so my
Much because guns themselves
According to
Kind of thought process
Are one of the main reasons that we have a federal
A hundred percent
Stated goals are defeated by the symbol that he has chosen to love so much
The reasons of that like expansionism colonialism were able to be so successful
Every time that they were
Specialized
Military weaponry that at the time
But everything is so relative
Tell the time
This was written
Again
In The Sticks
So
Well yeah but you saw that the globalist
Anyway
I will have a lot more once I finished
Facebook about how stupid Alex is about Carol quickly and tragedy
But
Nearby
And because he is not
I could be able to
Pretends that he
I understand
Rock Hudson
Countryside on first dates
I prefer a supposedly fun thing I'll never do again
This is the last thing we're going to hear from the episode with Alex
Steve Anderson
But I wanted to play this
Especially
Just to illustrate that Alex is agreeing with him
And the two of them assorted tag-teaming
List a conspiracy talk
Is there an agreement
That's out
Important
Play Thunder the dragon what's happening right now
Real real quick
He's going to have cures for diseases in life extension
In 2016 2017 he's been screaming about Trump bringing us
Cures for diseases of life extension
Going to have all the political power
And the Christians are going to declare him to be
You guys are drinking out of it
And then
And then the new embodiment of The Dalai Lama
Including apostate Christianity
All of the major boss religious but it's Christianity for sound Messiah
Okay
Now we are looking for the second coming of Jesus Christ
Comes first
This is the conclusion
Freetress he's a hates the pre-trib guys because he thinks it's a cop-out for Christian
Jesus is going to call you
I think it's a function of his weird masculinity
Thrilled to go to the rapture
Christians
Anybody anybody
Is
The flavor of the entire
Just them
Nerding out
Real hard
As if they were talking about Star Trek
Gamora
Dan
Pulled a bunch of clips from various sermons of Steve Anderson
Dammit Dan
Is the worst
This guy sucks
Service today
Jordan
It's going to make you really mad but I promise at the end of this is going to be really funny
I'm doing this is
One of the very important
Do this podcast
It was Christianity
Stealthing
Secretly Dan is an Evangelical Christian
Nokia's
I've been trying to get Christian iconography into this
Iconography
Like my Cthulhu
What I want
What I want to stress is like
The caliber of guests
Alex has on his show
Like a lot of times people who come on try and present themselves as like
He's trying to present himself as like a Biblical expert or something like that
Here's the first clip Malibu
Is college
Say in their hearts
There is no God
And it's an atheist
Fool's Gold
That teaches humanism
Atheism
Is a lord
Is it
Institutions of Higher Learning
Some of the smartest people
The Bible says of the word of God
The simple
The Bible
The simple I've noticed people when they get paid
It's not even just spiritually they just get smarter
Did the Bible make
What is a dunning-kruger effect
Is that the is that the one word
You're kind of dumb you think you're smart you can never know out
If you don't know how dumb you are
You never consider that as a possibility
Bruce turn off light
Restarting off light
You're dumb
You've never even read the Bible I bet
Multiple times
What I mean
Some conversation to have there
Years of abuse Slow Me Down
Destructive Behavior if you want
Convert to Christianity
Cuz he just said it
He's seen so many people get so much smarter
Gyro
Toronto College
Well then you wouldn't be so
Stupid
Here is a ears
Steve Anderson talking about wish for
I grew up always feeling like a second-class citizen
I wish I were a Jew seriously
Number one man I want to be I want to be his main people
I want to be the special people
I learned the truth
It was excited
My truth is that
His church
Are the chosen people
That's too long for me to play it on here but it's just titled
Why we're not a cult
If you got to make that video
I know it was his church
Are they passed like all the
Bible stuff in
We're the only chosen people
I know for a fact
That most of Christianity
Apple State Christianity founder of the nonprofit
Faithful word colonero
The faithful Word Baptist Church
In Tempe Arizona the Church of
Currently listed as a hate group
Because of Anderson Rachel stamp
Including the police are radical stances
That's really actually
Making whole not races
He used to want to be a Jew stuff that is going to come in
Play of course
From what the videos that I watch it I might have not watched everything but from the video that I watched
Really seem like a rapist
Little credit
I'm going to leave
He was he look like is it big
10 with good hair
Is fine hair
It's super
Super terrible hair
Established his church on Christmas of 2005 at his home address
Established it as a totally independent organization
The church's website States faithful Baptist
Faithful Word Baptist Church has a totally Independent Baptist Church
Pastor Anderson was sent out by a totally Independent Baptist Church
To start it in the old-fashioned way by knocking on doors
And winning souls to Christ
About a year-and-a-half later the church was moved to a strip mall is also used by Anderson
Fire alarm installation business
When questioned about the relationship between the for-profit business and a not-for-profit church in 2009 Anderson
Angrily
Yeah
Good Times
I'm going to go on the record as saying I think I would rather go to church and some dudes home then in the fire
Do you like holidays
Yep
And now you have all this
Judaizer
Sears out there
And how we need to
Rosh Hashanah and Hanukkah and all that
Bright
Hanukkah's all that
And they want to get us on all this
Jewish
Hebrew roots
Instead of
Christian holiday celebrated
I'd rather celebrate the birth of
Christ
10 Hanukkah which is celebrating dedicating a temple
That God destroyed
Like you're celebrating a building the Gods
Troy
Yeah this is where we
But then later it got wiped out
Doesn't make any sense
Yeah
You get Hanukkah doesn't make any sense
Exactly cuz you could make the site like
His argument that God destroyed the temple and all that could be
Flipped back that the miracle of the oil
Staying for a few know as long as it is
God's way of saying
This is so dumb
Do not buy stuff
My fantasy is better than your fantasy
He sounds more by Legend is better than
But say it that way
Andrew Dice Clay and then he was like well I'm up so I guess I'll
A little bit later
What's with these other holidays
Rust around
That would be a fun show
Terrible negatives of preacher
BBQ Workshop material
Episode
Kippur celebration
Terrible
They they do the opposite
Episode of Seinfeld Delaware
They have to
Masterbait Salonga
He's not into that can go the longest
I will tell you this
Anderson is not
I would have never got
She's not into
Well I'm sure if you would press that would be fun
Drive to Domino's
What's the real miracle
So the first many episodes of this podcast will drink red wine
Well drinking
Lost for words
Steve Anderson
Thoughts about why
The Bible says the pastor should not be given
Hawaii
Fitbit
In the Bible is
Fruit juice
Often is alcoholic
And other times
It is not
But you know what
After I should not give either
What wait what
Because if I'm given to the alcoholic drunk
Call kind
To get fat
And you know what all across America
We have fat preachers in the pulpit
Holocaust
It looks
Sounds like
I'm not mad at all
I don't drink wine
Cuz that'll get you drunk
Right
Cuz there are just
Too many antioxidants in there
I don't know what an accident is
But you can't have that in my body
Preachers camp
You do what you do it
It's a terrible argument that doesn't make any sense
I don't know it's
So let's just go over s*** so far College makes women stupid and everyone else is very very
If you read the Bible you know not to drink fruit juice
Steve used to wish you was Jewish Pastor shouldn't be fat and Hanukkah doesn't make sense
First Porsche
Church of God
Or ye also have suffered lights
Even as they have
Juice
Elbow
Please knock
Is he making a point here or what
Who killed Jesus
They killed their own profit
Persecuted
Please God right now please not God
Maybe I just don't get along with you certainly there's somebody
Take it along with
Sing other country.
No
Preferably they must get along with someone
Okay okay
This is breaking the lid wide open
God is enough
Hint
That explains so much are version of God
Bear version of God
Jeep
I don't I don't I don't like
I realize keeping a little bit
In terms of
What this guy is capable of
Okay I just was like
Are you insinuating
Get along with anybody
And like
For all time
Christ
Sure
He's going to give us
Three more things
No cuz we got to move on to some
And move on to something else very important
Alright you're talking about pouring earlier right
Either way
P*** or not
You know
You're struggling with
Bust
Just one of those deadly sins
Like fruit
Steve Anderson
Is the key
The getting around this
Lust
Richest people have come to me and
You know I struggle with
First of all I like the
Be a lot of people come up to me
Set up
Let's just say I'm at the grocery store
Somebody comes up
We're back to hockey Stadium
Party people
Have come to me
And that you do
Struggling with
You know the temptation to fornicator or temptation
Fear Temptation with love
Solution
A saying that
And say
That's just so wicked and ungodly to say that you know
That the purpose of getting married
What the Bible says
That's what it teaches okay this is it really
Biblical teacher
From the Bible
People like it or not
God's work
Purity
Marry than to burn
That's what the Bible says
Okay
That's weird
I mean
Fairly innocuous for a cult
Strawman argument to like people's criticism of him
Marriage does not
Deal with lost issues people cheat on their spouses all the
F****** time
See there's all kinds of you know there's all kinds
The divorce has become
From
Lost on either Partners part and then
People with the first people say you're dumb
Because
I would doesn't solve the problem you're singing this one would be so far down on my list of things to talk to him about
With this are you a Nazi and then maybe after a week or so I get down to
What's up with that
You do
Are you saying you don't fucken your marriage is that what you say I'm not sure what you saying but I didn't cuz I thought it was real dumb
But
Where we learned pre-show in the the musical playlist that we both love Milana
Love love
Some of these great
Comic cartoon movies
Better come out
A number of the ones recently
But that is next clip is Steve Anderson
Giving a review of Coco in his car
Coco's Grill
Arizona
My church
And the kids meal at Subway with this
Disney movie called
Coco
And Christina has a big skull as the logo
And it's at 10
Telltale
Artwork of Mexican holiday.
He hasn't seen them
What
Alright
And Saturdays
Child
Dino's communicating
Converted holiday
Bruce
Who's preaching
This holiday the so-called date
Can Halloween and
And obviously I could tell that it
I watch the documentary I learned a lot more about it
Garbage
Promote images children now
Esteban
Yep so that's
Illustrated by everything
I bet
For him it wasn't that big a deal but
Thinking about it
That is V
Heart
Of just about every conversation that I have with
Like Christian peep
Specifically
My family is
I'm not going to
Engaged
Obvious
I don't need to learn anything about it
I can see from here as
You know what
The goddamn film
And it's about the joy of muse
Family is held
The cocoa is in any way related to how I feel about my childhood this sounds demonic
Actually
You just actually embodied why they
Is because
There
Perception is that if you get too close
Desire to stay far away by being like it's
Desire U2 stay Faraway is essentially
Ignorance and cowardice running your life hundred percent
Absolutely
You is you heard
He got raped
What does Subway
The music is so good
Subway
Is kid got a kids meal
Enough to make a f****** video in his car
Did he let his kid have soda I don't know I can't at that time
I can say I can't say either way on that
Vitamin Diet Coke
That's still how you get
But
Aspartame
I'm here is that
Subway
Yes what's up
Other words for places
There is no food
You think their food in hell
You think that in hell they're serving up
Mealtime
For breakfast lunch and dinner
If a person goes to hell
Good food
Yeah
You got a lot of
So much
How much badge
You go to hell
You never even
So that means that like sort of the metabolic processes have to stop right and I would assume that means my son
Central nervous system
Some stops
Okay so my body just magically create
Energy then
When I'm down in hell
God Mash
The Devil Run
So okay so God is allowing the Devil to
Continue like
My pain sensors and what have you heard
No there is nothing to power any of it
Okay
Ezekiel
Remind me how traumatized I was by the song by the Newsboys
That Christian rock band
The song called They don't serve breakfast
Inhale
And when I was there
I can ask
Country song
Like a Waylon Jennings song about a guy who
Teeth punched out
Breakfast
Lennie kills the man later
They don't serve breakfast
He'll talk to songs like at all
They would always
Play the song
Blaring
Over the loudspeakers to wake us up
Hell yeah and I don't know anyone out there who's actually heard this song
But it is not something you want to wake up to
Terrible I feel like I still ring through my head I might know all the words
About the Newsboys
Their band
That
Feeling always played a part in my life
Because of that
But I don't follow them on Facebook
I would
Like something that they post on Facebook
Your
Your setups for these are getting more and more torturous
Subway reference I was like
Okay and then I got
I got it you're going a long way for this
Look up taking us out a Long John
Pastor Steve Anderson
Has some very interesting rules about what he likes on Facebook
When your friend comes to you
And lovingly tells you
You're going down
A dark path
Yeah I'm worried about you
You're going down a dark path
What you're doing wrong here's what the Bible says
You know let's get this right
Come back to the Lord
That
Things that we need
To do
On every Bass
A baby picture
Looking like
Pictures of an alcoholic
Honda palizzi attire of a harlot
And we're clicking like
I don't ever click like on a picture on Facebook
Unless properly
I mean
Ouch
Underwear
No life
I think you're trying to do comedy
Clearly
Bottle of booze in the picture I'm not cooking like
Woman in pants
You don't like that
I just love that
She's up there giving a sermon like this in front of his congregation
Before he starts with like you know your friends
If you're doing something wrong I don't like pictures
If your friends are getting away from
From God
Take them aside
Can you say hey
This right let's get
Set you back on
Now other
People go on Facebook
They're f****** all the time got their babies and you click like
You sinful p
Pieces of s***
You sit it's what you might as well have had your own
Picture goddamn you if I see you wearing pants
And I wear short skirt it should be a long dress
All the time
Ankle
No it's got to have
Like where
Where did God really fall
On the below the knee
I don't know man
You said you didn't put that so popular cuz he really got into
Skirt length but look this is all just about subjugation of women
Install about reinforcing ideas
When was all about the
We live in a day where husband don't want to provide for their wives
Deadbeat husband
And sometimes
Literally
Stay home energy
Which situation that needs to be
T.i. and I are old-fashioned traditional is man need to fulfill that role of being a perv
And we need
The one paying the bills going to make the rules
That's a general
And we have men need to be a provider
Our wife should be able to say
Providing and I shall not
Well
I think I think
What's craziest about that is
Just the ideas like
No collaborate
Men need to make all the money
Because you make the money you make the rules
And you don't want you're making the rules
Supposed to be
Collaborate on the best rules for whatever we want to live our lives together
Oh let's see I want to do X Pursuit that might
Do you make a****** maybe I want to do a startup maybe I want to start up a small
Business
What is a doctor and she makes all the money for a while while I'm
Huaraches
Supporting me as I
Nurture
Partnerships could lead to better outcomes for
Possibly as opposed
Ratcheting who sells vent
Chains made of the rules that you don't understand
Shouldn't want even though you're told that you have to make them
I think it's something along those lines
But you'll notice that all
Do not commit
With the nerdiest lamest voice telling me about what
Men now what
Bright
You're clearly just overcome
Open setting and you're probably gay
Interesting you should say that
Cuz this next clip
Sean McEwen
That's
But my question
Hello Seth Anderson
Is my gun from Nevada
Sure
YouTube lately
And I called someone usernames where you are saying
The gays have a reprobate mind in a
Yes we had to cast
Don't have your chairs not just wondering
Is it
Somebody that was gay
Actually be saving
No I don't believe so because of the fact that
Where
Jesus talked about
People
Whose Hearts have been hardened in there and their eyes have been blind in fact I'll read it for you
It says in
Verse number 39 of jonquel
Therefore they
Could not delete
Because it is I said before he has blinded their eyes and hardened their part
Debate tonight
See with their eyes nor understand their heart and beat
Convert is a
The strata knife to kill them
He talked about people's eyes are blinded their heart is hard for they could not be
And I think that enrollment
Clear that
The reason why
Pretty hard dick
Casting a Google thing
Desire that
You're going over to viola fection
Do those thing
Hey Blaine
Now their foolish heart with dark
Can how you know
They are
Greg Poehler
Cujo
Ain't God in their knowledge the Bible says and they are haters of.
Haters of God the haters
So a little bit of correctly John 12:39
No gay
No I think it's also actually about just like non-believers
I was about
Anyway
Fun facts about about Steve
That you met his future wife is Susanna
Fallout evangelizing
Streets of Munich
He converted to Christianity and they were married shortly afterwards
Do you know what I do know what I
Yeah I mean you know what I get Mom not saying you can make all the jokes you want
I'm not saying he's gay
The Creep
I'm getting you know
You get the
You've run into these cats
Goat
I get this Vibe of like you found this you know person in a foreign country and we barely could speak to each other
I am doctrinated hurting my very bizarre version of Christianity took her away from her family
In Germany and brought her back
Stateside in Maui
Gucci stock
And because I make all the money with my call and make the f****** rules
She doesn't wear pants
Need to do that with people that you take from a foreign country
People people who bring over
Your life
I just get that vibe
Also
On the other complaints about gays
Very weird there was so much
You did the exact like
That little answer to the question
Was exactly what
I have heard from somebody
Former Christian
People
Define because some people think it's gross and you're like wait what did you say
You said some people he starts 90 something percent of people
Think it's disgusting
And if you take the homosexual population
Who definitely doesn't think it's disgusting
And then you just take the people who are like
Having sex with someone of your same gender
I don't think that's weird a gross at all
That's not
Just 10% of the population
Unless you're including all of the world there's a lot of like the third world
Countries where I'm sure that would bump the average up
Either way it would never be
That's crazy
Because I listen to this
I can't
You guys don't even know what I do
Yu-Gi-Oh diva
Adventure
You're going to
Germany
For they have a hair on their face
He's banging on the f****** Pettit like his his pulpit
So hard
None of that you don't you don't feel that kind of passion
Little known fact
Do you
Steve has been kicked out of multiple countries for his homophobic preacher
Kicked out of Canada
For not letting me
Country is they said that the
On the radio program
Where Botswana
Deported me
It's on the radio about the homos
They said well done
You know because they
We're not going to lie
That's not in an interview that
Deported from Botswana
Telling people that homosexual should be Park
Today's like
You don't want to hear anymore
Why
I'm wearing pants
I'm not allowed in 45 countries because
Antagonistic
Yeah it's amazing
He is a crazy
So
In his next
What we get in
He has some props
His sermons
He has a nut and a bolt
Okay
And this is a bowl
This is what a normal person
Right here represent the mail
Female
Ecuador
People do
This is what now let me show you what insanity
Said to do
He's banging them together
But if he doesn't realize deadbolt could be a butthole
Or did not or whatever that or no mouth
Is
Ladies on
I'll maybe he's talking about his
Which
You're fine man I guess
I guess you're doing alright also somehow this is a defensive to me as well
It doesn't work stupid
David is crazy
This
First off
Did he screw the did he like twist the nut into the Bolton like screw it in there like not how it works
He does not know how to sex
You may not
Good fun
Cuz he's making that stupid arguments
Delmar
Go to the
Church
Sitting there in the sermon watching the pastor goat
Oh man I can't imagine being like
This guy
Get it
I think I want to go I want to see how long ago
I can take it
Laughing I think this next ramp might
What stand-up to him
Preachers that are a spiritual babe in Christ
They don't bully me
Wake me up
Sodomites and queers
You're so alone
Need to man up and stand up
What are you going to do
And the reprobates are always bullies aren't they
There's such a small minority but they're always
Minority
And then
Phrasing
You know what
Cuz it made me so mad that I'm still mad I still hate their guts
I still hate these reprobates
I still hate these sodomite I still hate these haters of God
And we need some preachers
No
The baby crying
Tell us that we're not like Jesus and you don't even know Jesus Jesus Jesus
Did he get sexually assaulted
I feel like you probably got
That's one of the possibilities
He's doing now is not
Not appropriate
The other possibility is
That he had gay feelings
Seventh grade or something like that
Or maybe somebody is beating out of
Maybe like he was
Not the amount of
Obviously
Obviously his feelings were not beating out of
It was like he was
Picked on for
In February
Opus X
There's a lot of possibilities
The context to know but whatever
Is something ink
Credibly emotionally-charged
Andy trauma that he's very specifically saying happened in 7th grade
That has led him to hate people with a violent passion
Please go to therapy
This is not the way to work those feelings out that's not that is not good
Put your big cock in my mouth
You bully
What they want they try to cram it down everyone's throat
Realities of like
If he is talking about being the victim of some sort of
Basalt
Terrible
It's how you feel about serial killers when you hear about their child
It always
There is there's always some sort of serious
Trauma there
I feel for you.
That's awful
You're awful now
Yeah yeah I can't we can't go back and fix that
You should try to go
Therapy
But for the time being
You're killing me
It's an intensely complicated
Version of a balance
Empathy and
Disgust
If possible
Soufeel
Epic for him
Forgot
From here is obvious
The fuk out the window
With Mike.
Everybody passes
Steve Anderson
Baptist Church
And I just wanted to
Video about
About the shooting in
Orlando
A Muslim terrorist
Went into a gay bar
Another 50
Pizza mod
Selfless
Shot
And
Here's the good news
The bad news is
Pedophiles
In this world begin
They're bunch of disgusting
Pedophile
Come here
Are a bunch of
Gassing
Okay
Just now going to be
I'm sure
Gun control
Where you know law-abiding
Normal American
5 guns
For self-defense
And then I'm sure it's also
So-called
The two things there is like that's how it's going to go without the subtext with the the
Good thing these
Homosexual
He always
In all of the interviews that he's given that have been like
I'm glad people died
Because they are gay Pacific
Play I'm glad
People are going to come out
Give me for hate speech I don't even understand
Hey I'm just going to go out
And say that if
Said immediately following
His church
Shut the fuk up
Christians are dead
Maybe
Maybe some Christian
Would call that
Possible
Right how do you get to that place
I think
I'm glad that
Here's an interview that he gave in to BBC
Documentary
It starts with him and then I will
Ghost
So the interviewer
Normal people homosexuality and pedophilia are disgusting
The interviewer says
Pedophilia homosexuality
In the same group
He respond
They are in the same group
Because any man who would have sex with another man would have sex with anything
.
Like I'll put it this way
Sex with another man would have sex with
An animal
Interviewer that's blatantly not true though
He responds it is true that's reality even if you don't
It's reality
So you're Nibiru
What do you think homosexuals should do that
He responds
Kill
As far as I'm concerned
Because they're horrible Wicked people
They're just going to keep elastic
Destroying people
So I don't have any advice for homosexuals except to put a bullet in your own head
So you don't blast my kids or anyone else
System thread
I think he was probably the victim
Some sort of assault
When he was younger
He is conflate it is mine
That
Oh
Homosexual
The same
Is the person who assaulted me
Is really sad
I mean it's at the same time armchair
Psychology to be like well clearly based on what you said
You were blessed
There's a child
And so are you you're caring this
Hatred with
Is really likely right now but I'm not going
You just go out
Childish misunderstanding
Without psychoanalyzing him
From a distance or whatever
I agree with you
Very likely
Explained
Cosmology
Handle you causing
To a bunch
Two people and
The misleading of 150 or however many people he has
In his
And
He's the type of person
Who Alex Jones
Willingly has on his show
As an expert on religion
Now I told you it was going to be terrible
And then it was going to be hilarious
He used to go on
Michelle
In like 2009 or so back in back in a ways in the past
And in my looking around
I found this
Video
Pretty currently
Pretty funny
To give you some thoughts
And tell
Going down the road
You know Alex Jones
Quiet
Is it because I was bored
I washed
Just real quick
You like them
We have 5 episodes about why if that's a problem
Time
When we came out with our film
The tribulation
You know Alex
Website starting in early 2013
He also sold
New World Order Bible verse
Just come out and say
I'm gay
Email
This point
Infowars.com
A worthless
Emigrate
These people why are they
So get this
Okay which is like this
So boring
Pro homosexual
All three
Homosexual
No Pro Trump
Man
So one real quick
Last little Parting Shot hear from that video
You know anti-islam
IJustine
Republican neocon
Warmonger
Apparently
How is it feeling inside
You can't do that
So crazy
Get it and then just not be able to
Turn and look in the mirror
It's an unbelievable story of
You know we got this Gaston Alex Jones Show Who's just
On the surface appears to be someone who's into post-tribulation Rapture and then it turns out
Is a really weird Christian
Seems to have some
Strong feelings
And then also
Also goes on
Violent
It's about homosexual to the effect
Even going so far as to say that they're all pedophiles and he's glad that they got killed
We can use contacts
Clues to figure out why that's the case
And even he
Idiot
Can't believe they
It's a broken clock is right once it halftime
How does that happen
How does it finally over
It wouldn't
Also I like it I like how it's boring
These guys are just boring
It's because there's a
Just anti-muslim and anti
Wichita
Exactly
And they're not invited
Come on and they are selling
Because even Alex is smart enough to know when someone
Bad for business
You know
Get involved with somebody and it's
When somebody's bad for
And that's crazy because
Is still coming on realized
We haven't even him just saying all these shootings are fake
Look like that terrible for business
But somehow I got to get more out of
I'm too long
This guy saying that
Good people died in Orlando
You can't keep that guy
Even Alice
Conspiracy
Okay faithful Word Baptist
W b
Friends with benefits
Alright
Fair enough
This is an interesting
Difficult episode 278
That's such a
Dunning-kruger effect explanation
Perfectly
Like that guy
Is smart enough to realize
That they're putting out this dumb s*** over and over and over
To realize that
He is doing the same
Yeah yeah pretty much
Can't figure that
Next Level out because of how
Ansley Payne
The piece of
But unfortunately the end result.
Brett
Panda
I'd like to look
Almost caught leaders don't
Don't come from peaceful childhood
I don't know at the end of the day all I wanted to do here was take a little journey through one of Alex Jones has gas
Anyway did you enjoy the show please check us out over at knowledge fight.com
Please do you can follow us on Twitter is at knowledge
Rick Tyler also on Facebook
You can go to iTunes you can download
Can leave a review
Uup
Can I send your friend link to Apple podcast app
And that'll be the end of that
We won't be friends anymore exactly
Banner from now on number one way to lose friends
I know I wouldn't be too surprised
I also
So far on the in our Facebook group to go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
It does look like the people are enjoying
The idea of doing a bracket of sound bites
Instead of a super long one
So I think I will
Looks like we're going to go I apologize
Cuz there's like two people last time I checked that were
Adoption my burial maybe make you guys at
Develop
More
Expensive and complex
In order to ensure that the majority
Take over the house
You got to do
Alexandra first in color with your Japan I love your work