Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
A little bit about Alex Jones good cameras looking great
Even though it got knocked over twice
I just wanted I just wanted you to feel
Is a collection of
Spiked Seltzer's
Four different flavors we get in front of us we get Cape Cod cranberry
Filter we got Indian River Grapefruit
Don't know what that means
More weird flavors now
Why do they grow grapefruit
Doesn't matter to me at all I care about is
Fun fun
Sparkling water
Stereo
$0.03 that episode anyway
Water that went bad like I don't even know how water can go bad
There is an expiration date on most bottled waters you should know that
My God that's delicious
Alright
Who's there
Alright you coming me with the water thing
There's a hook
Do this podcast
How much do I know
The good news is my memory is almost
Right
Amazing amount of fun
You know what is next
Thank you
The show
And I did love The Mis-Education of you
Great album.
Okay I also like to give a shout out to
Donation pump it up a little bit
Thank you so much Mavis
I'm a policy wonk
Start until you're brilliant
We appreciate so much
How could you not go with that one
Oregon Trail
Computers everyone play Mavis Beacon teaches typing I went number-crunching
The one where you solve puzzles
Did you play Sopwith
I did I don't know what that is
Early Mac games
What's the weather
Event today
Alex Jones is once
Again on vacation
Okay
Alex Jones is once again on vacation
The
He's started naturalnews.com that puts out a bunch of real bad misinformation of
But Health you also swear
Basically Gucci already wrote for them for a really long time and then would use
Stuff you'd written on
Naturalnews.com
To be a story on Infowars it's a very
Incestuous Loop that they have going on
Would be like I assume anti-vaccine stuff
You got like acai berry will cure you of everything I don't know I assume it's in League with that
Answer the
The same sort of homeopathic nonsense
You trying to work
Nothing
Don't
Cichlid
It's the noise has gone down a bit for the below
The thing is like that for a long time Mike Adams was Alex Jones
Does number 2
He was the guy who Alex
Forget to fill in for him anytime he was gone
I did not know that
Or around there all the time
Years since he's failed
I don't think so I think he just didn't need them cuz David night in house
It seems especially don't because
We have the most boring guy in the history of the falling out but I think
It's more an issue of like
Brokeback
Anything is possible but I think the fact that he's coming back into
To the fold now it's kind of telling
Needs a steady
Yeah somebody can trust a real man
Cuz Mike Adams is much more of a man
David
Your soft youngin in the form of Owen Shroyer Milo yiannopoulos
Is a dishy gay man
So you pick it like you.
I'm sort of Alex
Replacement Mike Adams
Doesn't necessarily get freaked out
Scream all the time
He's more in line with that
What the audience wants to
50 out of masculinity
Coming out of retirement for one last job
So I assume at the end of this
Mike Adams goes down for
All of the crimes Alex
If This Were a funny movie Yes 2008
Sometimes Alex Jones
Comes back from break with
Panther theme song
Things like
You are Clouseau
Except
Cuso is like
He gets the job done
I don't know anyway it just
Fun thought I have a lot more thoughts about 2008 to go get into another church
The beginning
Tea Party Movement
Through the prism of Alex Jones
Which will be my next
The new one
Investigation
Party
Iraq
Start
A spoiler alert
No-scope Brothers
Did he claim to
Highfalutin ideas
Confederate
So we got that to look forward to get the
2008 investigation
Some stuff that will be coming down the pipe
Also The Gnome Chomsky interview will be coming up soon
For today for today
What is her today if ever want to break
Valero stock
But
Project Camelot been really disappointing lately
Haha
So
I guess there's nothing like
All the episodes are like
There's nothing to work with you
So Project Camelot is out
Into what I
Like okay
You know what else
Alex Jones
Has frequently been a guest on Coast to Coast AM
Maybe
Maybe I go find an episode of Coast to Coast AM with George Noory to talk about
San Francisco and interviewed Mark Richards on your own
Alright though I was listening to these episodes
The coast to coast analysis really boring
Because you respect George Noory
So much
So it's mostly just him saying I don't understand
He keeps telling George Noory the he's the Sam Adams of the second American Revolution
He doesn't he doesn't scream at all in the most salacious thing I was able to find was that
He just basically lies to George Noory space about
Your wife
Like that
Because George Noory that you need to
Clean up the record about
Your position on
Yeah yeah
Sound like
We got to find some
Something good
Then I remembered
2016 election
I like
It's like there's a lot of
Content
From that election
And we could dig into that would make for a great episode
It's always like I know the audience
Really want
To do an episode
About Alexa
This is the night
Cookout
To make this podcast
Because you were so disgusted with you man and I'm not ready to reopen that can of worms
We need absolutely unhealthy for the show to be at a point where
Like we're making millions office at backup
Either that or we need to go to couples therapy to survive view open
Uptogether
But then I started to think about it
And I remembered
A really fun
On the way to the election
And that is what we will be covering today
The time
The Julian Assange
How they 3 a.m. Prescott
And Alex Jones covered it live
Okay
So to give you a little bit of Kant
Julian Assange held a press conference
At 3 in the morning that was I understood that
Alex Jones cover device
You are
The most
Clarify
This is going to be anything about this
Know if you know anything about Alex's response
Oh my God you're going to have so much fun
Just to set the scene
Coverage of WikiLeaks from Germany
55 minutes away
Who got it
2 something in the morning
Alex Jones
Live in studio
I wait
I thought he was
What are you talkin about
Was this pre-recorded send these letters
Will be alive then also he's throwing it to break
We're going to be live coverage an hour early
That's
He started it
Very early
No I feel like you could have started that Joe
What could you possibly have to say for an hour before Julian Assange
Know what was happening
Is the
Started I started to remember this
I have mentioned this
Okay and I think I played a couple clips from
The end
But not the journey
Okay so well this might be reminiscing
Sent to some listeners of something we've talked about before it because they have a much better memory than you
Alex Jones
In the morning
Is going to be very much worth
He was like he's going to be live you will always be
Baby alive that's pink
Birthday was the one word Julian Assange
Okay
We just take the ride of Alex Jones being so very excited
To just dying on the inside of Earth
Did I give up the game fun to watch believes it to be
The day that Hillary Clinton is destroyed
Julian Assange
Is just giving a 10th anniversary press conference for wickedly
What's going on
Built it up in his head to be the day that he releases all of the information about Hillary
And the reason is revealed in this
Ladies and gentlemen
I'm Alex Jones
Yeah you are
Eastern time for the grand we're going to be live here until the WikiLeaks
Has come and gone
The last weekend
Ashanti net worth
Joseph
Alex
Assange has always been very judicious releases things
Natural
Flash 5 or so because
The very same stuff Bush does Willy go after them as well and they do
Will they hurt the people I want them to hurt
That's basically that
But hey
Troubling
Cuz he said that Rodger Stone said Rodger Stones been committing crimes for a long time now and
So we know for sure that he's a crime comiter break right now when he's trying to build this up
I'd like this is going to be the good
He has to bolster Rodger Stones credibility and he knows he's talked to him
Now he's like
Ha you ever say that
You stupid assholes both because if he just admitted that he was lying about it then
Travel
Also we know he's not lying about it because didn't Rodger Stone say it at the time or less
Like I don't
I don't necessarily know what is what
But if I had to guess
I would say 104
Rodger
Coolchems
Whether or not
Like trying to make himself or whatever the reality is
Rodger told him I've spoken to Julian Assange the more I learn about Rodger
Just as evil as he is
He is such chaotic
Cable that there's kind of a
He's doing all the wrong stuff but at the same time it's just like
Nearest scale
No cuz parent evil
Rodger
Ratfuck people he's wrapped f****** Alex like if you do wave this
Stuart is going to play out this is Rodger Stone screwjob
Hey this is going to be when it's on drop its
Accidentally
So in this next clip Alex is
You know it's a late-night broadcast
But
You still got to get some
Some plugs in here and their young
Your support of infowars.com
And everything we do is so essential
Burbank Park
Announce coming public
Where is my flight
That would be
Actually
I'll have you arrested
Dot-com
Good for you for reporting
Load of horseshit
The story
So there is a journey Williams
Can Post article about why this is a load of s***
So are on January 9th 1999
Scoop about Bill
The president
It turned out was not
The father of a boy born to a former prostitute
Dude in Arkansas
Okay here earlier it has been drugged who broke
The story of Clinton
The fair with White House intern Monica Lewinsky
Drudge's credibility with
I wasn't about to
Throw it away on some wild claim
But a love child but it just been debunked
DNA test
Yes 17 years later as Insight relentlessly promotes the political ambitions
Donald Trump
And fuel conspiracy theories about Hillary Clinton
Judges decided
To propagate the idea that
Perhaps this boy
Now a thirty-year-old man named Williams
Is Bill
Sun after all
In the past two weeks
Articles about William
Last Wednesday afternoon the website when
Quasi
Droste effect
Posting a picture of William standing
Text with screen displaying an image of himself
It appeared in another drudgereport Banner earlier the day
So you know
You're not going on here
That's so weird imagine what the
Before we editorialize
Interested Williams
Things with certainty that
By suggesting that information is
This is a grotesque twisting of History
It's based on a report
From WorldNetDaily
No blood sample was obtained from
This supposedly shocking revelation
From the former editor of Star Magazine
Bill Bunton
Poseidon 1999
DNA testing
Included the williamses
Chocolate and son
George learned of a negative result
And publish the news before star or anyone
But if but now admits that he never got a blunt
Franklin there must never have been a real test
Georgia saying
Which means Williams
Could be legit
In reality
The Tabloid never claimed to him
Tainted blood sample
It didn't need one
Because a partial analysis of Clinton the blood was available in the public record thanks.
Mechanic Stars investigate
Lewinsky affair
Right so it is neither knew nor relevant to Star Magazine did not possess a vial of Clinton's blood
The Tabloid needed only a sample of Williams bloodwitch Williams provided
Compare Clinton
Available genetic markers
So
From what I understand
Because
Kmart address
And then lied about it and then it was discovered it
Is true
Then invalidate
The other conspiracy theory
Go to the original content because the DNA
Actors that became clear that like
The blood test
The story change
Amy playing became that
The only
We had Clinton
Your toy
From the Star investigation
Not be more specific
Rflp test
Which is however
So
They're really take
Things out of car
PCR test
Which is what you cook
Do with
Clinton
Public records
As a potential father
Prove
The potential father
You can exclude him from the potential
Pool with people
Falco
So judge knew what he was doing
Tattoo
Rodger Stone
I put out
So it all around this world
Discord and hatred ever he goes yeah
In terms of propaganda especially Auntie Clinton
Some stuff Rodger stone is Rome
Dell Road
He's got his hand in every one of these little pies
It is not
The more I think about it the more
It's kind of like
If you are anybody in Ark
That was
Born around a certain time
And you were just like
I think I'm Clinton's biologic
Michael Kidd
You right-wing news would almost certainly pick it up an amplifier
Same effect
Probably
True now of
Claims against
Trump
Unfortunately probably is but unfortunately there are a lot of very
I don't think I don't think any of the claims
That'll be made publicly are
I also do believe that
Who was full of s***
People would jump on it
Right I think the difference between
Opportunistic left-leaning blogs
Probably would
So I guess that's the
The differentiate
I don't know we're talkin about
Trump's kid
At the begin true thing you heard it here first I am Jordan
Beat Trump
But that's me
The clear that
Hey you know what
This this press conference
In a f****** happen
After it happened
The media
The mainstream media
They're going to lie about what have
They all just lockstep
They come out and spew their disinformation all loaded on teleprompter
Unify themselves next 45 hours
Northwood
WikiLeaks
Embassy 14
Ecuadorian
Flowers in Germany
Archway press conference
Arch
Paraguay
Now it's clear and start of approximately
7 minutes and change
So you got 47 minutes left
Before Julian
Massages
Press conference start
And then there's another bit of time
Before Julian Assange
Himself
Choose state
This is bad planning on Alex
Ian
Clearly
I want to see this
I know we throw that around a lot
I think he's straight-up guarantee this is just him being like
I tried to get an app
In between the early shower now and I didn't get as much
Flavors that would like so I'm a little bit off don't know what time zone I'm in right now I think there's definitely
A difference
You can tell I think it's important to call it out
Princeville
Very drug
We can go along
I allow that is a possibility
Okay I'll allow it is a possibility that once the worm turns
He starts
This is not drunk
It's very tired but also
Pretty excited
And then what you think
It better be bombshell because they certainly what are appetite
I mean I've got my fingers crossed
Because they're attacking or
Because he's killustrated somehow rigged this whole thing is
So just real quick
At this point
Owen Shroyer
Is turned off
Quiet right now
Owen Shroyer is talking
Can you get to see his lips moving but there's nobody was looking at the video like
Anyway
Sure. We're not going to criticize anybody else
Specific reason hold on to it for the end of the show
There's a big we're going to go for
And you know he's making a big deal out of
34 days
Tell the election
October
I remember when we were all so bright
Jung hoseok
When our only problem was
Will you know
Most of the same problems we have now but just like lesser version
Also this really funny this video is still up on Alex Jones at
Channel here's the
About in the air YouTube
Four screw at 2 a.m. Central on Tuesday October 4th for a live broadcast
As Wikileaks releases at
October surprise
They could swing the election against Hillary if it catches fire
They're selling it
And the graphic that they have for it is just a picture of Julian Assange
Wikileaks October surprise
So Alex is awesome
Did Rodger told him
Rodger told him
Don't worry about it
This is the big time
Absolutely
So here's what
Owen finally gets his mic
Go ahead
It'll be interesting to see what the response is because with a lot of these Wikileaks it's nothing that really shocked us
It's nothing that you couldn't
So the question is will the end this is what the sign said in interviews that he did
Or will they try to spin something off tomorrow will be
You know a white cop that shoots a black guy so they want to run that story all day long tomorrow
See what the reaction is
From the American citizen
And from the world I mean the world
Everybody everybody
That sign saying this bombshell is going to be significant
So in the lead-up to this
You was talking big game
About how like Hillary was going to get
Information on her and all that stuff
But he never said that this play
Press conference
Was going to be when he released it
That never that deal was never part of his rhetoric
This is them conflating
They don't understand
Will clearly over the reveal that this is a disappointment
Hope you'll like terrible
Dancing around that but like
Fascinating to me how little they understand about the
Things that they see and read
Right but almost
Like if I recall correctly
He wasn't exactly disabusing people of the notion that it might be the time
This is all that information
I don't know like I know all the things he said
Absolutely but as I recall a 100
I'm sure cuz I don't follow everything the man says
But I think that a lot of the stuff he was saying when people were
Floating these sorts of ideas
This is when it's
Going to happen
We're along the lines of like we don't release
We don't talk about
Contact that we released
Until it's released
Or things like
You know basically the same flavor is None Shall know the day of the Lord's return
He comes like a thief in the night which by the way
Next one
In case anybody was wondering
I got some information
Pre-trib Rapture is actually true
I know you're just joking but what is that
Debbie crazy
Jordan
Can you f****** ruined it for everybody ruin your camera camera
Like all of God's
The plans were thwarted by
5 hours
So in this next clip
Donald Trump but he says something
In this next clip
That shouldn't
It really take what you think it sounds like
60 years of work
World government
People their constitutional
Run the boat Norwall
But he's going to get the boat out
That's not
That's not the
What getting out of the it's not so important that we get out of the dock we're like
Crashed
I mean we're out of if you extended metaphor
Real dangerous territory what's he like
Destroy the country
Forgot to roll them bones
I say we don't let it ride
I say we do
And also I would I would argue that
The metaphor of the
The country being a boat
It's tied up at a dock
Does not
Alex is right in that the government that we have now
Was designed to make us all poor
He just doesn't understand that the government we have currently
Designs to make
Everything
Collapse except for
The interest
The very
Which will of course collapse eventually but they'll have castles
It's like a
It's like going
Who cares I do to extend
Does metaphor anytime
Send a text
Ray having a race
The Harvard what are those what are those called like the boat
Gatlin
Nope no
Boat races
Raspberry and cranberry
Cranberry the Cape Cod cranberry is a winner also to put this up on the screen it's look at this here at the
Bottom it just says beer
Justice beer on the bottom of the
Don't go grapefruit
Is go green after red
Okay we go lie
Where's the flying from
Here we go with his next clip so Alex Jones really pump
For whatever is going to come
From Nissan
Revelation
That's a good question was
No he's not he's in
He's a big deal
Can just be
Suggesting that
The f****** globalists are going to
False flag
Shoot a black guy with a white cop
To cover up the story
Here we find out that more of that more
And if the thing that worries me though is
This is Darren
Aquamarine
Is just how
Literally cannot win
Just about a lot of the Hillary supporters that are already out there cuz I mean she gets away
With everything are we going to lose this going to be worse than I mean
Will this be worse than
Fauci Badgers women in
They're about to announce
Emails confirming
Illegal memes
Confirm that she's been plotting to kill Assange
I think also
Email the shipments of weapons
Antarctica
Directing the media word-for-word what to say
What do
It's going to be
Lester Holt
The actual
Also
It's going to be
Other armed ship into
Why not
The EU officials with NATO and the UN being directed by the state department to prepare The Collector
The lot into this one brush cutter
Keep in mind
Alex said
This is my prediction it's going to be
Everything that verifies all of my narrative
Yep
That's
I mean it's tough to get away from how like
Invested
That sounds you know like that's that's a very unhealthy level of
Yeah but what I say
I think he's really doing is putting
All of his narratives in there
Approved any of them to be like well
We didn't see this stuff approved but I still got one right the rest of its,
Exact yeah you're probably right needs to get one
Yeah
No sniper
No no no sniper activity
Just just a shotgun full of rock salt come out
Soon as we get some more prediction
I believe it's going to be
The Hillandale Stephen Morris coming out
Before the election
I just watching out what's on those things
Well he's pretty much stated that as well as he said he was he's got a
A treasure Trove of information that he's going to release
Set a time
You know so we're going to probably see
Once a week
Something like this
But I think the big ones tonight
Both of you are what I was so hot
Finish my Words I was stumbling over my next word
But this year
Guilt
It's responsibility
Ijump hours
Yeah it sounds like a good
Why does my soul
Never felt so good working this hard
This is history
History
So pumped
They are so they are like
This is the vindication
Because they
Never been right about everything before I get one
And Rodger has
Weirdly told that your boat is coming in
Jimmy's going to break
F****** you know what it is
It's Dee it's like a kid
On Christmas
Like a PlayStation
And it's real and they're so sure
Sure of it and then they get disappointed on Christmas
F*** with Eric
Because their older brother
Rodger Stone in this metaphor
Finally time that you're getting the PlayStation
Even though he's probably already being inside the Box
This going to be hilarious we're going to talk with themselves to be so great
Exactly
Send a text with Alex explains that he's the real
You know why
Because you stayed up late
Media
Picture
We're here giving you real
Live coverage
I wouldn't care if they were telling the truth
It's cnnr
Cool cool cool cool get a real name
Bro
Text Cliff just to move up Mulan
Other West Indies lime
It's just
We got to get spiked Seltzer's a sponsor is the way to go you guys want to reach out
Spiked Seltzer's and tell them to sponsor our podcast we would appreciate it
I don't even know if that's the name of the company
This is actually us finding out at 30 B
Zima is
Great you know what I never disagreed with
Even when I was younger man I didn't have one of those sort of an
I didn't like I didn't like us
Smirnoff Ice
I know it looks bloated
This is like if the shity water you bought earlier was actually delicious go down the road of my history with wine
Coolers
It's going to be a long podcast if you do
Instead I would like to submit to you this next clip
It just confirms that Alex Jones
Is
Fully saying
Their October
You're watching live coverage
Eastern
The WikiLeaks
October surprise that kicks off
In about 7
The October surprise baby
The kicks off in 7 minutes
Isn't this
Isn't it almost
Very similar to the time. We're done
Junior was
Text it was on
Twitter with those people illegally I wish I'd figured out the timeline before we did this
Probably
Didn't he say like especially this would be great especially in the
Or was it in the summer
No the one
The direct message
About somebody who gave him who's going to give him
Secret information or whatever
Email for
Amara
Right right right
Let me look that up
Advance
If I'm going to well I will be
Fair enough
What is going to be there
I'm just going to lay out grievances
That's all it's going to be
I'm going to lock the doors and I'm just going to be like
Listen up
Here's all the s*** that my parents did wrong and I'm saying this publicly we need to have an intervention religion
Cool it was months
Before the meeting was in
June
There's a
Gmail
Number for that exactly
What was going on
Clandestinely
Empty at this point in October
That's what we got there
Alex says we have 7 minutes
Let's tell it start
Journalists who are giving a bit of a lecture about the history of Wicca
Because
Anniversary
Until they're giving that it did
You know given
Chelsea Manning
A hero
This is very important
Pretty much everything since then has been b******* you know what I don't have a clip of this but this is actually the only time that Alex Jones didn't
Misgender her
Really actually called her Chelsea
See on this episode
Nora Bradley Manning
Wow
Actually
He has adopted the naming
In convention he does say Chelsea
Generally speaking
Now but also
Misgender
But in this case
Really cool with that brings up
Brings up how
It's on tubing like
Like I will go to prison if you release her
Pronoun
It's very weird but I think it's
The secondary
Enough so that he
Finally isn't
So
Exactly
To be prejudiced against everybody
Different italics
Complaining about how like
Have to keep up with these new terms
Introduces new term
It's not that hard but I can understand how it would be tough for a bigot to be like
Where
Why do I have to have
Finding new tires
Why do I have to keep finding new rationalization for hating people who are different
Why are there so many ways people can be different
That's got to be exhausted
Press conference start
With these people giving a history of WikiLeaks
Yes
I don't
Knew that was going to
What happened
He just said it was going to be full-on
Julian comes out in his life
Instead
If this
No
10 years ago we started this website
You know and he doesn't really know how to do
Plays it straight
Course heaven
Interesting editorial Vitale
Drop them
Thomas Jefferson was a liberal
Telling the truth being honorable
Obama and
Hillary Sanger totally alone the whole world must be shut down
Free Press
So
There's a real liberals
School
Imallexx
2 super into it
You still
The Patriot
Absolutely
What is a real
What does that even mean
Thomas Jefferson Thomas Jefferson was a real American
The true are you create a new
Then he gets to adopt
Founder of our country
He could claim videos
European
This is a guy
From where
That's where I got it.
He's British
Australian
Where is he from
Paraguay Uruguay as the reality
Country of origin for the song I got us trailer from the chat room
Who committed a crime in Suite who's now in the UK and Ecuadorian Embassy
He's an Australian they come for my light of criminals I don't know why there's no reason
So does everybody from Georgia
My point here
Don't say that
The bunch of Australian Elizabeth is that you have a sister
Hoo-boy
Circuitous
Exactly put himself in the Ecuadorian Embassy
City of the UK
Great
We gets up
Considering
Nevermind
We get Darren mcbreen jumping back in I believe
We're talking about
Hardcore
Is going to be
Accusation
Dismayed about the
Here we are at 3:30 in the morning
Fabric
Hardcore
He's going to get along Hillary
Super hardcore you guys were talking earlier about how
Water time to go to these News website more information
Going a step further Hillary Clinton
Tina has a Troll Army
For these trolls to go to these news websites to go to infowars.com
Go to Facebook
And to argue with a course they are there pro-hillary
And they basically attack anybody who has anything to do at 8
So these are trolls
Well Darren is completely correct
I don't think it look
I don't care what side you are on
For the most part
You do not have to pay people to be assholes on
Everybody does it for free
And you know what
Honestly I think it's if you're on one side of the political divide and you're getting abused a bunch
By people in comment section
I think it's actually a much
More comforting
Idea that
They're paid
Because
Because if not that means those people are doing it because
Their monsters
Text
When you look at the ideas like
Like
Take a picture of humanity it's like
Much rather
These bees dick
Posting all the
Violent angry
Otherwise everybody
Consider that they're just doing it because I feel this in my heart
Then like little boy
I'm in for
The rest of my life
Yeah there's really nothing
Can do outside of
Hopefully
Education
People don't like that
Specifically talking about David Brock
Correct the record
Initiative
Where they had a bunch of people who are going around
How to find places where missing
Information was being spread about
Hillary Clinton
Supposed to be explanation
Idea of life
And stuff like that of the reality
Is very close to
The version that Alex
Texas people who work
Did the version that Derek's
Is conflating
Probably
Dumb people with the people who were paid
There's probably like
You'll never really be able to prove
XYZ
The person on the internet was paid
Then you can take the
Behavior of someone who is awful
And assume that's the same as prisoners like
No actually hears them
Here's an article about what really happened
I don't know
You're never going to win
Because they are always react
Yeah the only possibilities education in education is
Really going to win because
In order to be educated
You have to admit that you
You don't know that
Publix
You feel stupid
And the people that we are fighting
Against are essentially people who
Refuse to admit that they don't know
It's a threat
It's a threat to your identity
If you're a manly if you're like
Didn't this male identity of always being the strongest
To apply to the intellect
Actual Spears
Like I know
Packy
Nike thing
But I bet he won't
Casper directions
Like I bet
NYU
Why don't they make the plane out of whatever the black box
I haven't lived with masculinity what does
Does Mexico
The next clip
The manly as hell
He doesn't do that he does a pro wrestler
Style shoot
Alright David Brock
You know something I don't
Airborne
Fox News
Calls you out MSNBC calls you out
Doubt
And you respond Hillary Clinton calls you out says you haven't darkheart you respond with and I never cover.
Okay
I called you a money laundering fee
David Brock noticed he won't where are you want to go there
Is somebody is somebody said something that damning about myself about my personal record I think that I would
Want to respond about your a lying and accurate
Piece of s***
Right
I can't wait till calling you out
If you want somebody
Let me tell you something
You work for a line
Uline
You think you're a bigot
Even broken you don't even
You're all so bad at your job
This as a potential X
Explanation
Alex has something to
Game from engaging and that is increased
Exposure
Anthony sells more of his dumb
And David Brock doesn't have anything to gain by engaging
David Brock engaging
Exactly
This whole thing is like
Is so desperate when you really look at it through like the lines of
The real world
I want to dignify you with a
You're just trying to
It's schoolyard show
It's absolutely Boolean we're in something of
The opposite position
And insofar as
We only have something
To gain if
Alex comes after
He will then
So Alex what I'm saying is you're a giant
Write whole worldview is based on a
Did the issue to it when it comes down to authentic
Is that like
I don't know if David Brock
Is involved
I have no idea
But Owen Shroyer making Zack
In order for it to be liable like proving it in court
Is different
In the same way is that like there's
The way that our laws are written in
In terms of like slander and libel are the it's very difficult
To prove the legal standard of those things
To
Speakwrite you would rather era
Well they have to because that's their whole basically
Literally all they do is as
Is close to a libel law
As they possibly can
And satellite
It's Not Over
I'm accusing you of money laundering I think that you are an absolute
Mccratic campaign donation funding
You and Mary Bonner need to be audited and looked into by the IRS and probably put in jail
Okay let's hear you respond to that I bet your darkheart as nuts look how he's a total moron he looks like
Deluxe
I'm look at that joke
I don't have any proof that he's a money launderer so
Some level I admire that Owens
Troyer was
Least saying nothing
You know it's trying or true but at least it wasn't
Dumbass hair
And Alex can't hang I mean I don't know if it's
Just because you
It's that late and you're tired
But you do that at noon and Alex is
Alex's
Afraid
Making that kind of a conch
Creek claim
Alex Wood
Would much rather just
Go for the
Emasculate
As opposed to anything else because he knows his viewers aren't really going
Care
Like David brought you can say David Brock is a money launderer
And they'll be like
What's that he looks like I'd lobotomized
Whatever it is
The next clip
Topic of money laundry
No
Fortified supply.com
Text deadline
April
15 are fast approaching
Alex
I don't want to I don't know for sure I don't know all the answer
Isabel law
But I think he might be doing some money laundering
I don't think that's libel
This is when I get there this going to get their dicks
His hair
It's not enough
Mars attack
Actually
He's a connoisseur of Vienna sausage
Yes
David Brock has a
The super Pacs hosting these parties are actually he served miniature wieners
Boyfriend
Breakfast sausages
What restaurant
F****** Crush holes around like a
I bet
Rex
I'm trying to insinuate that is super gay
I'm trying to insinuate that Vienna sausage
The
That you said was actually a bit as a two-man Act
Is that like
Owen is doing
Exactly what you should do
Well because Alex's bring it up the mini Weenies and what-have-you to make
Expunge of the idea that David Brock is gay
And Owen is like well actually
Now bring up
Substance
It's true or not is another matter
He had to pay his boyfriend all this money
No no I'm literally
Alex
You are the worst
You have already dumped the B
You're trying to do it again
And Owen doesn't have the Improv chops to roll with it like
He's like
Yeah right yes I mean
Well the thing to is there like I don't know exact
Actually what the money they're talking about is
I don't really care
This is just part of their pizzagate coverage
Because David Brock
Ex-boyfriend is James elefante
Who owns
King Kong Pizza
Which was the center which was the center of the you didn't know that
This whole thing happen
Paramount Pizza
Obviously false
And then
It has a moniker of
Blank. I don't give a s*** already
After that figure out a different why is everything
Now I'm doing an old bit
Is it that they don't make
Planes out of pizza
The whole reason the pizzagate got Beaumont Event
Focus
Steampunk
Because emails that got leaked
There were emails
Between John podesta and James
Because James alefantis would host
Podesta
Hillary Clinton
Related fundraisers at,
Because it was one of the
Hottest
Best pizza places in washing
Got that
No I don't I don't know
I feel like it's not even appropriate before that
To another reason
That I hate them
Because it Rhonda perfect
I don't think so I think they had already broken up by that point
I don't know people's private
Not really all that important
Fair enough but
I do think
I do think that one of the reasons they pizzagate got pushed the way it did
Is because James alefantis
What had a connection
Interest have a very serious boners
They want to crush
Because
I mean Hijos
The most widely
The traffic site that
Debunks their bulshit
So it may all that is to say
I don't know what money
David Brock gave James Oliphant
I don't particularly care I imagine it wasn't blackmail
That's Wyoming
Claim that they never covered Pete
Pizzagate today
They talked about a lot of it
A business clip
We get the
First sin
Sensible thing
It said bye
Staff member of Infowars
RAB do
Says guys what are we
Rob dude sitting on the sidelines
And he has
It's not reasonable
What is the most measured response
I think of any
To this 10-year anniversary
Well let's see your hopes
Just beautiful to me
The problem
It's Rodger Stone
Not Julian Assange
He started to
Smell something weird
Weird
Stone
Smooth this over
Like immediately
Late like Alex almost certainly had like this
Rodger
We're going to take care of it
During our March 30th episode when I did a impression of him saying that Adam Schiff is a p****
Alright I have never been able to recap
Whatever we really translator
That's pretty close
Good but I don't know
Where's on
There's more and more the
The history
Of Wiki
More
People
Just talking to big game about all day but
Yes and it is certain point
Starts to grow
Questions from the audience
Impatient I'm here sweetheart
Don't call her sweetheart
Don't call her sweetheart 9:00 is he can get in these here parts
I mean I guess
I guess it's better than cupcakes
Still don't call her
He comes from a different era
He doesn't
Maybe ten years older.
That's really f***** up to
Not more than ten years older than
Yeah I know right
He looks like s***
Anyway
In this place
I don't I don't want to gild the Lily with their specific talk I can just bluntly throw that out
It is equipped
On with it
He's getting like cuz at this point
Still think
Is coming
But he's he's growing
Emily and Paige
I love that WikiLeaks
Porter's
Literally
Wiz
It's totally screwed emoji
Wards.com
Live coverage
42 minutes into it
Problems with people doing the presentation are so cool
Information
Also along the way you've been like
Really pissed off
Peoples haircut
Yeah like
It just all of these people who are doing the WikiLeaks
Press conference
Bassholes haircut
Do you fix a man whose hairline is receding
I can respect that at 3 a.m. he's like
Haircuts
Your hair is so good
Brandy motherfuker
Alright I'm going to let him off the hook for that cuz I will
Do not understand it at all
This is why I get called
It's not whatever it is you're about to
Sometimes
You name it
Because I don't have
On a weird Power Trip
Article
Where the future where huge Wikileaks is gray
But it's good to see how unpretentious grudges
You just said you're the future
How unpretentious Infowars
What we've done
Andrew Breitbart
Amazing video
Packers
And then the stuff they released
It didn't quite live up to what it would be
New video
So you guys back
Do the the Wikileaks conference
Because he realized
Because we didn't know
Is nonsense
Obama it was not the next day that he died
It was
Later he had enough
He died of a heart attack
Because he was a very unhealthy man who's probably deeply into cocaine
Who was watching
I don't know
Look I saw Andrew Kennedy I'm just going to go through a list of the Supreme Court Justices I wish were dead
A video of the other day and I got
The truth
You know what I did I know that I'm wrong about
I know I am
Ahead of me saying
I do I'm wrong
I think I could hang with Andrew Breitbart and not like
Beat his ass
Or something like that
I wouldn't I wouldn't be so angry if I hung out with Alex
I would Li
When I say beat his ass
43 NASCAR
Unless you and
I would hang out with Alex
Talk to him for a little bit I got to go
I think I can hang out have a couple drink
With Andrew Breitbart
And think he's an a******
Also slap him on the shoulder
Maybe like you peace
Play we could be
Conviva enemies
Like Matt Campbell
I watch the video of him like convivial by
Whatever I watch the video him like f****** with some protesters
Pizza
That's not
Whenever were reminiscing finally about whenever
Things were less
Roller skate roller skate roller skate
You guys going to push me over
Olivia
That is pretty funny
Anyway I will give the ghost of Andrew
I've also been considering the possibility that since
The Deep dive
Researched his dad
And I know how people like Alex Jones
Misused it
For their own purposes
I might do
Just feel misplaced
Entirely possible
Whatever the case
Don't.
Second player games
Kill Andrew Breitbart for their own purposes
There's no question we should be
Yeah
Your partner with that contented a heart attack
Anyway it is next clip Alex Jones confirms once again
Des
Waiting for Santa Paws
4 / 0
We start investigating reports out first
We Charlie waffles control
Let's go back to
Sarah Harrison abs
So no radish
Can Santa Claus
He is coming
Very soon
Yep that's where he's at
Snowden
Had nothing to do with WikiLeaks
It was Glenn Greenwald and the guardian
But I also think they just to give Alex a little bit of credit within that context or you saying
It's not 121 necessarily that he was saying
Vulcan
It's possible that what he was saying is
Stream media screwed
Snowden over
Maybe he's going to
Finger Greenwald
I'm not entirely sure
Screwed no I don't think you did
He didn't know I don't think I think that if you look at the what he said
I think if you look at a proper pronoun usage is beyond Alex
Yeah
Good morals the complaints that he made in that clip that you're referencing
What we're about
Like the Washington Post that's true I don't know
He might
Still think it's known was involved
But
I we can't we can
For sure
This point
The time has run out
Clock has run out
It's time for Snowden
Now you got to know tonight
I got if it's time for a song to make his his appearance
In this clip
They're waiting
The people doing the Prescott
To get him on the phone
I Am The Alex Jones
Violent
Come on now
All the
Watch the blood spray
Magic
Restarted the computer
That's out
So a little Punch-Drunk now I think I might have had a few drinks
Still don't think he's had a few drinks.
You get it that you get to that like for 5 a.m. moment
You stop being like I like if you
If you remember like
Yeah bladi remember when people use
To duloc
And you'd like to everybody
Cuz everybody's so tired.
The real you would
I don't know if it's the real real Alex
I'm scared
Budgeted lovingly
I want to kill political
First album in the guide
For good measure
That part was
Politico
That was just
Regular technical difficulties
First loser
PopularMMOs
So I was correct
Language
Fight time
Tonight this is annoying I'm not burning into my weird grammar number. Has been appropriate
Because I have mispronounced
Couple words or or
The pamplemousse
Anyway
So Alex
At this point
Saint John the
Alex
So they think they're going to get us on
Direct
What do you mean
Find me an Infowars thinks that they're going to call us on
And it sounds just going to answer
The people doing the press conference that they've been watching our calling a song
Because he can
That's what they're trying to get him on
Skype
And they had a little bike
Difficulty or whatever
Beyond hair
He's
Gung ho
In this the globalist
They're trying to stop him from talking
When in reality
Skype drop
Skype call
Suisan
Get on
Restart stalking
About the history of Wicca
Alex Jones
Starts to realize
It's not going to go his way to realize this might be
World
Alex is Alex
Alex
I think
Vicky wants to own a fox
I stayed up
For this
God what am I doing with my life
Alex
Disappointed
I meant something happen
I was with Owen Shroyer
Considering he claims
St.Louis
Okay
State Lewis me
Why does he say Shack
Because he
He's from the East Coast
He was going with
It's 3 in the morning
So it coming through
Flipped out boy
He's actually probably some sort of bougie
A******
Comes from money and you
Is claims that he's from Lisbon
He could be a selfie
Fine
Even so then why would you cover that up
That would be perfect for the info
Pretend isn't really him
I'm Shack
Probably from New Hampshire
Maybe I don't know
Whatever it is
It's the only state on the East Coast
All the recipe
What about Rhode Island
I never heard of
But like that that to me is really fast
Cuz it happened another time to I've heard that happen twice
And both times
He's like said
Shack or the other word was then immediately
I am shocked
Fitbit's
That's cray
That's crazy
Especially because
He did have an actual Missouri accent
Even be a thing
No
When
When Heaven
You been
So tired
That you act
Accidentally pronounce
Something in a regional accent that wasn't your ex
Actual speaking
Oh that's crazy because I am from Zimbabwe
So
Adalat can
I can't let that
We're getting out of the wrong
Country
Greenpoint from the chat room that is at Wisconsin also has that
Or Minnesota
True Minnesota
I don't know there's something very specific about the
It seems East Coast
I might just be biased because I grew up in Boston
For a little bit when I was younger
Spinx of Massachusetts
In in my experience
I agree
There's it that these owl is like
We different
The phone app
Wisconsin Minnesota
Boston
He's got a ginger
So they also have it also goes along with the sort of
Traditional Boston
Anyway it was next with Alex Jones realizes B truck
Well we're just going to be honest
And
Aaron baddeley
Because I'm sitting here and we've got him
Call Sharon
I'm struggling to make out a lot of boy saying I've been trying to hear the words Clinton Or democrats are you
Let's go back to
Might be a little bit of
Insight
The oddest thing he's ever said
We might be too stupid to understand
I mean he's being quiet but yeah
Talking about the
History of WikiLeaks
Right
That's what the press conference is about in the reason that
Because they are looking for XY
Lindsey in it
And you only get
This is all Greek To Me
It's just their disappointment showing proof
2 to the
To the actual reality of the Prescott
Can you really point to
Earth-shattering things other than
Chelsea Manning's revelation
And the way that they f***** up the US
For WikiLeaks
I don't think so
Yeah right
Interesting
Stuff possibly
Buena Vista
Some things that are
Interesting
Groundbreaker
A lot of releases bad
Are embarrassing for the US government but a lot of those were just things that
Uninteresting to the general populace
And if you really get into them you'll be like this
Does mean something
Yeah situation
Yeah yeah probably
Well
Anniversary
Explanation you need to be more like
Chelsea Manning is a literal hero
That was imprisoned
I mean
In their press conference Maybe
That's true of all we can do is look at Alex Jones having a real bad time
At 23 in the morning
It's delightful
I love it
Alex Jones fully realizes this is nothing
And that he floats
Going to
What
Call position
Like a little bit of love it I love it he's now insisting Assange has made a deal with Hillary
Nobody said there at the end
He's making a deal
Witchy reinforces
Miss Mexico
Change the weather to
Devastating
12 yd
So
Phineas like
If Alex
At this point in October
16 was so confident about Trump and everything like
Why are you freaking out about how we only have 34 days for secret information
To be released by this organization
In order to win the election
Desperate for this information on the table screaming 34 days
Kind of kind of gives a different picture than his
I just
This is
This is so good this is like
Are dabs
Broadcast live
He would constantly be like
Oh I'm wrong
Oh no I'm wrong oh no I'm wrong
Like that's why you don't do things live Alex
Hawaii
Rodger Stone his accident
Lirette.
So in this next clip is
That is the reason other news outlets
You teleprompters
And protect their overnight
Because I can't verify it
Also that's why news outlets don't be like
You don't hear Jake
Tapper being like
Here's my prediction this interview will verify every little thing that I hope
Pray for
At this point things turn ugly
Alex
Jordans
Crackly laugh
After he said
It's a
Constant
Paqui cracked up
I agree with
That was hilarious
Interesting
It was in the WikiLeaks
But not this time
I am greatly disappointed my God
So this exquisite
We always having
So much fun
At somebody like a Julian Assange
I get to just B like
Relax
Text and be like I am enjoying this too and then trailers like
Let beat.
Don't worry it's not over
Hillary Alex's b******* is not nearly over
Adidas Mexico
We get what I am going to label
Hap's the
Weirdest
I'm going to spoil it ahead of time is an adverb
Where is being racist
He's going he's going all-in on being sexist racist
Disrespectful
Text Cliff dude this is a weird
But I've ever heard
Did my tire time
Huibin Tang
Wife watching
Vegetables
That's so weird that's what you like
Sales and product by the way we have no no no no no
What's fascinating to me about that
Three pieces of that that's crazy
First is
We got trolled
Which is like admitting that you're not a journalism Outlet first of all
Soccer in house
Second
Is that
Julian Assange
It's all gravy
Anniversary
And there's a book
I bring
And it's not
VI minahasa product
It's
Like a knee-jerk reaction
Product for some reason I have to like there's going on
We're just like
We have some knowledge right buttons
And he will shut down and just start
Muscle memory
As the ball rules
Lower lower it one more time with that in mind
Weaving town
Selection
As Isaac goes on that's when he gets into
I started it
Let's f****** go through it
It's
What is always
In his heart
Is that
When you were saying but like your
Realself
Comes out
This is where I would make that argument as opposed to the slit your throat
More the
Do selfie
Also I've never heard himself
Heirloom seeds
Gross of real plant
It's one of his old sponsors
Stuck around
Whole Foods survival seed bank
Right and what have you
Someone did tell me that
That websites
Going to go to it
Drooling
He does seem I mean he does in this video again I'm hoping I'm going to keep my fingers crossed you later sound will come out
Something still here
What are y'all going to have
No no no he said
What the hell is your problem
Easter Bunny
I came here to chew bubblegum and listen to Assange leaked documents
And I got neither and I'm all outta Bubblegum
Man I have never been trolled like this
Hoo-boy
They're references didn't
Workout
The two main actors
Falling
Is not good no it's
Owen Shroyer
Is
The f****** worse
She's not good
Is really bad
Hoosiers Boston Expo
Let it free
And listen to a song
You can't
And I got nothing because that's not a joke that's a c
In terms of a line
Well but
The reasons I came to
Chew bubblegum and kick ass
And I'm all outta Bubblegum
Works
Right is because both of those things
You have can
Control over
Like I can't chew bubblegum or I can
Kick-Ass
Also rowdy rowdy delivered the
Hell out of a cat
Control what Julian Assange
You're kind of like I am either going to chew bubblegum or passively taking this thing
Happened
And I don't have gum
It doesn't really work
Was good
Garbage
Alex is bad
Brett he's not doing his part Brothers worth
F*** you for thinking that
Does Alex about to come through the Haymaker in this next clip
Is this
Explosion
Hillary's October surprise
Julian Assange
The world is Hillary's
Massage
Israel
Hilarie Burton
Are you thrilled
Excited to be lip-syncing
By the way
It was The Rebirth of The Rock
So
Hillary
October
Surprise
Rush is about plug and that is that she has
Co-op
Julian Assange
She is making a deal with them
And that's the surprise we've been trolled
Howick
His
His insanity
Tastic extreme
As just do it all
But for one night
Hated them
Much
Tired and they're the reason he's awake
Do good
It's fascinating because like
This speculation like where he's going with whatever his narratives are
It's so counter
To like just being like
Like if you or you and me
And we were doing everyday radio
Julian Assange
And we were do it like
Edit turned out he was doing I just like I do
This is our tenth anniversary would be like
I guess we had it wrong
Yeah there's no information here I guess but happy 10th anniversary
PS turned on.
I think
I didn't know if we were doing
Rochelle and you were like
1 Audubon Lake
No
If we did stay out of my life
Sky
All right what else is going on
I don't know what's get out of
Instead of
And I can't
Feels so f******
Hilarious
So bad
Because Rodger told him it would be
B-beg
Julian Assange
A lot of pressure being threatened
But I can tell you
Flash Maxwell
Every few days
Election
But
Decisive information
Ambro Eastern Time
Central Time
You don't know
In fact
UK
Of course
Literally you didn't show
Because you do
And you were
Screaming
We got 34 days
You had the real whistleblowers and real document
This would be
You'd be in bed
You are
That you have those documents
You could release
Pizza
But you were waiting for Julian Assange
Tilly's really stem
Because he has a wider audience
What Cox out the fact that you don't have enough
+ 3
You had to say we're not losers
Well you did upset
Because you don't
Cuz he is a loser so now the real true comedy of this
Is that
Has been having people on like
Esperanto
And
People like
No I don't
Pretty sure that the fence
Benghazi
In his
Rat
And Tosh Plumlee
Proven
Did Hillary Clinton
Was an out-of-control that I've been Ghazi
Why
At the beginning of this show
Would he be saying
Oh
What's going to happen is that
Prove everything
We say
That we
We didn't prove a goddamn
I don't know what proving is or maybe that's worse
Well he does and that's why he did the show
You know what proving is the show in order to prove it halfway through
When he was like alright
So he's going to give us
Before everyone
We're going to ride
Sure he gives us the dirt is doing a business meeting in the middle of it like here's what we're do on break
Exactly
Cuz he doesn't have s***
But he does have
I'm still trying to figure out
Hack job
You are saying that you couldn't have no I was going to and I said I would
That's not going
Also like the
You can't even give us good audio that's where we flashback to
The beginning of the show and Owens Mike wasn't
Stab you in the back like
By the way
He has destroyed himself
Rold gold
Is there black gold
That was soft
Now we have to wait
I think we got a new we got a new who was it that remix the last one
I think we got a new one to talk to Matt
He heard that song and he just got into the part of it
Too many other words
Does not release
Just describe Rodger Stone
Course that was it uses or just describe
He's going on about how
We had all this information and we were told
And it was a was supposed to comment we had intermediaries and we had the whole thing
Nothing
And then he's going to say
You just gave the exact
That Rodger stone is about to give you
One more clip left
It is sort of the end
Adventure
Early hours of the morning
In this clip
This is our Colonel Kurtz
He dead
Alex Jones end.
Little bit of advice
Assange
And then close
The only way
Synonym for shokan
This is basically the
Freebird
Hookah Infowars
Everyone knows exactly how this show is going to have
I was just wondering news covered and phone calls and cover it up video
If you want to sell some
Here's a little advice
It's hard to pay for all this Runner and support
Equality video
Planning this this is something they had to plan
Calling off great great job crew
T-shirt Starbucks
Slam dunk slam dunk add pivot Jesus
And they were planning this room we just decided to do this on the web
We're bad it was earlier
But also the other day
The beginning of the activity was
Forced to work overtime
Technically jaller salary
And this does not count as overtime
Exactly so I mean
Disgraceful admitted to end
Giving
Add pivot advice
Is just like
Listen if you want
Just David
Physically giving him advice on how to fight over
If you want dum-dums to send you money
Pretend you're a victim and then they're going to f****** throw you so much money
It's crazy you have any idea of millions I'm making office cam
He was an overnight if he was like 3 a.m. to 6 a.m. slot on a lot of shows
We would get such an
This version of Alex
Credible
She would have
He would not know how to lie the correct way
He's given up
So much
Episode did overnight
To sleep schedule with a job
Eventually he'd be able to live very well
But
To the end of this adventure and one of the funniest
I got super excited about this b******* that Rodger stone is lied to
About
You don't know what the hell I didn't know you told me this is going to be good clean fun
Infowars could ever just
Be good clean fun
Purely good clean
You know what the other thing is really good
Is the spiritual end of the
Michelle
The actual end of the show
Is Rob do is in the booth
And iOS
And Alex are at the desk
Announces like
Time tomorrow
And get off at 3 when it shows other guys get out at 3
Are short day tomorrow
Takeoff
What what what is like we got a video
I know Adam Adam Alex is like
How long is it
9 minutes
The two ads at the end
Is that the one that we were talking about you
Alright video
It's traffic controller at the end of the night
No idea how they were going to end
One production
Meeting
A week
Come on day legitimately thought they were going to go all night with like
Is working behind the scenes
Digging into whatever whatever Assange is brought to the table
And instead
This is
B I mean this
Truly is
What happened
When you allow yourself to
These are the
I somehow
Pink
Like I suspect
That Rodger stone is going to escape
Lake
Rodger stone look alike
To jail
We're going to find out he has a secret
Twin like Rodger stone is the trickster God if anyone deserves to live
Live the life of Ernest Goes to prison
Truck but I'll be goddamn is not a part of
He's like
No do you want him to get hit by a car
Fly
40 feet up in the air land with stars around pets
Look at the goddamn party character on the other side of the street
Homeless man sitting there
Who looks at his brown bag in the
Mangos
Oh man like you though he's a f****** monster but fifty years
50 years
For now his life will be the greatest story ever
Is Catch Me If You Can
Is profound I can still admire that in real time
Just stop next
We could go back in time
He should have been murdered so soon and it would have been fine like so much would have been better
Easter
That's on the
Homemade
Facebook
How the f*** is
He lived this
Yeah it is
Egypt
It's out of everything
God I hate
Well we'll see we'll see if you eat last
This one
See the only event
Peppa Pig the only person like
F*** bright
Like I couldn't give a s***
I do want to have a drink with Rodger Stone like he's the only person
With Rodger Stones the next time be like
Rodger none of us were in the wreck
The night
Juno
It's this weird like
Confluent
Personability
And my
We're like Alex Jones
Not personable and a month
Rodger Stone seems fun and is a monster
Think we could have fun
Right
Never ever agree with Rodger Stone on
Any point
Like big
Right
It doesn't matter for what we're into
Interested in cuz
These things are never go
Going to happen
Hey let me give you some advice
Swear to God I think Rodger Stone would contact us and trying
Screw us over
By the time we get big enough for to be on his radar
We will have to bring a drink
Is commissary
Tell videos
Look
What's a Girl Carrie Callahan goes to a meatza
You Carrie Callahan
I don't know they get drunk
It seems like it
But I don't know if they actually do
The real thing here is that
Whether or not Rodger Stone did anything
Explicitly illegal
Alex Jones
Say he did earlier today
Now he should go
So we'll see how that were
Works out
Ben van Jordan
But
You want to find us
We are at knowledge
Also
I'm going to buy a bird by Mark
I don't know baby we'll find out
On Twitter
Whatever it is you do
I know what you write up Jordans broad over it
No don't worry about it
It's just me threatening which set a new post
I did
I took a couple of weeks off because every time
So I
Like I wrote about gun control
I don't know what
Nearly a year ago
There's just nothing
Hangouts to write
There's no point in
Continuing
To say the same thing over
Have been made
Now is the time for us
Just f****** come
Come together and ignore everybody else and
Do it
And until we can do it there's no conversation too
There's no leg
Well maybe we should raise the age now we should ban all of these bucket
That's it
Problem-solve
You can also follow us
We got a special group
Go home and tell your mother in real life
If you want to do that also
Good Times all around
The reason.
Would you like to choose someone who sucks
To give it over and
Just
As much as I hate to do this but
Go fuc
Yourself Rodger Stone
Bulshit
I would like to
That I'm going to I'm going to
Vito that
Okay
That's fair
Because Rodger Stone
Ratfucker is the only reason that this episode
I'm going to say
Go fuc yourself
Shroyer's
Fake accent
Good call
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color