Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Burgerville
Dan Dan
Dan
Meaningless talk
I couldn't keep it up all the hot load of b*******
I know a lot about the show to like what is the
I don't know how to
Fix this
No cuz I didn't finish next bit is going to be out typing a
I'm leaving about our introduction
Jordan today we I hate it when my boss comes out
How it's going to be
Portable meeting
I had a lot of those meetings in my life dear Lord
Before we get to it I would like
To give a shout out to a couple of new donors going out to
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Lovett strong name
Congratulations on becoming a Ewok
For All Seasons
Any of these could be the name of by Danzig podcast
First episode
Cortez
Second episode
Wilford Brimley
Okay what's going on
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much for
Spider iTunes is real glitchy
And that it will be a done deal you'll be about to walk
It sounds too good to be true
Have you ever tried to donate to a podcast
I don't know what's going on we'll try the clicklist
That's the best way
I've teased vest
And today we are beginning
The next invest
Navigation
Into Alex
Famously
Over the course of most of last year
We dug deep
Into what happened to get Alex Jones
To join up with
Team Trump
Came away with a pretty solid consensus that it was artificial inflation of his traffic
Vorw sandbox
Because he admitted on-air that his traffic and tripled and his sales were flat
Mysteriously no one buying anything
But times traffic
Very sufficient also the
Influences of Rodger Stone in
Text Sharon.
I was there 45
Right around the same time
Right so we've got a pretty good handle on that there's go back and listen
Hundreds of hours for today
Perhaps
Laborious Lee covered
Exhaustive coverage of the
Oh yeah you knew
Yeah
HD it's one of the most in-depth and long investigations with no one asked
And it turns out and doing another
I am interested to figure out
Himself as
Is the person who is most responsible for the tea
Tea party he believes
Some stuff to be a leader of
The party from the jump
And I wanted
Explorer the realities or lies
Lovett Varian
Also along the way because of the timeline will be covering Barack Obama's first election will be covering the
Primary where Barack Obama and Hillary Clinton we're going
The Democratic nomination
We'll see
There's going to be a lot of interesting
Stuff cuz it's a party in earnest
Came to the Forefront of the
Conscious
In the beginning of 2000
Yeah immediately after a black man was elected seriously clue
Yeah after that however
However if you actually look into
The history of it it'd been something would have been
So the roiling under the surface
To the Koch brothers
For a while before that to a lot of that and try and figure out what is what exactly along the way
And in doing so I hope we'll be able to learn more about Alex Jones
RECenter
Like exactly what is
Bulshit
What is
Actually important that likely no guns or super important
Absurd and we know that chimeras are strangely
But beyond that there's so much of these trappings
Citrusy
In this day today especially currently
Sincere just seems like he is
Trump
Right
Two 2008 just
Because
He is still relatively under the radar
It's true
Showing up
In all kind
The places that he wished
Is like
Discovering you wasn't getting sued by everybody
People he could just fly under and everyone to be like who
You would happily married to his first wife
There is also a another episode
2008 previously seemed much happier
Just singing The Highwayman for half an episode
Never woke up in the morning
Crazy
He just had Ron Paul that he's hitched his wagon
To be consistent through all the cancer
But Google
Do all of the
Nonsense along the way
I started this investigation too early
I didn't know
The primary season started in earnest
It's what I started on March 30th
So today recovering March 30th and 31st 2018
Nothing primary
Nevermind spoiler for another episode
He's not at all episode
And he said stuff like Obama is going to get killed
Cuz he's an outside
But still no like talk about the primaries no real talk about
The election at all because
Who is like this election
Twisted my mind
Chicken Mart
To take 3 years
But what was
Let's start on March 30th
See what Alex is obsessed about
Spoiler alert
He freaked out about CERN
Different job
Different particles
Aladdin
Uranium
Meconium in gold
Other
Heavy elements
At the speed of light
Into other Ella
Or the accelerator
Porgy
European Union. The biggest one
They've got a whole bunch of them here in the US
And I'm going to go back to top sinus infection
Every time I'm in
Email Music Manager
That all I know is
British
Royal Society must procedures
Vision World
There's a physicist
Wrote a book 20 years ago saying was good
Or the solar system
I was a bunch of physicists that are now suing
2 block
Others new Collider
Deftun equation show
Explosion
Is the simplest way to
Maybe even
Tomorrow
Attack Trey my producers in there yesterday
I dug up
Physicist
Ceiling fan
I sent that to you
These are not quack
If you have questions that selling also
Hotel
Puerto Rico Hotel
Yeah
And listen
You can trust these guys
They're not quack why did you say that
Alex
Because I'm used to not being on shows he must have had General stubblebine on recently and it runs I called out
I don't know about this
You kind of think
Well if they're on CNN
They're not a quack
Assuming that they're not quite
Looking at it
People have on
Are the New Yorker or the New York Times
Through their hiring
Oh s*** maybe all of these people are quack
There's a matter of good Alex doesn't do and we're starting to realize that
Other places do we have made a lot of assumptions and turns out some of these people
I'm so excited trouble
It's trouble
Pretty obsessed about this and he says that he's going
To get these physicists
Write a little bit later
Not today will be dealing with it on the next
Episode
I have some knowledge of the next couple episodes
This is a difficult place for me to be graduated from
University or what kind of
What kind of physicists are we getting
Guys actually pretty legit in terms of his credentials
But at the same time he's a guy in 1999
Colliding
Top articles against each other
Destroy the universe and then
It didn't
I'm in here in 2018
Basotho stops earn for being
Open
I don't work out
Judge says
But he's failed to prove it anyway that there is
I dunno
Potential Threat that would Merit it also
Us courts don't have jurisdiction over European scientific experiment
He's like well it's better than other cases I've taken recently
Yeah I don't know I don't know exactly the process wherein you decide what
Gets on the docket what does it
Because you
You don't have to
I mean unless you really believe it course you do
The entire world is going to be turned into a black hole
Terms of jurisdiction
The sheriff is the highest law
Speaking to someone whose name sounds like a terrorist
Alright that was a perfect
Early on Alex Jones
Has a visit from
Jim Marrs
Do you know who Jim bars is
No he's a gentleman who is notoriously
Like he's a big guy in
Conspiracy theory conspiracy
The Forefront of
The JFK
Conspiracy that mean he also taught like
Accredited college
Class on conspiracy
And I think that elevates him out of the muck
Okay alright
So he's a professor of the
Conspiracy theories that he makes
Yeah
It's important
To know that he also wrote
2buckz about 8
I don't like
The more we learn about Ancient Aliens and the more they are still from
They're at
Not
You want to have about JFK I'm all yours
You know like I'm I'm open
During arguments
About the anti-castro Cubans
CIA
I'm open to hearing any of these
Because that is a thing that happened and I'm willing to believe that there was some sort of
Conspiracy involved more fun world
Testicle world movie like world
Might not agree with you
Actually Sirhan Sirhan who did it I don't know if it's
Fine but I don't think you're crazy
If you believe in JFK can
I think we could have a cup
Jam cake
Listen to all of them there is a line
I do
I do think you're crazy
If you believe in Ancient Aliens and I want to make us on both sides
So I consider him to be someone who has ACT
But also researches
If you stay
One of the
Foremost
Conspiracy theorist
Isn't that the end of credibility
Subway
Aref
Vrsk
Well
Is actually nothing new
And many other people almost sense
Time of the robber
Loudly
Tried to shout out that he was
Not killed by
Sirhan Sirhan
Who cannot remember any
Anything that happens
Likely story
Significance
Is that after all these years and after all the
Further Evidence
Including scientific evidence
Comes out
More and more people are waking
Up and
Beginning to realize that
We're actually right all alone
The conspiracy theorist
The right all along
People are realizing conspiracy
It is sort of like
Conspiracy theorists tell you they're right
And that you need to wake up
Sirhan Sirhan and assassination of RFK
There are some interesting elements of it that I think you're not being
In terms of
Compelling circumstantial evidence
That there were other people involved
Looks like there was at least one woman who was involved
And they may or may not have been
Stalking RFK previous assassination
Is the one thing that I
Like this is the one thing where I do not need any evidence
I am just going to
You come out and say that I swear to God
I think the XVI killed
Really really do
I really do
Mainly because RFK
Perhaps
Becoming the most
Compassionate and
Progressive candidate in the history of the United
David by the way
Martin Luther King jr.
He came out and gave an awful
Look up speech that was one of the more
I mean
Credited with the fact that
The city he was in
Didn't try
Because they heard that
Right right that's how I'm going overseas and
Seeing all of this starvation
First
Made this change
And he was
Going to win
Like he was
Rushing
The other candidates
Timer
Walter Mondale or whatever free
Humphrey
Primary
Exactly
Yeah it look
This is a conversation that I'm fine having I don't think you're crazy
If you believe this
But also
GID
Also isn't crazy from the court transcript
Hamster hamster hamster trial
Sirhan Sirhan
Quote
He's asked so that there was a time the love
Turn to hate
Because he had previously to this said that he like
What time when Senator Kennedy was a candidate for the
Just answer yes it was during the time he was but not exactly specifically
What it turned into hate
Not only that hate really because I still loved
But when he came out with his support for the state of Israel
Israel
And then
Questioning resume
At that time he was a candidate for president
United States
Question
You say it wasn't until all of that that
But you hate him
Hate van Avenue cutoff
No but it was enough for me sir that anything that has to do with Israel or the support of Israel that is enough
Question
But not all of that
Answer well enough to have an impression only
Question
Enough to kill him
Answer I don't know about that sir
Question
Well did you
Didn't you just tell us here a few days ago that if you had him right there you would have
Blasted him
The answer
Bombers I would have done that
Question you would have done
Answer
Yes I'm a very impulsive person
Whatever my objective would be be it's just
Good for that time only
That's like
That's like an interrogation in the drunk tank
Yeah I mean I
Mitre
Could
I certainly would have at that point
Maybe I would have I don't I don't know if I did
I don't remember but I was there and I was shooting
I don't know all the stuff about
All the stuff
Control and stuff like that is also
Murky because
Who wrote diary
Yeah I know it was an entry that said to eliminate RFK becoming more and more of an unshakable
RFK Must Die RFK must be killed
Robert F Kennedy must be assassinated
So
Because always
Twice
You're going to kill me
Most likely
Psychiatrist
Psychologist
Gone on record and say that
Manipulative
Person and also of dual natures and fairly skits
The phrenic probably want to tell you that I don't remember
Right
If you believe a murderer who said I don't remember that murder
That's on you
Because I thought we went over on that Project Camelot episode about Mark Richards he says he was off
Planet during the murder he was involved with his word I don't know
I'm going to look at
Endurance of the evidence
And I'm going to say
The FBI did
Fine you can have that you can have that I'm not as convinced
That
And
Jamar's I have more credibility if you had written two books that answer anyways
Talking about Americans who supported
The names of prominent American Tusa
Supported Hitler is
Pretty amazing
You've got the Watson of IBM you got Henry
Ford and Ford Motor Company
You've got Chase Bank in John Jay
Chase Bank
Put conspicuous in their absence
Fred Koch
Never heard of
The Koch brothers father
Fedco Kinross
Sympathizer named William Rhodes
The Davis to help build the third largest oil refinery in the
The Third Reich
He also made a ton of money selling cracking stills
The Communists and
Somatic John Birch
Society
Mysterious in his
Absence
There's always a lot of people that they list
Fred Koch is a big one among those names
I mean
But I'm sure
He may have had an outsize impact
He may be proud
Personally responsible for at least
40% of a lot of be war crimes
He doesn't remember it
He said that he didn't know what was going on he was like
He felt like he might have done it
The time but he wasn't sure
Favorite
What's the history of Fred cope2 is that
Crystalline
He came back
He was really anti what he saw over there
Write this was not the case
What's fascism
Did not become like an anti-fascist dude
I'm still him and his son
If traffic with
For a large part of their careers
I live so that's interesting to me I don't know I don't know if it's like
National leaving them off the list
Cuz you do it those people we talked about Watson he definitely had some
Inclination
Towards
Absolutely he also was responsible for disseminating Protocols of the Elders of Zion
There is a lot of
The troubling history of US business interest
And
Morality code and you have to do all of this
And there was a whole like lifestyle that you had to live by
Just to work for him
Like he controlled every aspect of your life
Is going to be like
Yeah
I get the mentality that you're described
But I'm just talking about like why isn't this on the list
Why aren't you
This isn't the strongest
Sentiment that I have
Buddy
Curious cuz Alex does talk about these Americans
Token Network
Comes up
That I'm so that might be a little reason to be suspicious
Also turns out I don't think Hitler was that bad
Hitler
Empower and then set him up
Mainstream history mystery
Can't we just have
Can we just have
Nicer be nice
Cuz histories
You think it's predicated on facts
Not know
It'll change
Whenever the FBI
Murder.
Play that right now
We have
You know a very weird
Hitler was set up
Declaration
How do you setup
For all of
The doodoo is trying to have a
Like he was just a situation where he threw out the Holocaust
Newspaper like yeah
Is he mr. Magoo
Everyone thought it was Eva Braun now
Blonde wig on a coat rack
It's as good a time as any to go to
22 very weird commercials
Did Alex
Plays
On this episode
Is that
I don't know what to make of
And
What about Israel if you could only visit
One country One Nation on the face of this Earth since Judaism
Because then you'll never be the same
That's weird
Weird
Drillers could change the way you will ever approach the Bible
Deeper and richer way because you have been where it happened you'll never be the same when you visit Israel
That's crazy place to commercials about going to Israel
I can tell you what
I can tell you that busy
And I looked at their website israel.com
Can you scroll down
If you scroll down all the way
That the history of
Tourism of the Israeli government
Right
No this is from the Israeli government's tourism board
Ahead of the Foursquare
I don't care
Exactly what kind of force
Foursquare
You're glossing over something that I find ink
Ratably weird
Because I want to make it totally clear off the top I don't know
Anyway
Alex Jones Israel like so many of his critics claim
But it is
Proof
Indisputable proof
The Genesis Communications network was making a revenue off the Israeli government
In 2000
And that's why
Cuz I don't hear any other commercials for
Guatemala
Will soda other countries
The Israeli government was like info
Is where we're going
Great
Right
There's that
I like they must have just been
Turn on everything and not really paying attention to what they're doing
Patience
I think it's a network
This is before Alex had his own 20
Volume boosters the commercials that play R4
The documentary
Most of it is in house
Commercials for his
Documentaries
And then
Every now and again something like this
I got to be honest it's through me for a crazy loop
Yeah I don't know what to make of it
Going to go to israel.com you were never this
But I
It's almost as good as Diamond gusset
But it's crazy man it is a nut
I don't like
Again I don't
Because
Look I don't
Agree with their conclusion but one of the pieces of argument
That
His aunt Alex's anti-semitic critics make against him is absolutely true Genesis Communications
Was making money directly from the government of Israel
Right like the tourism government
For like
Go to Mexico
Caribbean cruise
Go to Wyoming
VTA buses
Wyoming
What happened
Different
If lcta bus drivers
Work anti Wyoming
Worldview was based on lies about Wyoming
And everyone everybody who criticized the Ventra said that they
Secretly worked for while
That's what would make it make
Difficult for me lick if I were Alex Jones and I were Ted Anderson
I would say thank you tourism Board of Israel we appreciate the offer but we don't want to accept this because we
We are afraid it would give the appearance
The thing
That we are in accurately criticized about all the time
It seems like bad Optics
It's for us thank you very much but we have to pass
That's what I
But again this goes back to my argument about his anti-semitic critics
In that they give him
Cover
So he can be as anti-Semitic
Does he want
And they are like you're not an anti-semite so he knows commercial to bait them exactly
If you call him
These guys are anti-Semitic
Miso I clearly am not
It's possible that it's probably like
If you want to meet
Debbie was doing it on purpose
What you probably was
There's so many layers of intention there it's
It's very confusing
I don't know I don't know what it means
I have
Zero idea
I don't think that adversity works for Israel anything like that I'm not changing my position on that
I think your position is the most sensible
Because I did least accounts for the psychology of the individual
But I don't
Well and then there's the other psychology which is
Whatever they were offering to give it to him at the time to show called
What really happened with Israel.
Michael Rivero at the time
Music
Aggressively
It's very confusing
I don't know the ins and outs
Anyway and his next clip conclusion that
Weird
List of people who I've spoken out
About 9/11
And then comes in with little bit of
But now we have just everybody all these visits
Italian president
CIA section chief
Willie Nelson
Top actors Best Actress this year
Bruce Willis I no longer being a neocon saying they killed Kennedy in the same group that did that basically did 9/11
What are they going to do
Well unfortunately they'll probably go to the tactic of desperation whisper to launch Another War artists
Set office
Nucor Sumter Biloxi
You take morphine very simile
Admitted
Superconducting super collider and other similar facilities are doing things our own equation say
Good chance of blowing the entire planet
Good chances strong
Is straw good
35%
Neither much lower
Willie Nelson is on par with scientist
Multiple gas cuz this is Silvio Berlusconi
Inside Job
Probably
Drunk he was crazy
9/11 Inside Job
Transition between Italian president
But then also just to illustrate
10 years ago Alex
It was still doing the
Exactly I'm scared
Let's get that around the election to like this last year to make before new
It seems like you got it
Do this we do this like nuker's at the bottom
Daddy just wants to
Chicken nugget
Crazy
This is probably my own Prejudice but
Anytime I hear somebody who is supposed to be in
Expert with a Southern accent I'm always going to be like
You need to get over
Really kind of invalidate a lot for
There's a lot of dumb people speak like that
Logically it doesn't track
RightNow Media perception
Two people with Southern
Playing
I've represented
Who sings there's a good chance
That also other people
Deb never graduate
I don't know what I don't know what the
I don't know where I was going with that famously smart people who speak with a Southern accent
How's it going
I know that's possible
It's not good that the only person I could come up with is Jim Ross
WWE announcer Jim Ross
So this is a Sunday affair
Interview
On the show and it is an interview with
Japanese politician
By the name of fruit
And
Threw it out with the bathwater cuz it's nonsense
But if you look into it
This guy the Japanese guy
Only isn't 2911 truth cuz he watched
Loose change
Which was produced by Alex Jones
So Alex Jones's film gave this guy questions about 9/11 and then they made
Now he's a guest on Alex Jones
It's an elevation
Cuz now you have a 4in politician
Who's your narratives backs
Do you which elevates them from your standard Rebel
A Japanese translated version
It probably be riveting
Be so good never Jimmy James's book was translated into
The Japanese Superdry
Kill kill
War
Or so
But the show there's a couple
Callers that I think are worth listening to and you're the first one
Nick spelled
Okay which is a good sign
Ahead and take another ring-a-ding
Go ahead and talk to AJ Arizona you're on the air
Good
Call tante girang inspiration absolutely I mean my brother I saw this website called look up and wake up that origin
Chemtrails
Example of what happened to me the other night
12:30
In the morning until about 20 minutes later I go outside have a cigarette
The chopper in a distance in it
In-N-Out
Can I have the chopper on the boards got to be on you
A quick flat
Let it ride around my house
It was a full moon that night drink fluoride everything's okay
Calm down Rick fluoride fluoride
Real life Samantha Hemi good
I'm looking around Chopper and then all sudden
Flying over my house by
Stop mode and I turn around them damn
Freaking light is shining down on me like that understanding well your Elser your evil
Okay
You need to be traction Friday
There's no more warrants no more free
You're bad
Okay
Submit to it it doesn't exist
No toll roads
Road
Centra isn't Spanish
Austin Chronicle
Everything's fine go to sleep shot up Samantha governor
Loveland breaker floor I take her Mercury filled injection
Love them love them
Please learn
Metronome
So ideally known to say there is
At the end
It's bad I don't think that's sarcasm I think he's phoning it in but I
It's irresponsible if someone calls you and is like
There is a helicopter following me because I write a chemtrail blogs
I'm at Target
Surveillance moment I started
Chemtrails
Now helicopters are coming over my house without their lights on exactly 121 I think is someone calls you
Dewan says that it's your responsibility as an adult
To say
This is paranoia
You bleed to look into
Living with your brother not scream at them drink fluoride submit to this
Paranoia
But paranoia so he's
Conflicting these poor people
Indulging
Bizarre paranoid
Just look the other day there was a f****** the helicopter flying over my house for like
Almost the entire day
Freddy year-and-a-half after
F****** time and you know why I'm not
Too far from the Lake Lakeshore Drive
There's traffic helicopters
Over it
There's crime
Around and sometimes there are helicopters
That are
Looking for crime
Exactly
And so it's easy to interpret those things
Police helicopter
Pilots just being like
Helicopter closely over your house
For example
It's easy to think
Oh this is suspicious
Because you don't have all the information
In the same way
I get a lot of
Calls
When I answer them no one's there
And I if I wanted to I could play the game of
People are
Stalking me over the phone
And if I were to express those things to you you would very likely say
That is an unhealthy way to look at it
Maybe being a bad friend yes, maybe it would be better for the show.
It's the same level of paranoia or the same style of paranoia which is
Taking an innocuous thing
It has an explanation
Giving it the exclamation
Do you want to have my phone number
Looking for you
Valve
It's it's
Definitely the explanation that is
I have to deal with
It's a bummer
You know what it turns out we found 100 you can't get on the Do Not Call list
Like telemarketers
Just keep calling you can request
Take me off your list they don't respect that
Take me off your bounty hunting list please also
Their job though
Sonoran for me
Alex
Get another color and this one I think is actually this one illustrates Alex Jones his lack of
Meant to the cause
Let's go ahead now and take another call
Colorado you're on the air
Hey Alex get you again today I was going to suggest what if we had something like a Woodstock 911
Big Contour we had one day where we had all these
Musicians in all these acts
Famous people
We'll come together and we
We just spent one day
Did he just say Woodstock 9/11 concert Logan 911 Woodstock
Woodstock all about 9/11
What do you what do you what's your problem
I heard that
Like that was very strange for me I let the
Clip keep going and then in my head all the sudden I was like wait
Woodstock 9/11 concert
Should we have a 9/11 in
Party no
Like a pool party
As I read all jumping we would have
You know how you have powers
We would have
Weird have two people standing on top of each other
And then we throw you at the
When I was in college and then the third plan would actually hit
The house when I was in college and I had much
Worst taste
Let's say and I had left
Decorum
I had an idea for a 911 party where I had twin bong
G.i. lighters would be dressed up at planes
I thought I would make a
Layer dip
Two different dips
There was something
Great party ideas
No
Which was a drink a 40 minutes and 11 seconds
Or else the terrorist away
That was a part of my 911 party idea that we actually
We did a couple times
Mayonnaise
Really hard do not recommend anyone do it
Usually win
Answer your question no metaphor
Really
Let the great metaphor for Impala
Sure Harris usually win
Usually because you can't drink
40 fasting
Yeah
Yeah you end up throwing up
Too much liquid to drink
11 Woodstock
Try helping the
People with art architecture
Media
That one major big event
If we could videotape sell and try to show everybody how many
People there are from the sure here's the problem you know that
It would take a lot of groups getting involved in the groups would never agree
And also no one group I'm probably only person
Actually pull it off
Could go out and get the celebrities
Celebrities don't know or don't trust
Because I don't know these other groups they have been around as long as
Yellow celebrity just call me up
The phone rings and they're on
I am at because they have been around long time
Aware of what I've been doing a long time
You built up a lot
People but I haven't really actually going out and pushed it
Because I couldn't imagine the headache of it all
Shirts
911 Woodstock
Infrastructure
First one
I agree I agree with his premise that no one would agree on
I definitely agree with that.
The only person who could pull it off as me
And I don't need that aggravation
You're not really contesting the
Claims that that would be huge for 9/11 truth movement
What you're saying I wouldn't want to put that kind of work into
Tacitly saying would be effective
Well yeah it would be huge for the 9/11 truther movement
If there was a real legitimate 911 Woodstock
I would I would watch
Well you would have
Absolutely going to happen
Covergroup of the Four Tenors
Italian president off the top of my head
Holograms music for Selene
Kid Rock
Kid Rock would play as one of the Four Tenors nude
The nuge wood death
The new just
Sarah Palin will probably show up
Danzig Mike show up
He would just throw his own probably as we
Cornwood play metal guy
Tuesday Woodstock
This brings us to the end
March 30th
Sunday March 31st
And Alex has a hole
He is no longer obsessed with CERN
Although that will come back up
Bendy very near future
Today
He's pissed off
Because the media is reporting
That there are white people who might be an Al-Qaeda
He is
He's taking he's taking that news.
Looks like
Because he feels a little bit of personal responsibility for the white race
You know what you're not far off
Let's play Let's play a couple clips
I will get into his feelings are that are very
There is no Alki
And so
And by the way here it isn't Associated Press
OKC attorney general terrorist behind copyright violations copyright violation
Terrorism
White Collar civil stop
If I were to
Perfect case of Alex Jones
Twisting a narrative
He has a story
About attorney general Michael mukasey
Who is saying things
Things about
A river
Alex
Change the story
McKay's
He saying the copyright violations are terrorism
Which is absolutely not the
If you read the story what do you think
Is that
The continuing worldwide escalation
Counterfeiting and piracy poses
Threat to Public Safety
He said that the mission of the
Department of Justice
This is clear whether it's a complex International narcotics
A corrupt public officials abusing his office or
Some scam artists
Counterfeit software
Our job is to enforce the law
And bring to Justice those who prove
Perpetrate these crime
He said quote
The counterfeiting of products like Pharmaceuticals and medical devices
Does Auto and airplane parts or electronics that go into our nation
Critical infrastructure
Can present a real and direct danger to the pub
This isn't
A speech that he gave
Add appointment
That he was trying to drive at
Is a
That
Was that
Stuffed
Inventions
Points of poses
Threat to the nation
Health and safety
Can Foster
And
That a lot of intellectual property theft is being done by
Criminal Networks
And the money that is made off of
Them
Which doesn't mean
Fitting or copyright infringe
Is Terrorism
Just that this is a source of something
Yeah I would say that's a little bit scared
There is
Conflate them far too much but he is also being a little bit irresponsible with the way that he
Combining
The two
I don't particularly enjoy that
It's kind of like
If you're going to bring in terrorism it better be terrorism
And not
Sure
Copyright
It would be nice
If we lived in that world
Unfortunately we're looking at
Just for a second
That is one of the problems with with this show in 2008
Is that whatever that guy was like
Call latara
Is it to take more power
God dammit you are correct about that
You're just f****** Raw
Yeah
You doing this on the right
Like that's what
Not doing it that way and you
You're not helping
Fight what they're doing because you're like
Well the problem isn't what they're doing the problem is
Magical thinking over here
Jordan Belfort
Also the end result of all this stuff is just rationalizing
Yeah
It doesn't charm me
You know like in terms of
What mukasey was doing
Edward Bush was up to
I agree spiritually with like being against it but it don't help
Talk to get back
Into the idea
People are joining
And this is based
On a report that came out
Al-Qaeda was trying
White people
And
That's a reasonable thing
Because
I mean most famously we had John Walker lindh
Right back
In the early 2000
Who was a white guy who
It signed up with the Taliban
Garden
You have
You haven't number of people over the years who have been White
Westerners who have joined Al-Qaeda
And in a clip that we're going to
Just a minute
We will get
The obvious rationalization
For this
Go get Alex
Take your kind of personal
Get their building this
Giant mechanism
To track everything you do Trace everything you do
Micromanager Turner national ID card off
Your pharmacist your doctor your lawyer School teachers
Neighbor
Tattletale Squad
Try to train the feds how to do this
Pause. Just for a second
Alex
Is being involved in tea
Teaching people how to do this
Write a couple years later
He would make the exact same Claim about social
There's the head of the Stasi
Is involved in face
Consult
In the same way that a lot of irons in the fire that isn't just going to focus on one
In the same way that a couple Clips back we heard him to Z like the globalist
Flag
That he does all the f****** time it turns out another one that is done
At least 10 years now has been saved the head of the Stasi is involved in some
He'll getting
On specifically enough
Almost impossible to research
Personally involved
Delegates response
Possibility but he's the one who comes up with
Project
The former head of the KGB I mean they're really doing
Going for broke
And always
Afghanistan rate Foley
Middle easterners
No I don't think
You know what they're going to do
You're trying to make up something now
We're just going to come
Improv
Right in there and burn your house down burn your farm down
And they're going to announce on the news
But they were fighting outside
Try to call about
URL
You are the chair
Take away from
Good idea
That
Recruit westerners
Particularly white people
Is that it's actually the globalist
How to make it so everybody suspect everybody
Else
We are all
Right
And specifically so they can get the Patriots
And one day Waco them
We want to use that as a verb
Exactly that making just say
They were Al-Qaeda
We already established it with a new story about how a kite is trying to recruit exactly
Business
You just made it up on the spot
What do people burn down
That's all I got
He's trying to speak to a specific community
Cuz he says you're home
Exactly
A little bit from Fox
News about
Story
Alex
Again
He thinks they're talking about
And that's very weird
Because when
Most agency officers
Obviously
That's the Holy Grail
Forever
Ben garbage the whole time
We need to listen
But Fox
Has been
Pile of s***
Consistently
Cuz you need to contact
See what Alex is freaking out about wreck
Report
But
This is just trying to extend the fear
They're trying to make the fear bigger
In general
Completely different
To go into a prison and try to recruit individuals
And then it goes on and on
Just like the FBI training manual say
White male
Boxes desk
Lot of times it says
Working management
It's weird
Keep to ourselves ourselves
Evil white males and their Al-Qaeda there every
We're ladies and gentlemen
The guy pumping your gas outside
That schoolteacher Alki
In fact the FBI manual says that preached Al-Qaeda
It's just a Caucasian woman pushing the baby carrier
Al-Qaeda
That's a quote
Everywhere there just
I'm guessing what he's talking about his FBI manuals they talk about
The ascendancy
Terrorism
So was that white
People do rats are
Yeah
Tamia
I think what he's
Trying to do there
Invalidate
Any possibility of you calling
White male domestic terrorism
Preemptively excuse
So whatever your Timothy McVeigh.
He's going to
Conflate the idea of them being terrorists
With the government calling them outside
So it's like these guys are there mentally ill
Because
If they were terrorists they would have joined Al-Qaeda
Globalist
Preparing
The ground for you to have your farm burned down and then they say that it was that they were fighting okay. And Isaac
So someone like Timothy McVeigh could blow up the Murrah building
Mexican say
They just get it.
What we're finding
I believe
Is
Free decent evidence
That the
Using
Of white terrorism
And things
Encroach upon
Alex's white identity
This is 10 years ago
Very essential piece of his world philosophy
There may be nothing more guns might even be secondary
White maleness
Yeah absolutely
Very weird
It's not that weird
McDonald's app
Eliza Schuyler
I mean I would say probably is a terrorist Force white people are historically
The there the FrontRunner I would say competent
I would say I was doing some terrorism for a long time
I'd like a report that says that Al-Qaeda is looking for people who can blame
I hear that and I don't take it personally I think
That makes sense
Tyrell Davis
Looking like
If you're a cartoon of a terrorist you're not going
Of course you would look
Alex Garza it takes a very personally as a
Memes
He is somebody who has said
In private
Because I don't know if you said it on the show but he said race-traitor
I would imagine I would imagine
If not literally yeah that idea in not so many words
I don't know if he's taking it personally so much as
More on the lines of
I'd like to me what I can hear there is him being like
They're saying that all white people aren't on the same side
His mine
There's some of that
Together for some of that
What do you call the wife
We get to
To deal with
The fact
That's recently when is episode aired
George
W bush
Threw out the first pitch
At the christening
Are the Washington Nationals
Stadium
Yeah
Apparently
That are playing the brave
And the Braves tried to get him to wear a Braves Jersey
He said he didn't want to be booed
His contention is that he was mercilessly booed anyway
Replace the audio later it's a mix
Pizza
He plays the audio of it now explains that he's getting like
Boudin
Piped-in some flaws
You can tell that it's just a mixed react
Mitch Hedberg
The sound right there's a lot there are Boos for
For sure but they're also people were clearly
Which is what you'd expected apartment baseball stadium
So that's a difference
Is him
Collapse
The 2008
So people weren't even really on on the boo the f*** out of
Gwi
Not quite yet
You talked a little bit about that
Let's really ironic
In hindsight considering
What he says about how
Trump is going to save America Trump is basically America's last
Globalist
What have you
This is very ironic
Years later
I was reading the AP headline here and it says that the Washington Brave tried to get him
From where
Hey Brave Jack and he said oh no they watching me
That's wearing a Nationals
They bowing hilarious if you are an excellent
Announcer just kisses up and just says I like the best he's gone
Got to dig up that Fox News
It's like a martial law have that clip from his second inauguration
Weather for him
I know that you love
Musica propaganda
You love America don't you
International news
Martial law
Science fiction movie
For the emperor's driving Turner 12 blue any minute
Vegas going
Now they made a lot of those in 2000
Well everytime from the 1950s
Now consider
Yes
Inauguration parade
The cavalcade going down the road
And Alex Jones screaming
The people love him
You get out complete mirror
Consider
The upcoming military parade
Of course
Look
Look at how everybody loves
Who's the president
America our glorious
It's fascinating
The past
Alex about the future
What's going to happen is because
We keep having these things happen where
Trump says he's a globalist
And Alex
Trump says I like taking the guns first and then due process later
Alex is like
Whatever any keeps saying like all turn on him
I'll turn on him harder than anybody all this stuff
I think eventually it's going to
Become clear that everyone but Alex has been right the whole time
Eventually Alex will catch up and something will happen that will be too much for her
A handle
And you'll be like
And it'll be like the child
Who thinks that they know what to do and they make a huge mess
70 adults have to be like don't help
Don't help you're making it worse
Are the kids trying to
The cleanup and making more of a mess
Alex Jones is the embodiment of that child who made the mess
Thinks they can help clean up but
We just have to be like
Shut the fuk up
Stay on your
State go over there
You're in time-out
Centigrade analysis
And he won't listen
Yeah but it only hope
I don't know
So confused
I don't know how that
I mean prison or the destitute getting sued out of a
To be fun Alex
Yeah
Who starts up a podcast
At Living evidence but it doesn't cost much
I'll be great to get some studio equipment
Speaker
Hyundai move time bedwetting right now I love you
Just just just red diaper Doper baby
Is specifically a Michael Savage catchphrase
Michael Savage leftist a red diaper Doper baby
I don't like that
I don't think that makes sense
Has to smoke a lot of weed
Red diaper Doper baby
Anyway it was a very much
Is it that the term may exist
Previous to him but
In terms of like radio personalities
Media Folk
Images that that's f****** Savage
Rat-a-tat caller called in and asked about Michael Savage and Alex is very wishy-washy on whether he's
Support them at this point
You clearly listen
He's ripping off his phrases
The show called red diaper
For babies that was
Vegenation
Yeah
I would watch it I would
A Rugrats was actually communist propaganda
The twolegs are you always
Stalin
He's actually very short
Yeah
You would be most of his mustache
Depraved
Compared to the Muppet
How do you know are babies
Alex wants to talk all about how the government stealing your blood
Brace
Where do they
I will tell you exactly where she comes from in a minute
Alex their interview is all about how government stealing your blood
This is something we covered on
Show in
Passed so I don't want to belabor it too much
But the reason is that there are
Diseases that need to
Bored
And also
You know it comes down to
Another one of these like you're not that crazy kind of arguments
About privacy
But in almost every state they take any identifiers off
Blood not like their coding all of your genomes and everything to create a
Database
Not a
Personal
Database of DNA in the
You can find friends
Correlations
Between genetic markers
4 things
Do you have the more Act
You're able to save people from
Generally speaking
There are
Success stories from
Anyway I find interesting about it is that the interview
To say the name of the organization the Twila brace works
Miss brace why don't you and the nutshell
Tell us about yourself and your credentials
How you got into this and what your organization does little get into the blood
Sure thanks so much
Our organization has been around for about 12 years
And
Beaufort
Newborn
Are they at that privacy really allows you to give
So anyway she's just hasn't boring shitt
Like I said we've gone over this
Entire narrative
Nothing that she says
When I was like maybe like all that's a new it's all the same
This is actually almost
Undoubtedly
This narrative
Interview
What organism
Well I don't know
Men overall organizational lot of privacy issues but give us
The skinny on what they're doing
To talk about the blood
Don't say the name of the organization
When it's time to like
Plugs
What happened
Because everybody knows who she is
Who she works or no
I don't know
You think I don't know why
Purposeful that they're avoiding the
I don't necessarily think that that would be paranoid of me to pick
I think Alex or something like that or something like that
Occam's razor tells me it's bad broadcasting
Play up front
Until much later in the interview
Organization that she works for is called the
Council for health care
Okay good cuz if it was the n-double-acp I would have been on
No
Is that what you work for
Is a tea partier from Minnesota
Interesting already
Minnesota goes by the name of Ted
Is the Genesis
Communications net worth
Probably probably coincidence I have nothing
The two of them
Together but
It's interesting
For healthcare should tell you was a member of the state policy Network
Remember Oregon
Innovation of the
PN
Which is received significant money from the Koch brothers
As well as from the
The Claudette are lamp
What about Coke Family Foundation
They're so
Evil in there
Everywhere
Hold on
Everyone is more to the story
The donations
Jokes of May 13th
Generally not disclosed
But in 2007 it was accidentally revealed
The David Koch gave $125,000
Pioneer
Institute for public
Food policy research
A massachusetts-based
ESPN
Further he was accidentally revealed
2010 F150 9000
834 dollars
Directly to the text
Public policy
The foundation
And an additional sixty nine thousand seven hundred eighty eight dollars and
51 Cent
From the claw door lamp Foundation
I got another family
Foundation
Extrapolating the specific amount
Yeah I don't know what I don't know how to explain that
Extrapolate
Mark of the beast
Probably it's pretty safe to assume that they funneled a ton more money
See an outlet store
Benfica
Also
ESPN
The state policy Network receive
10 million dollars between 2007/2008
From organization called
There's two organizations
The donors Trust
Any donors capital
These are water called
Donor-advised
Spawns which means that's fun create separate accounts for individual donors
And the daughters then recommend disbursements from the account
The different non-profit
It cloaks the identity of the original mystery donors
The funds have been distributed in the name
All donors trust or donors Capital fund
A Coke Family Foundation called knowledge and progress
A 4.5 million dollars to donors Trust
2007-2010
But because of the setup attempt
Possible to know where those buns
Cloak money from these two funds were funneled to at least 51s
Deanne member organization
2011 according to
Epicenter for
Integrity
Twyla
Is also
Apply the brakes
Is also a member of the Heartland Foundation
Does an organization specifically created to spread doubt about causes that would involve government regulation
Such as climate change help
Tobacco
The Heartland Institute is basically an organization that's just there to Stowe.
Heartland also has received significant donations from the coke
And their foundations
For instance the donors trust donors Capital fund
Heartland between 2000
Detroit
The lamps mentioned earlier
Contributed Elise 4.8 million dollars to Heritage
Between 1998
Why the braces writer for cnsnews
Mostly writing anti-obamacare article
This is a conservative news Research Center
One of the media research Center's main f****** is
ExxonMobil
Also the Richard and tell him DeVos Foundation
The parents of Betsy DeVos and Erik Prince Blackwater
Terry Bradley found a
Another major
Conservative
Sound
Like these weird out at dark money thing
Also
Twilight
People real early party activist
I campaigned aggressively against Obamacare
And if you don't roll them you'll never happen we can all fight this by just not doing it
Koch brothers Americans
For Prosperity spent millions of dollars fighting Obamacare
The tea party was almost a
Entirely bankrolled by the coax
Through the American
Prosperity
Foundation
What used to be the same organ
Relation that was called the citizens for a sound economy
Started by the Koch brothers in
So
All roads lead back to the coke
Monsters
This is something that we're going to experience very frequently with Alex Jones as guest back in 2008
Yeah
I don't know what like
I want to meet these guys
And I want to just find out what it is they ask
Cuz
I don't know if they believe they're just like
Sociopathic monsters that they're like
Any amount of money
To completely dismantle anything that isn't
What seems like a deregulation
Super heavily because their main business
As they were coming
Two prominent
Royal
It seems like
Wilton wings
Involves government deregulation
What I see from all of their stuff though
Is
Like
Secondarily
I think it's business
You know they just want
Any possibility of a regulator
Just sowing chaos I think it's much more Insidious than that in that
They are
Less interested in the business and more interested in just like this
Vague concept of impunity
Like I want to be able to do
Control
Whatever
I want
Whenever
Sleet
Desire for autonomy in all things
Noah
Can say I
Is there only ideology
Interesting thought and I think as we go along we'll learn more and as we go along.
More opportunities for us to get into
What what indications
But at this point we can say it's suspicious
When listing Americans who are deeply involved with a Nazi somehow Fred Coke
Is not involved in that list
And habitually isn't for Alex Jones
It's interesting that Alex Jones
And this isn't the only example
Multiple multiple times
Yeah Alex Jones has a guest on who's essentially just
Works for Coke front group
I think
So I think we're going to see a ton of that I think we're going to see a lot of these people that are
Rrr
People who are on Alex's show
Donald Trump
So that's exciting
We're never going to ever going to win
Evil this point
I don't think that there is
Strong
Parallel
Or anything like that
There's a lot of Coke
Connections
A lot of
So
The the
The most common idea behind
Is this like Darkman
They know that they're doing something
Evil
And they are hiding it because
That's how you get away with doing evil
Bulshit
This idea of like
Because I'm anonymous
I can do whatever I
Because I will hide behind different organizations
Doing whatever the f*** it is I want these people are
Are carrying it out for me
I agree with
I agree with you the bed does
To be the modus operandi
But I want to be cleared
Because we're going to
Pretty speculative
I don't in the same way that I don't think of that
Commercial
About Israeli tourism proves The Alex Jones works for Israel
Right
The fact that Alex
You know on
On some coke tip
I don't think that mr. Lee means
He works for them
Wright's just weird
Again that's not even
Comparison between
I'm just saying this.
Improve anything
It's just
It got my ears up
Anyway it was nice quote we learn that Twilight
Probably belongs
Hope program
Not just
Parents
It's about cost
Prevention
And I think
You know it's good for your lips
To let that roll around
Their brain
A little bit
Because
And prevent
Likely
Queen means
That we don't want
Perfect
And we worry about the
Today where is it
Child
Fist into Define
Imperfection
And it will be
Part of whether or not you
Married
Whether or not you should have
Children
So Gattaca
Well I better just described
Absurdity of that play
Look at it another way
Is
They cost
Prevention
Is indicative of
Freebirth
Or very early
We're able to treat it
There are serapis that we can use
But if we don't
You will have a handicapped person
For the rest of their life will require
Expensive medical bills
Or like with
50 homeless population
And if they have
Homes they're far more likely to
To wind up
Banner Hospital
Bringing up
S*** tons of bills that you eventually wind up how
There are ways to measures are more effective
Always
Costco
Action or something like that
In a really
And there's a way to look at it
In the ways that people mean
Brett and they're not the same
So anyway it just seems to me like
Cheese
She perfect
Just good fit
The show
But also
Boring
Alex Jones in 2008
Pretty boring
I'm not enjoying wasn't she doesn't scream that much
Nonchalantly
Taking most of the calls
Yeah so far
Alex Jones
A subsection
Compressor
Paragraph babe
Yes
I can tell that I have missed something and all my research
Sure have
Paragraphs
Again
We discuss this over and over again
That's the subsection that he uses to justify his belief in chemtrails
Paragraphs
Which is right after paragraph be that he cites
I said that informed consent
Is required for all of those
And
Blood stopped
Location for
Chemtrails
Nothing
Is just talkingshit because he memorized something that he can
I'm confused people
It's very much
The
Between the two leg like
I see you big things
Two buckets
Of how much water you're putting into each
Each one is how much more important
You think one is the
The paragraph bead has all of the water in it
Requires informed
Consent
To him
That's just like
Do they have to
To put that in
And then they'll manufacture your inform
Consent later on
Like that's always his idea is
So if you have any kind of if you have any kind of thing
And then you have a regulation on it
The regulation is a lie
Even if it's like just as regulations
Don oil company
Climate
Changing all that
Are manufactured
To destroy
The very thing that they're supposed to
So is the regulation on V evil ship
That they say
Really something that there for them to destroy whatever it is
Any qualifying Clause is too complicated for a
Ignore it
It's probably there
Exactly
Earlier we heard that I was Jose advertising for tourism to Israel
What else is the advertiser
Mail.com
Is your choice for everything spy related
Tell cameras cleverly.
Disguises items
Commonly found around the home
Nest cameras
Recorders powerful
Security systems
Interesting interesting for someone who's very concerned about the surveillance
Commercial unlike
This is off and on brand simultaneously
Commercial Door
Listen to this
Yeah
And then before I forget I keep forgetting to do this
There is going to be the biggest announcement this radio show has ever made
The biggest announcement in the history of this
Particular manifestation of my radio show
It's been here for
9th so 10 years the syndicated show
Osho
Coming up next
Monday
You people
You will see a huge announce when you're very very
Important announcement
Next Monday
This is the Julian Assange of interviews right now
Jesus
The government did 9/11
Yes he is announced that the government would do 9/11
He has announced proven both of those New Year's Eve
Leave 2000
That the missiles were being launched
Cortez concentration camp at the Austin Airport
F*** is this announcement in the history of speculate
That's a big one
Yeah
Did Pearl Harbor
They
Never dropped
Atomic bombs on
Nagasaki
Yeah no false flag themselves
I knew it
Actually was just a bro
And I you know what
There's a famine
No big deal
What else we got what else we got virgin
Oh boy history of info
Yep
Is overcompensating
So I was like there's no f****** way we can do this episode and I can allow that teaser Togo's on
Marshall Eye Care
So I skipped the week into the future
To find out what the rest of this I got to hear this s***
So the big announcement
Yes is that Alex is at in the fourth hour
So
We've heard the reintroduction of it in 2015
Announce before our place but we'll get to that once we get to April 7th
Cuz I'm coming up in the future but spoiler alert he's bringing back the 4th hour
With authority
So that's great
The mic down moment
Because we get another
Endearing
Alex Jones Loves Country Music Moment
Asian gentleman
What are the cutoff Junior edit
Buckwheat
Also right there
That's where Alex Jones gets his
Talks about what it means to be country
A black hole Chain Reaction the superconducting super Collider
You can't
Throwing that in
Old old stereotype of country boy
Always survive black
Neither can they friend in New York City
Call Junior
I'd like to spend some Beechnut in that
And shooting with
Bowl 45
Artisan of torture
For sure the audience
Rather just have fun and play music are on the show
You have your hard rock music with your country in your classical
All mixed in with your 60 you could stay
Okay
Gary Hart
F******
That's it baby that's a hundred percent
Even says what we keep saying
Play music
Music here play some jams
I would
I think the world would be better if you would have just gotten on a different format creation
Unlike the old country hits
And on the side
45 minutes of non-stop hits
With some stuffing and then his in his is like intercutting just like
From Waylon Jennings
The government did 9/11
Next up got some wonderful
I think eyes are going to love this
Government
You're not going to get 45 minutes
A great
Radio format would be him listening to music and screaming over it
Getting real Intuit
And I would really enjoy that I maybe I
Throwed
Revolutionize DJ
Quite frankly like a time when you needed
Coming to Providence
He's right when Clear Channel was taking over all these like to install a dating
You're saying is that Alex Jones
Could have been the next
Kool herc
He's never going to play Urban Music
He could have been a weakened Revolution idj like he could have done
Whitby
Like obviously
We can't take away from him his creativity
The b******* that he spends
If you could direct that creativity towards
A more benign format
You could get
Fascinator
Anti-semite
Private
He doesn't really have a rematch of course we have no idea
All the game show host
Who is the Senate Square
Whoopi Goldberg
Translator app
What's his name
Richard Oliver
He wasn't ever in the center Square on the match game now
God dammit I sure wasn't Charles Nelson Reilly know it wasn't
Charles Nelson
It's going to kill me
I'm going to look it up how to better life
In front of them any bluish
He had a beautiful
Beautiful
Possibility
On this episode
But this next clip is really interesting considering that Alex
In present-day has said that he had sex with
200 women by the time he was sixteen or so
Hear this clip in context
With that
Women in lasting a
A diamond like a
Unhappily wishing I could have them all
You know that feeling that
Anxiousness
Comanches Gorge
Gorgeous man I just
Want her
Now
I've developed to the point where I don't even
Women I mean I do but but
A smaller part of my psyche
I just admire their beef
By sharing it
And it's not even sexually not explain its LOL
Much fun
It's so great build appreciate Beauty all around you
I said I'd get into
Things on planet but I didn't get into this news first here
What the f***
I appreciate women on a different level than any of you can ever understand
Of course
Women's Beauty
I don't
Experience at
I think what he's trying to say is I have
Nobody's trying to say
I think
That was him putting up the bat signal for someone to
To create superbells Italian
I mean I think I think
It's just not as interested maybe there's not enough variety
Difficult
Now we could be cool
I think that there is a I think there's a way that a smart person
Could express similar things to what he say
All-encompassing lost
For women in Israel
Set alarm to an understanding of people's Humanity
A little bit more than you had when puberty was going on alright
I think there's
Possibly
Something in there
This is
Completely contradictory to his story of
Having sex
I mean that was before he could share in their Butte
Ofl
No just tell him to work
If that wasn't what he saying worth
No
Siri
Keller writes in their diary
Before they strangle and rape women
He's a f****** that's an insane person
I don't I don't think it's as crazy
Not like the actual content of it
Think is that crazy able to appreciate women
Beauty in a non lost
Away
Is I think what he's trying to
Express
Again I'm gay
I'm reading contacts
Blues and I think that's what he's trying to say
Look look
Nobody
Nobody on this planet right now I feel
Is more in tune with the way Alex's brain works
Probably so I'm going to lean on you for the
Alex Alex
Still getting accustomed to it right still have to get my sea legs as it were about this crazy thing.
Cuz what I hear is there somebody
No no
By the way this is a great and save the person I was thinking of was Paul Lynde
Call Linda
Shadoe Stevens
Matter
I posted
Interested in the fact
Exactly
Is funny
In conflict
With Alex
His claims of
First of all right having sex
250 women Battlefield
Because
Because he wouldn't Express things that way if it was also like
You be like
When I was 18 I felt this
This
This unrequited lust
Towards women
Could be with them but I could
Well that's good
Had already been
No
It's not fair
Is this f****** make sense
I'm confused
I don't know what he's trying to
That is though
But like behavior in that
Insofar as
It is always a manipulation of his past
Is to support his present narrative
Right so
Whenever he wants
To be like
I'm the manly man you can respect me cuz I
Then he's like I already had sex with everybody everybody that you've ever wanted to have sex with
Don't bother I got it
Already
But when the narrative is
You know I am
I actually don't even know why he's
You saying that
There's no reason for that right there's no prior context but psycho
Was f****** going on the intro to that what came right before it was his talking
He was talking about like
Having money isn't bad
But having money be all you
You care about
Is bad
Towards the Lost
For women
Right but it's
Still doesn't
It doesn't like
Me telling you that
Doesn't give this property
Recently
It's between that talking about money and him getting into the
Long pause where he's clearly
But yes I don't know man again
Feel of like
All the sudden
All of his previous
Lies and
And bulshit just like
Catch up to him for a moment and he's just this Berry
Open an honest person
Telling
Way more than he wants you
Interesting people in the world to talk to
Because I think he has a
Perspective that no one can
Can possibly imagine
Write like the idea of lying for 20 years
But even if he actually believes that the global is
Exist
He has to know that he's lying about a lot of
Of other stuff
In order to reinforce that narrative
Himself
And has the cognitive dissonance
What's involved to be like
Well I'm lying about this tiny detail but it's only because it reinforces the
The bigger thing that I believe is true
Anything in service to the larger
To solve the larger problem
Isaac wants it all collapse
Pinky probably live
Incredibly it
In perspective
That I will go to
Prison
And interview him
For my forthcoming novel
Try try and make
Peace with my
Evil twin
In this next
Clip
What's Jones
But you said earlier this is before
Entirely collapse
Like full-on financial crisis
They come to the end of 2008
You thought
You are excited for Avengers 3
The sequel to the 2008 financial crash
Is going to be
Huge hearing Alex made over a billion dollars
We're going to lose over 2 trillion
Incredible Alex is rhetoric as that
Because it's going to coincide with the rise of a child's face
Obama's fault he's running for
Here in this last clip
Talking
Sing about
And they're getting
Total nazi-like power over all the other banking
And lending
And brother chocolate Usha
Weatherall
And then I'll offer the next solution as
Kind of like one of those traps
The more you struggle the tire gets
And they're just always there
When I'm your friend never mind my hands around your neck there you go
There you go
I love you so much
Ma
Just helping your net just wiped
Bring some standoff
Don't you mind that
Yes
So that
Not
Like this Alex I feel like I could go out and have a conversation with
Yep because that like with the cobra
They have the center for Freedom progress
Witches Library
Games for progress
We're helping you
There's a there's a point there that
If I could just like twists
Globalist
They are General you're right
What
You're just wrong about how and who and why they're entrenched
To listen to you
Because no no no
Is an example of the Broken Clock being right twice a day
We know because of history that the financial crash
Is coming
Right now it's
Doing what he does all the time because he works
Oregairu
Who sells gold
Which is warning people and saying everything is going to f****** collapse
It's not like this is the only time he said it and he's f****** right that this is what's coming
Just 88
Just what he does all day
Time it just so happens
Bit after this
It did happen
And if you're playing me like everything is going to crash eventually
You just say it over and over and over again it's coming
That's what's so weird about now
Are you saying that everything is going to turn around and
And a crash
He's saying it's going to crash but it's going to because of the globalist
It is not because
About the bank
Ready
But because it
It's a good demonstration
Even ten years ago Alex
Still really
He's still really gross
He is
Deep into those weird fantasies where he's
Playing it out
You
I bet you can even know this
But even back in about
Like its current version of it is
More animated and exterior this is just sort of like
He's not even committing
Like
Details of how they're taking you through the back
They have a gurney down there they got your why wouldn't they have
Keep Gurney's in their basements
Gurnee they're going to have your kid blood
Cuz they're going to make it
Get high on your children's blood
You have even more adrenochrome
So I mean look we've come to the end of the first episode of the 2008 investigation
And we've learned a lot
I'll be perfectly honest with you like I have mentioned this along the way a little
I think it Bears repeating
2000's more boring
Then current day
Mostly because he wasn't
Icons
Italy in a state of being press
Against the wall and a caged animal
Like it has the back to the wall
He is f******
Screaming about anything and everything
Easier Road a hoe
He has theirs got money coming in from the Israeli tourists important
People are donating cuz of his dumb documentaries that we had early to punch me out and he has a comfortable
Existence like I said he's still married to
The Kelly at this point
Infowars is a small operation with only a few employees
Have a ton of overhead but it's an independent
He doesn't have to worry about about
There's that there's so much going on about his life
Listen to Country Boy
And have a great time with it and then get into whatever he wants
Whatever narratives he wants to spend
And he's he's
He's living it
You know you do hear some of that like
I'm sure he
He feels like he's getting
Complacent he's not
Fulfilling his ambition
In the same way
He feels the way that he takes those calls are just like
Yeah sure there's a f****** helicopter are you
He's dismissive his f****** colors all the time
But
The only thing that's important about that talking caller is not his
Naive
Dismissal
That he is irresponsible invite
Not helping them
Bedford
What's going on with that
Friends
So I think
In time the singles group
Right you need to meet up
OkCupid
Harmony was around
Kim Trail blogger wouldn't you bring up the subsection with him
That's good question
I know I think I think in time we're going to discover things that are
Much more
Concrete at this point we have
The beginning
Indication
I don't know why
I don't know what
Here's the here's the thing
Whitney 2015 invest
Navigation we had a concrete thing in my
And that was
What about
Trump
Announces Canada
Install what happens from there
Here this is so much more open-ended
Because
The Tea Party doesn't quite exist yet
The primaries aren't hot yet
We're laying a lot of con
We're getting indication
The case I think
This invest
Applications going to be
We don't I don't know what we're going to find
I don't know where we're going to enjoy it a lot of people who might not be the target
Play quick with Alex
Back in this time what I'm hearing is working to get all of these kind of different Waypoint starting
To generate
Yeah and
And so what we're going to find what we've already
Clearly comes from Twila brace who works
For a Coke funded
Put that's what I'm saying
That's what we're going to find here is all of these
Sources
And how it is that they are affecting
His worldview now
Yeah that's what I'm interested in this investigation is like
How is it that this guy who is
Hey
Just
Like
Again
Right in the wrong way
Sprite how did this guy turn into the weird
Monster
That
Is just an unhinged
Azure as you said rabid Wolverine
Where did this come from from
Stinking f****** The Highwaymen
And the country boy exactly
Radio
It's weird I think I think those are the two things that we're going to find my intention starting list
Is figuring out stuff about the
Tea Party
I am the rise of the Tea Party through the lines of Alex and I think ultimately
Probably
The Accidental thing that we're going to find is the beginnings of all of
That's probably much more value
So this is probably the worst time of my life
But everybody else is going to have a good time trying to make the best out of it and make a show out of it yet. Thank you all so much for
For supporting us
Knowledge 5.com
Just renewed foreign
We got it
That's another year that
Very confident of you
Cheaper that way
Can find our podcast on
Basically those two places
I mean I think the obvious
As far as the
The evil
That we're going to deal with
Keep popping up a
So we might as well get it out now
Go f*** yourself the Koch brothers
Fred
Oh yeah he can go f*** himself to a man
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work