Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
Indeed
Who is Riza
You're supposed to say he is risen indeed
That's alright
Jim Toth
Recovering
Where is the Easter sale still going on
After 7 Days in Colorado allegedly
He has returned
Or not listen
Owen Shroyer
Excited but not quite as exciting
As I are new donor
Ladies and gentlemen
Oh God I forgot I have a
You so much
Thank you for doing the show
Like this I know it's Nathan's
Billion crumbs
Mantle
Wow wow
Wow
Everything is bad
Anyway
Alex Jones is back from vacation
Call last year from Chobani yogurt
I went on vacation immediately right after that
Very very strange
I want it I forgot I was going to Heidi and Spencer goes to different
Showing up wherever hadiya.
Spencer go on vacation
Colorado permit
Bear with blood coming out of its jaws of the back
Everything is possible
At later than episode does indicate that he's stalking people now so
I'm fine with you.
So Alex is back
Like I said
Very excited about it
We're going to go over this episode
Is a novel context from March 12th
That's correct
Trivia
Is an out-of-context drop of Alex from Today Show
Today
What
I've barely plug today or any other day
Barely
Spiritually alive
Right up top
Alex
Clearly shows
Episode
You cannot have a fill-in host
Like he comes in
Like he has something to prove he comes in like
He's trying to
Apologize
He's screaming about Satan
A lot of the episode
By talking about a recent rally the Trump
IPad
And here is his take on
Clip here on the president at that rally because it just gets
Better and better.
No
As the crowd
Channing
CNN sucks
Then we've got
I'm calling Chuck
Great
So Alex
Not realize
How
President
Rally's
Where in
People chance CNN suck
It's to understand
Screwed
Which we have gone if it's sort of aggressive
Crowd version of
Impressed
You know it's very uncomfortable
Especially since I cut out the parts
Of the
Tuxedo touch
I meant the other plays is Trump
Yeah conveniently Alex leaves up
Apart from
Trump's rally
The only way to solve
When you catch
A drug dealer
Put him away for a long
When I was in China
The president do you have
No no no
Ice rape
1.4 billion
Not much of a drug problem
I f******
I said what are you tripping
Neighbors
If you're a drug dealer
Are you know you're going to get caught
And you know
Did you really kill people
Chilling or family
Chewing our workers
Okay
Again
To be clear about this I've said this before I have studiously avoided
Hearing his voice ever
Sometimes it's important
Know what's important is that if you voted for that you should have lost your right to vote and you should
There's no
There's no defensible reason for that being
Representative
The human race no no no truly beranak and stupid monster
The f****** human
The concept of the death penalty even for murder
Balloon for trying to make a
Selling smoke
You f******
They're the ones ruining our children not the children themselves who might want to f****** get Iowa
Get high all the time
Or order
Babers
Also
Also the bigger issue is drug companies real
Or smart
Reasonable at all in the sense of
Aura idea
But if I really want to talk about is like Alex doesn't
Like you doesn't play this part of the valley and of course he
Or like it being a good idea to have the death penalty
Really long sentences for drug dealers
Alex's principles are
He's a Libertarian allegedly and that drugs should be legal
So what you're going to f******
Put someone to death because
They're selling something that should be legal
Alex's
Hey you know the guy that president
Doterra from the Philippines famously keeping the government out of people's butt
That was a big thing that Doterra was all about you
Sure he was personally going out in murdering people probably is
Human rights violation
Yeah he is there are charges that are being event
Skater Buffet
He thinks he is the thing is is in the past that had duterte's doing the
Good job
If you take all the context clues from all of his the only thing you can take away
Is there a
Trump think that's a good idea
The other thing you saying
Goodnight goodnight
From the rally is I went over to China and I talked about how do you not have a drug problem
We are a ruthless state
Imprison people all times and kills them for doing drugs
Can't be on board with the time
You can't
Ckn
No one
Stay the night
One reason that you're racist pieces
You're fine with all kinds of
Goddamn
Authoritarianism because you never really had any beliefs other than
Beer and nonsense
End it
Banana
Totally bananas
He quit
Kula is he still president
Rid of him after that didn't everybody collectively go
It's supposed to
This is what supposed to
We're through the Looking Glass Jordan
Mom
Couple questions
The first one
Betty Rae's
If you're ever in the Kansas City Missouri area go check it out there's some the best ice cream
As we say in Missouri
Get cool
Jordan
That's how we get cool in like a physical injury sentence
I told you earlier
Has been on vacation
You know that
Yes
I think he was talking to lawyers
He was hanging out with his family and haven't
Good Times
Because in reality what is what you would do before you go to jail you won't spend as much time as possible
But I already secondary
The fact that he had a breakthrough
While he was over there
In Colorado allegedly
Beyond
The last week
And
It is shook me to my very core
Professional
More serious sleeping by moron the audience
That I am going to
Give it all I've got
Sometimes
Don't jump don't have that
By the tiger Focus that I should
Experiencing
The truth
Growing in this country that we cannot let win
I think he's talking about us
Talking about himself
Elizabeth
Countermeasures
Covert action now
Covert operations
We got to get it to spy it
It's really weird if this is a thread that's going to continue throughout this episode that Alex is like
We got a spy
Alright
That's
Me that he's very worried about something
Fat guys
What I would like
Follow Ashley Bickford around because she has got me over hot coals
I am
Possible
I don't know tonight
I wanted also say that that guy who invented Pepe
A frog
Yes I'm and everybody's like
Jumping up on
I'm just being a big deal
Guy protect
What is intellectual property
Other people like Mike cernovich
Cernovich used it on the cover of his book
And I think that the argument of fair use
Does
Apply in this setting
I just want to be on the side of I don't think that's okay
Compelling
Things that I don't think that's stealing
The same time if he were a corporation
If he were Disney
He was calling intellectual property rights
Yeah you would have won that lawsuit
25 seconds
I don't f*** with Mickey Mouse
About Mickey Mouse
Keeps
They keep extending the date at Beyond which something
Becomes
Public
What is it
Public domain
Specifically based on the date at which Mickey Mouse would become public
Interesting that's a real thing
That's very weird look up
I just want to be on record as saying like I think that Ashley Beckford and Rob Jake
Gibson's lawsuit
Deserve
Much more attention
Pepe lawsuit is frivolous
Useful words
I could see a decent lawyer very easily make the argument that
It becomes Fair
Interpretation
Is that this guy created a
You know really
Manifest
The frog that turned into a Nazi symbol like that's a bummer
That is a bummer but I don't know if there is
Like it summer
Randomly grabbed a clip of ours and was it was like hey guess what if you guys love Nazis this clip is the one for you
Don't give people ideas
Okay fair enough infiltrator
I don't actually think that they are spying on us but it is interesting
Paranoia
Publicly saying
We got to start spotting up folks
So in the next recruiting white people
Prefer alkayida
Exactly
Next clip
It's about
Things that are breaking away
Globalism
As he always talks about
Marine Le Pen
You've been corrected on that okay not running president right now
And every other Nation on Earth is beginning its away
Consciousness
Racial
Punctual
On the face of this
Planet orbiting the Sun
You can feel
The Boyd
Tenderheart my friends the moment
Realize
This is important
Use free will to begin even understand
You will feel
Once your contentious understand that
The word is that
With our five senses
Tasty
We have Morrison
Alex forgot the other two
What about Michelle
Alex
Spelling sergeant
Intergalactic
Beautiful wind chime
Yep
Great
Only our that's all we are the three vovi
Yeah
That
No man that is enough
Hot nonsense
It's really funny coffee
Intergalactic space
I don't know is that a thing
Anyway
It's a little bit esoteric up in this bih
But now we got to go back down to earth
From there the space twins
Sirius through the
Replace us back onto the Earth cuz Alex has got to try and get them
We got to go back to
Alright
Let me try to get another nose here because
I get all wound up
You do when I get all dialed in to the news and then I just got to run down the rabbit Trail without getting into the big issues
That
Surrounded
Coming out today
You want to guess what the big news is
Is this is this like today news
Yeah sort of over the weekend over the weekend
Let's see
Nope
The ongoing crisis in Puerto Rico
Doesn't
Touch it what does
Worried about it
Nope
You're never going to guess what the big news
Let's see what happens
Tommy Robinson
Is a patriot
He understands all around him a globalist
Communist
Islamic enforced
Sure
Come here a little bit is the big news wow
I mean it's not news if you listen to Infowars
In the real world
But we're going to talk a lot about Tommy Robinson
Is talking big about Tommy
Is because over the weekend Tommy Robinson without agitating it seem like it's a Muslim
Related events people found him McDonald's of beat the s*** out of
And apparently he fought back in like the guy apparently the
Musically in German
People who beat
But everyone was laughing because there's
Is a gif of him
You're getting clock
We always love to see that love it
It took always punch Nazis
About
This for like
Animated
More than that
Our interview with Tommy Robinson
About all of this
Inspection last night
All of this is
Is them trying to retain his masculinity after he got beat up internet
Roboto
Give me all the time too
To give some sort of it cuz I don't know who Tommy Robinson is
He's a really really aggressive Muslim agitator
Either white nationalist
Almost
A lot of fun
Once we get to his interview
But for now just know
Seasoning for work desk
And he hates Muslims
Every time
Alex Jones goes on vacation
Something happens
He's got to tell the story about it
When he gets back is somebody going to be in a hot tub
There's no hot tub story
Does not pass the smell test
Airplane
Call if you lost your family and there was all for my children
From Colorado
That you are
We have a discussion
That works
Vista
Accurate at all
Personae
Videotapes Alex
You should be banned if he's aware handy haha you lost your family and you lost your family is next
And then
Separate
I think so yeah okay guy
Threatened
To beat up his child
Start f****** with him at the baggage claim and then later
Tell Rex
Time to go
Got to f****** throw down
Doesn't sound right to me until the longer version of the story later and their Clan am assuming we will
Hear it
Too long and
The way you
He tells it is so scattershot you sell all over the place yet
6 Minute clipper
You get all of the broad Strokes
Hear the rest of it is like
Normal
Zippy game
Hello
Exactly
Just the idea that someone to be like on the beat up
Is it's f***** up
15-year old boy there's no way
Alex is using it as a way to make an argument that like
UCI
I don't care that you're gay
I am gay people coming up to me all the time and they're so mad that I have a family
I just farted
Not because of their game
Against me Bible family
That's just always
See how the story is going to
Play out and evolves over the next week or so and see if we get some more globalists involved that maybe
It's like he is
The worst
Short story writer
Like what he is not
What are you guys not at work
He's like sitting around like JD Salinger with his little typewriter
To make it about
Three
Threaten to beat up my son
Should be the lead
Of course not
Even in his
Steven is made of b*******
She's the headliner man
He know what happens to Alex
And then of course is like while they threatened to beat up my kid to
He said that
Let's move on
Go back to a very bizarre add pivots
I'm telling you I had
Because it's not
This isn't a normal activity
Is very weird one
Smells of death
Easter sale
Superman vitality
Absolutely not turn you gay
This is a two-part
Second part
So now that he is on his own
We are
Going to be working with mister
Robinson and trying to build studio trying to get him a larger team of people
Just real quick he used to work for Rebel media but I've
I think because he kept going and f****** people f****** with people in public
Yeah
Someone's going to actually be
Beat you up for real
For sending you on assignment or something like that we are bad people
Alright
Temperature
And yes
They do plan on killing
Fresno on a passion he's reaching out to all the minority groups
Yep and
And so he needs security
That's one reason we need to
Capital here
Get us more money cuz Tommy Robinson's going to die and we need to hire him isn't it
Recipe
It's pretty aggressive you don't give us more money
Tommy Robinson will not be able to afford a
Security
And then he will die
These bees you don't give me money
That's another minute of Life Tommy Robinson
These basically holding Tommy Robinson Hostage philosophically to his listeners which is
Bananas
I love that also
Instead of Dodge having those like
Country music songs in their in their advertisement
They just had like
Dave
From it
With a gun to his head
Look
Buy a car
Or don't or orive it like make it more realistic you could have like Dave be there in be like
By car
Job
At least not be as police locked up
You're killing the Auto industry
Unless you buy a Dodge Ram
Is the kind of guy who's made his bed
And now he's got to lay in it
Involved
I'm not saying they're right
To kill people
I am not
He were to not be here anymore no no no no no no no
I'm not terrible
Because I think that there's better ways to deal with stuff like that
But
That's where I'm at get in Tire late and he brought it on himself
I heard that he sold drugs
So that means
He has been arrested for drugs
The president will get to that later anyway
Second part of the ad pivot which is
A little
Satyr it's a little sadder and also
Much like the Colorado airport story I don't
Now I'm just going to say this here on here
What's capital this year and last year
Sudden death overtime
Play the Showman
Optimum energy
Shop
We got specials
Operation
Boston
80%
We're losing money on stuff 80% off
Special today because it's gets its not making it up
He's a f****** used car dealer
My prices I hope aren't too low oldest Rick and Morty
So first of all
Match to even it within that send
At the end
We're losing money
Cuz everyone
Did the elections are over and we won
Well that's cuz we're selling too much product glass product
Insults
You told too much product you make too little money
The underlying assumption is different in the beginning
The end of the
I don't know what reality is
I would need money
Alex
Money
Give Alex his listeners don't particularly care if they sort through like
I'm sorry this next clip Alex has some
We're in
Overtime
Woodward Sports NFL
You have to get the match whatever points were scored by the other team right
Hockey
That I mean
College ball
College sports have sudden death overtime
Alternating
I didn't think about that.
Claude Van Damme
That's the one next clip Alex has the
About his own
Being up for sport
No no
Dealing with
He's talking about the wall
The crap he's been dealing with his lawsuit
Occupy
Cuz I know none of this is work
This is such a big deal
Sure
Stupid
He's almost always
Or
People have just decided
Tentative
You know like
Balita
Assassinate
I don't know cuz I mean like it was there he was like before
Or before Martin Luther King was killed
Well Martin Luther King possibly but RFK not
Public
I don't know I don't I don't
Vape
I don't
I don't know
From history are examples of what
Just talked about
Remember when Gandhi was a loser
Vicious disinformation Corey in about an hour
Yeah snake oil
Oh yeah
Who else who else Lincoln
I think that was just recognizing was probably going to
And he's like
To be very broke for a good long while
That like once that happens
I can
Play the victim
On the other side
I think that's
I think that's the game veggies playing
Oh yeah
Is it possible
It would make more money
In prison
Then he would
Donating
I'm going to protect
You know that
Mark Richards
Kind of profile in prison
Maybe becoming a complete weirdo
Or just the fact
And IV started to make a profit
Because he was I would say it's unlikely that you would make
More money in prison
Navigate maker
Because any could sort of take that time in prison to regroup it would clear him from his obligation
Trump
A lot of those other things
He claimed he was a political prisoner
The book next
Sissies in not being Hitler who I totally want to be Halloween
For real
Hitler and parentheses in a little bit
Hold on before we
Podcast illustrates the dangers of immediately agreed with something but in this next
Click Alex's complaining about Marina Abramovic
The artist
She is in the f****** news cycle
It for everyone who's forgotten
She was the artist who was order wrapped up in all of the
Repeat the gate nonsense because she has some art
About
Spirit cooking event
Yeah they would have liked
Cheese that was supposed to be people's fatty tissues
Cranberry juice that was blood
And what a view
Pretend that they were eating human
My body's
Cooking being used as a negative because
To me like you say Spirit cooking and immediately I'm like
Alex was complaining about her and then he says this
About how she knows about her ritual
We know all about it
I know about it sweetheart
Every
Call history art
I've been down the rathole lady
Further down than
What
I think it means
Well I'm because they already know they are spiritually dead
Smell
What's that smell
The sound of death
The smell of death
Is he
Unbelievable
I agree it's unbelievable
But I kept that last part in there is specifically to draw a line between the singing country jams 10 years
Country dance now
So anyway Alex apparently has done some Satanic ritual spirit
Physically I don't know what that means
Spiritually dive down the rat
I legitimately
I think that's what you guys
Alex
You f******
Gross
Stuff
He's talking
Sing about children being assaulted
John dumelo
Globalist
Loved it
Judy things
Stockade
Right out the gate daily pilot podcast project is back
Head start on
So good
It is next clip
I've cut out the stuff where you talk
All that gross s***
Screams
Hillary
The reason I don't like him is because
He talked about
Is weird
Betty was just
Just talkin about
And I don't like him
Right
AR
I will never falter
You are bone
Cincinnati weather
Because we can't end not
Principalities
Places of power of the air
Asphalt
Principalities municipalities you name it
We're against it
Against territories
Little stupid
Psychological
You know we break the Goldwater rule but it doesn't matter cuz we're not
This guy's very obvious
I'm about to give up
I really am tired of this
I think there's something to that how long he has been doing this because
Anytime I've ever had a job every 2 months
Do I really need this s***
Any little thing happens and I'm like
Just quit like if I had his job
I'm just really tired of jobs
Set up
Pretty quickly but
I still love this
I'm like
Right
Today was that was like
Really delightful
In terms of doing that's good like
Alex is back
It's a breath of fresh air up from these stuffy Dixie's been having a blast hose
Yeah but nobody suing us into Oblivion
No. But negative
See there is
Like
It was easy for him to do the show cuz he's doing very different show
10 years ago 20 years ago
Yeah it was much easier for him back then
Because you wasn't
Operating on 5th
Level exactly this level you can't keep up
It'll be over it'll be long over
You got your
Frankly
You should have probably quit immediately after Trump got elected you should have done the whole like Michael Jordan I'm retiring at the
The top of my game
Start your start you wouldn't you're okay
Here's here's the dream on the election or something like that
Take complete credit for winning the election
Tires right on the top of his game
Leave it all behind
3 monthly almost immediately
But he starts his own podcast or some dumb s*** like that
Bill O'Reilly but without being forced out
His route
And play the country music and laugh over it and scream you can still talk about chimeras and what have you
Then
Don't go south
Because he's going
Then what becomes our retirement
Retirement
Michael Jordan exactly
Billions
But that would have been what would have been really smart
For him to do
The career Consulting
Tropicana Field
Listen here the transfers out this is going to go I know you're going to think that you're going to ride it forever.
Retire now because
Cuz do you know what's going to happen when you
You come back you got to go away to come back to Jojo
You got to go wake up
I'm going to make you a star
To come back to a lot of people where you got to go
Are you alive
This would be a great TV Leo auditor alive
This is up there with get out of it like interviewing a good
Consultancy for propaganda
Almost a shark tank kind of life
Anyway
I told you that I cut out all the gross stuff
I had to leave in a little bit
Because of where it goes
I go somewhere where the heck we're all going to
I enjoy but you have to hear a little bit of his growth
So I apologize about that
All about how powerful they are
And that little kids chained up begging for Mommy that makes them feel real big
That makes them feel real power
Alright
They want aquage down into that hell with them
No Hills real
Weird question
Craigslist New beautiful things
Stinking rotten meat sludge
Metamorphosis
Slap off into the beautiful voice
Singularity tips
Bernie Sanders
Yeah yeah
Yep
Is it still burning
Allstate weather is
A hundred percent
Cannot have a gap
No one else can
That is not good
Yes
Second City class doing a bar show and somebody's got terrible impression
How to keep being like
You know like that kind of
It's so bad also in our Consultants
Seashells that we do
Keep doing Bernie
Scold
VSCO
Jesus Adomian
With
The Great
In terms of
I think it'd be better if we just kept throwing out different names like
Who's that
Is that
Oh oh it's the
Looney Tunes
Let It Snow
Do it forever it's real good I can't believe that you work with him don't like sit him down if he likes
Does not like your
It's not it's not funny
Okay here's what I had to do while I was watching
Thought
This was a delightful day for
Fancy going on
Owen Shroyer sitting just off camera
Cuz he posted for the last like 3 or 4 days
He's just sitting there as Alex launches into that Bernie impression
Like a like a student watching the master
I never would have thought
I see the closest way he's a place
Cuz you can't be like
So
The closest way to his employees get to it is
Alex walked by an office
It's a cubicle and they'll be back and forth
This is what he sounds like
No no no no no
I'm doing the impressions
I am going
I know he would take that is like a good boy
Is really bent out of shape about
As he always is
Any
Fascism
Exactly because I
Most of the show is
I'm talking about how Tommy Robinson
Beat up buddy
Supercooling is also the victim
K Robinson
Camera people
I don't know what I'm not going to watch all this video I don't really care
I don't have the time
In the face
Engage with the reality of fistfights
Because whatever the case is.
Charming
WorldStarHipHop
He's
Got some thoughts about what's going to happen
Auntie forever
And
I'm going to jump on top of
Aruba
People don't ever get up
You guys are asking for it
Support
Jamshed
Okay
Trump says everything I say
I'm going to murder
You very
Very homo-erotic Lee murder anybody
And you know what I say
I think that could be used in court
Because like that makes it premeditated
Seem like he has massive fantasies about murdering other people
Talk to him first the plan in his head I'm going
The murder that doesn't make that justify
Murdered
Hours and hours of video of Alex Jones being out of protest and someone bumping into
Call the police
Egypt
Easy
So amazing
I'm going to jump up on you
Don't have
I do not trust I do not trust the Integrity of your Hammy's
Who's hamstrings don't have spring in them
You know what that's the real thing that's a she was Tom Arnold
What you got to do
Challenge them to a slammed
Contest
I think that be fun we'll probably isn't much better shape and Alex at this point
But
What is he even described
I heard was I'm going to f*** you
All I heard was going to jump up on you
With my
I put your head back
Mx250
Which is probably
Probably generous
But also
I don't I'm trying to visualize cuz I think
Maybe what he
He's talking about its
Some kind of I'm going to jump up
With like MMI knees would end up like around where your shoulders are and
I come down on you or is the person
Already laying prone and he's going to jump
What does that mean
Like push their head back top of their head hits the ground as they fall I don't know
You staying right
How many murder
But it's also
Interesting
No cuz he said he's going to jump with his
What was the
Finishing move
Probably differently I know he will call it the Infowars
Describe a tombstone different than that
A Wonderful Life
Is about talking
He's not gifted with
Survive
The other thing
The big the big story of the day is that Tommy Robinson
Oh that poor man
But
So
My heart goes out to
Absolutely
A dog
Prayer time
Narrative
Over the last couple days urban three bombs
Today
Yes I have read that story correctly
It is
It is entirely
Minorities and
Have no
Passion twist
Subaru ascent
As we recorded
They don't know about it but it is all
Black people
Now I don't know if that is the motive or not
May think that that would be the motive and so now
He needs
Proactively
Absolve white people of this terrorist Act
General guy
Actual title
We don't know what the motive Behind These Maybe
We do know that both of the homes that were the recipients of these packages belong to African American
So we cannot rule out that hate crime is at the core of
So they're saying we don't know that
McKay's but
It's possible
But Alex
Know any
Oh okay Alex
Haven't read any stories about it
Fresh air
Of the fact that there have been bombs that have gone off
Here is how he is going to absolve
If you see a white person mug
So you're kind of right
Yep
I'm not
Speculating
Was anti gin
Vacation there's an article in The Huffington Post
Application
Organizations and people who are active
Against
Navigation has stopped putting up with
The b******* and they're starting to fight back
I want to drive businesses out of May
Neighborhoods that are coming in
Specifically to gentrify them raise the rent make
Yeah places
Cuz where they live
Didn't read the whole article
Pretty long
And he thinks that
B positive
He thinks that the Huffington Post article as saying hooray for these people getting violent about
Action causes all that is is a reporting on the fact that
This is something that
It's happening it's not
Just like how Pro
It's probably Pro in
In terms of
Navigation does damage
Rich people
To afford
Rising prices
Hey let's move these people too slow and I also even think from my reading of the article 8 Santa
To a certain extent
Tactic
Because of what
Come from that inheritance collection
It's kind of a mixture of those things
It's just a reportaj
Positive
And so he is now put that Bugaboo
Into his
His Rolodex
Do you think that
Also because that article stay in Austin
It mentioned Austin in the cities
Vacations
2nd suspect
Pretty quickly his Narrative of saying
I don't know what it is possible
Evolves very fast
Where to go on the ground at the second bombing
I smell a little antifreeze
So
Sounds like
Bob's
Old timey cartoon like a babam
Mario
Obama
No
Kobe's last album
Really
Um no no no no
This is a conversation that has almost
Ended French
Am I in my past
Sitting around really high in someone's garage
It's a babam
I don't want to revisit this this podcast to report
Is the universe
Alex has decided
Narrative
That
Confirmation hear from Sharon.
Bob
Okay alright
He has read me articles he doesn't know anything about it
So that's just rank
Speculation
Also
Mike Adams shows up on the show to talk about how his YouTube channel got deleted and I don't give us
It's boring.
Just a note that he was on the show congratulations
Mike Adams from natural news.
Great
Dude
So now
Access point
Tommy Robinson
Complaining about Muslims
Quite a bit
Alex
As we know it
A Tommy Davis
The beginning of the show as we know Alex is like
A cobra attack
Gotta satisfy so Alex's
Suggestion for Tommy
Trench mouth
To go undercover in record the Moscone weather entire operation
I think that's a new shirt
It's time for cobra
What's the newest time to pray
His real name is
Probably
What all of it's also possible that his name is Paul Harris
What's
It's unclear
What is absolutely not
What
It's unclear
A 1/4
Steven Lennon
I'm not convinced this is your real name
Charging you under this name
Because whatever
Dickhole
And he started this organization called the European Defense League
The edl
Richie
She claims is a non-racist organization but all
All of their history
Case they're ranked
Are filled with devout racist
Does the drug
Like to get involved cuz there's a lot of fight
They have demonstrations regularly or
Ironically because he
Complained they were getting two races
Beginning they would have demonstration
Protests which it almost invariably deteriorate
Into drunk fight
Quote about them from the bedfordshire
Police Department gentleman by the name of Mark
We have had a series of marches were receiving damage to property would be people being assaulted
The tack
Simply can't be taller
Hey 2011a Yorkshire concert name Rage Against Racism was attacked by edl supporters quote
A group of around 15 people estimated to BHP
Between 16 and 23 barged into the premises shouting and chanting
Edl
Said Kevin Berry
Distant manager
Quote
They were throwing bottles and rocks
The police attended quickly and arrests were made
Have a long history of just being
Real drunk
S*******
To go around
Towards
Liberal
Stop
Is there a map
Fat people
Claim to not be race
Always seemed
To be the ones
Throwing rocks
Whenever
Racist
Seems to be very cool
Consistent it seems like
The same sort of thing you track with like
Why who's mad
People who insist they're on your side always wind up being
Not on your side
So from at least 25
15 on Word
Has been involved in the British chapter of an organization
Call call.
Pegida
Small radio
That's a dumb
The German
Relationship
Super possession of cocaine number of times as well as failure
As well as failure to pay child support
I'll be super again
He's convinced that Europe is being Islamabad
Patriotic Europeans against the islamist
Islamization
The Fighter
Please create that organization to fight against Muslim immigration
Ironically in 1998 after he was sent
3 years in prison for burglary and Theft
He fled Germany and became a criminal immigrant himself and settled in South Africa
Great
Gray
Yeah baby
That's not hypocritical at all
So his first rally with pegita was held in Dresden
Which is
The only choice
See he was being persecuted
In his own country
It is
Home Country he was not welcome
Many more
He was being gone maybe unfairly discriminated
In his mind go somewhere else
God he was a
Except it's really important probably hanging out with the speaker a
I'm glad his white Nation
Amen
Extradited back
His first rally for potato is held at Drive-In because he thought that city was a great example of
Of the Islamic
Haitian
Yeah whatever
Contain
308 people
Which made it a population density of .14 percent
Real scary
When you know everybody
My name
Probably not enough people in your situation
Doobie
Islamabad
Pictures
Dressed up as Hitler came to the surface a little while back
Organization free regularly uses terms like gluten free
Which is the Nazi word for z-line Jewish
Press
Many organizations have basically being
Akita members often go on
Quotes trolls
Which are basically just people getting together to protest about the present
Muslims in their City
Rat it's a bad luck
Tommy Robinson was pretty deeply involved
It's really just be a bad drunk fight
What's the law
An internet conversation is over when somebody
Vegas golden knights
That is an issue because now everybody is it from everybody
You know who came up with that rule
Another
Tommy Robinson
Speeches for this
Paquita organization and was heavily involved
The point where he left his own
Edl
Curaleaf Oxford
Nationalist organization
CDL
Get your s*** together apparently you're more racist than not
2020 11th
12 months of community Rehabilitation
Not long enough death penalty
The 10 months in prison for traveling internationally with a fake passport
Tommy had been refused entry into the United States
He is a hate agitator
So do use his friend
He got caught when they took fingerprints when he arrived in New York
And he ended up having to go to prison
Smart thing for them to do Tommy was convicted of committing mortgage fraud
I was sentenced to 18 months
In prison he conspired with others to use fraudulent information
How much
You're not welcome
There's no limit
How much time commenting career criminals it's a mess
But when is a comment ever going to be like
You're too hot
I don't know all these
He is super anti-muslim
Muslim
Message
You're pretty fit for a Muslim
He sent another one so I don't want to get rid of all Muslim
Least of all pretty girls like yourself
Both of these messages Jordan death
We're set to 15 year-old girls alright
I was terrified you were about to say Malala
F****** underage girl creeping on Twitter and being like
You're beautiful
That is
Listen
I have a prejudice
Monster like no you're so sexy I get over my big
But only momentarily
Only temporarily
Viciously like it's just
Those stupid like you have people where it's like
Your bigotry isn't even
Inconsistent
Respect as a legitimate
To even give.
The time of day to
He's a f****** career criminal who's playing out
How many printed he does have a history of being a racist
Borderline
It's some of that probably is genuine but it's also obvious
On some level
He found that like I can make a lot of money
Off of this
D.l. Hughley
Tons of money running this organization
I'm sure the dues and donations and stuff that he got from fellow bigot
Exactly
Keys
Using it
Kemet got a job at the rebel media
Through
At the end of this episode
They don't do background checks
Oh you did a year for marijuana possession so you can't work at
McDonald's
Rebel media
Oh man.
Really s*** is that like
It really turned one of these propaganda
Tight operation
Goddamn
At the end of this episode Alex announces that he
Descending Tommy
Thousand dollars
1/2
To give any salt
Him saying
I need the audience
Give me more money cuz I'm supporting this guy giving him money
But it's also Tammy Robinson
Kid like
That's why he's doing this
Is because he gets Alex Jones said
$20,000
Muslims
He doesn't need any money
This is all a scam
If you look at this dump
Career like that's what you walk away
From a trump Robinson can like
Preemptively go f*** himself we don't need to wait till the end of this episode this guy Steve
No.
I always wonder
Who is were
Because these
These guys
At the heart of all of these
Like every in at every race
This movement
You wind up coming back to a conman a prop
Demagogue those kind
Really believe in any of this s***
Scamming dump
Who is worse
To a certain extent
The guy who's like
Dude I I'm just trying to make a living to this is my Hots
Euro
Pull that off what is it
At the end of the day
Identify with the people who find
Themselves under the sway because of my experience with the
Evangelical Church
But I look back on that
I should not have
Yeah and what have you bought because of
Vulnerability alienation as a child
Any number of things that set the fuse
Their situation that picture of yourself in where you fall under
The charismatic influence
Both terrible
Put to use Alex Jones is sort of
Or things that you talked about
He talks about the Judas goat
He talks about like going back being a Judas goat
Leads all the rest of that
Slaughter you got the one who doesn't get killed
Leaves everyone else
Rifle
Because without them
I mean you just find another bigot later
Probably not all of them
Abington doesn't exist
Or whatever
Okay I don't know how to
His audience size
Just for the sake of argument say it's 100,000
Every single person named
Skyler in the world
Maybe
Looks like it's 100,000
People right
If Tommy Robinson wasn't there
I would say conservatively 90,000 would end up
Under the sway of some other charismatic Europe
Korean fashion
Thousand
Might
Find a hobby
They might find
They might find like
You know what I'm saying
10000 people is not nothing
Your ear argument kind of boiled down to like
Well
These people could be massive horrible race
His biggest for they could beat you to work woodworking 10% might be
Obviously a random number and maybe it's too high
But there is
A subsection of those people
That aren't really
Out now big
Necessarily
There are some people who are
I know that that
Well somebody preaching
Truly believe in
Everyone
You can go bowling with friends
It's like get it
82 Somerset 10,000 100,000
Centage of those people could find
I healthy
Alternative
That is just as appealing
That may be a rotary club
I don't even know what that is
Find
Something
You could find a bingo night
If you're f****** really old
You know there's something that you could singles meet-up
Any Wright bowling league
There's a hundred different examples where you can create a social life
That isn't
Princeton bigotry
But I agree with the underlying premise that most people would end up finding
Another
But anyway
Also weirdly enough
Bigotry
Fall pool leagues
Entirely run by bigots
I believe that I don't like school much
Yep my buddy make a gift by over Hitler that's what you doing
My buddy Nikki
Back when we lived in Missouri
Team
Kill Bill
I want the guys on the team was named Bill
Three women
Annabelle
F****** a******
He would come up
Scream
Depends
Whatever the Atlanta or bowling
Kill Bill you get really drunk and then you would come over to like table
Cuz we're young dudes
Are you just riding tell us jokes
The only one I remember is okay
This is this is
I apologize for saying
I don't apologize
Why do women have
Periods
No I'm out
I really like y
Deserve
And then you look over at the girls on his team and they're just like
He was really good at bowling
Anyway this is
Alex Jones
National
What do you think might be
Eagle
They're all rich
He's our corporate
Time Warner
Evil people
Wait
Tommy Robinson
The next segment.
The like I do
Don't live in their mom's base
They're not allowed there
Methhead work
Yeah until if you are still living in your parents basement
You are not yet a method
You're just somebody
Who enjoys
The moment you are kicked out
Is when you become a
Through
I don't know
How much
Like based on my experience
Based on my experience of looking
Take me to Alex Jones's research methods
Mpow
His biography
Full of holes like
Swiss cheese
I don't know if I trust him
Use legitimate
T.i.
For this undercover work that he's doing
I think he's stalking people over that just because I was like
No you didn't hire a p i
A friend you know
Said
Schedule
Harrison Smith doing it
What is underlings
Stalking
This isn't this yeah
I got people committing crimes over here
We followed you to your home
Yeah that makes me very uncomfortable
No I don't like that
He's stalking us to
I know that
Chicago
Following us around and we don't realize it
Now we're getting into Alex Jones loves paranoid
The only way that this is why I know that the world is going to be
The only way you and I die
At the hands of Alex Jones fighting
Top of volcano
Of course
That's the only the only real way that we can go down
I died
Scream yell at Alex a doctor
That's what I imagine
Think that
Ahead of time warner we've been stopped
Him
It borders on dachshund
Cuz
Is easy to figure out who that is
I don't know man
It just makes me very uncomfortable
Makes me very very
Very uncomfortable
And Alex can't prove any disease
He's acting like an ant
People is an actual like centralized organization
It's not I don't trust him to
You have infiltrated
Good thing
Trust him to act
John information that he gleaned
From infiltrating
Inappropriately
I don't trust him to
That's actually a
And interests
Sting line of thought
Follow.
Play whenever we saw
Specifically antiques
The idea is or or Occupy Wall Street
If a rich person
He's involved it
Any point
The opposite
Is it side will use that to invalidate
Even if I was like we were talking about with WhatsApp
Who was putting on the concert with
David Rothschild
His heart is in the right place
He's trying to do the right thing
You have all of this
If he is involved in
Anyting
Despite the fact that because of his money
He's far more capable
A being involved
Anythink
Invalidate
Everything
For everybody
One of the one of the central struggles of an antifa or the like is
The ideas that from the outside
Lack of pee
Means you are worthless
Yeah over, and I don't
I don't think
Is when we like on our last episode
2008 stuff
To what extent
Describing relevant
To the idea that
You know all of these
People who work
For Coke funded
Rebuilding
These narratives
And stuff like that
I think it's differ
But I'm not entirely sure how dark
Circulate why
But I do think it's
David Rothschild being
Involved
Charitable
Yeah
I don't know I don't know it's really complicated but I agree that it's a problem for both sides
It's far more problem
For people who are
Because
If you are
Correct
If it well Prince
Antifa
If you just
Toilet down to
We're against fascism
You are correct
Yeah right
And if you are right you are
Far more easily chipped away at
Because
There's no kind of amorphous ability to
You know.
Do you have it
But you're right
With the
Conservative movements like the tea party or whatever
Because they don't
Actually believe any
Then you can say oh well your ideology is
I just like
Why are you saying ideology
I'm so
The only thing that
Being other people's impurity for is
Priority
Yeah I don't know it's really complicated
I hope this is a line of thought
The Weeknd
Continue keeping our hearts
As we go along
And look at
Cuz we're going
Continue doing the
The beginning of
Life has that
That line
To self criticize
To certain extent
Look it back onto
Because I don't think we're going to resolve this
Polite way of saying Jordan
Please don't bring this up
No it's not
I would cut you off work earlier
I'm so just next clip Alex
Evolve
Yes. About the author
Austin bombing
Very trouble
Tommy Robinson
Just living Peyton
Tommy Robinson down about 8 years ago
England
Was from England
Create
He's a great Patriot he's not talking about patriotism
Being something related
To love of country
He's talking about
In F
Nick identity
You would call it the West
Or whatever
But the fact that Alex Jones
Thinx
The Tommy Robinson is one of the greatest living Patriot
Swears allegiance to is not the United States
It is white
It's white
That is what's more important
Dangerous
Until
But he keeps saying the Tommy Robinson
Great
Strangely enough
Is
You could describe
As a
Global collections
Trying to run everything
With its
I think he's
Global
BoBoiBoy
Anyway look infected
Wait until all the information
Himself into it it's probably probably
Did you a sweep of other houses
So he's
I think he's figured out that rolls off the tongue, bombing
So
Towards the end
Turns red in Ark
No one someone read an article
And got the information to Alec
Have been Africa
Oh no I didn't know if you didn't know and all I said was
I feel like that would be
Far less effective
Offensive been what he is about to
Information
You get to see him trying
Process
Gators breakdown smoke
Steam come out of his ears
By the way
It's a white supremacist meditation
Mexican Mafia
Oceanaire
I have no idea what's going on here
I wish you'd say that more often
There and then
Wildly disparate and ridiculous example
Exactly
Or perhaps
Stop giving
Most likely example First Billing
Probably cuz they hate black
Even though historically
I have no idea what's going on
Ifucking family crest
He gets there eventually
Kind of nice
It is so stupid
It's so irresponsible pictures all of these possible ideas
Might be going on with it
Is John an entire show
It's been ranked
Speculation
It's callmehbob
Over the course of it like it's just a family crest? Over its
You know you
I have
Trump
Jumpman
Been very anti
The conversation about fake news
The idea of like what
Can be thrown back in
Conversation at all
What this is
Is bad word
It's not even like
This isn't about him saying something that's fake
In terms of I think this is a commie bombing
Slime decorations
Editorializing or whatever
But the fact
It creates narrative that he's pushing throughout the show
He could have looked into be like I don't I don't know what's going on
Invalidating
Tomorrow
Bad work
It's someone who's not good at their job why you left their job
Great job well I mean fake news has ultimately just a euphemism for allies
So that the media doesn't have to
To say
They're lying
Brightly because that's a full pot
So this is your right this isn't fake news this is just
A guy who's like
Interested in this story
Heck yeah
Is a hack
And then we'll start the damage later
Brings us to the end of our show
Some interest
Sing times
I believe welcome back Alex I wanted to get the Welcome Back Kotter theme song
Cute up for you but
Also dreams are not your
Take it out
Prison
And if you're not going to prison
You're going to be
The rest of your cruise
Talking to you
I would not I don't care I will talk to you once you're in prison
Cuz he might jump up with his memes
Do not get up from that
So I don't know man
This is sad the present is still
Incredibly sad it's getting sadder with the idea that he's going to
Fire
Tommy Robinson
Nae
Steven Lennon or possibly Paul Harris
How much time is left
It's been years
Like
Community service
Doesn't really
Lee County arrest
In 22005 I couldn't find my
Rite Aid off on like
Something like that
Sure he could have gotten away with
Some sort of slap on the wrist and nose
The only the only ones that I found
Amazon where the 12-month
Community Rehabilitation
10 months
In prison for the fake passport
80 months in prison for the mortgage
Broad
Confirmed
We're talking to
Yeah you did get out early though to on the mortgage
Fragua
Yeah cuz of course
It also fun son little little tidbit
While he was in prison he had to be kept
In solitary confinement for a lot of it for his own
Oh that's
Because you they
Yeah I probably would have got himself
God dammit
Sub saving people from themselves
Prison
I think I think what I want episode
I mean first of all time
People who deserve
No
Not bad although it is
First of all is our plugs we have a website called knowledge 5.com
You can join the Facebook group tell your mother
Go to our website knowledge
Absolutely would appreciate it
What I want to hop on iTunes
Roto grater
I think the most
Important piece of ass
Is the fact
Did he
Creeped on Twitter at underage girls
With Muslim related pick-up line
No it's not Muslim related
Biggest bigotry about Islam related pickup lines
The underage girls on Twitter
Now
Harry
Parody account
The other stuff
Like
MBM being arrested for assault
I understand
You're running out sucking big organization
You might get into a skirmish
Maybe you get picked up but it could have been anybody
I don't think it's necessarily right
That people have to go to prison for drugs
So I'm going to throw that part of it out
Bear the idea that I think you should get the death penalty
Change my mind
Kmol
The ideas for using his friends
Kind of funny
In the sense that he was so stupid that you didn't realize that I'm going to have to go through customs
That's insane to me and it's not something that I can be like
I hate you for that or you're you're the worst
Something that says
I'm a trustworthy news
And the mortgage fraud I mean along with this, anyways
And stuff like that but
The victims of it are back
It's not
I just think that one is the most
Indicative
Literally eight
Creeping on people on
Underage girls on Twitter using bigoted Muslim
Is really the core of
Alex Alex
2crave
Alex
Rocking understand who he has on his
You would think
Come up
Write anyway
It's pretty clear that actually considering that Alex is so afraid of three Muslim girls
Can you into a pool store
Fears of
Adult
Trying to lure your children place right
You just gave $20,000 to
So unfortunately
I have to say Alex
Please go fuc yourself
You're the worst at your job
You are so terrible at this
Alexandra Thurston color