Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
Yes sir yes sir
Sir Sammy
Sir it said I know a lot of you don't know anything
Northeast IPA
St.Louis
This isn't associated with Phyllis Schlafly
Schlafly Brewery
I love Saint Louis Italy throw this out the window
If it was associated with
So anyway
Could you turn me up a little bit I can turn up the cans
Do for you today but alright
Alright
I realize that I've been a little bit lacking in
And some ways
Ewoks at the moment and I believe
However you can go to knowledge hi.com quicksupport the show
We would appreciate
But I've been really terrible about getting back to people who emailed
I apologize everybody is said
You know damn I'm feeling I'm feeling good everybody I'm feeling very
Self-conscious about it in terms of like keeping up with the communications and I'm going to get back to everybody
As quickly as I can that I had not
I got to get to what's going on here
One of the reasons that I hit
Not gotten back to us because it was Avengers Initiative related
Got caught up doing the endgame coverage at the same time
But
I want to make this clear
Next episode
March Madness picks
Coming out on Monday
Do my best to know
What everybody
Involved
Call Deanna
I'm going to be gone for a week
Whole wheat
Who's going to be in a conversation
Have you do another Field Report like you did
Forehead art
You might have to
Free for a little bit
I think Alex Jones might also be needing everyone involved in Infowars
Is probably on the cusp of fleeing but but their words
Would not indicate that
Here's an out-of-context dropped from Today Show
Nowhere
He personally feels very strong I personally
Feel very strong cast long long exhale
So what I want to do is when we do these episodes give you a
Philly
I want to do the week that was
Is that one of their segments
Okay well the Alex Jones Show
Earlier this week covered Monday
We don't need to talk about that but will be going over the 13th 14th and 15
Ocean today
Some would say it's obvious living
Let me give it to you this way
My ability to plan with you is not existed getting caught up with all sorts of other side
Workout
Pretty much everything except for the Ender game coverage
Has been the idea that I've had that about
Is going to be really fun
Alex has been on
Some real bulshit this week
We all know he's getting food
Another lawsuit comes around
And the way he escalates is
Classic
UCB style improv
It's alright it's saying how quickly alright
From reality
Play Never starts with e starts with an elevator
And then gets to a preposterous
Another long way there's a lot of really stupid things
But we're going to start
Shockingly close
You real well if he missed his first clipped we're starting on Tuesday the 13th
Alex
Epsom salt
About this lawsuit
And this one is being brought against
This one is a defamation lawsuit that's being brought against him by a guy named Brandon Gilmore
Politico article here
The violent clashes at a white supremacist rally last year in Virginia Charlottsville
Far-right new site in Fort Worth
Leader Alex Jones
On Tuesday
Conspiracy theories
But he was working as a deep-sea operative for the governor
That's the basics about this lawsuit but Alex Jones
Start off on Tuesday
Affect definition
Right
Debatable
That's kind of a compliment the weirdest part about your way more than what
You actually are I don't agree with that assessment
Spiritually deserves to lose this lawsuit
Think he can probably win
Horse saddle
It really tough to do defamation
Yeah you got a lot of people with
You know
The way the way that it does always seem malicious
Let's do it let's hear Alex's version of here in this first clip
From Tuesday
EBay spokesperson
So they're already the public
Public figure he's harder to slander
Guaranteed
Article 4
Hero Antarctica
Purple indigo
Alexander Jones
Weather
Take me to finish
Wait what
So Allie Max bringing her in here
That might be great
A little bit
It's because she did the interview some of the interviews and questioned the people she interviewed is also being
Who comes on the show later we're not going to hear anything from him what you need to know about Lee Stranahan
Batman quit in protest over an unspecified issue
Sounds right and when asked about it he said
I'm on the Russian payroll now
Also in the interview that he did on import World crime
Maybe I am now don't worry about it
In the interview about the Charlottesville rally
He compared what was going on there with
The Russian version of events in the Ukraine
I know Russian narrator of the Ukrainian crisis
Blank was anak
Weather
His argument is that Soros was the agitating
Enforce in Charlottesville
Increment so
Little bit
I thought I was busy with
Everywhere
Pans and so many pies
Is anybody actually work for sore
Soros and son
The mom-and-pop globalism operative
Also
They have a special on hamburgers
Honey biscuit
Text orison and fam
At last clip
Alex was recognizing
Yes that does not last long
Are the Gilmore Girls also
You son of a b**** you got to listen to
Deposition rooms and Hammer those white shoe boys for the return the Republic
The Rebirth of America and the second revolution
JTV live
In the heart of the resistance you're listen to Alex Jones
Dupree Market
Number
If you want to know
If you want to know what the
It's a war
Americana
Sharon Tate
I'll get more into
What's the Deep state
Quinton command base
El Supremo
Operation
That's a lot of work
One he did not realize that Hillary is currently unemployed
He's mad cuz Hillary video
She was in the deepest of the deep state
Operation operation
Dim the Jesuits
Jesuit
You're getting a little nuts you're getting a little bit ahead of yourself
I promise you I'll explain everything in describing the
Against
State referee operation
CIA Jesuit
So now
CIA
Hold on
There's a little more in the next
I would watch that movie trailer
Free speech in America
You think you're going to be some Amicus brief today
I guess they think they got everything worked out
Catherine Virginia
The best laid plans of mice and men
Austin
Though
Australia
It's hard to tell if he couldn't come up with the end of the quote or he was doing that for Jamaica
I'm going to
Often
They often go
Out-of-this-world
Martian base
No literature is
Coordinates
Let's not
Too much because I can't
Serious
This is so tertiary today at the matter of him
So we've got go how do you feel about letting
Okay
Problematic character but 11
We start with Brennan Gilmore
Is doing
Then we bring in the Jets
Now we we've established that I would leave the Jesuits
I promise you I promise
Everything
Taxpayers financing the Jesuits
Explain everything
I have so many questions one more installation that needs to happen before we reveal the truth
U.s. Bank Fairmont
Georgetown was founded in 79
Washington d.c.
Basically is today
But
So now the pope is doing
Sir
Is suing him
Yeah this is a pope ever delegate
No the pope to any of these people literally right
Yeah yeah hope is going to be defending himself in court against Alex
I'm so I did all of this all of this
Just
Comes back
To a couple of stray facts
And it's basically all because
Brandon Gilmore the suit that he is bringing
Was filed in court
5D Georgetown civil rights
Talk to Georgetown University civil rights Clinic
Yes clinic
Here are the only facts you really need to know
Carol quickly does the white smoke come out
This is nonsense
Georgetown University is a Jesuit university or historically has
Who Alex Jones hates entire book
Professor at Georgetown
Ergo Alex
Connecting those things
What was filed by the Georgetown civil
Wright's Clinic
I'm going to read to hear from their website with a civil rights clinic is
Civil rights Clinic
Yeah I suppose I don't need to read the paragraph
Operates as a public interest law firm representing clients in
Public interest organization
Primarily in the areas of discrimination in concert
Additional rights workplace fairness and open government
Sounds like a pope students developed
How to file complaints in federal and state courts conduct Discovery engage in motion
Practice and prepare Appeals
Is what like it's what you can do get therapy
This is essentially he is doing them
Through
Like probably deserve money
Who's the number one Law School
America better than a lot of lawyers
You know what why is it Georgetown is it because it's the pope and the Jesuits could be no it's because
Best university in a two-mile drive from Charlottesville Virginia
It really close to Charlottesville Virginia
And it's consistently the number one law school in America
Georgetown no I'm sure because of the area that the offense
Took place or I'm sure that
He has to bring it into a court in that area
And what's the best I don't know I don't know what Brandon Gilmore is addresses
Georgetown University you might have connections
Go to Georgetown
Connecting like
If you just to think logically about it like
The tragedy happened in Charlottesville Virginia
And 120 miles away
Is Georgetown University closed up in Columbia Missouri
The University of Missouri's pretty good
I guess
If I needed
I don't know what Webster does Webster University in St Louis.
Question
Alright so we know the ncaa's an evil organization
I've heard that
They if the students are
The lawsuit for being his lawyer
Ineligible for the law tournament
It's absolutely
Experience course credit
Brighten Alex is misaligned
The way he's escalating his own oppression
And let me tell you this
It's not done
He's going to escalated even further but we will have to wait
You see it's a little bit later
It's a little bit later. I'll get there in a bit first Alex Jones
The only thing
Does he save the pope is almost as bad as the juice
No it'll say something really sucked up in the next place though
Here's your sister
Boxers
And I'm so honored
Abreva
Tennessee
He's not doing it
He shall products
Something really terrible
And it starts
Starts with Alex
He's encouraging people who went to Georgetown and their alums to stop giving them money
Really I don't have the clip of it but on one of these shows he says that they've been going
Through the alumni rolodexes Georgetown
Contacting alarms and stuff
Which I don't I don't know how I feel about that you got to do
You're not
Susceptible
I would imagine.
That's sort of his plan is I'm going to
I'm going to crush Georgia University
That works but unfortunately it says something at the end of the clip that
Should make any Georgetown
All of your alumni Georgetown as well but you got to pull your money
Other people
I'm having my rights violated by Jim Crow
I don't think that's true cuz they're suing you
They're not
Discounting you as a human being
Brightright
Right
Like they're like
Literally going to treat you as an equal by going into court with you as opposed to being like
You're not allowed
Yeah.
This is
Keep calm
B firm position on Alex
Go to court
Lake bright if you don't have if your rights are being
Violated
Go to court
You have to
Yeah
Got show up
Well I mean
He's not going to be treated
Barely
If there's anything
If there's anything I know about
The justice
Is that rich people are never treated
Did fairly rich white males especially
System
Hey
Rich white male
There's no way to have
Is fair day
But I just
Concerns that he's screaming about in making up
Like okay
You believe that the Jesuits
Through you through this
Right taxpayer-funded
Go to court
And make that argument
See how it flies
Anywhere but on your stupid show me how
Anybody
Because you know
Fine I would love that
Beautiful
We go back to this over and over again the concept of proving something
Alex versus the real world
Are very different thing
Behind
Sir sir
This is about your comment I made about this guy
Who is not the pope if you recall
I think in the in the just
In the justices
I got a scary those hiccups anjal
Scary
In the justice system
Alex is a very different man
No I mean he was screaming it is
Custody
Well yeah but that was he was going to lose too much month
YouTube kids
Do you want to take
Gargle some water
No I think I'll be okay
Actually worked I don't know about that
I think I'll have a cigarette
That's as a cure-all for everything
I'm in the next clip Alex Jones rocks out to a little bit of music and then make
Revelation
Is an exaggerated
Red Rocker brake guy
On just one more
Ally
Did Hillary lawyers have filed
Studio season 12
Lawsuits
And most of the last couple months
I think the number is high
Because he goes on to say that you had six of them thrown out of court
I think he's creating fake lawsuit
Pretend
Shamefully settled the lawsuits that we're aware of and the other ones are still pending
Exaggerating
But at this point Alex
If he has 12 lawsuits pending
Cuz I can't imagine what those other one
Yeah I know
Number is a fair chance he can win this one
Separate lawsuits for child
That could be
If you can
I don't know I don't know enough
About law
Another lawyer
But I don't I don't think it's
Totally out of
Like the realm of believability they
Did he could win
This one against Brandon Gilmore
I think it's possible
And I think the one again
The Pepe copyright infringement lawsuit I think it's very possible that as well
EEOC complaint
I think are much more of a toss-up I think
Probably going to have to settle those
But
He's not going to win against actually back
Don't seem like it but I think he's going to settle those
I don't know there's
Like the oppression that he's presenting doesn't make sense
Be pretty decent
Position do you then
They considering all he's going to do is lose a bit of money
I mean not against the Pope
Volvo
The pope is not implant he's going to lose
Is Boston
Andrew Jackson
No not at all I was going to go with
Lindbergh
Gustav Lindberg
We've always heard Alex
Keep children tied up in their basements
We hear that all the time twist
On this episode Alex Jones
Presents himself
And America
As being the ones
Trapped in the basement
That's interesting and because of that it's not quite
Is gross to listen to right so I'm going to go ahead and play it
Who's keeping him in the basement pitstick globalist and maybe one of them is a worm being
Everybody knows what
Control
Basically
Kick you in the face a little bit
Open
Both arms out of shackles
You open the trapdoor to come down
Metaphysical
Dark Souls
And around
And you're screaming for Mama
Down the stairs
What are we going to do that big giant
What are we going to do that worm
I mean the only answer is murdered right kills I do the worm
You have no chance against
The big worm
Okay so it's either we're going to get f***** up by that worms
I have literature
Fanfiction
There is a
The Tremors were sure they were there
Pack all this
I don't know who he thinks is winning in the
Free and put a piece off the baby
I don't know America has opposable
Trump getting in his arms getting Free Rx that metaphor
Maybe
We don't have any clips of it cuz there's really inconsequential but he's thrilled with Tillis
Play her we're on our third little bit of tillerson's farewell
Press conference
Alex
Clearly
Confused
By the language
This is all code
Nutella seems clearly talking to a globalist stay behind Network
Okay break Tillerson
Famously getting rid of most of the state department
Has a stay behind his death
Got fired 2 there is no one
Snowsuit
Torture Master like what what are we doing
Comes on and I think
Is Eddie
Why would the CIA director b.good
I don't know man
Alex makes the argument that the
CIA is run by
EXO
Of course
I mean
That's his explanation for why it's cool that the CIA director br
Chief diplomatic officer
Done
Like everything is soaked Through The Looking glasses
What is happening
I don't even know
Nothing
Everything and nothing
I don't know I don't know what to tell you no take on it
Do you know
What are the things that I find interesting
About Trump being elected is
Why do people are calling themselves dictator for life
Like Prince
Yeah people who would have been checked
By our state department in the past
John Kerry's not allowed right now
People
People who would have probably use some of our soft power in order to be like
Hey hold on now
I don't know if that sort of thing is appropriate China and Saudi Arabia us
The weird things watching our foreign policy get dismantled your kind of like
Evil before but
Well it's kind of a difference between
I don't I actually don't
Believe the
First part of the sentence
But I think that the perception is there a necessary evil
I think that right what you kind of come away from Obama's term with right
In terms of foreign policy a lot of things that are really f******
Unacceptable but the realities of the world we live in
Necessitate
And now we're just an anarchy
Yep we're just basically in a foreign policy of
Look Russia
You are probing to destroy our power
Get it
But
Our responses
Come on guys
Come on guys on Thursday
That's right but they're not really targeted at right places
Circus like 18 guy they're wildly inappropriate
Russian oligarchs themselves
Maybe
Just maybe
Donald Trump
I think that what you look at
A really interesting article written by some Morgan talk about a little bit later on podcast in preparation
Cancel that
No
And only on the periphery
Use making the argument long while back and he was an article
Like 2009
About the United States
Right
The reason that there are
Destroyed you'd end up in a multipolar world
Order place where there was much more
Universal respect in power between Tundra
And the reality that he argued for is that
What would happen if the ABS
Essence of us
Power
Unipolarity is
Chaos
And international Anarchy
Sure seems
I'm not sure if I believe all of his
His promises
But it does look based on things that you're talking about people saying I
I'm just going to do whatever I want it seems like we're at the beginnings of what could be an era of
International
Anarchy
Some point down the road deciding
Power now being able to do that
Is China
Russian wouldn't
They don't have
The capability either because they're not
They're constantly speaking
Well they can only use they can only exercise their economic power over there
At the end of the day America has
All of the gun
Like essentially our military what our military is
All of the other major countries plus a million combines like
It's intense how much military
I honestly don't think there's any way we would use most
Well the good news is
That's right
Is that now that we do have
All of this military power
Hegemony
There's no possible way with our stable and wonderful government that we will
Use that in a negative possibility way there's no way
I still have
It all
After that I don't know
I never know
Clip where
Alex makes his claim
So this way yet
The lawsuit
Defamation of character that
Do you put towards
Nope
Is considered dark poop situation the black pope
In the day of and after the Charlottesville rally
Alex
Kessler the guy who organized the unite the right rally
Bulshit
Could fly in his face
Alex's defense about why he's not guilty of the thing that he's being charged with
Is that
Onward
And they miss quoted him
Oh no
And I don't
Texas is going to fly
Here's Warriors number settings
It was a bombshell connection
Charlottesville
Bombshell connection George Soros needs to be charged and arrested
Causing Charlottesville
Marriott
Is amazing real
Again the guy who writes respond
One he doesn't have any
Aside from
Contract
Now
I am also not a lawyer
I'm not even a lawsuit
At Georgetown
But
Course
You got that contract
Cigarette
No no no he's talking about
Bead sucking
Contracts that he found on 4chan that were
Exact
No those are
Fake
Those are absolutely not real
Fortunate
Talking a lot of lawsuit
Things are real defense of like
They're suing me
George Soros
Cars supercharged first edition for causing
Cos Charlottesville chaos
That's weak
I don't know what I don't know the difference
They're I think it me modern parlance
The vernacular
The cause of law if you say you called charlotteville
Charlottesville
What you're saying is that
Woman was murdered
Soros
Paid a MP4 to agitated that's what
Isn't that the distinction is opposed to just Charlottesville
Crazy s*** happened
Not Soros is responsible for the murder
No cuz I look at like
When we say Charlottesville
We're talking about
The math
So Charlottesville in Charlottesville chaos
I think are synonymous
You would think this is not a glaring omission
With the lawsuits
Maybe very easy
This
Open court
Alex Jones Talk Dirty about his wife
They've been frozen
Talk Dirty by his wife
How many throws it to commercial with Ted Nugent
It means we thought
This is Motor City
He should just be at the
Yeah
Between them
It's their business whatever
Probably but then like
We good
She's not she has other qualities
Nope she hasn't she's not street legal cuz she's got too much horsepower
Too much horsepower
The same car is me
And then he throws got rid of the Hellcat
I think he said he was going to
Salad
You like this guy
Cars me let's go to Ted Nugent
I meant he we use in the name of the song
Being like we got you globalist
Strangle
Pretty smooth
Yeah if you gave him like
5 minutes
In between
Like an hour
Solid music amazing
Well
So that's his new wife
The next crappie talk about is old
She is deaf
When they run their mouth
What you're already doing
Outside of that Court
You don't do that
Tom Brokaw say
You are
Literally every time he says the quote unalloyed racist
He has to Define it cuz he knows his audience has no idea what that mean
I'm also I remember eclipse of this in here but he's like
Statute of limitations, Brokaw
No that doesn't make sense because they're going to sue Tom Brokaw
Called to testify in the
Is Alex Jones a racist case
God we would crush it
I have a little bit of an archive
Circumstantial evidence
Indicating
Talk to try to distract
The fact that he's being sued by it's literally everybody
Talks about
That's not a good sign
Let's see where this guy
Sure
Oceanside
Big Lots
They would be able to
That's that's
True
That's what also doesn't make any goddamn sense
That's an
Because the entirety of his
No that's not what
Because for the entirety of his career up till this point he's been denying
Kelly was part Jewish
Father was Jewish
By denying that his children were Jewish
Because the complaint that is anti-Semitic critics
Made against a witch again
They're wrong
But they they said that Alex Jones working for Israel and that Kelly was Jewish
And that made their kids Jewish and that meant that they could
Have right of return Israel
When they committed all these Christ protection from
Committing a bunch of crimes
Is real for Asylum or whatever
Santa's crazy
But
The reason that that clip to me
Is like
That's damning
Is that
Fake uncomfortable laugh
He's covering
Him staying
I'd never thought of
You f****** thought about
All the years you've been f****** denying
That your family is
Jewish roots
I mean wiwik theory about eggs
Exactly that
The right of return
Crazy about it
It just would also apply to almost home
Decade
His career
There have been
People who have been harassing her
I couldn't find the clip of I forgot what episode was it on the show
There's a guy who called in whose like I've been inside your house
Yes I recall that and he was saying that his family was Jewish
Retalix
Specifically said
Really he says it over and over again
He has no nervous
Forever people have thrown it in his face and again
I need to keep repeating
They're wrong
Their argument is wrong and
Put the facts italics
Has made of
Change now and is using Kelly's Heritage in order to protect
Himself from accusations that he's racist
Memes
Crazy how much the way you feel about things changes when they become valuable
Yeah really crazy how that
Yeah it's real
Really really important until I get in your way
Abandoned
That's pretty f*****
Crazy I just I always believed in Behavior
And this is a big
This is a really big one
Did he know his wife's Jewish heritage
They ended up getting married because of like common law marriage
Together for a really long time before they ended up getting married
And knowing that she's Jewish
Now or Never
I do not put
It seems it seems
Difficult
Not much of an a******
Seems
Far more unlikely to me than him
Being on
Good terms
But you that you're forgetting
That
This is
Years and years ago out
Alex Jones
You could sit down and listen
I think he would be
You do a nice job of talking to the In-laws
Fahrenheit
Brings us to the end of
Tuesday show is come
There are a couple interviews but they're not really important lady
Pettibone was on the show
She was just on because Tommy Robinson mentioned her the day before cuz she was trying to interview him and got
What's up
Yeah it's not really a good interview at all I do, Robinson
Only knows people
By their fake synonyms
The interview
He just tries to be like
Impress her with his plight
I'm at Natalie Stranahan who again as a writer for Sputnik
But I just talk about how like
Beaufort
Follow the money
Call the money eventually get back to the Pope
That's the that's what I knew about the Watergate
Yeah that's why I fixin actually resigned is because the Pope
May 10th
You're right you get it I get it now
It's the Jesuits
The tourism
Exactly
Tuesday and Wednesday Alex
I've gotten some
Cider information
He's still complaining a lot about the lawsuit
There was bombings in Austin
You know that's true
From very reliable
Cite sources
Some information about these bombings he wants to
Am I able to
Overwhelmed
Our security folks around phone
Smart bombs in the refrigerator
SOS
People can understand
Never happen
Tom Brady
That was on Monday
The one on March 2nd
I'm going to give you the exclusive during the break
For the security guys you're the one talking about
I want to have him
Of the year
These are bombs cook
On
On the front porch.
On the porch
That last thing is fine
Did you order anything from Amazon
Don't touch it don't touch it
My friend
So Alex is saying that his law enforcement sources have given this information so he can report it and when the truth comes out
In the end
Yep and I will be like oh s***
Also if you are
Take more than 20
Visceral
I would I would assume that's all
Slow cooker bomb
Yeah absolutely
Dutch oven
The dude
So Alex
Restoration gear and it doesn't change over the course of the
The show The only things that he says
Secret information is
That they are a spa
Someone is making them on porches
Infrared which is
Crazy
Great idea
That seems
Unlikely
Because it kind of undue undoes all of the advantages that bombing
That
One of the reasons that you bomb things are so you don't have to be there very long
You generally
Throw them
Or
Drop them somewhere and then run away
Do you like one of those
Suburbian
Cul-de-sacs for he's just out on the front porch
Goodnight little mcmansion house and he's just
Stirring up some
Waving it
Hey you're mowing your lawn as a great day today
Right
Seems like that would put the would-be bomber in it
Vulnerable position
Seems like
I don't know the reality
Situation I don't have fake sources
But I do
If you're going to bomb something
That is
Not the plan
Like that's not you
If you if you Google how to make a bomb
And you found this result sit on someone's porch for 20 minutes
Go to the next result for the first Google
It seems like a bad way to make a bomb
Let's
I mean we'll see how this plays out
Ulta
How would you
I wouldn't
I'm also unwind
But I wouldn't make a bomb
I make a bomb
Or a pant like a mechanical pencil bong back in junior high
Not not to use or abused in any way
But I'm not really capable emotionally I have a lot of fears
Dislike
Oh yeah absolutely
That's fair
So on Wednesday it also came out
Not only is Alex Jones
Exude
Fox News
Just getting sued
Family rights
Seth Rich's parents
God is here from this mother June
Article about it
This is a lawsuit
Guns Fox News one of their reporters
Gaston
The suit accuses Fox news reporter
An occasional guest
Buttowski
Of having intentionally exploded separate
Is death by promoting Rich was killed after
Democratic party emails
WikiLeaks
The nation's intelligence
Please have concluded that the Russian
Directed The
Democratic email
The suit also claims
Names of the defendants acted in such a way
It made it appear as if Joel and Mary rich
Step parents
Involved
Confirm the substance of
The smear campaign
So the reality of everything that is real
Is that separate was shot
Twice in the early morning hours of
July 10th
2016 not far from his home washing
Police suspect
Burglary
Diet pills robbery conscious
If it was some sort of
I got
It's crazy for me to eat
Even say is even like
I think inappropriate
And I want to walk that bad salute
Strawberry
In the absence
Conspiracy theories
The proliferated online claiming without evidence
Under more suspicious
On May 16th 2017 almost a year after Richard's death Zimmerman
I was being sued
Publisher story that's
Titled
Stafford had contact with WikiLeaks
Say multiple sources
The report quoted an unnamed Federal
Seen and read the emails
Between separation wikileaf
And was heavily promoted on Fox
Local Host Sean Hannity pedal Zimmerman's find
Get a week later Fox
Retracted story after the rich families filed
Complaints the sources for Zimmerman's report received
One of them are Men supposed sources
Private investigator named Ron Wheeler
Later filed his own
For allegedly fabricating quotes attributed to him
The connected rich with Wiki
Also there been number of emails from Petoskey that have come out
That are part of this lawsuit
One of them is going to read you here
This is a email that Buttowski wrote
Two bunch of
Fox News producers
Including Steve Doocy Gavin had in
Ainsley Earnhardt and Brian Kilmeade regarding
Okay
Regarding
Richie was right
If you have any questions about the story or more information needed call me at blank
Phone number
I'm actually the one who's putting this together but as you know I keep my name out of things because I have no credibility
One of the
Conclusions to draw from this
Is it the Russian
Did not pack our computer system
And steal emails and there was no collusion
And the Russians
So there's a bunch of
Incriminating
Yeah
Very clear
Episode
This is Criminal
They're so bad at
Yeah
They should learn how to
So I'm at this point they are the
Bomb makers
I just bought this lawsuit is going to be
This is going to be
It's very difficult for
The people on the right
To have to deal with
Rodger stone is also in play with this cuz he pushed a lot of it on Alex's show
But
Here's the good news about
That lawsuit
Is not
About saying
Zip
Seth Rich was killed because of the DNC
Or anything like that
It's about specifically
This conspiracy
Petoskey Malia Zimmerman
Executives at Fox
Conspired
Yeah that's what it's about yes so Alex knows that he can insinuate himself in it
Ambulatory
Talk about the Seth rich
There's a little bit here on this
And then makes a weird
Admission
Wissports
All right one of these days
Keep track of options things
And then you're like and now this next clip and I don't have an interruption
Interruption
I disagree
Huge Avenue like
You Can Have This Dance
It with with this lawsuit
Because it is not about what fox
News personality set
Can they force and on-air apology
Because I don't know I don't know is get a s*** ton of money
As well as censorship and at all that kind
Stop
They can't send sure shut it off.
I think they could make
Like advertised ski or Malia Zimmerman make an apology or something like that
An apology you want he want f****** handy and going on tonight
Literally
But I think you could introduce into the court record and all that
Story is a product of
A conspiracy to
Commits fraud and propaganda
I don't know how helpful that is your right
Yeah but
Cuz that's what you need out of this
Lawsuit is you need
These guys
To go on Fox News
I like
Do you know what you know what I think it is this case could be a building block
Because if they are successful in this lawsuit
Then you can establish that the story is
Is Bass
In this conspiracy between epitaph
You could probably bring
Smaller suits against people who push the narrative
Yap Ashley the people who worked at Fox
You couldn't you couldn't
Sue them
For damages or anything like that
To retract
Yeah or something like that
Did the story
Oh really
And Rogers
He is a miracle worker fancy little Teflon
Leprechaun at
Goddamn
Fairy ring
Alex talks about that lawsuit
But only in as much as he knows he
You can't be an right because of what the food is actually about the fake version of it he's presenting
Which is a smart move
How many makes a street
Starlink mission
Fox News
Democratic Party
For questioning Seth rich is murder
Help
Opposuit
Because
He's a sorcerer
She said she can't work anymore after his son was killed
Because of the murder
Coverage
You're not investigating
Is always the same as crazy
Oh what a
No
What a coincidence
Ice cream about how if you don't give me money will get destroyed
Voice
That's f***** up
In order to
Flex Rosati
We care more about solving your son's murder than who do lady
So are you going to get mad when we investigated if I investigate I mean
Use him as a prop
Yeah
I would be mad
Give me
Any sign of an investigation
That they've done
I don't have one
Any like any even do any reviews
Hold on just
Hearsay Countess investigation at the
Cuz it if so
At this point where I work
And on Tuesday evening there was
Special election
Pennsylvania
18th District
Now
Technically speaking
Democrat
The humans
Well cuddle Amazon
The greatest candidate ever
But what you take away from that
The district going
Plus 24 Trump
Before
Numbers like that
It matches up with
I'm coming to the middle it's just the Republican light is the reason we got
Republican heart
That's the issue
That's the situation
This idea of neoliberalism being a f******
Yeah
It's just
Republicanism
30 years ago
Neoliberalism
Republicanism isn't
I don't want to I don't necessarily want to engage with that cuz it's irrelevant
To the matter at hand
I don't care I don't live in Pennsylvania
Conor lamb supporter
Ferret necessarily also Scott Adams
End up coming on the show today
Here I can listen to it but it is funny cuz Alex keeps calling him Gilbert
Accidentally
He doesn't like four times
Scott Adams argument Conor lamb 12
Because he is the person who run
Voters most of trump
Doesn't
Track
Could ever have run
Seems to be a trend
Pennsylvania election
Spoiler alert
The Democrats stole it
Congressional election
Nope
That's an argument that he keeps making is that like
The Democrats
And that makes it right
Disenfranchised did not want to come out and vote
Which is a stupid
Would feel threatened the more likely they are to come out
Like every report on all of that s*** was like
Yeah yeah
And when he says he's up 10 or whatever
Predictions were up
Parrot
Is the 2016 hebraic
You made a three-point switch
Democrats
Obviously
Look up
Under smiley face establishment
Attack is appearance
Sunfolding
Call Sandra neighbor
This
You think cuz everybody saying
Essentially is that if you ever have a close rate
That should
You saw the movie Black Sheep
What
Chris Farley and
This old white lady goes crazy
I mean
If you really want to
Didn't get enough into policy
Really at this point
I don't know who to be rude
FairPoint what you're talking about cuz it's sucking stew
Stupid and it's just
Like
If the if the Republican 640 Voice vote
He would have been like
Congratulations on defeating the Democratic
This is true
2.0 is what this is
At the end there what he says that
More votes
Forecast that registered voters
Liking
You can trace this back to article on a website called Daily World update
Got to be a bad website
It's
Political trolling
Tire website
It's a completely fake website
Voting in the names of dead
Yeah
People talking about how like
Everybody says it's
The illegals it's not
It's an interesting art
Homeless
But he's had to move on because of the Lycans
Toxicity of these hearings about Crisco Bashas
His voter
Inquiry
Where do you mean the fact that I was just f******
Where they were analyzing people's names
To see if they were Anglo
But that is that is unscientific realizes enough
I got a twist
Narrative a little bit
Hobos
Yeah it was hobos
Have the legal right to vote they get them a bunch of whiskey
I need stumbling drunk to voting places
Yeah I'm him
Yeah
Presidential vote the black
Boat and the drunk but have we considered adding the drug for how much does the drug boats
Swinging election
It's not real
Is all nonsense I want that put into demographic
Do you want
I think a lot of you ever get elected for everything
Because of the hobo pie like one of the unfortunate things you're going to run political career and aspirations
Wow that's going to be a part of it another part is that a lot of the times
You're going to run into
Florida felonies
In the home
Community in the hobo
They don't have the right to vote
Yeah you're going to run into a lot of
People enthusiastically on your side without right
Our justice system is
I mean
You can only
Really be on drugs and loiter for so long before you get a trumped-up charge of something
Yeah just have a severe mental illness and have been kicked out because Ray
Reagan destroyed the
If you think Reagan was a good president
F*** off for speaking people with mental illness
At this point
I just wanted to show
On a Wednesday
Alex Jones tattoos
Boy it's tough to figure out who's the worst
It's either first or second worst guests of the day
He's just boring
Rodger Stone
Yeah if you know what
This stuff he's saying is like
Good
But he's
So boring
Yeah he's he's a dick
Kind of boring
He sounds analytical but what he saying is just nonsense
He's like we don't have to worry about these kids walking out of their schools
The protest gun
Rod laws
Because of the kids
Is are the stupidest
People in the society
Like
Seem like it
Scott Adams
Creator of Dilbert
Albert Albert
The reason they're protesting is
They don't want to get shot at school
Seems like that's a smart move
So everybody still.
Creating cat
He was actually my favorite character
Oh okay
Play squeeze
If I squeeze
All right don't forget that song
The two top
Costco gas
On the show
1st
No
Still around
Hasn't been around for awhile it's been a long time again
The show
When we last met most black-faced with reverence
Right
Yep
Levi's
Created the definitely
Not racist
Not misogynistic
Fraternity
The proud boys
The Fraternal Knight of The Proud boys
Go around in Tri-Cities
Wilson
Material has been going around as aljoeson to
You know that right
I've heard that
Back then
He was working for Rebel media right
You had a show on Rebel media
And I believe he
Lessons that started working for
How do you spell
Media
He had a Gavin McGinnis there but I believe that his sense and dead
Another show that I believe is just on YouTube
Get this it's called
Get off my lawn
These are the least we lose
People in the world
Jeff McInnis sucks
We are leaving
Get off my lawn
Show time
Just decided to do like with our ability
Intelligence just decided to do an episode where we were
Intentionally antagonistic and racist
I bet we get a new followers
I agree I think you're right they would quickly learn like
Some of our fans be like
That was not worth it
Never do something like that
It's very very easy to attract followers with your grief
Here's what we should do
Weasel
We should call our show get on my
And then the next
Turn off with get on my lawn
Let's not even get off my lawn
The next recommended video will the
Get on my lawn
What's the opposite
Get on my yard
Get off my
Yard on my
The yard of my yard on my lawn
Hit a couple dingers on my lawn so Kevin McGinest sucks
Yeah he's the worst
Listen to
Butter
It's worth it on on some level
Will you start advice
Quickly got
Right because of of course
Yeah
Because he hired people who were like
And this really weird
Fairly hostile abusive male-dominated work
Place would be much
More fun with
That guy
Telling me in the chat room
Don't care about that is
Interesting trivia but certainly does not explain his celebrity
You were too toxic
Mail
To work at a time
Typically masculine play
Early
Yeah
So
That's a good one
Property
Furby redo my lawn
Call Dago
Return to do a home improvement show
I got you
Here's the first clip
So Alex introduces Gavin McInnes
He's the host of the show get off my lawn
And I almost did
It's so hockey still on the nose for like
I'm f****** pissed off white
So stupid
Psychic reading
What's on your mind
And then there's a long pause
And like your mic wasn't gone
So go to the middle of a ramp
Bright
So he's talking you here if you see his mouth moving but no audio
Reanimated as well just
Yes
Charisma
Ones video game
Cardigans
Album
6 minute cardio
What food
Songs
Anyway
Jordan
I'm I'm only engaging with all this because I also don't want to listen to get it
I know he has to
How would you
That I feel like that's the worst possible way for you to try and make more time
Didn't want to talk about
Fair enough
No you're not wrong
It is a bad call back for the particular situation where get off my lawn
Is introduced
Alex says what's on your mind
Big silent
Cabins in the middle of a raincoat and Alex tells him
Hey man
We didn't have the mic on
Start it over
Cuz nothing is more genuine then restarting erase started over
Amazon.com
But I can't stop thinking about today
George Soros
Comedian named Atlee
Did I just saw
A a
Jordan shorts according to laugh is not a Nazi
I know that he led the Nazis
Two Jewish homes where they were that exterminator
60 minutes
However
Anti globalist Duchess Alan dershowitz Dennis Prager bench
All of these
They are not
You see
And it's amazing the pretzel
If they can twist their own logic
When it comes to this ridiculous
Nazi allegation
So
We have a very interesting start
To the interview
There's one thing
Always
Say
And that is that the Jews are the
Right that's a part of Holocaust
Very large part of the Holocaust denial community
Happened
Gavin is really
He's triggered
YouTube triggered little buffer
Baby because his friends are being called Nazis
And it turns out that George Soros
No one wants
Friends
Things that aren't true that I keep saying about him and Alex
It's not
It's very.
I think it's obviously the
Yep
Historically
They loved
There is never been
A huge issue with the Cavs
Bat cat
Conover over and over again with George Soros
Not sure
Anyways
He wasn't
Actively killing juice
Are you going
The camps along with his
He was in hiding
What's 0
What's the name what's the murder
No it's still not the Nazi they described
Certainly
Knox
The collaborator is Alex Jones being able to get away because
He knows that sources never going to sue him for that Grant like that
It's just a s*** game
You playing at all it is is
Trying to
We have to deal with the f****** have to deal with right up.
Comedian it's like
So many of these right
Wing guys you can
Can find them at an open
Your
And you did
Get white
Hmm. He said the reason that he never succeeded
When I was listening to this is famous for people who are not at all explosive
When I was listening to this all I wanted like I can't
Writing drafts
Tweet I never sent out
But they were just like
Gavin McInnes a straight-up on Infowars right now
B that would
Open mic
Exactly
Did like
Doing comedy
But he's doing it
New series that I've been working out
Specific
Passing the last couple days
Shrek
I also cuz you've been drinking
I haven't know I don't like that dessert beer
I believe
Your people
The Jews
Your Stouts
I believe the people like them again
They present themselves as doing comedy and political commentators
With the awareness that they're bad at
Raynaud's
It's so anytime their political opinions
Negotiating be like
Seriously
Political commentator
I'm trying to make you think
It wasn't supposed to be funny
So he play they're trying to play The Line
Yeah and it's really sad
It's fun on episode of little bit
Because you got Alex Jones and him doing the two-man Act
Alex
The worst two-man Act
Doesn't
Improv training
No you can't go along with things
Every kind of winds B
A little bit along the way
Training for what he's doing
Don't negate the premise
Really understand what
Premise
Is generally
He that he doesn't realize
Anyting
So at this point
About George Soros
How do I say I actually have video
Pair that shows the George Soros
This is everything
You know this is Alex Jones
Like here's my demonstration
The George Soros
But
When we get to the end of this it will make clear
He is actually proving that he is committing
Slander
Did he say first
Does anybody like
Impressions
No you don't do that and then did he say
Here's what
I think
Soros would sound like
If you were in
Who is Blaze
I mean
This is just like
One of the things
Coming back from break
Sometimes commercials in
Is this
McGinnis was talking about where Soros
Ashamed at all
Real quick before this video starts
It's very clear that
But Alex says
He rounded up
A rounded them up
So that's what this video clip is going to prove
Intex
In Texas
Parlance
That mean
He wrote them up
And then
Put them in the
If the claim that the
Representative
Come look at the background George Soros is one of those people
I understand that you went out with this protector of yours or that
You were robbed is adopted.
With a difficult
Right there already I have to pause it
Because Alex is selectively edited it
He's not app
Interview
Asking if it was difficult
You do it
Is difficulties asking if it was difficult
If you are one of your many new listeners first off thank you
Second refer back to
All of our episodes
Where is not enough
Reticulated
About
From 60 minutes
He's asking him
If
Do you wear it like
Awareness
Was difficult for him as he got older
The reason is because
If I didn't do it someone else would have done it
What are you saying by that is
I would like to live they were already gone
The Camp's I didn't do it someone else would have done it
Even says in the interview
Pretty clearly
I didn't go along with him all that off and it was a very occasional
Do you think George soros-funded the neo-nazis do March 10th
Find out
It would be interesting to find out
That's from a vice the vice special about Charlottesville rally
Listen to Reba first spread by radio talk show host Alex Jones
Is there anyone George Soros Nazi collaborator
From the information for
It's Alex
Jones
So it must part in there it just makes it
A package
Improve any of the stuff he says it has nothing to do with him
I just stopped about the best time of my life
In there
Why are we all
You said that I was creating a scare clip I would definitely put just
That
And then maybe like a little bumper of like
So you worked with another
Please and then
Cut it and then if he likes
And then
When he was talking about it being the best time of his life he was referring to being that age
And being
Somewhat
Free given that
Sacrifice
Is the father
And of course he was a huge Green Day
Yes absolutely
Holocaust
A very interesting song But at the end
Still not right
Play God's R Us have the time
About how liberal
Just
And then it's just that they're going
Brothers company
Yeah it's a bizarre thing I'm convinced his daddy issues in all these children All The Children of Divorce
Dematic
Or Louis Farrakhan Orlando
Or basically all of Islam
I don't mind it then so they're not about ideas
Who's Stanley idea
Their dad
Dealing with petulant children
Who are still butthurt
About a divorce than 50% of the country
Ghost real grow up baby
The black box out of juice
That's a bad b****
That's not analysis that's not interesting that's not
Political even socially
Relevant
Premise correctly
We're mad that
He's an anti-semite
Because he looks
Sly car.
It looks like
Daddy Yankee
Daddy I'm mad at you Daddy does not look like my dad
Is it just cuz he's white
Is it just cuz we're mad that
We have white fathers
Yeah I think that's what he's talking about
Also I want
I'm just going to give you a little bit of advice
Comedies in
Pacifist
Well there's that also in creativity
Also in
Like making your premise makes
Plant right things that are important absolutely
I would I would say
Personally
Find
Semitism wherever it exists
Offensive
I'm not a huge
I'm not those people are not
Target
Of mine necessarily
Specifically because we doing Alex Jones
But that doesn't mean that they're off the hook
I believe whenever Alex Jones went over to Farrakhan we made it very clear that
The reason they got a lot because they're both
I can I can be against Israel's
And at the same time
Against
I also met our parents are super liberal
And I'm still not mad at you cuz you look at my dad cuz he looked like my dad
We come from very different backgrounds
Neither are mad
Italics because of our dad
My parents Tommy do stand up for the very first time
Did not have the courage to do Michael
To do it and then I was advised by
The rest of my family everybody
Don't see the carpet in front of your
Ben McGinnis
Is the rest of this stupid and
Analysis
You were wrong about this. Two years ago
They go ask you why do you have so many kids after family in front of me
Sounds like a stripper
It's usually weird white male
We're
I can explain it most I'm not racist
The spot you can get about
Kind of but I can explain
Everyone hates
You
Giraffe
No one's mad that you have a family
People yelling
He didn't you lose your kids
They're trying to hurt
Everyone
You public discourse
I mean the enemy of
Decency
He talks about how like everyone keeps sending me messages on
Twitter and all over the place
About like
They want to attack my marriage you're going to get divorced
What about it
It's not about life
Attacking the family are attacking
Your family
It's using your family to attack
You because we hate
Now I think that the people is approaches
Claude
I get it
I just love that
It's not Twitter people
First
It's people it's
It's always people just
Walking by monster
Oh yeah yeah
It's always
Trying
To go to Aldi
Where I shop
Because I said I support small businesses
Always always
Especially gay people always
Always saying he doesn't
People but
Old white women
People hate
Because he has a family
The last
Their religion
Is destroying
Different religion
It's all wild
Destroying the family
Observe
Abs
Boy there's a weird
Chat rooms
Western weird image
Call celeb
Traitor train
Put like some
I don't know
Anyway, so
In this next clip
Look my dude
Is this our certain this next week we got it we got to chat
We got a Vibe about
Here's how Gavin McGinnis would like to
Present the difference
Between himself
And the last
Mardi Gras
The left
Is them
Dental Depot
Politic
Always
Always Gavin
Either night
Be a man
Oh he's an idea guy
These guys are not at all interested in white
Never never
How whites are great politics
Because
How the whites are the best as really struggling to find a reason I had to jump in there
Like
Chauvinist
Tremors
And I'll say at a time
Stupid
F******
Craziest things I've ever heard in my life
This is legitimate Lee crazier than black
Text face with Reverend
Alright I'm in
Well those people
Let's talk about ideas
So your concern is overpopulation
Set the American citizens that they tend to have a population
It's stationary or going down
Operation is going up
So you must then
Here's why your idea is flawed those people already exist
It turns out it's a great idea
When people talk about overpopulation generally what they're talking about
The big picture as opposed to 20 people over here 50 people over here
So you're already
Little
He was talking about
Create more kids shockingly
That's about to come up
If you're against overpopulation
You know we love them
Can you look at Time Magazine and they'll have one month it'll say
Don't have babies we have too many babies in the picture
And then the next week it will say
The new face of America
You know it's f****** weird to me
But there is an actual organization
Call the voluntary human extinction
Can movement
I guess an actual group
That exist
Find their website
Body image
Friend friend
Heart
Voluntary like pledge of I will not have kids
We don't deserve to
I continue to live on this planet
WhatsApp never mentioned them
And they are real
I just realized that I like
That's because
They might have a legitimate
Tough to argue
And the phrase
Then the white man came and not be like
It's about to happen that's even true for like
Animal King
Yeah
That's not even
Just threw for cumin
No I mean the white man right now there's no more squirrels
You're all about identity politics and the individual
Wehrenberg
And what's kind of fun about that is
Is not to breed and not have families
Our stupid idea is to breed like rats
And they are going to be at
Our children
Are not going to have to deal with these annoying childless lesbian feminist
Because they're all going to be gone through the dodo bird
Like
That's Alex not knowing how to play the game
That's
He's doing a bit
Probably expressing things that are lucky
Pretty close to his heart
But at the same time
He's doing something that he thinks is funny
He thinks that's funny he's doing
Turn on the
You know what they say
Are good for you
And then the next week
They say they got too much cholesterol
Ugly eggs in Irvine
And you know I love whites
And let me tell you brown eggs are good
Is that at the end there that is
Real
A sentence that he says
If you just unpacked the idea that
Children won't
Have to deal with these
Lesbian feminist dodo bird
Here's a cure for the
Various assumptions that underlie the
Yes gay people
Give birth
Two gay kids
Exclusive
That's the only way that happens unless
Cuz they are gay
That is part of his premise
Lesbian feminist
Arnot
Going to have kids
Therefore
People who have the same beliefs as them
Razor
Feathers
Not if there's anything from the
High schoolers have react
It's that
That ideology is going to die out
Right
On some level I hope it doesn't because it's snow
It's so amazing
That's it
I could write
Probably a 10-page paper
Alone
Just because of the the various peace
Like what I just said.
He
Seems to be representing the position that
Gay parents give birth
The gay children
Feminist
Parents give birth families children
Otherwise now
Let me hear about that first one
And then we'll go through their his ideology is that because gay people
Call can't reproduce
Deuce which he thinks is a thing
Prong of this
Is this
Weird f****** bullies
I believe that he's a thousand
Witches to invade Russia
Yelp
Somehow that makes more sense
He's presenting
These lesbian
Feminist
But he's so annoyed by
Haven't
Is the first time that they have been grumpy white males
Eden vet
They're not having kids
So it'll be a Jew
Phenomenon
Grumpy white dudes to have to put up with
Pretending that the Isle of Lesbos wasn't thinking
Bacon grease in history
Like VIP
Bright
Throughout the entirety of our history or the idea of women's rights has
Existed stage of matrilineal societies in in
It whatever
Never an issue in the past so
Crazy Easter
I thought Wonder Woman that died out
Triggered by
Having
Economy in authority
Executive
Create
Perception
Current
Sing
Just now
Being like on out
You could have
Two very right-wing
Parents who end up giving
2A
Childless feminist lesbian that will really piss you off
Because the philosophy is not
Genetic
Then the third prong is
What really seems
To be pissing him off
That's what you brought up
And that if he's mad that
White people who could reproduce
I think that's really what's more
Behind
Derek did you keep talking about how like it's all these weird gay white
Evoland
You know he says we breed like rabbits
You guys don't breathe
Actors that we breed like rats with
Which is yeah
Put
Think his worldview
There's a part of him
Pissed off
Well that is
Reason number one
That you see those
Gay people aren't allowed to adopt
Which
Adopt
No not which is they're going to raise them gay
Ghostbusters
My mind didn't go to that is I felt like that is such an old id
Exactly
Their concept is
So if we allow gay people to raise joke
That means more gay people
Right and if we allow them to have children they're going to raise
Like their concept
Of sexuality is
Is genetic
Kind of like we can get rid of it in one generation
Exactly just ostracized
No it's it's good
Like all of this all of this
Concept
Is built on the idea of
Jeanette
And it all goes back
It goes back to
Pieology
Goes back to
Play Black
Legos all the way f****** back
God damn I mean if you want to go back to the
You can enslave these
The f****** Canaanites like you can do all of this s***
Genetically
You are allowed
I don't disagree with you at all but I realized just at this second we are almost two hours into this
Alright let's do it
Absolutely
Stretch things out to some extent
And this next clip isn't
Going to help but
AOL
Why are lesbian so uptight
I'm out
But I can't help but notice minerals dancing around
Lesbians are always Grumpy in ill-fitting denim pants
Male gaze get laid more in getting late apparently makes you happy
I want to stop real quick the only thing
Buckingham
Forever actually interesting about that
Exactly
You know that great analysis
He cries because there's no
Little lesbian
.
How many men are married
Yeah you always used to call it
College lesbians
And it's easy to be bisexual when you're young and gorgeous
And all you got to do is make out with another hot chick
Lesbian
That's
Rock and roll
And the numbers dwindle
What is the tiny
Population is Tiny
Control
Which of the political narrative why are entitled elections
2 something is irrelevant as gay marriage
Because she's a lesbian
That's fun
Cuz you know what at the same time
You're getting so mad about this
And I understand
Rhetoric
But he thinks he's doing, Dateline
He's trying to give at least trying to piss people off
Like that
Gavin McInnes
Probably has quite
Parachute when they kicked him out of Vice
Amy wears nice suits
Politically
Going to start building a bond
Politico
It's just the worst analysis of any
Comedy presented as
Leben a late 80s mid-eighties Andrew Dice Clay routine
Absolute
Project
Absolutely being presented straight-faced
Cuz if you did that
You did that at a comedy club
No
No this is this is
Literally like
What I just said
The Comedy Club
Might be more Progressive than Infowars
Considering how terrible Motown.
That's not
And somehow
It is less effective
Coming from
Yeah
Pathetic man I just think
Buena Vista
Versation resist
Is what like Media Matters covered from this
Dissection
Yeah
I get it
Inflammatory
You certainly responded to it most harshly
Of anything I'm not happy
In the back of a car
The reason that I'm
Chill about it
Is because I get
He's a
Arabic
He thinks he's like
He's edgy and he's being like
This is going to get me booked on
Jim Norton Show
Lamborghini goes on there and I
Dyckman
Is like saying the
Saying
Misty word 5 years ago
Is like saying
However many words
10 years ago
Texting all of this s***
It's this idea of
Just because
Said the word
The people don't feel like it's okay
Automatically
Legit
I've been I'm automatically the most courageous
Instead of
A shity writer I've been pushing this
This theory that I think that
With all of his lawsuit Alex Jones is about to get into
Late. Lenny Bruce mode
Complaints against lawsuits
And I think
Gavin McInnes
Is doing
Next Generation
Hacky Disciples of Lenny Bruce mode
Where they think that you think
He's being edgy just by saying the word
Do you think the n-word on stage like that
I think he's doing really really drunk
Unreliable drugged-out bill
If possible but the Bill Hicks that everybody f******
Is not good
Jordan
I was trying to make a Transit
You were doing great
I am essentially ruining this
No you're not
Terrible job of the transition
Cuz I realized
Within introducing Lenny Bruce idea
Read
Go off on
Allied Road
You're not going
Going to be able to
Yeah
It's back to his lawsuit
I told you at the beginning of the show he was going to ask
He did he was worried it's collected even further
Wildly inappropriate level
Yes
My lawyers
Georgetown
On purpose
Call Sabrina
Holyshit
Wait
Hold on
If he
If the case
Alright
15K succeeds
We no longer have the first the first amendment gone
So as far as a her legal system is concerned
The entirety of our 200 bulshit your history
Will be tossed away
The first amendment has to do with like freedom of religion freedom of assembly DeSoto
Journalism
Gone
Dunno how to repeal anime
Snow help
Nope
Nope 2/3
The Congress
And then it goes to the state
Recorders of the states
38 states with the 50 states
So we have now
All of their state legislators have to sign up
No because you know why
What's the only way to repeal an amendment
Create a new Amendment
It sounds true because once you make an amendment
It's not an amendment
It's a part of the constant
That does explain why replace with another Amendment about
About probation going
Are bad guys
Alex Jones
Getting on his
Dumbass show
It's saying that his lawyers tell him
But if he loses Ace
Civil Trial
It will undo the first step
Love that argue
I need to
Crazy Eights bananas
Because like legitimately goes back to what I was
It goes back to what I was saying at the beginning of the show to that like if
You believe that
Go to f***
Can Court in this trial of the first
If you lose it
All you have to do is appeal it
Seminole f****** win if you end up losing this trial because the Jesuits and the Pope
Is against you
All this horseshit
You can appeal it
Based on the fact that you're
First Amendment rights
Violated historical
Hard on the First Amendment easy what do you make millions and billions of dollars and biblically whenever you're
More money comes in
If you have all those resources
Seems like
Just f******
Prove it and quarter shut the fuk up
As
Crazy is Hanukkah is
According to other previous
Right
The same
When it comes to Alec
Alex Jones and lost
Bring up we did that episode about Steve
Was that crazy
Preacher
Infowars
I know what I forgot I want type of preacher I am intimately
We familiar I wanted to bring a horse parallel
Call between there
Lesbian
And how
Usually take me to man they get much happier that offense
Pilobolus
He believes the similar things anyway
I told you what is it what
What's up
The logs
Lesbian until graduation no one has
Ever said that
People say that
I wanted to get away from it party
Crash frat party
When I was younger
I lived in a area of Campus
At Mizzou called East Campus
I was surrounded by like
Lakefront houses
Pretty Charming
So I would go with like a bring a case of beer
And then just wander into a party
You crashing at speed
Side Steel
It was a mess
Anyway
I told you earlier detail I learned about your
Awful book
For now Jordan I told you that I was debating whether or not Gavin McGinnis
Force
Was the worst guest right most appearances
Politically
This is a mess
Mostly
On because he wants to make sure that Alex is okay with the idea of Mike Pompeo
Being the Secretary of State
Legitimately
Based on Alex's
Technical ideology
Should be
So against Pompeo
Being secretary
You should be what event what is it
Full throated krita
Sprite
He should be like I don't know if I like the idea
Absolutely
You should be
Mike Pompeo
Allies in some ways
Or at least
I don't know if it's a two-way street but stupid support smite
Pompeo
All that's not really important
It's kind of boring.
Sonic says this and
This is way more important
And it sucks
Soros
Uber
He said giraffe
He did that's a thing he said
Out loud
To be fair judenrat is
Historical terms
Like it's not
It's not no
Good
I don't know what to think about that
Okay Bob number one
Politically
You're going to botanic over McGinnis now
Sing
Previously
I didn't like how I said
How I could say
And not the c word
I don't appreciate
Like I would
I would prefer that it was less acceptable for me to say
But
Jurat
Proof
That's a f****** baseball bat to the face you know what's fun
Media Matters
I know
Neighbors
I know it's crazy
I don't know what to do I don't know what to think about
Like its
It's me.
What's the same time I do I do
Give Steve pieczenik
In this area
A little bit of leeway
Because he
Parents fled the Holocaust
And he has that in his background
He's not like Alex
Who's
Entirely beholden to
Justin Durant
Somatic philosophy
Has Steve ever considered a how
His parents would for you
I don't know
Him I certainly don't want to ask living internet
Anti-Semitic worldview
I don't know cuz I actually
I don't
Too deep into this but the more and more I see
Think about Steve pieczenik
Understood that
Getting him to say things I wanted to say maybe they be okay
Train of thought I don't
Want to go down later as he goes on he talks about how like he knew Soros at the Council on Foreign Relations
Nation
And stuff like that
Doesn't like him
Personally
So
Without any
Virginia
Yeah. Also if that's not okay
It's not the
It's not that it
It's not okay
Then he said
Jurat
Because even if he
Didn't say that
That pretty
Particular
Braised mean
Exactly
Exact
He's a pile of
F******
Steven
Actually I hope he doesn't wake up with a note
Attached to him
So I Wednesday the
14th
Alex Alex
And then we go to the 15
Little bit of a pep talk.
It is not going great
These lawsuits are
Still there
Andy turns into
Call Frank
Can character Stuart Smalley
He basically turns into Stuart Smalley
No fear
Other than hoping I can be a stronger man
That's what I say
I'm a winner
Overcomer
And I
Use imagine him vexing that into a mirror
Bring victory
Bring victory that makes me think of that episode of fantasy factory Rob Dyrdek's Fantasy Factory
We're here
Hypnosis ceremony
His Name-O cried
Battle-hardened
Yeah no again what is your name
The issue is it
Certain age
Anyway
Yeah cuz he hasn't been
For the last few days
Now he's stalking lost pretty much
Non-Stop
Does all victims
Some censorship
Ship news
Penny chooses
Instances
To talk about
Three specific examples
And they could not be worse example
Pope Pope
Jesuit
Starring
Steven Crowder has been banned off of Twitter
More censorship Facebook bans right-leaning group Britain first
Well it's not doesn't have the same speech laws that we have
They have very specific
Cific laws
Against a politically racially and religiously
Just like Germany has like
Hey stop
Apologizing for the holiday
Yeah those are
The phrase
Right-leaning
Britain first
Is
No
They are right
All the f****** Hardwood
Let's
Let's f****** I know about Britain first but apparently don't
F****** girlfriend
Britain versus a hyper right-wing party in the u.s.a. reference
To Oswald Mosley in the British Union of fascists
British Union of fascists 2014 the group started doing Christian
Allegedly
Streets from Muslims
On one occasion they posted a video of themselves holding a banner that said we are the British resistance
Pouring beer out in front of a moth
White hoping to rile up angry Muslims to attack them
This didn't work any Christian leaders
White
After that they started invading mosques in cities
Including Glasgow
Coincidentally the city
Tommy Robinson operates out of
Can give out Bibles and
Free Christianity
You telling people to
To quote reject the false
Prophet Muhammad
2016 UK High Court
When their leader
Decided to run against London mayor Sadiq
Con in 2015
His Deputy Jada
Since they face the Wrath of the
First movement
We will we will not rest until every traitor is
For their crimes against our country
Stymied good old-fashioned British Justice at the end of a rope
On June 6th
Threatening
Lynching
Sadiq Khan
Is
Okay
They claim it's the Decon is some kind of like Sharia law
Wildly popular London Marisa Decon
Some sort of islamist sharia law
Yeah
60th 2016 labor Mt
Jo Cox
Was murdered by Thomas Maier
Who shot her with a sawed-off rifle
First yes I recall her as a Target because he believed
The Liberals leftist
Stream media with a Cause
The world's problems
Because Cox was in
In favor of immigration and the
Tu that made her a traitor to white people
First
Political party as well
Tommy Robinson
Although I will say in in honor of just being completely Fair
2016 is after Tommy Robinson
Left
I don't need to blame
But he is already gone
State save
In court when asked his name Thomas
Merced
My name is
Death to traitors
Freedom for Britain
That's a long name that's a long name you should shorten on June 23rd 2020
First anniversary of the brexit vote
A drunk Britain first supporter attempted
What's a curry restaurant called
In Haro in West London by driving the van at it
And shouting
The restaurant owner was injured in the attack by polish
First Armory
Zara
Who pled guilty
Dangerous driving
Beating his wife
Domestic violence
Is
Always also weirdly
Abby UK they've gone on the record saying that they want
Nothing to do with them
Babes
The fringes of our politics are Nutters
And we don't want them anywhere near us
Consider that you are
Yeah they also have a lot more
Connections
The van
Either wants
They just sort of getting
Sing with Alex Jones
Is interview with David
We can argue over
Semantics
Because you absolutely
Cuz you're
Your underlying philosophy
He with so many of these
Is
Whiteness
Always
I feel threatened by others
The three things that I was brought up were
Marine Le Pen
We talked about that already
Not Britain first
Now we have this article
But Alex is referring to
About
How we need to
Social media
Will decide elections from now on unless conservative
Alex brings this up about 5 times
I never mentioned
The guy
You never says his name
Probably so anyone listen
I looked into it
No guy named nail nail
It's Neil but it's
Iall
Ferguson
He's a British guy
And his argument is essentially
That
From now on
Social media will not allow
People
Music
Like Trump did
If you want to make that argument
Because
Has Trump used it
Illegally
He'll be much more careful about the influence of Cambridge analytica micro-targeting Bluegreen
I hope so I don't know
Conservatives are going to Bear the Brunt
Of
The changes that happen
Probably true
But you'd hope
More important
Things to note about
Ferguson
There's a real problem the problem with Cambridge analytica
Is that
They are
F****** Brillion
They're one of the few examples of the right
Being
Really killing the future
Unfortunate
Politically
Do you know anything about Niall Ferguson
I don't
Alex Epstein his name spelled and I've been
Furious
Just hit that
Alex a sighting in
That's already
Citing him
No no
I'm out in 2015 Neil Ferguson Road in biography
Henry Kissinger
Call DaVita idealist
It's a flawed peace
Historical revision
Contemporaries and historians write it off as historical trash
Simply 1000
Page Plus
Peace dedicated to rewriting
Kissinger's Legacy
You know it's at the
The thing
Kissinger is like
Every claim
That they make about Soros
Reasonably consider about
Well you need to do more research but you can probably get some
The broad Strokes
But be that as a manager was really really
What was the case in reality
Alex Jones
Harriet's kitchen
And this guy
Rodent authorized biography
Kissinger
Exactly
Then
He was very in favor of the Iraq War
That's not good in 2003 New York Times calling for American Empire
Including the following Passage
No quote
So long as the American Empire dare not speak its own name so long as it continues its tradition of organized
Hypocrisy young men and women will take one look at the prospects for post-war Iraq
Talk about my voice don't even go there
No Americans need to go there if the best brightest insist on staying home today
Imperial project may end
Unspeakably tomorrow
But he's
His entire offense
Is about like
The news from 2000
It's all about like hey
Let's keep this up
See it through
You understand how the British colonial life people
I can do it
Savannah in December 2016
Neil Ferguson
Who also is a writer for foreign policy
Alex Jones's globalist publication
Frustrated is written for them since
Article titled the Russia problem
The burning question of American politics
How far the Russian
It was successful in its efforts to influence the outcome of November's presidential election
No longer in
Serious dispute
Russian hackers
Especially access to emails of the Democratic National Committee
Wikileaks acted as the conduit
The resulting email Dobson leaks
Probably reinforced voters negative views of Hillary Clinton
A little bit later in the article
Quote in the end it's not for the United States to solve the Russian
That is Russia's
But by re-establishing the Kissinger
That the United States
Should be closer to eat
Then they are to each other
Ministration could take an important step
Towards cleaning up their geopolitical math bequeathed it by Barack Obama
In 2016
After the
He's espousing
A kissing Jerry and lion
About
Geopolitics
Hey bro
This guy is a globalist
You know what
Here's how Despicable that guy is
Kinda believe in Globe
Alex sucks
History is 3 news stories for the day
And also
French the French
Government doesn't have the same free-speech laws that we do
Defending a British
Fascist organization
And then the third guy
Is a huge proponent of Kissinger and a fan of the Iraq War
Current day
I hate everything
He says
Right
Anyway
They don't have any idea
No but it's fun
They don't mean
It's so fun for me when Alex is citing all these people and then you see their history is like
You don't give no printables
Go to court
Frustrated
Alex Jones gets a little bit esoteric
Can enjoy that
Okay good
You freeze nurazzo
I should say
You didn't call until
Freezer on
I should be clear
I forgot to step
ShopRite
Alex is talking about there's a startup that that's coming up it's like we can put your brain
Cloud but it's a hundred percent fatal and everyone's clown
Stupid
This is what I
Alex read transmetropolitan
So he's getting into how like
They just want
Kill you
Electrochemical and die once the electrochemical
Resuscitated
Is a dimensional spiritual Force
At the six Dimension jump
In your mind that's how people that will predict
The future
Always
Which FaceTime
It's electromagnetic
Frequency
And then that's only third dimension
At the very least for tonight you understand
The time is
The fourth
I think what you don't
Is the your brain is a joke
Date
Bow Wow's
Interdimensional
None of that
That's all
Lure
I guess
That's what I would say I don't know what the
It's just all kinds of
YouTube videos basically after
Abid like
The thing that I think is really fascinating
Cuz all that
It's pseudoscience
It's the line between pseudoscience and the ravings of a mad
Bananas
But the thing that I think it's
Like
Can't
Thought
So he's like your brain goes through a jump
Japanese are famous for especially the women
Baby everybody knows a ride
Really far away
Would constantly have to fly 2000 miles
Because they got a premonition that their keeper was scaring my mind
I don't think
They can't delegate
Hittite
Look I don't think
Most
New cell phone most
You could have just called
Most aborigine population
That exist
Still to this day
Don't need to travel 2000 MI
Always
They're very busy
Salt
Earlier
Jordan in this episode
I talked about how Alex Jones
Inside information
About the author
Boston bombing
And that was that was on the 30
Mary comes
To the 15th
Some news
Alex
Validates
That's an earlier report
Take a listen
That's not good
Sources at the bottom side
Involved
Directions
Austin
Unfortunately
With that.
On the site
Wait
But you said they were constructed
They're constructed on the porch and then you can't move them
Cuz once you move them they explode right
And that he says that talks
In Austin this is
Confirming that
Going to read to you from an article in Fox
Austin
How's it going
By Wednesday afternoon police had taken down tape and opened up oldfort Hill Drive that's where 17 years
Drelen Mason lost
After
Bringing in a package
An opening it inside his kitchen next to his mom
Quote I heard this loud boom it woke me up the walls of the house that Jesse washing
Nextdoor neighbor Neighbors
Do you understand it like what he's saying is apps
Absolutely literally contradicted by the information that has come out
You can't move them
Eddie thought this was
This confirmed it the case is
Weird
It was the most movable
Such nonsense
I just I don't understand
Understand he's grasping at
We have one more click left
Play an Isaac
His real son
It starts pain
And then we get a sense
I don't like
I wish you would just stop it
It starts
You know that that whole like
Rite-Way
Complaint whenever there's a school shooting
That like you would mediately turn it political
I'm going to spoil this a little bit
Want you to spoil is a little bit
So earlier today in Florida there was a bridge
Yes I recall people passed away
How fast Alex
Political do you get that that's not even wait for it
Situation
McDonald's inside
Of the information War if Alex Jones
950 John
Pedestrian bridge collapse
Our prayers go out to everybody and that's too bad
Are in the Washington
Cars
BMV
Avenues in hours
Well
Gone forever
Bridge
Highway
Killed
The people
In Florida
According to that broken logic
Of course we didn't tell him
Quercetin
Into a anti-gun regulation message
In like 12 seconds
And also
Logic doesn't
Because you know what would help with these Bridges
Is type
I think it probably be like people everything needs to be up to code to needs
Bee inspection
Of bridges
Who are actually building it need to be licensed
Those are things
So actually
By his own words
Skis kind of advocate
Elations Alex you're stupid
F******
Unbelievable
Even come
Close to understanding
Wyatt is
Bridgewood color
That's crazy
What's think about wire bridge collapse
Okay
Let's start from the beginning
Alright you're building a bridge
Really afford to replace
Haystack Bridge
To the level that you
You need to cut some corn
Cutting
How do you cut costs Dan
Low beds
If your government was funded better
You'll be able to afford
To do the
F****** right in the same way
The reasons they were in the situation that we are right now with infrastructure
Is because I went the New Deal happened there was a ton of money for infrastructure work and Roads
Pretty strong Bridges and now it's been
70 years
You know it's bridge collapse in Miami is going to be indicative of
More Bridge collapses that are going to happen
Debbie still use meat
Harbinger of things to come
Personally shutting down the New York to New Jersey
Trainline
Like he's doing that just because they
Is what like
15% of our
Economy that is
Elves
Hostage by him.
Doing this bridge
There's so much
Of this that is
Exactly what the New Deal
Was in response
Capable of dealing with some
Something
Preemptive
Cast
Stupid, disaster and then America's like
Oh
I got it
4 what 40 years before the Great
Depression it was a
Constant
NeverEnding let's cut taxes let's make
Income inequality
Insane as possible
And then once it is
Orderly
We destroyed
America's like oh yeah socialism is great
And then when everything's fine everybody's like oh yeah
Free market is great
And then that f****** destroy the economy and everybody's like
Oh yeah maybe Bernie Sanders
I think this is
I think
Hannibal
Bulshit system that we live in
And the fact that
Let me get back to this
The guy is the best that the Democrats can f****** do
Hannibal maybe a liberal
Disc
She's the best I can do
Maybe if somebody would actually
Both Road
For reality
Maybe people
I'm just I'm just saying that that
But the concept
Democratic party has
We need to be at
Parade of our ideas
If the idea was
F*** yeah
Let's f****** live up to what it is we believe instead of this constant
Mitigation of our Concepts in our ideas
We would f****** win
Maybe the Overton window would be
Closer towards the f******
Center
Instead of closer towards the edge
You can possibly go
Lake Murray Loop
Winning election here
Myalgia
The problem that you have is
Did your rhetoric is that there is no
Exactly
It's not a
Two-dimensional specs
There is there is the right
And there is
Reality
And if you are anywhere near the right
You are as far away from reality as you can
I think I think
At the end of this one
Tragedy that
We're about to befall in all
There will be no
But if there is there will be another
FDR ish
Move
It would help in order to
Everything from the design
After we find our
What we should do is kill everybody over 15 if you were able to pull that off
The next thing
I would hope that we do
Is do it better
Cuz at the end of the new deal
I think we blew it
Adverbs of transition
Immensely
Cause of this very same
Concept 15 coming quality
Bottom line is Alex Jones being sued by a bunch of people who are real
So I can draw on this anymore I got a bit
If you were looking for it I've made a critical mistake in that I had too much Conte
But if you like our show you where I know
At knowledge underscore fighting
3 hours of our podcast and go to iTunes from Facebook
We are on Facebook
Hi if you
You go to
New calendar up there too so you can
Check out to Alex
In history we have a lot of new listeners
Like
It's kind of
Incredible and because
As as ridiculous as this podcast is
It is
Really important
Verily
Anyway thank you all so much for listening I think we're all in agreement
Pringles
Alex
Birthstone colors