Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
And sell this podcast
Somebody who is never heard
Right
Has heard
Very similar podcast
We got a lot of fun
Call Dave
H man
Replying to emails from Dumbo
Full blast
First of all like to give a big shout-out to listener Keegan
I believe he's a technocrat at this point
I'll look over the Patrick's Day weekend
And it was very nice to meet him at always a great time
This is why I brought it up
I'm just sorry I couldn't make it
It baffles me this is not why I brought this up
No I brought up because it was also his birthday
Jordan
He donated on time travel level a while back and one of the things you wanted was a drunk Alex Jones
And it turns out even though we are another episode for him
I'm able to sense he was in town this weekend
Honor him with this episode that we're going to be doing today
But first
I have to honor all of our listeners
I haven't even taken a sip of the wine then already grandiosa
So I told you on the last episode that episode we would begin
The March Madness bracket
Of Alex Jones drops because we have a lot in
Front of us and I didn't want to overwhelm you
After your long day at work
I decided we would have one teaser matchup today and on the next episode
The putting out on Wednesday
We'll have a bunch more everybody right off the top two I don't want all the matchups
Using bet so today we're going to be looking at one match up from one of the quadrants there's 16
Write for division one of the divisions that we will be looking at today
1 matchup from that
Is the guest division
Okay
We got to get you out of the house are from people who are not Alex Jones
The other 12 will be Alex Jones drop
Different variety of XX
Go home and call you
But the selection committee has over long and hard
It's sort of like the people who like the Pope
Service Electric
Number 1 seed vs the number for
Amanda revealing first
The number for recede is Darrell hamamoto gayest instrument
I said the gayest instrument in my collection that I could take to visit the
Esquire Esquire
Absolutely lunatic man number one seed is the gayest instruments
Which you accurately predicted
Is Steve pieczenik it's not go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
It's Alex Jones getting a manners lesson from Steve pieczenik
What do you make of this
Going to call me after
Because I've been in the middle of a major storm which was not created
I want you to come
I love it so much
You could ask how I'm doing I think the selection committee what they selling that clip over the go home and
Tell your mother from Alex
Screaming about the globalist
Crispy potato be like hey come on man
I'm a person I'm in the middle of a hurricane
It's better to get out of the first round in this one I
Turning into your mom that I love so much
There will be a pool
That'll last I guess
Monroe maybe twenty-four hours I've been decided yet
Go home and tell your mother
You're brilliant I feel like that would be
Two on the Doobie like us having an Indian Kansas
Jordan I mentioned earlier
Have fun voting
That's my wish for you all earlier that you know this episode
Is God
Nice time meeting with green beer does
We were at the
Tongue turned green
Then I had to walk home with my hand over my mouth
I just didn't want to blend in with the rabble-rousers and passed out on the street drunks at 11 in the morning
Or whatever on the Chicago
The great place
I could
Give the gift
Fulfill this birthday wish of a drunk Alex
On Saint Patrick's Day Saint Patrick's Day I mean Saturday
Now it's just never show on Saturday so I watched Friday in like maybe he's going to get the booze going early
Nope
Buddhist Parable he just have to punch people on to talk about how they're all being censored and all this nonsense
Then that way doesn't have to talk about his own
Crowder
United suck
Thank you so much for not suing me for the things that I did actually Bedford that I'm almost there
As luck would have it
God smiled down upon us
Alex
For reasons unknown
Decided to go into the studio and do a special report on Saturday
And I have
Almost
No doubt that he's drunk
Out of context drops from that episode
I can do this
Give you a little bit of the flavor of things
Is titled
Hillary about to be indicted by a lake
The precise title was because it's
It's inappropriate if I don't give you the
Precise title
Cuz it's just that
Important like this is a salacious as title
Here it is Special Report
Trump set to indict Hillary
We're already off to a lie
Yeah it is
It specifically about the McCabe
Andrew McCabe being fired is going to lead to Hillary's indictment
I've so we'll see how much you talked about that
I don't know what to do
Expect anymore but
Starts with 20 seconds of Silence
Alex Jones looking off into just looking off into
The middle-distance 4/22
Hear that silence
That's the silence
All the tyrants in history
He thought they were a vegetable
Thought their people
Who ended up getting shovels in the dirt
You know I became a student of History
About 67 years old
Time Life books
Encyclopedias around the house mouse about World War 1 the old west
He's like that about
Channel 1011 Auburn College level
Causal textbook history
Books written by Julius Caesar
Beloved
You're not
You're buying a book on IC Germany
Yes that's when I knew how ignorant
General Public
If you buy a book that's not a no
Rise and fall of the Third Reich
Cheers
Sadoff Hitler's Mein Kampf my struggle you must be for Hitler
Respond
Winston Churchill
3 volume set history of the English-speaking people
British crown
Which is really a
Transylvanian crown
Flying under a German crown the saxe-coburg-gotha
Of the formally established now-defunct austrian-hungarian Empire
It would be from
What's wrong when you capture
Wow that's a drunk
Yeah just rattling off work
Because you don't you don't even know
English crown comes from
I would come from
Transylvania
I don't know if you know that or not
Who said that
I am a vampire
These people at the bookstore were more like
Are you old enough to be reading this please and some pretty heavy stuff
The order of the deaths
Yeah he gets the author is wrong there too and he's referencing those books
A little bit about his claims about the British crown
Because there's some problem
With the historical
Didn Transylvanian crown
No it doesn't it doesn't do that I can I can affirm the crafted not
DuckTales
FairPoint
Queen Elizabeth the second is currently the holder the crown of England
Not that good
Yeah yeah yeah
Can't turn into a bat while people be like in contact with the air
Queen Elizabeth the second current holder of the crown
For her father George
The 6th was king before that his brother Edward the 8th was King for under year and had to Advocate because he wanted to marry a lady
We've been divorced twice and the court deemed her unfit to be the consort of the king
1910 witches
Before World War 1
This is interesting because
Yes
I promise everything is going to come full circle
Vlad the Impaler Alex is going to look very stupid because people were not really enjoying
In the mid-nineteenth N George the Fifth change the name of his branch
His house from the house of saxe-coburg and gotha
Do the house of Windsor in 1970
Is it a wise decision that you made about three years into World War
Perhaps the most grisly war of all-time most people blame the Germans for
The Belgian wing of the house decided on how you feel about that
Scraps
The Belgian Winger the house change their name a few years later for exactly the same reason
Think of Germany
Was upon me
House of
Saxe-coburg and gotha and they'd wanted that appearance to be
As moot as possible
Is its name as well
From saxe-coburg
Alright
It does have German roots
I'm looking for screen as hell
The house of saxe-coburg-gotha does have a Germanic Roots as does every house
Because
There were a bunch of
Germany didn't exist as a nation-state until 1871
There were just a bunch of Regional family and some of them in Turlock
And some of them created larger houses
Yeah just a little fi
Increase their power
Beds
Crown family has always
Kind of avoided
What is the fact that
They're related to just about every other Crown family
Hundreds of years between
Tons and tons of people
It just so happens that they had like released
Strategic and selective marriages in order to consolidate power
Here's the thing
The Sak
Emma title SAS
My name is a reference to Saxony the state modern
Eastern Germany Medieval Times
Become the UK along with the angle
What are the term Anglo-Saxon to rides
That is also where the Black Knight comes from in medieval
Exactly
The Angles and Saxons collectively founded the kingdom of England in the mid
Turley
Hundreds
When Queen Victoria died in 1901 the crown Pastor her eldest son Edward the seventh was a member of the House of saxe-coburg
Coburg and gotha
Through his father Queen Victoria's husband Prince Albert
The ruling lineage went from the it was patriarch Ali handed down
Give me House of sax
Coburg author where is
Hanover
House of Hanover is also aligned
That has German properly called the house of Hanover Brunswick ludenberg
Hanover line
Back in 1740
The first began the Royal lineage of Hanover the crown after Queen Anne
House of Stuart
Which is a Scottish line died without an heir and they picked her second cousin George to take over
So Alex saying has a Germanic root obviously it doesn't that means nothing
He brings in the Habsburg
The empire
Which is just
Just such a distraction on his part
It's just another name for the austro-hungarian Empire which is defeated and Scattered of the many pieces of the end
In 1919
Many Habsburg monarchy
Working currently a Holy Roman Emperor which
Would be confusing
Read that really doesn't mean anything
Exactly the house of Habsburg is also a completely different thing if he was trying to talk about that
Instead of just the austro-hungarian empire
Add House of Habsburg became extinct
Dissolved on November 29th 17
The junior Austrian branch of the houses
Extended SV House of hops
Berg Lauren but this to I
Dissolved in 1918
Did not dissolve because it's
Was secretly apart of the House of Windsor
I am positive also
Conception vet this Empire got
Defeated in World War and wanted to become like it's like
In World War II
Hitler Express
But he hated the Habsburg identity
And he was a harsh German nationalist
He claimed not want to fight in the austro-hungarian Habsburg Army because there was a mix of races and
You could call him
You could call that his struggle
That was a comp
I apologize
The time in my my life where I
Knew that and like
I had memorized those facts
And then I became a person who is like
Victoria
We'll get to that in a second
There's a lot of progeny and a lot of people ended up scattering from there
As you know cuz you're not an idiot
So you sing and it makes me sad I'm German
I'm so in the 16th century Transylvania was absorbed by the Empire and their rulers adopted
Title Prince
Transylvania part of the royal list of acclaim
Until the austro-hungarian Empire dissolved
1918 Daenerys Targaryen goes around and creates like a queen of the unsullied
The unburnt whatever things happened she had things to her royal title
It's really fun whenever it was absorbed the title Prince of France
Sylvania ended up
Becoming part of
A moniker that got
Austro-hungarian Empire
And that doesn't necessarily mean there's a
Like a genetic connection or even a passing down of a crown
Come from
I'll tell you what I'm going to go with
Bulshit
In 2011 Prince Charles said in an interview that he was a descendant of Vlad the Impaler which started the rumor Mills running and he should be named
King of Romania which experts viewed as a Preposterous idea
There's no evidence of Charles is playing
And it's more than likely that he just said it because he was in Romania at the time and because he owns a summer house there and he's active
Live with the mihai eminescu trust a British charity that works preserve rubbing his Saxon history
It could also be
Because Prince Charles
Is a lunatic
He's also
Kind of love him he's a horrible racist monster
So also the confusion comes from the fact that the last king of Romania King by Kohls
The great-great-grandson of Queen Victoria
Which makes
Third cousins
Queen Elizabeth
Because of colonialism in the way that people would just like
You know I'm I'm a prince of England I'm going to marry a princess in Russia or something like that
Weird connections that would end up happening
You can find like
If you just
Dig deep enough you can find
Connections all over the
He is the great-grandson of Queen Victoria
The great great great great
Great-grandson of Otto the first king of Greece
The first modern king of Greece
I hear Spain has a
The king I'm like
Beckett be real functional monarchs
I understand there
Imaginary
Still like
For sure
You know we could go with like
Did that lady who is on suits
Who's marrying one of the princes is now the great great great great granddaughter of Queen Victoria
Order child will be the great great great great great great granddaughter
For Sun
Queen Victoria
Popular like you could you play this game all day long but what it really comes down to is astray interview the Prince Charles at
And the fact that when Transylvania was absorbed
As a region by
The austro-hungarian Empire The Prince of Transylvania title
Breathing part of demonic
That's f******
Exhausting way too much information
The rest of the clips won't have nearly as much
Constantly be getting into biblical lineages at this point Victoria begat
I'm sorry Alex
Is also going to claim
And he was one of the 300
Fighting against
British tyranny or whatever it is
Possible he's a f****** lunatic
So if he gets even crazier
I learned it
Lazy people
That's great.
Like you didn't actually have them
Race memory
And that's why in 2018
Without even wanting it
Long pause
I have a sickening amount of power
Thesaurus crowd of the globalist
So
This is
Certified
To the races in terms of like
I'm tariff
I'm terrified this is very much about
Hillary Clinton being indicted we're already right into it we're digging into the reasons that she
You going to be indicted
You know what my theory is
Dracula like Fox News
Keep talking about Hillary
Is because the campaign was
So good for them.
Have to deal with what a piece of s*** is
Present
I think there's a part of that
Kansas of the good
What's a loser in adulthood but you are a star quarterback and you like flashback
Potential
And now you work at your dad's
Metaphor for Trump
Used car dealer you remember when he was out there throwing bombs
Just downfield
Lavender we need to unpack Alex Jones's idea that you super powerful
Is the super powerful
Because he's
Smart
Because his knowledge that other people don't have
Like the fact
Dracula gave birth
Do Prince Charles in a roundabout way
Controls Drac
Exactly the lawsuits against Alex are fake
And then it spirals out of control into him realizing it
Saint Patrick's Day
He said some other stupid s*** about history
Congress
Presidents
Connected
Please.
Now that means
Renaissance in American Reawakening is commanding us all
But as
2.0 visuals
Open the universe
They don't even get the
Show me sad
Saint Patty's Day
Wearing green
My daughter
Your mommy
Park Cafe hours
That's really weird that's a really weird thing to say
Actually for green shirt earlier wear my green shirts around all but
I love that I'm not trying to patronize.
The reason so you guys
Don't know that I couldn't find my green shirt
I just told you
Whiskey inmate I called Rob do and showed up over here working on a schedule
Is it look what the Irish went through everybody else has gone through under Imperial Brett
It's not a British conspiracy
It's corrupt leads to conquer powerful Britt
Use the power of those tribes
People
I was laughing around Technologies of control
Power the world
Rogue forces
Ability of
The modern
System
Doughboy
Follow the money
Fact
Yeah it's really
Very prosperous Society because they had a very
Strategic places
The port has Genoa came to prominence that sorta fell apart there were other options
Stranglehold
Ted Nugent
D.c. Commerce
And what have you
That's a really interesting. Whenever those guys start going crazy at 8 at each other
City-states
In Italy gold shops along with
You know
Where does the pope come from
From which one
Get the pope and then they all go f****** fight each other about the pulpit
Pope's going on
Under counter counter counter
Yeah as I loved it and Italy's history
As a unified
Today is not that old
Still kind of
Not great
I mean if you really look at it wasn't even a Republican
Cancel 1946
So it's that is recent as a
Sort of democratic
Existing
Italy is good he was under fascist rule before that
Friends before that right
E46 Berlusconi had his first bunga-bunga celebrated
Scared
F***** everybody in his alien they became a republic
Because he f***** everybody
Exactly
So black nobility
Nobility
Black nobility is just a term that's used to describe Italian in Italian because of the time
. but in the area of Italy
Aristocratic families who sided with the Pope
Kingdom of Italy
Came into Roman overthrew Pope
Pius the 9th
In 1870
That's what the black nobility was people who sided with
The papacy over the state of
Because Pope Pius was a piece of s***
He was f****** garbage
Exactly the kind of thing that Alex Jones
Super against was corrupted who is monstrous and who was apparently
Just
Destroyer
Able to do into the idea of the black nobility and what have you
Leads back to a bunch of theories about to howdy Venetian oligarchs
The black nobility who is becoming black nobility were comprised of
You're about avocados hours
No
The name is applied to a semi-nomadic group of
Descent
Yeah I thought that is not related to the Cossacks
I don't know I don't think so I don't think it's a Pacifica.
It's very popular in a few somatic and anti-zionist circles
But slightly less popular and academic ones that the
Because our bloodline or
Case if you make a one-to-one comparison d-black nobility the Venetian oligarchs
I thought that bloodline is responsible for the ethnogenesis of us
Eskenazi Jews
Not that it's not very real
That's one of the reasons why Alex
Third of compelled towards these ideas
Cuz you get into the idea of like the black nobility
As a historical entity but also
It wasn't like it wasn't some Grand conspiracy that still lingers to this day
I think that is the case in a lot of conspiracy theory worth
But at the same time you get these ideas
And in all this like these evil
Extra Vatican entities with a lot of this cannizzaro
Or idea that I have time to unpack right now
Have a
Do you think we'll ever have a black pope
Like not but I mean like a boy
African descent
I don't think so he's not Catholic
That's a first problem
That is an issue
What is an issue
I don't know everybody I think I need to ask
I think eventually we may get there but who knows
The world probably doesn't have enough time
Black nobility in
Probably a dog whistle to
Anti-semitic ideas about the roots of
Ashkenazi
But be that as it may
Alex
Famous Mexican meinkampf at 11
Insist you're not enough
Everything you believe
You know eyes
Egypt
Of the Rothschild family
Is almost exclusively from Nazi propaganda
I was going over the Friday episode
Cuz I was going to initially go over Friday
Episode
But
It did not
End up making
In the cut we have big narrative on Friday
Is that
The
This church in Australia is not allowed to
Disabled Jesus
In there are in a banner that they put up
The great narrative that really covers the big issues of our time
He's taking this
He's taking this from a Daily Mail article and I went and looked at the Daily Mail article from it here
Claimed Lend-Lease what's the name of the mall or the company that owns them all
Requested to withdraw the word Jesus from assign as a suspended Shoppers and non-Christian
Pastor David said Lend Lease has to change their mind and allow the word Jesus to be included in the sign
In a statement the Lend-Lease spokeswoman said that they regretted asking for the sign to be amended
It was an error of judgment to ask Elam Church to change it to messaging a tweet
Apologise unreservedly
That's in the actual article that Alex is reporting
I don't trust him to do anything
I don't trust him to know about history
Based on his inability to read an article
You can't expect anybody to read all the way to the third paragraph
Forever
That's his reading comprehension at-44
I don't fucken want to know what it was it
Fix I don't know I don't know what I
How Abel he was to parse
The language of a monstrous
Future dictator and his anti-semitic vision of the world
Is a six-year-old
Or even is at 10 year old
I don't want to f****** no he can't do it
That's not good
The other job
He described that job in this next clip
And then he said some other explain
Look at me.
And so I'm here
Trying to explain this stuff really works
From their own admission
And they think you're such fools
He'll just tell you doesn't exist but look at you
Heaven wants to told me Alex they'll never listen to you
In fact
Will tear you apart for warning them
Grainger Supply
Can I play the globalist
Hollow Earth stopped revolving
Cannot join them
So
Fairy
Disassembly
Warn all of you that the decision
Andrew
McKay
Does bring it up
What is media Access Control
Sure just political hacks putting Power by Bush senior in Bush
Obama and the clintons
Covered up all the crimes the Communist Chinese takeover of America
Makeup
The Conjuring of country
What else
When American Embassy Patrick's Day
The Gallows
From the neck until dead
Before that switch.
The floor open
Country forever
Providence show today
Face again
Space again
Just that to me is
Boy
I don't know what time he recorded this at but no time make sense
Well the only way you can say it like if you think Trump is the face of Providence
F****** face
Is the face
Of Providence
We did not
Enjoy that it came in this for
Looked
It's just all bad
McCabe
Trigger into the media personalities are presidents
Yep place in order to lie to us about the Chinese takeover also
One of his big narratives that he's pushing right now is that Apple has moved all of the cloud keys to China
And we discussed
Before you moved
The Chinese kids today
The Chinese government has access to it
Entire world
Right now
Chinese
Government has a real bad history
Onboard
Onboard I'm with you there
That's not a great
That's the biggest reason why capitalism
Really needs to be regulate
Because Apple has that opportunity to be like
No it turns out
Like realistic
Apple
Is
Capable of being stronger than the Chinese
Then the Chinese government realistic
They could draw
Now go f*** yourself
And then China would become
Essentially North Korea like they would have to develop all of this s*** on their own but they probably would probably be successful
Connected to the rest of the world
A much more isolated place
Most likely go
And it starts to collapse
The size of
Like that's one of the big things about their control is that
If they are connected
To the outside world
Control a much larger
Yeah North Korea was as large
Just tryna it would have collapsed a million years
Absolutely
Be a dictator over that
Without like a amended version of
Without the
Tacit approval of everybody else based on your
That's what it comes
To save it like everyone's complicit with
The Chinese government in like
To a certain extent I don't
Totally
The other piece of it that goes beyond the complicit part of the univet economic picture that your drawing is that
A war would be ridiculous
Like that would be absurd would be the only way to deal with
You know
The actual human rights
Horrible record
Imagine
If
Global Corporation
Actually they really cooked
Its Global corporations
Their own
There's nothing anybody could do over
That's interesting
Nothing anybody could do about it I would I would I would
You just said is a refutation of the idea of globalization
Exactly because if that centralized organized group that Alex pretends he's fighting against
Really existed
They already have done that
So that's interesting that reality that
In all honesty maybe one of the things that is protecting us is unregulated capitalism
Insofar as
If corporations actually wanted to become their own Nation
There would be nothing to stop them
At this point in time
If if they wanted to
No one could stop
There's no stopping their economic power if they decided to become one block
Then we would have a global government essentially
Interesting thought
Alex
I think we're in a couple of bean bags
To realize that a corporation could become a state
Alex wants to stress how important
Times are
He is unable to put it into words
Probably cuz he's Daedra
Providence showed it
Already off to a bad start
Face again
Smiling
Patient
With fake hair
Pulling us back
Racist
And just a spirit of
Life of spirit of success.
Joyce.
Future endeavors
That is dead
Really like future endeavors it's fun to use that terminology because that's like
You know it went wrestling when you get fired you get future Endeavor menology like we look forward to
Future endeavors
You have a Culture of Fear like
That terminology is always used in a in a firing
Future endeavors
Came back in the world like a son
Cutting through
The Tempest
And that's what we all right
Destroying you can feel the energy
Literature
Tectonic
Shifting
Seal
All the old scores all the old battles
Repercussions
Percussions
Drums
We can always help
Where is an amazing moment
Industry right now
I struggled before I do these life is like
Your mind Dua
Articulate the gravity
The importance
Historical nature
The timer
Secretive
Quarterly
I f******
Love
That like
If Alex was a stand-up
One of his b
That would get the audience I can get her done
Don't know how
To express the Majesty of the
Subs
Stars aligning in solarwinds
Coming through launching off on a soliloquy using all this grandiose f****** language while sitting idle
Don't know how to describe how important these times are
Is a term for storm is actually
I don't think I was even a reference
Quotes from Donald Trump
Then if you're paying
If you're paying close attention
The event
The big old drink
So here we are
Watch WhatsApp
I always go with my gut
Play Slash.
Oh my God
Everything okay
Call masala
I'd like to study
You know I used to remind myself
Obsess over things with
The deepest thing I ever did was
Start going with just my
First assumption
That was the cheapest thing in my life
So I want to read the actual Trump quote
This is from his book think like a billionaire
Personally
Easy for him to write he has a
Great
Attention span
The actual quote is the day I realized it can be smart to be shallow was for me a deep experience
Different than what Alex is suggesting
Because what he's saying
Sometimes
It's advantageous
To just use your basic
Impulse
How much superficial distrust is reading comprehension
She doesn't know what the word quote mean
Right because Alex
Who's presenting it is like
It's
Deep to be shallow
Or something like that like
In there
Anyway let's finish this
See if you can figure out where he takes a drink
A shower
People didn't get
Halcyon
What
They thought his a*******
The cheapest thing ever
It's right here
Do you have a room
You heard him swallow
Georgia woman's intuition
Funny after he takes a big Pole from that whiskey he's like
Olivia woman
Doesn't get more obvious that it's a mixed drink with ice
Have the second camera to cut away to actually I have snapshots of it
He's going under the desk
Cuphead takes
F****** pull off it
Never take from a water cup
It's
0 chance and there's actually a part of me that like got really sucking
A tutorial as I was watching
Drink
He side-eyes the camera
As if to say
Come on Alex
Isaac
We have the courage to drink live realistically what it was was that he was taking the drink
He didn't realize there wasn't a camera to go to
To the cameras more I look of like
I'm on I'm on are clearly
I've never seen him do this before he takes the drink and slides it to like we're just out of camera frame
I'm in front of him
Play Kyoto Rob do comes over and collect it from
It's not it's very weird
So anyway you taking to drink
He asked about women's intuition will pick up right there
Ignored your woman's intuition
Women consciously
Statistically are men at making decisions
Decisions about how to buy robbed
Intuition about Street smarts
We balance that out together
So in closing here I just want to say
So in closing
He's already closing
She has mentioned Makeba once in passing it on reporters
Spoiler he's not but
Buzz
Get wasted
You going to stay out there a little bit
Oh yeah you got a ride this out
Good classical Western chauvinism
I love solo
Kia of applying stick
Statistics
To what women can
Can do on the bed
Battlefield
As though
It's been something that they have had
Controlled experiment
No it's not it's not like there is an equal representation
Visitation there 2X
Viable
Measure of
Statistic
Alex
Stupid
That's light
Statistically
Women
If they're on their. They're going to lose their uterus whenever they try and
Let's just true facts
Statistically
So many women
Uterus is just Fallout
I mean for me right now I find his chauvinism a little bit boring
I don't know I just I don't even want to engage
I keep dreaming of it as well
Whiskey on the rocks
And he's like I don't want to talk about the thing I'm supposed to
We talkin about
It's not
No mixed drink I
Right now
Present
Oh that's interesting
To make you feel as though I drink it straight
Yeah
You're probably right you probably a silly boy who pretends to drink black coffee
We are taking it back I said it would never happen we're taking it back
Starlight
It's not going to work now
20 second experiment
Flo-Jo
In the last
If you want to go back a couple months
Trump saying he's a globalist
Just look at the last month or so we had Trump saying I like chicken
Morgan's early
Yeah we had him
Suggesting that maybe he should
Be president for life
Drug dealers make you should get the death penalty
Set alarm things pretty counter to Alex's
Philosophy
Inception but talk a little bit about the gun stuff
But he could have pushed
Woodside in Saginaw
Machiavelli
12 Alex
Explain the
He's always wrong
Whenever he Quest
Show enclosing here
I have watched Trump in a
Compendium
What he's done
Can always when something looks like a betrayal
It turns out that the opposite
Not going with my gut
Shoes just so I could
Feel like I was being fair
That's why
So they get one
Like salad
Turn right
And all of the setup
Criminal Network
Evident
Inside
The jesters.
Haven't paid for fake dossier Zentorno at workout
That sound
It's Alex finally got to McCabe here a little bit the timeline of the Fusion GPS
And the donations from McCalla to McCabe's wife
Run
Don't match up the timeline doesn't match up
All this narrative is
Pretty wack
But Alex is saying that it's all over the news now
That McCabe made
He's a subordinates change their
302 form
Which of the forms of the FBI uses to report on interview
Suspects or Persons of Interest in what
Well feel like I would know if it was all over the news it's being reported in Gateway
Way pundit
Oh yeah well then
And I went and check that out
Fans that one source on that
Completes
They're put out
By Mike cernovich
Mike cernovich has source
Anonymous source
So I don't have to hold off on this one way of trying to get Flynn off the hook
Right that's exactly what they're doing
Attack the Mueller probe
So anyway I don't really care it's not
It's not in the news
But also
I don't think that Alex should be
Critiquing Trump
Funny says really f***** up stuff
Because he wants to appear Fair
I think you should be attacking Trump because Trump is saying things that run counter to his beliefs
Canto
He is a f******
Sycophantic
What a pathetic little
For somebody
Still disappointed
At the very least
Prior to trap
He was
Trying to be an iconoclast
He was trying to be the only guy who is doing what
With a little country music
He's trying to be himself
Now he is trying
He's actively trying just by that clip right there
Wendy's contractor not be
Every time that I disagree with Trump
I'm wrong
He's trying
To be a little bit
Yeah yeah
Have
F******
Backbone anymore
Pathetic
Yeah and it's really sad because like
If things go the direction they are
Cure to be going
And
I don't know let's say Trump does fire Mueller
He will text you earlier I put it in a 94
Against the advice of literally everybody anywhere near him
3 a.m.
If we do see those sorts of things we we are at we are seeing the deter
Curation of
Civil government
Not like civil government meaning like you
Just be
The idea that we can govern
Yeah
Is being De Pere right in front of all right
And the idea that I would like a mouth
That pushes for and apologizes
For that
When that's so counters everything he stood for for the last couple decades
It's particularly sad it's so pathetic that
He
For whatever reason
Maybe money
Maybe blackmail
I genuinely don't know it
Tell me something real powerful those a drive that's really really powerful
And I can't just be like
Maybe
Maybe it's syphilis
Have we considered that
He's just
Lonely at this point like
That like you can get Rob to come down to the stereo on St Patrick's Day
I mean
He has tried to avoid aligning himself with a movement
That exist
Do you know like the Teto
Really
Cuz he's always been a Ron Paul guy
Community there
And 911 truth
He's always had a really secure place within that
That world
I don't know I don't think
And the truth is Dracula calls 911
Stroop
He was a town
Turn into a bat
Yeah I don't know man it's it's really f***** up and the more we think about it the last we know
But
Something good come out eventually
Anyway
We can we can speculate about
The reality of the world all we want
Globalist
And Patriots
Not true
No it's not
You might be asking yourself
Who's ahead
Is it
Or the Patriots
Is this like one of those
Go to a basketball game and they have the Dunkin Donut racing
The milkshake or whatever the f*** I would rather it be that
To be like
We're here we're here I love it the audio of it
No Lie
Comprehensive video you're not missing any
Is
Everyone knows that I don't
I think I was super Peter Gunn
Now
Falling apart Alex
Not what I had
Because in the time-space
But let's say they're this far ahead
We're like Warp
Right now
I can cook them
100 Years of global ocean robber barons the British Empire population
To get up here
And just in five years we're just that's why they're like
Don't know what to do
Easy cheesy analogy
They already blown up
New
Skynet
Stop
And and we're basically
What
Getting this this system of globalism all businesses tell people jokes
Weird that's why the energy so high it's why they're so painting
What are they going to launch
MX6
I don't know
Yeah probably will see we'll see what your periods are about that
Weird
Cuz you talk to me what it is
He thinks he say
I think he thinks
You saying
That in order for the globalist
To succeed at this point they will have to go back in time
Yeah
They'll have to send someone back in time to kill young Alex Jones
That's not a bad idea
I guess he thinks he's
Jon Connor for woodwork
Is that is that right
Yeah and the globalist have Arnold on their side
Yeah until the 2nd
Okay they're secretly movie
I don't know I have no idea how to re watch Terminator
I don't know
I always find
Like we kind of distasteful because it's always
It's very much it's very much
Him
Constantly trying to keep you on your toes you know like there's always
We're winning in because we're winning
And then it's like
Well maybe we're tired and we're losing right now in order to win
That's not always
There is a losing
Is always be able to
Succeed
I need that money because it's getting food like crazy
But in the next help me settle my lawsuit with laundered money
Paint
Globalist oppression
People would think the government
The persecution
Then offered all the former employees money alive
Hillary's people
None of that is what happened
Not the government and Georgetown is not the one
What's Brandon Gilmore
No he's not in play and also
If anyone is giving
Talking to ex employees of Alex
I'm saying like will give you money
Some sort of like
Protect you from your MBA
Yeah or something like that disclosure agreement you signed when you work
Write get around that right now offering people
Thirty pieces of silver to turn on Jesus
Nda's do not protect
Yeah but there's probably a lot of embarrassing
Stop people want out that's not quite a crime
Maybe journalists are asking them about
I believe that
Alex Jones committed a crime
The ndaa doesn't cover crying out there who used to work at Infowars know about 425 Supply
Hit us up cuz that's a crime for real
Anna left thinks I'm like them like that miso
Usher
I go towards the attack
Do
Change the world
Insincere
Expressing how every
Time
He brings up something
Where is like
They think I have a bank
We didn't think that
And you're really stressing about how much he's lost after going to cost you when you settle them
It's like
You're the unhappy why are you saying
So obvious
Absolutely it's so obvious
Episodes from couple years back
Having a blast talking about the globalist
Metallica coming out of the break
Now in 2018 a decade later convincing himself
But he's important that he has power but he's happy
That we can get both
I don't know I can do this anymore
And I'm the happiest I've ever been in the same context of the I can't do this anymore either.
Alright
Is it level starting
Couple years ago
This is like Patrick
Top retired General
Halo CIA
Transformer
Or people in Hollywood or whatever
What do we do Alex
We're waiting for you to leave Alex what are we supposed to do
What do we do
I thought it was like
And then I realize
Conversations the president dollars
What the President says
Are Spirit strongly I believe in God
Hillside be strong Army Strong
Sweetheart
All of us
Why do young Asian
As long as we love God we're all equal we are better
He's just a lot of strength
Heath Ledger
He understands what's going on he is putting a very strong face on
We going to finish the rest of this clip but I just wanted to buy
Cuz I Alex
The point of Saint Patrick's Day drunk where he's like
You really into talking about God
Keep coming up basically turning into a preacher again
This is supposed to be a special report about McCabe and Hillary Clinton
For everybody
And
It's happening
IPad
Leaders of the most elite military teams are are
Tell me
Alex you're too humble
We're waiting for leadership
What are we supposed to do
It's get down he's talking about
Alex Ezra leader of Seal Team 6
Is that an eagle they're like no you've already done
We understand you for real
And your specialized in this what we do
Sure
That's really sad to me
That's very very sad
Because I think what he's worth selecting on when he's talking about this stuff is you talkin about people like Steve pieczenik
It's ever been like
Steve on the show buttering up his ego like crazy
Clear that he's manipulating
Literally obvious
Easiest person to con in history because
Really wants to be caught
You know what I bet we could fake a fight
Or something like that on one of our episodes where
Pretend
That like
I have been convinced
Did Alex's right
Right then we fake a kind of a fake a couple episodes
Where I'm like doing fake Alex's totally right about stuff
I bet I could get on his show
Globalist
Doesn't mean you're an anti-semite now especially if we did it in the first
Couple minutes of the headline I bet we could I bet
Whitewash the entirety of the last year-and-a-half and he be like
He's very Triple A man who
So now he is become a patriot
I was responsible for album see the light
Even though I would be a hundred percent
And even if having this conversation wouldn't preclude the ability of us to do this in this picture
Relationship
You know how sometimes Alex Jones likes
To say if you understand
This clip you understand every
Kingsley when he's talking about chimeras attention
This next clip
If you understand what's going on in this neck
Text clip you understand everything about Alex Jones
I think this clip
Kind of perfectly sums up
His head space right now
Especially when he's drunk
D'lites
Bite down on this one
Infowars has
Has them scared and what is it
I don't get off
I don't get off at a bigger house
I don't get off on having knowledge I want to share it
That's why they think Trump mentally ill
It's why they say I have a dark heart not a monster
Because you don't give that knowledge people to have this knowledge
You don't give it to the profaned
I instinctively
What knowledge for people that have more than I
And I want to give you the knowledge I have
People
They believe
I can do this anymore
Listen
All I'm telling you is Hollywood
What
This
Is
Everything you need to know about Alex Jones
Word salad nonsense about like this is why
Knowledge and you're not supposed to give it to the uninitiated
Everybody golobulus Cherryville
My wife mad at me
Do this anymore
Long pause
Hollywood is not support
Trail because he gets a text from his wife said he's not happy about
Obviously it's something like why are you drunk at the studio with Rob Duke
Saint Patrick's day was supposed to be hanging out with our kids
Something like that
Thursday Keegan D I can't do this anymore
I don't think it's about the show now I got to go home
I think it's about it
Family is getting in the way of my preaching the truth about Trump
It could go either way that could be like I'm sick and tired of doing this show the way I'm doing it or could be like
Family responsibilities
Anyway
Anybody
Regardless of anything
If you agree with me 100%
Or if you disagree with me 100% or anywhere in between
If you start talking about how the leader is connected
God
I'm out
Oh yeah I know thanks
New god-king
.
It's next level
You know the rhetoric that comes out of the supporters of dictators
Kind of
Even happy
Hockey is a propagandist to do that work
Still works
It's very easy humans are s***
Yeah maybe we should
I mean there's that old demon movement that I mentioned on our route
Anyway
Alex Jones gets into like the Hollywood has nothing for you
Miss transitions into a motivational speech
Kind of get back on topic
And then ends up with even more of a dictator Eli
The whole system has nothing
Feeling insecure
Stop
If he just said that and nothing else
Lovett his listeners
No
Feel insecure
You don't have power
Please
Please Retreat into your own fantasy world
And don't interact
But the power to break free of the conditioning at Alex's putting off to them they're not
Everyone has a chance for a second or third shot
Everyone can be the hero of Their Own Story if they just turned things around a little bit and I wish nothing but the best for you
Is out there but I expect very little
It is that Alex Jones listeners have second act
Problems
That's the issue
If you're going to go with a class
Joseph Campbell and kind of situation a hero's journey of your will
You guys got to figure out how to get past the crisis
Will the problem with psych trying to frame his listeners into like a hero's journey is that by definition
None of them can be the actor in the
The story the protagonist
The antagonist
And you had best AR
Someone is along for the ride
You're just helping out along the road a couple pieces of gold or something like that
Seaquest at Beth
Side quest he answered your phone call
I still like
So desperate in the Alex Jones land
In 2018
That I'm like
I like this and I want a pointed out that I like the idea of Alex Jones saying
You're empowered you don't need all the right stuff in if people just apply it in the right direction I think
Positive message
I think he's going to
Stop
Thinking you have to look outside yourself and God for answers
Because this whole thing.
Trump
Going after
McCabe
His fraud
Yes falsifying
Just running
Oakland
Again
The fact
Trump fired
Is everything you need to know your side
Is real
Trump
And I
Because we believe it's Rob.
We given to Hillary leaving to Michael Moore
Given the Dianne Feinstein of
To the Rothschilds and Rockefellers
We die
We're not fighting them because we want Power
We're fighting on because when we're with them
Underwater
It's spiritual
Strangulation
So real quick before you respond to that I just want to point out that there was a click
In there
You could see his phone
Wife is not happy
But you know that the indictment stuff is all just probably Rodger Stone in a year
It's just the hot talk
In the
The conservative World necessarily
Involved like that everybody
Everybody hot narrative
Really trying to convince themselves that Trump isn't guilty
Okay
Meteor shower
Based on everything that I know about human nature
I would guess
Really
Really doesn't believe he's guilty
But based on everything I know about Trump
In the past
Today's
Really
Really believe he's guilty of money laundering
That's gas
It's so that's why he's going to fire Mueller
Is because this time
There's no way he knows he's not guilty because Mueller has subpoenaed documents
There's no collusion
It's because
Nose
He's guilty of
Some serious consideration I might agree with your 90% assassin
Look
I don't know man
Did the idea that even as a political distraction there would be indictments against like Hillary and Bill
Obama
Right stuff like that like
Do you understand the Powder Keg that's that's all
Like that is an unbelievable shitstorm of
Descent
To tyranny that like punishing your political Rivals a year-and-a-half after an election
Doesn't send a good message
It certainly would be
Tragic Prelude to the
The midterm
What I think
Issue there
Is
That they are jealous
Because
All of those people
Totally committed crimes
That they should be held accountable for
They're better
Getting away
Set the new guys
Ain't there nothing it's not the crimes that
Alex is accusing other crime
Good at it because they hire people who know how to do this s***
And you guys are stupid
Feel like you can just
It like you're like well they can hide their crime so I can hide mine but you don't learn how
It comes from that like inferiority childishness that Alex Express is all the time
Exactly that sort of thing
Right right
It's like it's like you're a kid in school and you see the cool kid
Why can he get away with all the stuff and I can't
You can't get away and still living in that Paradigm for some extent
Go to be like
Hey I'm better at you
And it starts
Just being a statement of fact
Competing with me anymore for me to tell you that your
Because you just are and I'm just
You just make it very clear that we
Don't think
It's good that they are committing crimes
Either I think I think I'm cuz where we are sort of detach idli saying they are more comp
Appleton added doesn't mean we're like
Real they're doing it
I am against all of those people I just I just wanted to make it clear in case we have any new listeners who think like
Thrilled that the Democrats committed
So
Last week a story came out of Believers and vice maybe was BuzzFeed I don't know it's one of Alex's
Usual Target
And they laid out a bunch of times that Trump and Alex have said very similar thing
And it's an important conversation we need to have socially
Not with Alex
Pretending
He is trying to react
To the idea that
He's writing Trump's words
Or something like that
In reality it is just that Insanity has taken over the body politic
Inner discourse
Has become so eroded
Did Alex Jones E-Type speech is okay
And whereas it was not before
And so you can
You can make a pretty clear line of times but it's out in the open
And so out this this one story came out and maybe a couple people did like sort of rehashes of it
The stories talking about that
And people ask why
So many of us are on the same page like a left
Follows orders they follow Scripts
Ideas of the higher-ups come up with
Because I want slice
Not out this vertical
Lego giving speech
At the same time as Jones and they said the exact same thing
They got computers at look at this.
A computer that goes Jones right here
Believe that the speeches
Hornstromp there's a lot of this is original stuff
No
Spirit riding
God doesn't possess it's like solarwinds
So
Videos always articles 100 times
11 *
Stop
I'd love to take
Is it it's that
It's the same page
It's the same sheet of music
Resonates with
And
You Know a Man by his enemies they are so
The only people I see
Publicly panicked
Alex
SAR Alex
Because I
Lumpen
Alex world
I don't see
The msci
Freaking out
He has been for the last two-and-a-half years
Alex don't pretend you didn't make a functional
Giant pivot literally 2 years ago we watched it happen in real time
When you change
Here's my ass
Yeah stupid a******
But like a
I don't admit Italy I don't watch
Being mainstream news that
Msnbc's the CNN's everyday but whenever I see clips of it I don't see people panicked I see people
Boy
Trying to report unbiased Lee and slipping a bit
But at the same time I don't
Atlantic from them
I don't see Panic from Muller I don't see Panic from
Smart
Folks on the left
On Twitter
I think I feel like that
But the
I feel like that
The wrong direction to
Like I think we all should be
Right like that's one of my biggest issues with that concept of unbiased is that
Reality is unbiased in the reality
They're f****** destroying the world
Really quickly
You should be
Because that Panic will maybe incite you to f****** action
I think
Freak out everyday
Living
State of panic
I want to
Fights
Bright
You f****** know how we
Way too large
I think that a lot of people have found a
Complacent stride
Based on the fact
That are going to
The time that it's been going on
Mueller investigation has
Borne fruit
In terms of
Flipping people please
What have you and I think that a lot of people are freaking out because of
The faith
In the system that this is going
To get unraveled right
That well maybe it will maybe it won't but whatever the case
Freakout might need to come around the corner at some point
People are Panic right now the only people that are panicked
IC on info
Those are the people who are panic
Ralix is creating space
Wow yeah
Yeah yeah it's not great
I don't Focus too much on that though cuz I still I still think that's more of a simp
I know Alex is a symptom too but it's like
Alex is more of a primary symptom and I think Trump is a secondary
Maybe that I'm I'm biased
Because of my area
I see Alex
Freaking out about these lawsuit
To the extent that he creates fake versions of them to respond
I see him
Freaking out about the fact that Trump said I want to take the guns first
Maybe we should kill drug dealers
I see him freaking out about those things
I'm pretending he's not freaking out and that he's totally at peace
And what have you and that to me is much more indicative of like
You are
I can't do this
Kind of moment
You know what that moment was to me
Riverwatch Lake Geneva watch Tom Green growing up
So Tom Green Show there was one episode in particular that stood out to me
I never liked him
I didn't think his shows funny
I thought my friends love to be on with smoking weed
I didn't I didn't enjoy him much but it was one moment that always stuck out as like sort of very transcendental
It was an episode where he was sucking on a cow's otter
I'm like in character like sucking on the otter
A man afterwards
Like they were still filming him anyways like
I'm f****** done
Like he was really pissed off in the character broke
There was a moment like why am I doing nothing
That's the moment you see an Alex there with it I can't do this
Mark yeah that's what a gero would cry
On jackass
Ragnar those moments of just like
You can't keep it together
I think that I think that
You're going to see him crack
More and more
Anyway I'm going into a r a we don't need we don't need this
It's a little something
But Rob do
It might surprise you
I don't know if you know about Rob do
You know that he is a
I know his wife is mad whenever you take super male B
Boehner's we know that from 2014
Yeah we also know that he
Clearly is on Alex's beckon call
Yaccarino whenever he needs it becomes a running cuz he knows where his bread is buttered
But it turns out
You know there's a sixth sense
When you wake up my wife
Children
We're doing something
I like think of thought
My little Temple daughter
No
Not a chance
Transcendence
I just want to be part of this good stuff
If your 10 month old daughter is saying the thoughts
But you have
You got terrible
Thought
You're in
Yeah probably but also I love the idea of like
Improv is
I mean you see enough Improv
When you realize it is
Fascinating thing that happens when people are collaborating in the freshly created
Does it does have the appearance of like telepathically communicating
What are y'all doing things well but it turns out it
It's just sort of an artistic Pursuit Thief go in Vibe with each other if you get the right people
Looks amazing
Magic
But also
I love the idea that like
He's sitting with you rob to play
Clarinet
He plays Jazz clarinet Alex either on
I love the idea of Alexandra ten-month-old sitting around and having a great time
Cinema 10 month old is like
I don't know when like
You know the last time I went back I went and hung out with my brother and his family
For Christmas
This last year
And at that point his daughter was about
Maybe get ready
Right
She wasn't
Coming up with sin
Right
Take 6-8 months
Off that age I don't know what unless Alex is like
They're all laughing and having a great time and like them googoogaga
Isn't
I just want to help people I want to be nice
The enemy comes and goes
Don't be a racist don't be a capitalist lookup wasn't healthy
Concha
Also he's comparing I don't be a racist joke from the same set
Daisy Daisy for your position
And I know where Shayne Topp
They know we've already arrived
Those that
We can't get
Who are your serving evil
With realize they're trying to sabotage
Who haven't fully made the decision
They want peel them off and have them go
Is the allegory of Lucifer want the angels to go with him
They just
Not really nice
They want to piss in the Cheerios bro
That's not really an allegory doesn't think it is either
He thinks it's a literal
Very literal get through the rest of this year
He's just turning into a preacher as his
As it's drunk
Gets a
Crescendo
He tries to end the show
And it's really fascinating to little bullet points he wants to get to cuz they are tracking weird
Appreciate coming in Robinhood
I would want it back tomorrow for 6 p.m. central
Lord willing
The justice department is going to indict
Oh so we're finally there
So
The president the next couple weeks
I've never had more peace.
Doesn't sound like a piece of
The fog about
Term doesn't refer to
The peace
It refers to decisions that are made that are not good
Ateez it's referring to the
The f****** unknowable and inability to plan
Morris movie The Fog of War McNamara
Is the most evil
Middle name is strange
How fun is that that's fun
We got this now his only he was a doctor
Kill Trump
In the next couple weeks
Everybody everybody everybody
Literally everybody I guess so
Tell supplies by geopolitics
Quickly and something we've been waiting for for a really long time
And because he's drunk he makes it
Pretty clear
And that is
Tells us exactly what he means by Birthright
Ono Korea's falling
Notary will
Saudi Arabia's falling radical Islamic backing off
Globalist
But it was the Providence
The birthright
You can do this
Come on man
No
No understand
Fallout
And it's at Birthright
Can I get pregnant
Oreo TV
All of you
If you love God
Birthright
And
Except
That's what I'm going to be hate you because
You already won the
Jeffrey Wilson
So that's why they gave this is me
The lottery
And they point out where we've stumbled and where we're not part of
God knows
We're not perfect
But we love God
It's all really just a bad Christian Supremacy
That's all
Yeah
We got the birth White
Yeah it's not even I mean
For him it is cuz other pieces of his cosmology
He believes in did bring in the whites
The mail
Dominated
The ideas but to him the birthright that idea is very
Specifically Chris
Extant
Like in our world
We did hit the lottery
I'm awake dude bright
Like f****** as I was going over
Today a lot of his research about the
Like the Kings and
The various lineages and stuff like that you know you see all of these
The people throughout time who had
Just like Charmed f****** lives cuz they
Happened to be born into the line of Queen Victoria
Or whatever
And you also every time you see one of these people you have to think about how many people headed f****** miserable
And in all of that and how much of that still exists today that dichotomy of
Like
It's lock
You are you
Happened to be born
Even certain circle
But those poor
Oppressed people in China or North Korea
Or even the Islamic terrorists you're so afraid of
Are you
They're all us
You're all them
We just
Happened to be born where we were at the time we were
Edit so
F****** stupid
This idea
Cuz he talks about his Birthright s*** all the f******
Kantime I'm the idea that
Vistana
Is crazy
It's absolutely not
It's
Everything about him
Is infuriatingly dumb
But on some level I do enjoy that he's like
Birthright
Providence
Salonpas
Birthright
Appreciate that
Because it's too long and it's just him talking about God
You love it
Is like a moment he's like self-conscious about
I'm going to shut up
How many looks at the cameras
The camera lingers for like 3 seconds too long
He's sitting there like
Like a deflated Alex Jones post rant
Finished
Am I going to make Rob do stick around for another 20
Alex Jones
Thursday I hope you all had a great
Saint Patty's
But if you'd like to find out
Knowledge
Participate
In
What some have called
The most exciting event of March
That would be the created and that
What's a good name
You're brilliant
Facebook group we are also just on Facebook
For a lot of fun to happen
Absolutely
Radar detector
In the meantime
Got a
Close this up
Answer to ramble around drunk
Stupid
Transylvania
Black nobility
I would say there's only one candidate
Himself right now who enabled
Because without him Alex couldn't do these things
He makes it possible by
Leaving his family
To go do all this b******* literal Renfield
I'm talking about
And I wish
Talk to you you can
F*** yourself
Holding
Alexandra First Time coloring with huge fan I love your work