Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Everybody welcome
Then we need to work out a new introduction
The point of the matter is that I watch too much Infowars
And I like to sit down
Describe it to you
Jordan
Wait did I redo that I don't know later. Can I just say I'm Jordan 3 times in a row
Beetlejuice
Boone's Farm
Strawberry Hill.
Cover we need to get into the right heads
Space of what's going on here
Amazing Lisa
Firefighter but quicker
Yes
In the last week
I always had recorded
Donald Trump has given a incredibly unhinged press conference
He went to Florida to have a campaign rally a month to his present
No off the chain
I can't do it come out and give a little bit of an introduction
Candle in the Wind started playing
I don't know is he going to kill princess
Princess Diana still alive and take him out
I was like why the f***
You playing Candle in the Wind
But then I started to listen to the lyrics
And they talked about how evil the Press is
All the papers was founded
There's a couple lines in the song that are about how depressed
Makeup forced Marilyn Monroe
To change into Marilyn Monroe from Norma Jean
Stretch
If you're listening
Yeah we got some stuff to talk about
About the alignment know that you're the one
Fallout 4
So then
He's the camera pans over
And it's to the open
End of the hanger
Cuz there's a bunch of people in the hangar
And I'm sitting there like there's no f****** way he
He's going to taxi in on a plane
Just pathetic thing he won't do there was like the the stair car
Was there
He's got to come in on a plane
F****** Christ
F****** ever
I mean that he gets off the plane comes down and gives
Absurd speech
Let's a fan
Come out of the crowd
Speak to the audience
Just some guy
On Fox News being interviewed by recognize come on up here
What
But we know our people know
Why do we even do this I don't know why are we even American anymore
Everyone everyone
Go
Go now
So there are other place
To be this place needs
To be abandoned places for loans
We need to build biodome
In the rainforest
There is no other solution
Cuz Breakaway civilization under goddamn ground
Nuclear weapons the whole f****** world are advocating
Underground military bases
Yes
We all know trumps cut up the greatest
Yeah
The guy
Funniest f****** thing why don't we get to enjoy it
Funniest fuzzy
I've ever lived
Through it all
So hilarious
There's nothing
There's no way any writer would be allowed to get away
With writing the story
Outside
Do you need to punch out
People react
So the gives his speech
I meant the Applause it all comes at very predictable time
Quite frankly I don't think I heard any lock her up or anything like that so maybe we're moving on from that
Hillary for prison signs
Still
Really horrifying
I don't like we're taking this much time to talk about non Alex stuff
There was a bunch of people with blackspur trump2020
Signs
Behind him there like seven people
Is a campaign
The rally in Florida with a campaign if it's 2017
He's campaigning 3 years in advance
For the next for his re-election
This is
That makes me
Yeah we plan
Along with everyone else has blacks for Trump
Everyone else in the audience along with them people who are behind Trump all stand in unison
Handclap
Straight
Grbl desk
It's implan
There was a lady with us Veterans for Trump sign
And one guy in military fatigues
Behind him
And at one point
Who here veterans
And what he says that
The lady with a Veterans for Trump sign
Sit down and hides her sign
I'm a guy and
Doesn't even
That would be your f****** time
That would be
And forgot that you supposed to be military guy stuff
And I got to be honest
This is wearing on me
Yeah it's getting to the point where I
Starting
I'm not starting to go crazy or anything like that
Starting to hurt
Oh no I'm not saying this for pity
To take credit for
Martyr for the cause
No I'm I'm sitting at most part our Jesus
Get myself off the hook a little bit
Because
I've been listening to a bunch of
Is s***
And then
During the rally
When I was watching it I started
The drink
That is what you should have
Yeah but it got me
And I started drink
Sommore and by the time it was over I realized oh f*** I've got to get
Clips for our next episode
So I isolated all of these clips drunk
I don't remember what some of them are
Yeah this is our next grab bag
But I do know that it's from February 27th
17th Friday episode
Respond
Two trucks
Prescott
So we get to get to into that a little bit
And then I have a little bit of
Double bonus clip
From an episode that he put out only on the internet
Does unfiltered on the internet
He
Put out an
H clip
That might be the most
Boring and stupid thing I've ever seen in my life
No maybe we should just start with that looks with the bonus
It is actually
Introduction
To the show that he did
For the internet
This is interesting this is like dessert for dinner
We're having a bonus ahead of the actual episode
So here's a introduction
Central Standard Time
That I've never succeeded in
A big frustration I
This morning today during breaks probably
300 articles
There were a couple others I couldn't even look at I watched all these video Clemson
Complaining
So this may be a train wreck it may be good at may be bad
Their system of like being on the Shadows running everything is coming down
Does that mean
No no the fight has just begun but
So this point are you getting any sense
Of what he has tried in the past to do but failed
No
Make a woman come
No you don't, 43rd
I've learned.
Is a good 500
Where
He hasn't all-in-one are they stacked
He has them all on the desk and tabs open on his Chrome do you have them all
And they are printed out articles I don't know
But I will tell you this
500 articles
Way too much
Ever cover
Of the substance of it
Do you know how much a ream of paper weigh
I do
Because I used to work at the Office Depot
Okay
Now put two of those on top of each other
Cut Alex Jones
Alakazam that's how many Alex Jones is red
1/2
Spoiler alert
Boring stupid f****** show I've ever sat
She has all these articles and
Does he ever reveal what he's not done
Successful in the past
Getting into the weeds
Getting through all the article I think is what he was saying
Oh cuz he always interrupts himself or go.
So he tries to just read off the headlines of all of these articles
I didn't count okay well let's listen to all of it is what he is not telling you
All of them are infowars.com articles
Not all of them but I would say 85 to 90% are Infowars or Prison Planet
F****** Synergy is what that
A little dried multi-level marketing
Fascinating
Economics
Hey man you did read it
Define the word Mercantile
I always thought I had something to do with
Clothing
Natalie clothing
Yeah
You know it's the big one
You know the East India
Alright this is going to be a badass
Medline
I'm supposed to pick the kids up about an hour and a half so
I said it'd be a two-hour I guess I better just shut up and actually just online
And then not comment on because I always comment whenever he's been story
But just imagine
At night in the morning
What
Headlines of Articles account
It's gives you what news he wants you to hear without knowing what the actual story is
You think it's an accomplishment to read the headlines of apparently
Especially not on Diane headline
That's like reading that's literally like reading a library but only reading the names of all the
Book by its cover
We all have
Because it's like no wonder Gardens
Political leaders create
Comparing that to
Other people
I don't think anybody
My person I know recess
My window is open then versus than Alex
Reeds
More news
Is metallic K on this planet
Aside from maybe Ron Paul or Donald Trump
He can't read
Everybody shut up but you're not real
Just cable news
He is
On the way here
I don't
So I don't use this
I think
Guys this is a really big here
Inoffensive words
But I do believe
Is it Donald Trump
Look in the delayed
I think I think
He was
He's with trap
12 year old child
You have millions and millions
That's all he's done he is
Retarded has not know anything more than what a seventh grader
It appears that he's least not very capable of abstract thought
Yeah
It sucks to say that it
I don't see that is like
He's an idiot
In the way that we were all bummed out whenever the
The Twin Towers
Twin Towers falling
Yeah
Driving up his goddamn rent
My building is the tallest in the door
Anyway
Can't we just can't get rid of it
Let's build
Fake White House
He already had
Now
Rebuild Big White House
We build
We put all of this
People in there
Truman Show let's turn it into a reality show
Government
People who are a bunch of nerds
Give us a nerd
We'll just watch him
Hilarious if you
You didn't have an impact
Sonic
His first article is about
Trump's line
Is doing well
Despite the backlash
Despite the other protests
Greg who cares
Wonderful f****** Wonder
His argument is that everyone hates
The globalist so much that they try and boycott her products
The only answer
Bit of news lady gets to this
A little bit later
2018 Michigan
Set up the show on Monday
Michigan
He reads the headline wrong
He said
The Event Center
Run
Newton wants to run
The guy who is notorious
For saying the n-word all the time
The guy who
Often
Goes on stage
With guns
And it's like suck my gun
F*** it
I don't care
Let's put all of the
And I mean the band
Are House of Representatives
Just be
Faded 80s on surround 2
Those guys are both Detroit guys
Frederick's death run in Florida I think
Yeah we welcome you into the Senate With Arms Wide Open
So I mean that's problematic as hell
Eclipse with him just reading headlines
It's cuz it's boring
Yeah it's super boring
I'm reading headlines if you wanted to show I just wanted to show you and I
But he's in the weed
That's like him being like
Hey guys
I'm going to show you this video of me brushing
I've never been able to do it for you
Clip where he actually literally with the Russian ships
Off the course
Of the coast
Which is
Yeah
What's 5
Within the span of about a minute
He literally contradicted
Realize he's doing it which is gorgeous
Also just to stop by really quick that is
Search
I miss representation
Yeah
Company conference we found out that
Just learned what mutually assured
Distraction beads
Learn to act like none other uranium is you
Used for bad stuff
Miles Austin
Like 57
There's a hundred ships
That's how this works we should deescalate
East Coast the X
Callers calling up
What's going on before you try to run the world
So from this first part of the clip
Right
He's talking about
Signal ships that can relay
Messages
Yes now what
This is the next headline
Okay
Russian spy ship
No kidding
East Coast
Horrible
Bethel literal contradiction of the words that just came out of his mouth
He's talking about how these ships are there and they can signal
Also existing submarine
That will destroy the East Coast the next story is there's only one and it's not a threat
Threat
Legitimate dissonance is actually Alex Jones middle name
He's got to respond to that
This snow
A long-term memory
Now if I
If I think
Give him as a key
Little puppy
So much better
Yeah I mean it's an annoying puppy but he's so cute he looks like a Shar-Pei
All over the place logo
Possibly could use it absolutely we always love
Really awesome
Anna Elsa
Seeing these numbers grow
It's heartening much like Obama's seeing protest
Tell your friends
60 degrees
In February in Chicago normal thing that happened
It makes me a blizzard in May last year
So cool I love I love unpredictable weather
I like how I took
Sick from my window I'm a horse f*** in like 2 weeks
To get to the actual Friday show put out on Friday
You want to go watch it
Highly don't recommend
Him trying to read headlines
Just f****** it up
Just completely f****** it up
Did not ask
Has he mentioned
I don't know
Friday's
By Evan about what
About the media
It is
Not interference
Deception of
I thought of this morning and I'm sure because it's such an obvious
It is well
It just hit me up
Can we pull that tweet up
Show me some perfect
And fourth on new Independent Media
Journalist investigative journalist
Just somebody to videotape something
News
The government is fake
I know you could accuse that of being fake news
Like video of Cop
There's no there's no reality we are all living in
It's Fantastical dream world
This is such a
Cure
Pure
Insanity it's one of those things were like I've been starting to wrestle with it I don't really know if there's any way home
I don't know
I don't think we can
Can click are glass slippers together and wish ourselves
Even even if
UNLV ends up getting impeached and we
Trying to right the ship I think the damage is done
All of all of the rules
He broke
Are forever broke
There's a template for breaking the rules America
Is nothing
Destroying
You can't just break rules with
Impunity and no one's going
Stop you
Tax return
Yep you're right
You're yelling
Still we're still we're still waiting
He's already
He's already present
He can release them
He's already has a thing as an advisor who committed
Light
Light treason
He can just
And you can just do it
I just want now I just want to know how
Fuct we are
Don't know how deep it goes but it's probably like Olympics
It's high dive deep
Dildo up his ass
That's all.
Did a write off
So do I use the term that he came up with
He's really f****** proud that it came up
And so it's the fake stream
Nail there
Searching
Searching and searching and
Search
I agree with him puns are hard
Getaround I'll be like
How do I how do I play with words
I'm sorry hard
Oh man
I like fake news
And I know there's a mainstream media
Let's go with
Fake Media news stream
So close
Jalisco
Let's go with
False media
Mediastream
Let's go
Lies on lies on balls on my face
Alright maybe it is pathetic
Cupid looking and looking
Proud of him
Yeah
Guys he puts on his like scream that's behind him between
Look at the corner pliers
But he's a Greek he's the new Michelangelo
The walls of the
The Sistine Chapel
Disturbed live on when I'm dead
This will be my great work
Twitter malveira censoring Trump
Find what he says
Cease on Twitter
It's all
Trump
I don't know if
Twitter is
Juking their algorithm
So whenever you look at
All the responses
UCR negative
Alex is theory
Is the Twitter is doing this intentionally so the president
And feels alone
It's improper
Get that most
Of the world is pretty much on the side of
Hope Trump
You and I are on slightly different sides of this cuz I think that would cause more trouble than it helps
You know what
I don't even know if your on burn it down and run away
Is joking around the Rhythm like this
Is equally likely
Baby more likely
Is that there is enough
Negatively responding out of his mouth
It seems awesome
Terrorist attack
People are like
When he was talking about that
Iraq news
We won't talk about an actual terrorist attack news report on Fox News the day before
About how
Made by immigrants are on the rise
In Sweden
Yep
It much better
President watches
6 hours a day
Now I'm on let Trump living just look at it
Athletic
Again if you go back just a month ago on my Twitter
All the comments
You go to YouTube
Definitely not for those who looked at Twitter audit
Yeah people do
And
Of Alex's
Followers are
I have got a third of
Prison plan
What's up Paul Joseph Watson
Twitter
Numbers are few years old I don't know if
Estranged
Since then but I would assume that the trend is
About that
I mean
I think there are a lot of
There's a lotta box
Involved
In their online price
Anyway
The first
Manifest
Did read the headline
Zuckerberg wants to hurt you
Through
Through throughout
Yeah I'm out about them
They have done that selectively like
Experimenting with what you see on your Facebook
Like what types of stories
You see from your friend
Which friends you see
Kind of
But I don't think this is one
Also I don't like
How would you even how do you begin to write a
An algorithm
That targets
Negative responses
But only for Trump
Apply to so many other people I don't know
Where the issue is
Of course
I think that you have a difficult time
Having a robot figure out what is a positive and a negative
That's a good
Does tone and irony isn't going to be able to be
Picked up
Cyborg
Have invent
A robot that can pass
Is Trump
Two things I want the globalist to get to work on right now
An algorithm
Biscuit pass the Turing test and also trolls
I am a human algorithm
So f****** stupid
Trout
Alright
Shopbot 2.0 about this and then
He gets into one of our favorite podcast
Stupid
Facts of Lent
Call out to smoke
I mean you're making that
Richthofen
That's how it comes
Is amazing
Absolutely
But just look at that
Now every where it's to make us feel bad because the majority of the work
World waking up
Wait
He doesn't get to
These articles
Beginning it doesn't really play it all out
How many times do you think
I would say
Like 50
Maybe in the 50 range
He really hammers
What you're saying
It is
It's like
Mean Girls
So you saying that
The globalist
Don't want nationalist
To feel verified in their own opinion
I think we met is validated
Very specific connotation
Frogs have a blue check mark
5 of my friends have check marks
Maybe we'll be free of them once and for all
The number of listeners we have compared to
Floors we have is crazy
It's really easy for someone who doesn't like us to attack us
Yeah but you dumbasses is 40 followers
You still download so pretty decent
Dude
Dude that's not
You're no it's not
Your defense
Should be
Yeah
You're one hundred percent correct
You know what I think I'm projecting that other people are bullying me maybe a little bit and that's not healthy that's your victimhood but
You know what who feels it more what do you want
Safe space
Oh man I hope you have pills
F****** Alex Jones
Are a bully cult
Fastenal
He doesn't
He doesn't but also get ready for you know how we has like this
Thread to go through our retail stories but did
Didn't happen
This
Is an excellent version of a story
Didn't happen
And when it when he's done
I would really like
Explain what I imagined
Even happen
The business
No we can't Rivera
The New York Times we've we've emailed the New York Times for comment, or not
Perhaps better yet
No response
Hey guys f*** off
The answer is no response
Here's some fun fanfiction
Definitely not the ladies
That's not a
Mitsubishi
Add. Me sometime
It isn't
Potterhead
It's possible the New York Giants game
It's possible there was a reporter there
Pornographer
It's possible that all that is true
But I think a more realistic version of what happened was
This photographer
I got to go take pictures of Alex Jones and then she shows up
I don't want to engage
Pictures for us and not because the liberal establishment will bully her
Choose like
I want to get involved here you guys are nuts
The snow and well
It was not
For us it was more like I
Hey
I'd like to give you some super female Vitality on the house
Turn your p**** into a log flume at least
So what
Magic Mountain
Oh my God
The visual that you just gave me
Imagine how Alex Jones Mike sexually harass somebody
I didn't have to involve super female vitality
What you can get back.com
My dad makes
I should say that I actually that to pay superblue would not work
Did he make 100%
It could not be used this literally makes a big deal about how it's
Stick
Insubstantial
Toothpaste
How do you make toothpaste
This photographer
He thinks a dead
Fascinating
The paranoia is
Everywhere
I asked if she was being bullied but kind of naughty
She gave me the liberal media the fixery media is bullying me
Politely
Blink your left eye once if yes when your right eye
Twice if
No
It's absurd absurd fanfiction about his own life
Based based on
Actual
Right probably
The weirder things
If it was a
Photographer
He spent all this time talking about writers out of
*
Yeah
Is one photographer
The assignment
Touch
Yeah but I also think
If he is lying and making it up out of whole cloth
The Narrative that I had a writer, and I tried to get him to write stuff for us
That's a harder sell
Jennifer
Freelance
Like a writer would actually have to care and like be on the same page is up
Just be doing
But but in our history of Alex Jones
He does not go halfway
No believable
Yeah that's true
It would literally be
Woodward and
But we're a little bit
Because of the globe
He keeps talking about how much Seymour Hersh loves her
This next clip
You told a story
Emile Hirsch
Judd Hirsch
All the Hearst Clan
Even even the one who's not related
So does next
Make a point using a law that never existed
Then he conflates reality with a movie
Another f****** wild a
I love
Spencer Rivers
That's completely illegal
They have big contain slurry pools that they put it into
Water runoff.
Austin farming
$1,000 signs the next one was 20000 just went up
So I looked into that
Obama wanted to ban
And dust
You would have to Define.
Really well
This is an article from 2011
Ideal talking point illustrate a federal bureaucracy
Only God
Control
The Dust in the Wind
Now here comes my favorite part of the crazy regulatory Act
The EPA is now proposing rules to regulate.
Representative John Carter of Texas
Set on the house floor
He said Texas is full of Dusty Rhodes
The EPA is now staying
Can be fine for driving home every night and your gravel road
You are a representer
Your automatic
Yet I have
Have yet to hear
Single with Kinky Friedman in the house for a little while
Anyway
There was just one
It was not true
Never did
Oh my God
Yep
Remember do you remember when this thing that didn't happen happen
I hated it I hated it
Still the Spectre of this rule has spurred three bills to prevent it
One of which was approved Thursday by a house subcommittee
It sparked a late night
GOP Presidential candidate Herman Cain decided in a debate as a reason to eliminate that
EPA
The hubbub over this Phantom rule
Surely one of the most controversial regulations that never was
Involved
The EPA and its Crossing
Never existed
Is that is that worth
Completely and utterly
Really evil the fact that they
Still get away with s*** like that
Truly amazing
Yeah
The old
The first thing that came up
To mine was like
Reading The Art of War
No point in The Art of War was it
Just like a man make
Shut up
Like there's no way someone could have figured out that you could just
Pretend & Win
Especially if you repeat the pretend thing over and over again
People just start to education
Instantly says that the Chinese are trying to buy Hollywood
To the point where people get used to hearing it no like oh I remember him talking about that but he never approved
What's my source my source
Was that I heard it a bunch
Sources
I think I'm going to do is take his talking points and on our Tumblr
Every now and again I'm just going to thoroughly breakdown why it's b*******
Savannah will in the future when it comes up on episodes I can go to Art and reading
By Holloway
Is we are going
To reference art
Selves
But the issue
The difference will be the amount of
Primary resources
Headlines
Just like you have those
Twitter where they take a screenshot of their note
Just transcript insane like
Jordan Holmes was quoted as saying this is not true
And that's our response
To make this even worse
Actually change the rules for dust on farms
EPA would have to formally propose a new rule
And as of March
EPA administrator Lisa P Jackson said
She was not likely to do that
Quote we have no plans to do so Jackson
Sunset
Luscious lips
Started
2 second
Just to s
It's
How
Could you possibly outlawed dust without
Turning it into like ever
Chemical bath salt
What time do I have to live in bubbles
Outlawed
Even if you want
No
Dream
Was this o.c.
CD and nuts not to be
Sure sure
Sotd meth addict dream of it
It's finally time to outlawed.
Finally
No
Would ever
Consider doing
Super horse
I mean even take away the outlaw part everyone understand
Dirt and dust
Exist
Lack of cleanliness
But there's not really anything you can do about it
In the desert
You're going to get.
Alex about regulatory stuff Gone Wild in order to reinforce his point
That what they're doing with coal mining shitizen
Polluting Rivers
All the time
And that was the rule that they just got rid of the one
The what the Only Rule
UA
Can be no way you're again
There can be
No human being who's like you know what
I hate
Petco
Coal miner
From throwing s***
But the reason you can't
Terrified
Fluoride
Making water right
Love f***
Call call Mike
Makes me warm
Makes me drink good
What's well there's been a couple things if you believe this b******* about regulatory should Gone Wild
Ben you might assume
That this
Dumping s*** into a river
A regulation is the same thing
Those are my favorite commercials that around 1
Pant suits
Titties
So
Hillary election
Baby. I don't know
If you believe
It's like Alex does the clean
You would think it's all Much Ado About Nothing
Legitimately believe that there's clean enough coal that is all it does when you use it is it puts out water
That's not true
That's not possible
It's not possible and it's not like carbon dioxide and water vapor
It's not a thing
I'd love to get into it at some point but it's
Not real
Brilliant strategy
Make a thing up
That we have to
Because then
Get away with f****** at 8
If you're just making up like
Hey there trying to outlaw dust
Now I have
No
Legitimizes that is it just me saying
Come on
Do you remember
The Phantom Tollbooth when Milo was trying to open Milo
He was trying to get
Doraemon reason and free them from captivity run into
The terrible Trivium
Trivium
Is like a big pile of sand
Put it over there one
Colonel at a time one little piece of string
His basic thing was just like
Creating tasks for Milo to do the waist
It is time it seems like there was a point
I know what Alex Jones.
It's pretty good yeah doggy sound
Let's go further into this clip cuz
We got a ways to go we're almost
Anime
So not true
McDonald
Just like the Deepwater Horizon
I just shut up
Absolutely word-for-word
What was
Now he doesn't cite the actual transcripts but what he does now is
Performs the theme from the movie
What to show with me
To show the policy
Instead of getting into the Weeds about the actual details he does enjoy this
It's great
Russell and
Listen
379 billion-dollar company
No it's not
Don't matter I'm going to do whatever I want whose voice is that
So it's just how I covered
This
What is this
All of the article
Nobody can talk for hours about this
Referring to
An impression of Kurt Russell
But it was a greater pressure
Is escape from l.a.
The Kurt Russell as Snake Plissken
I could talk for hours about this
2 minutes that we listen to of it
What you talked about was
A Federal Regulation that never existed about regulating.
Yes about child labor that he's completely misinterpreted
Have your family members work on a farm
That's exactly what they were trying to outlaw
That you know
It's it's not
It's definitely not a
Straw man argument
Not at all
It is a it is a 100%
Real thing
Could you imagine 4 hours if in the time he allotted he just lied twice in order to justify the
The idea that regulations
You're crazy
Yeah man it's cool to
Pollute Rivers
If you just makeup regulations you can just do that forever
Isn't that Kurt Russell voice
Billion dollar company
Build.com
Brooklyn
Queen from the 70s
Weird
What are we doing
I don't know
Accompany
They're putting
Against
Hey
It's bad that they put arsenic in the water and is like
It's probably better that they put f***
Poison from the
It's all good
It sucks it's all bad
Yeah but you know what most of the time when you complain about things that
Business wants
To do
Or the Nationalist one
All you're doing is
Virtue
I don't know what that
It's this idea Paul Joseph Watson talks about it all the time it's
Black lives matter
Or
Post something about Reproductive Rights
And stuff like that on Facebook or on Twitter
You really care about the issue you're talking about
All it is is you were trying to perform for your liberal friends
And show that you're one of them
So your signaling your virtues
Through poster making in behaviors
Don't
Well on a known one level you are expressing your virtue
Junior standing up for things that you
That fall within your principles
Just posting something on Twitter is not really
Pause lot of people who are
Maybe do a little bit shity
Certainly
But there's there's
There's a lot of people
Uncle Express their opinions.
Anyway Alex virtue signaling he wants you to know that your pizza
That's exactly because I have a beard
Virtue signaling talk about black lives matter whatever
Carnival greedy people
Do you think about stealing
Actually wait
You can
You just
Do you think about stealing stealing land from Hawaiian
What about Mark Zuckerberg trying to build a house
But
Probably
Any billionaire allowed
To go out
Sure
Open and someone who grew up in Hawaii
Small little boxes
Under the ground
I hate
Trying to get back to the
The point but I grew up for a bit in Hawaii
Who celebrated King Kamehameha day with native population
Also known as Dragon Ball Z
If you want
To make the argument about
Stealing land from Hawaiian
There's a lot more you're going to have to do American history that would involve
Always been America
Pretty sure that Native Americans
Not
The American
Landed
On me
George's place but the native populations there
But I've been making claims about how it's going
I'll listen to that
But if you don't care about
Other parts of it
Then you're just
Capitalizing on someone you don't like
I can't imagine anybody that
Being a
Complete and utter Giant
And I'll certainly not everyone we talked about
Have any perhaps
House
Justice committee leader
Name Chaffee
Being a complete and utter
F****** HIPAA
Yeah anyway
Let's get through this
White papers article today about Zuckerberg says users are dumb
He already has
Elegant crazy
Absolutely devastating
Devastated
Yesterday and
They just don't know what to do the confidence
Nobody's getting hurt
Being a superhero
Definitely not racist
Paste for people not the post-industrial technocracy
Where they're all saying the end of humans is here you will submit
Machines it's all over we already spawned a Little Liars
Drum roll
I was reading papers
Which wallpapers was 30 articles
The numbers of Articles is really good
Facts about transhuman
I'm guessing that's what he's trying to say
He's made
So is about the extent
To which he covers
The press conference
This point
Okay does end up getting to a little bit of it later
But if he's like
We have a press conference and was on Thursday and I was really really waiting for him
To go off on it
Like really
Be like yeah
You know you the specific instances like you told them
Black caucus
Like I was expecting that to happen
And it really wasn't he didn't respond too much was really boring
On the
It really disappointed me that he didn't get into a ton of that
Let's get into it
Do you think it's because there is
Even for him
Nothing really defensive all about that
Talking about so many of the things that came up in the press conference
So many of Trumps Behavior
Are kind of put it behind the eight
I think that he realized like a lot of this
It's going to be too difficult for me to
Defend
So at the end
We're going to play today is when he finally gets to actually talk
Press conference
You'll see how like
How little he engages
The Source material
But what
What is the
You'll see I'll let you know what's faster
About that is
Is that I was really
I wanted to see
Because there's
There's so many
People who would
And whatever none
They're already always
So they're going to do that
If you
If you have
Any sense
Of critical thought about
You watch that
Even if you voted
A trumpet
What the f*** is happy
I can't imagine
Frazee I can't imagine any of my people in the red state of Missouri
All my old people to Maita voted for Trump
Any of them watching that
Boys off his rocker
Now you know how it
How you could possibly defend
Exactly right there and that's why
Really hoping that
He would have something that's what I was looking for.
Today conservative websites
And they were all like
Zero from what all he's all
Prince was bad
Go through anything
Here is a
Possible argument that Alex
Please and that is look look
Trump may appear to be crazy but it only appears crazy
Because you may or may not have superpowers
Abreva
That brings us to our next clip
God dammit your transition skills are
Filtered blocked on Twitter
I might as well tell people
She wants to talk to her
At the switchboard
About 2 in the morning
Please read
Code
And weather
Is sportsball which Harkins he has autism
I mean
I guess
I can't think of any
Cuz I'm sure it's okay
Alright
We got that magic
That's not great
Toad
What about you
Toad the Wet Sprocket I think that's very heroic character in Mario
Absolutely Toad and that the very the very gay Series where the toad
Load in the rabbit or whenever I know that
That's not important
Incorrect
Goes to Hell
Traxxas
You're totally wrong if you think that looks traumatized me
Why is mr. toad in hell for kids
Anyway
We haven't gone to the Superbowl
How can they
All of
Trump
Sits there with his reading drugs
Not
He 70
You should know
He just okay
Why is there
16 women with all these little headphone Jacks in there like
Operator
Switchboard just talking to regular people
Sor
Are people call in the White House and he's like 2 in the morning
This one sound
Sounds good you up
McDonald's
But also
It's clear that if a seventy-year-old man is up till 2 in the morning then wakes up and does his job
He's got to be on some sort of amphetamine
Like that
Can't you just like your body does not allow for
His wife
He's a magic toad
If there's anything
Alright
It's at when you are a magic
Quickly
Engineer
Weather
And as we all know one of the
Powers of a toad
If you stay up until 2
And wake up early in the morning
I think it's more like a superpower is a deist
Secretes hallucinogens
That explains his appearance on Jimmy Fallon
That's for goddamn sure
What Spiderman was that
Photographer who showed up at Infowars
Oh my God
I know we got we got Batman
New York but there's no evidence
He's freelancing for the New York
And the New York Times
Him on this
Oh my God
Freelance mission
But
In the meantime
He would turn into spider Gwen
Which is the new thing of Spider-Girl
And
And that's
As logical as the story he f******
And Marvel in the
And
Mr myxlplyx or whatever
Whatever
We have a new hero to answer the pantheon has Donald Trump superpower
Alright
Yes
Stop right there
And basically he knows on the switchboard
This is incredible
What
Lame superpowers
Because it's
But let's not talk over the cliffs as much cuz I'm getting this weird feedback then
It's hard not to respond I know I know I'm sorry
Grade a nonsense numbers come up
He memorizes numbers for memorizing
Dino's phone number
Which is
Amazing to
People that's really cool
Is impressed by somebody knowing phone
Alex
He just said it's
I texted you
Yes I recall cuz I knows what color ideas
Which I really don't think he understands that modern phones
Have a name that comes up with a phone number
Connect
Because
Again I'm living in
He's in front of us
Actual plugs
Yeah
Alright people who like using the first two numbers as letters whenever
He's
You remember phone numbers
When people are calling
The number
This is way over there were only eight numbers
Okay and then
But why
Yeah yeah where they mad again because they can
Everyone else knows
Unclog up the line
Maybe it's the media's going to be pissed cuz then they can't call Trump late at night
Which is not happening
I don't know
Insanity
It is on all sides
There's there's no there's no way to get in there without going through
Nightmare of crazy
Describe it
If it's true it's crazy if it's not true it's still crazy
If even a part of it is true is crazy
Reading even the slightest bit true is
Verify
The reality peace
Is possibly
He calls Trump the only part of it
How did he know in that press conference also was complaining that the media never calls him
Direct refutation of what Alex and sing
The fourteen-year-old child the most insane
So Alex Jones
Has an iPhone we've established that he's had his phone on set Buffet
Is it an iPhone or a
Now
Based on what he just told
Does he know how to add
Didn't recognize.
He is
He is Amazed by
Buy Trump being able to recognize
Just before he
The answer is yes
Because he doesn't know how to put
Name
In the
Trump doesn't like I don't think
The Trump would give Alex
Nexus cell phone
That would be that would be
Neighbor sitcom I would watch all the time
If if your if
A f******
Kramer was Act
Text Jones
Just calling
Trump all the time president this is a knowledge
Intellectual property
Do you know that even better
MB Home Improvement
Where Alex Jones Wilson
Screaming from the other side of the fence
Instead of
Running a TV show about Home Improvement
Stop the president
Instead of Wilson giving out good advice he yells about the globalist
I just had a real rough
Fight with my
Who's my wife
George Soros
The move on and grow as a person
All right I got to get on air
Don't don't steal that either
SNL skit
Call me mad TV was still around
Already have a 5-year deal
You gets back
To the New York Times photographer narrative
I am and I don't remember exactly what the
This is about but I've labeled it as a
Really bad example of a
Slippery slope
He doesn't care what they do what they say he realize they're a bunch of bullies slave
And he's just out there to show them they're bullies
Photographer
Can't
Contract
Country
You're not allowed to ever work with anybody who's not
The big corporate liberal approved
Gulag
There was a slippery slope
No
That makes perfect sense
But also another conversation
He's showing us
It's okay to be who
Yeah so long
As you are not Muslim
Sure
Latin
It's okay to be who you are
If you are white
Can stay here and if you are everything else
Be who you are somewhere else
Exactly Trump slogan from now or somewhere else
That sort of mentality that people who believe it don't think is racist
What is like
Europe for the Europeans
Africa for the Africans
It is super racist but it
Everyone who believes it thanks
They're not be more of me at my homeland
Why should mixing
Why
Reasons
I can I can pretty comp
At least
He interpreted their interactions very wrong
Definitely would not
Infowars
If she did
In Alex Jones's nightmare scenario where she's being bullied into
Freelance work
He desperately needs
Which she doesn't
That still doesn't lead to gulags in a year
Doesn't leave the gulags ever
Alright whatever
What's wind-up in gulags
Vladimir Putin
We want to start arresting y'all Trump
He's talking about Evan McMullen went on
MSNBC isn't he a senator
From Utah whatever used to work
Intelligent stuff
Okay
Definitely not good
Do not make me happy
World president tube
Be compromised or working with enemy countries like
An anime
The domestic enemy of our country
Like he is
McMullen said it wasn't great but it's way more nuanced than what Alex was talking about
Do you mean
What the way you said it
The way he said truth
Send
Specifically about Madonna know the White House is really nice
Also talked about
Madonna's speech where she said
I sometimes think about blowing up the White House but I don't want to do that
Yeah but you know
Even before Trump was elected
Sometimes I think about blowing up the White House
I think
Roland emmerich I think also I think
I'm not sure about this
But I think the White House might get blown up in that American movie that Alex Jones is in
He got blown up
Thousand
Independence
Roland emmerich
Is a enemy of
State
To say anyways
At the Republic
Just like Evan Baldwin being on CNN
The intelligence Community talking about how Trump is anatomy
Blow up the White House is about Madonna
The idea that people want to
To kill Trump I'm guessing is based on
Tweets Houston or something like that
I think
You're speaking at least I am not
Norton
Insinuating that I will do anything
No and you're speaking a little bit glibly
Very much
Emilio
Fully protected under parity laws
Well they've outlawed dustox with flowers
Like that
They cannot get that's why they hate real men they cannot get
The real men.
Like
Problem to be absolute filth
Eagles on to explain that that's why they're creating robots
Yep it's that this is the first instance that we're playing so far of what I would call Joe
Toxic masculinity
It always goes back to
It gets Warriors
To get so much worse as it goes along like there's a couple things that actually left my jaw open
And I've been listening to him everyday
You know if you want to get excited for later
Part of this episode
You said some stuff there
We're really going to have to unpack a real dangers of male identity
Male identity I can think of
Except that last clip in about dogs
Anytime he talks about what a real man is
It is so
Glaringly obvious
A real man is that which fits the mold
And anybody who disagrees with him or Trump is a chicken neck to weirdo
Or I call them effeminate
You know I wouldn't say that
An insult to women
He doesn't understand
The things he's implying with his own word
I don't understand any of the words
Step through store hours 3 hours
Hate whenever there's that
Mail
We're manning that means that week
The man
Explain some of the ideas
Videos about his mom
Was bullied
Victim of bullying
But unfortunately that transitions
Into him not understanding
He is wildly
Well
Operating system of early reducing language vindication
Scrambling
You can't go to somebody
Are there just monsters
I just remembered
Always online
Bully bully
That was a lot of
Erebus
Saudi Arabia
What does dialectic
The whole thing's fake
Hollywood was pushing
I just real first agenda
Also pushing the agenda
So what
Under
Let me try and help you
Parse this
Was
Conflated
Then call from Nate Burrows
Every
Possible enemy
Yeah
Leftist
Would you like me to explain results
Okay
He's responsible for.
Conspiracy in the world
In the world but at least in America and people online
Sister and Subs because he's been going for so long
In such a public way a lot of people get there
Productions
Conspiracy through Alex Jones
He has done wonders
Ford
Creating and building the world
And think everything is a false flag
Unfortunately the byproduct is at
It's that whole narrative story that you create something you can no longer can
Control
The entire conspiracy world not all of it but a lot of it is
Because they think he doesn't criticize Israel
So a lot of people think
He is a shill for Israel
There's a lot of scary to think it's
Conspiracy
Because we are down
He's responding to hear what he's saying he's being bullied
He's not being bullied
Or by Erebus
Or anything like that
Keep being bullied by people that
He's had a hand in creating
They have gone too far
Down the conspiracy aisle
Too far and they're like
Go that far
He's a crazy enough.
That's what he's getting at
Fascinating like
Fork in the road if you're an Alex
One span
Either I did
Agree with Alex
2insane
Or
He's not insane
Like everybody ever
Conspiracy theorist
Fork in the road
Like that's your ultimate like that's your
Directions to Manor
I actually think The Road Less Traveled is the one that sticks with him
I think that most people who go that far down the road get to the fork
And they're like well
You know what this
Doesn't do it for me anymore I got to
Switch to Coke
Flipping on what you believe previously The Alex Jones
Okay
How do you how do they want him to call out
Do they want him to don't know specific because Israel is like I'm like there
There
Destroying the two-state solution and they're not creating a
Creating
I get the
Feeling
Instinct
They're not on the side
Relation
They f****** take Mossad did 9/11 they think that the Jews are basically responsible for everything that's
Cyber hacking bad
Like
Did the fact that he's complaining about being bullied by the people who think that he doesn't call out Israel is really unfortunate
Because
Everything that he believes in in terms of the globalist
Is poorly packaged anti-semite
It really all goes back
To the fake document the protocols of the Elders of Zion entire episode on that
Yes I've just done
I have like in the past
Also protect
Nice refresher course
When exactly how it was a Ford Raptor
Right it's f****** insane how clear
The five do bankers
Sealab
Exactly
People who were trying to hurt the world from behind the scenes
Is all taken directly
From the protocols of the Elders of
Because you know
But if you bring that book up
And act like it's real because it is
Discredited
Not that that matters
The only thing that people
Right-thinking people will respond is
Okay
Repackaged it
In a way that is
Acceptable to talk about by calling them globalist
Write in the same way that David Icke does it with lizards are in the same way that George Soros is a Nazi
Yeah it's George Soros a Nazi collaborator
Because
He has enough
Be nice
Fall through
Really was to be like
Now I need to tell you about this book
Pretty much all of my beliefs about Nature's and communism
Look in the middle of a lake with no paddle
No one would get on board with him
Stormfront Israel
So is he inside Israel
I don't know if I have enough information to say
Right
The most
He generally talks about
To say that he's
Fair
He doesn't really
Beetle with too much but he always talk smart move on his he always
But then there's no substance
There is an actual evidence in my
Experience
That he does either of those
Of course but he does call out the Erebus
What what
I don't know
The Erebus
Probably offensive word
What's the weather
Sing about a Sierra Vista
I remember back when I was a kid
Do you like 106 & Park
Arabic
That is anyway
Civilization
Program
And that in Israel did anything it was the worst thing on earth
Well I'm sure the truth in between you know Israel do some bad stuff that the Muslims have been stuffing
Work for the Catholics
I want to send
Alexander
But also I love that
Snap
Clarification
I'm not sure if it's in this clip but he's like
I talked to Emma as MI6
I want sex as a real thing I think I'm I-5 is removed
Play talk tomorrow about
Alien
Seven billion people on the planet
Muslims
How many Muslims are OnStar there on this planet
Billions
Yeah
How many do you need to have a large
Engine of Muslim
You would have to
Like
Statistically speaking we would need
What 25% would you call a large contingent
So let's let's relatively speaking call it a small
If you have a very small reference
It's a large
Hundreds of thousands of pressure
Alright
Christians
How long before you're out of Chris
It seems like
You would run out
Harley Quinn
At least weather
Is there slightly more Christians are there are Muslims which is even more
Or is it 100,000
Ever the statistics very murky
I've learned stuff like that I just
I'm giving this new skill I'm giving this new skill which I'm not actually happy about what I do
B is like
Whatever he says stuff like that it's
Like water rolling off a duck's back
I can't engage hundreds of thousands of Christians
Means like 10 guys
Maybe
Let's be clear about that
We are the one podcast
Take the stand real hearts.
But not with acid is like I think every podcast
Agree with that
Never cover it
You know what
You know why cuz they're not real men
Keep the ends up talking about Morrissey
Secret service agent
And then makes a horrible false equivalence
Around Saturday 1
It's just
Everybody should just be able to talk to everybody's like that New York Times photographer
Let me see your portfolio
I think human beings
Just a few minutes
Suicide bombing Israel
Somebody cuz you're a big man you're a good person
Moral
Bad person or whatever
I apologize false equivalence about the Holocaust
I must not have had that in the clip
At some point in the show he talks about how like a holocaust was a
A Jew's now it's again
Chance the white
Great to go back to the light
Oh man
If only
What a Wonderful World
Cuz you you're a self-hating cook white man
You know you you are
You defended evidence
The programming what's going on
I'm trying to
Turn white people against themselves
It's called
Yeah all of the history
Yes
When you talk about that
Yeah it's very complex and abstract
Alex doesn't understand it
You and I are both you and I are both white men
Yeah
Fortune things from history
Breakfast
Yet but
Everyday we
Yes
And that is the piece of it that makes
Talking about
White
Send
Or white
This in the past
Whatever we don't have each other because you are white and I am light
It is about a shared history
Of benefiting from a pressure
When I was in London
I did see the crowns
Well I was Prince
They were good
Little
Those little ginger balls
No it was it was really
Because they did have them
In a way that you
Go through
Pictures
There are these weird little thing
Kept looking at them going like
Did you guys call this
Cuz that's not
That's also to take a step back
Killer Mike
They were there yesterday
I just saw the sign
Which is the David
VapoRub
Run them Jewels fast
I did not go to the concert cuz I
We didn't include the thing that I said
Evidence cuz I don't like saying that
The proof
Slightly higher
Fairy not unrealistic
Sick for you to believe that Alex Jones has ideas
Scum
You think that's what people call him online
Cuz you work for is
Alright
Okay
Alright I don't know exactly what this next clip is so let's get surprise together
Coming to you from the former United States of America
How crazy
States of America
Zinus company right there
You're walking on the Fightin side of me
The nut Merle Haggard whoever is
Detox
This is one of those new catch phrase
You know when you want to go get some
Play Walking on the
All the way
He says it's against
The Constitution
You walking on the Fightin side
Meowth on
Is like anytime so
So the biggest
Bummer that I have
With our system
Is that it
Really bums me out
Because anytime
It's like all the concert
Says this
I mean
A lot of crazy
It's not it's not a good or bad.
Weird
You can't change the f******
I still don't know exactly what this is but
Alright
No longer the United States
Merle Haggard
Gas coming up and
Trump sabotage infowars.com
Carbon dioxide
Behind
Trump leaked when talk about that mumbler gas
Amazing
Don't know why
Human being
At this point you are a Muslim
Because
I don't know if you know this or not
Muslims are also cute
Yeah there's a lot
And there's a lot for
Yeah it's really bad stuff being done in
Inwardly outward
Delete all of it
The others problems
Who's in the community
I just realized
What business
Cliff is where he talks
About the Holocaust I apologize today
For the second time
We bring you the
But
Within this clip
Alex wants to tell you a little bit
About what he would like
He probably.
Hardcore history
Country books when I was about six years old
Red
200-300
University
About
Yes you are a big store of knowledge
Scholar level
F*** you
I understand the roots of the different Control Systems when I see them
I know it's being built
So he didn't read thousands of scholarly books
There's an interesting thing that we can
You know we can use exegesis
Take his word
See what's actually being said though
It's possible
They started to understand history
When he was six
2/8 to 10 years old
Will know
I'm saying he had a six-year-old understanding of History
That's what I'm saying
Possible you had this understand
Meaning of AU
Have a baby
That able to read us both
And he reads books and doesn't understand what he's reading
What comes up with a fantasy narrative that a child might
Okay
And because
He's so stubborn
And
I don't know I had a paranoid weirdo dad
Okay never got correct
You
You are creating a Jenna General unified world theory of Alex
Figuring out all that you are f****** full-on
Zodiac Killer
Trying so hard to get into his head space it's the only way for this to first of all be home
Andy
Not be boring
So I think that
He just fabricated that whole cloth
He is not read he did not read
Also also the
The f******
The headlines
The books that they pretend to read
He Redwood
University
But I was ten I read the Bible cover to cover
And I've read other
Another Bible
I recognize that when I was 10
And I read the Bible I didn't really understand it
In a way that I did when I was
Taking
Biblical classes in college
Right when I was older person I had a more robust worldview I was able to
More into
Abstract language is more able to understand metaphor
Contacts
No matter who you are if you're 6 you're not
Like what is that even
Second grade
First grade second grade
You're not reading scholarly books
Well
Some second grade you might
Hold them
Do you know
Do you know.
Hop on Pop
Okay well
Pikachu
You and most
I would also
Everything I own
Yes which isn't much
Exercise bike over there
We have very little at stake of this Farm
Anything that you have read more books
Books than Alex Jones has
In the past week in this entire life
He
Thousands of books
Thousand
Start to take his word
And his own sort of
Telling of his own history to get a better picture of
Exactly why he is
The kind of wrong
Videos
It is one of those things where you can learn a lot more about
The Grecian
People
Okta
Sometimes by the myths
As it refers to the
What what what externalization our culture holds
The deer species
Okay there
Right there you look at it within
In the context of their gods
Isn't all of that stuff
To see you
The motivation
Behind why they would believe
Are doing
That's why they would believe it
Contact
Mythology
As being a
Preternaturally gifted
Six-year-old remember phone number
Kids
Probably wants absolutely reading white papers
White papers
It was they were putting it out there when I say these things
This picture of him I'm not doing it
To get it like
To justify
I'm saying
It's interesting and important to look at why a propagandist behave the way you're like an anthropology
Somewhat
Threatened
Why are the
The Pharaohs
F****** weird
Buried with your
Your cat cats
When that s*** going on here
What's what I'm doing here
What I'm doing
Is I'm hearing up
For when the collapse
There's a terrible Civil War and then on the other end of it we try and figure out what how
Happened for weeks I will be on
Future MSNBC as a Alex Jones specialist
I just tried to become an Alex Jones expert witness
Yeah yeah
Will be the first witness I would call
In the trial of Alex Jones in his Nuremberg Trial you are on the list
How to get to that part about the Holocaust
It's just those who don't know history
I only wish that I had time it's been years
I know science fiction book
Containers
Watch football game
Constantly wash the enemy showing
Hiscox Diantha Copley watch with a direct no time
Very vividly and
At length about how football is
Is just a retired
No I meant to say men's testosterone I know that I know that's his
He watches a lot of
He totally watches
The Superbowl on his else does
Yeah he watches football
He was going to boycott the Super Bowl and then live stream
The his Sunday show
While he talked s*** about George
HW Bush
For throwing a coin portal
For that
Police negative thing I hope
Tell me about
I just can't do it because
Globalstar
Receive the civilization the society
The culture in Israel
Israel
Nordic
Which is utterly ridiculous
And wrong as can be right there
Yeah
Perfectly correct
Correct
What religion is bad
All all of the stuff
All of it he's correct except
Except
Muslims
Yeah
Has been Meredith
The culture is saying that all white people are inherently evil and no one
But it's also too many of us to say to our face
Has anybody ever
Considered created by
Yakub
At this point as reasonable as everybody voting Trump for president
All of all of it is reasonable right now
Everyone thinks they understand what these conversations about privilege
Actually meme
He has no G
But it's like
Didn't enslave anybody
Well I mean but yeah
I don't think that makes him inherently bad because of that
Either but like
His inability to understand and his
Destin
Need to take that s*** personally makes him think
But everybody is saying that white people are inherently evil and therefore
The victims of an impending genocide that's
Being made right
It is so hard
Listen to any of
In the context
Them spending
So much time
I'm saying that everybody else
He says a white genocide is
Because everybody
White people
And I hate
Muslim
Play the victim
Yep
How is black lives matter a cop killer
How do we
How do we fight against
What
What route
Trick and they're available there is none
Is that hard
There's none
Commit white genocide
Darling
In order for him to deal with the press conference
Yes
He actually ends up talking about another press conference but trouble so did that day
Axilla
I want to get to a bunch of Clubs trumpism
I better get a small extra next hour
Economy Inn
When he just gets
That's not ahead by the commercial evolution
It's a big deal
The very edge of death
And demoralisation
Shuffle around
Programmed unhappy.
Connection to the spiritual universe
And that is now coming back into the world self respect
Belief
America
Shutterstock
Can I have something
Build a civilization
We can go to the stars together but we're not going to be
Run over by a bunch of Zuckerberg
Alliance with China and some pipe dream
Whole system's getting
We're teaching you
Two cabbage
I want to listen to the eclipse
What is
Houses are so long
But okay
Disease in China is
What is
What is not being
How does
Civilization right now
Do they not have one thousands of you
The common man on the street
It's maybe not doing
Compared to what they were 30 years ago
Straight like it's not good it's not but it's a lot like America
The industrial
A lot of
Also
Elsa that come with
Haribol
But also I love the line
I know what that's how the
I don't have never heard of that turn of phrase
Do you know
So you got a cow
Alright
Not China America
The other day about how it's
That's really absurd
To imagine
All of the parts
The plane rebuilt in the same
Same place
How it works is there's different
Three component parts
Tractor parts actually are made already
Well there's a lot of stuff that's hard to transport
If you need resources
And let's not f******
Split hairs the idea Factory job saving
It's a saying
Did not recognize how automation
Absolutely
Going to take all the jobs
But actually reading a really really
Good
Thought
About how
This camp
Both
Werehog
Getting back to the
This vision of America
From the night
1950s folksy
Yeah they are like they're the personal
Grandfather was a
Small business
ISO
Like that's not a story that resonates at like
Our Generation
And we're watching climate change
Happened to us
F****** February
Culver opening in La where the fire trucks are falling
Flood coming
Real bad
Till 5 years
Like
Why didn't
Why isn't
Cooking monster
But tomorrow if he comes out and says we're going to be the most radical
Country on fighting climate change
As we possibly can
He's going to be better for us than any other but because so much of that regulation
But look at this next clip
And I I'm going to make
Was just looking to this all the way through
It also gives us some weird inside
Has passed
Are you believe in ism
But what he ends up talking about is
One of those horrible examples of talks
Masculinity
And I really think the story is to
The globalist
Control Revolution to the university they only control the big donors and the corporate branch
All human Rebellion to be socialist or comics
Decentralized system they control
Can you get demoralize and you're so dumb down
What college degree
Screwed up
Competency
And that were just absolutely really scary
What kind of the end of America
Wanted to go see movies like gangs people meet in the parking lot with chains and knives and
They call that Justin movie so that's what a person
Used to be
People shed
Knowing there be multiple people there they're all into the dark
Bashas Hospital still win
Where is that today that that's a fighting spirit
Neither
Pretty much it
Really bad
Every time
I just want but in there cuz you yelling over
You even saying
I got
Switch got flipped
Yeah
And then I became a
F*** you you made a gesture and I'm not
Entirely sure that this is what he
Cement that looks like you
Which would apply
People got hurt real bad
Why what
Why would you this is such a lie
Masculinity
No and then
Lemon learn not to flip that switch
Even have that switch or you wouldn't want to go or you're trying to take us
Because you haven't been there as adults
You didn't go through Rites of Passage you're still trying to be men Zuckerberg
Cannot be part of this control freak
Ciocca Schmitt
All of you but
You just come from trash
That's why I guess trash begets trash
F****** in
Have you ever read
I would recommend
Aspire
Invite
Okay it's this
Near future
Science fiction
And
It is
Basically
Like
Reddit culture gamergate culture 4chan
Like Gone Wild in that
There's this one dude who is
Is just basically
So my love
His whole thing is like reclaiming
Testosterone flowers
It's it's
Right on with what
Terrifying
Man would go beat each other up in the woods
Roast
Yeah
Plan ahead
Whenever I
I got bullied a lot
And I was a nerd
I was chubby as a kid
Took me as a good Target
Yeah
Like
Going to kick your ass
Like come meet us over here no I will not
I never felt like I wasn't
Being a manly because I didn't go. Being a f******
Amanda
Globalist
F*** you
I support you take those fake teeth out and it's game on
I don't understand this fetishes
Asian
I don't understand what it is where
Masculinity is all that matters
I don't want to live in that world that's no
It's a bad world
I also don't want to necessarily live in Alex Jones is fake fantasy-world
Lesbian create
We're men and women don't exist
Or anything like that
Like I don't
The idea of trans identity and
Gender fluidity
Don't at all threatened masculinity orphan
No they don't at all if anything they
Games
From everything game
Accepting a broader spectrum of reality
It's okay
You learn
What it comes down to
We've hit on it
Couple times already
Episode it's that
I don't understand privilege
I don't understand
What these marginalized groups are actually saying
I take it personally and I get mad about
And frankly you don't understand the lesson
To be learned
From Westside
You love it
He learned one lesson and that is that he likes
To be in America
He's referencing the Warriors
Warriors come out to Alex do you remember that part in the Warriors where they
One guy tries to rape a police officer for that something Alex
In the middle of a broadcast Village
Remember that partner Warriors
Warriors
Kissena Park
Female police officer on a park bench
Have you gone
F**
Holyshit this was okay it's fine that was the world we lived
My six abroad
Strokes of the Warriors is a really interesting story that's being told
You can't
You can't go back and watch so many movies without being like
Do you like really clunky understanding of
People in the seven
Go back and watch
Eddie Murphy special without being like
No oh no oh nice, man
We only have a couple left
This
It's called I don't remember what it is but I know that it's him
I'm saying something really
Sincere and serious
I meant pivoting
Hard into an app
Which I always f****** love
How do you how do you
Is it from
White genocide is happening
My dad makes his toothpaste
Gods
Do not understand that you all right we got weird pills
Roundup
Also it is that you can see the transition from like
Demagogue Alex into salesman Alex
Call amount
Yeah calling all of them
Going to see you again
We defeat them we win
Not be a bunch of losers we've gotten to the point where anything's possible
Future
Also I'd like
I'd like to just take a second to be like
Also I like the idea of
A real bummer
The time you can't even think
You're losing if you're the one getting murdered but you're not you're well it'll feel like lose I don't feel out
Not like getting murdered
Celebrate
Unbelievable
If we wanted to celebrate our humanity and God to celebrate the Rites of Passage in New York
I got to get the clubs to briefly
We've come out with
I just had looked everybody bone broth is so good
Zombie Pub
Ever get super threesome feeling good I want to go out research stuff out there and come out tomorrow
Free paleo formula infowars.com purchase operation bone
Broth paleo ingredients
Selection ratio Advanced paleo nutrition
And it's the bones actually have with the marrow and all the rest of it the real
A lot Morris also
Pechanga mushroom
Alfalfa herb powder
Bee pollen
Turmeric root and so many other ingredients
Chicken broth
Chicken bones
Chicken noodle soup
Original chicken noodle soup
Concentrate
A bone marrow and
Huge businesses Newport
F****** happy
This is a new product he sounds so bored
Okay alright
We are more fast-paced endlessly fascinating the number of ingredients they have
Play pill
How could you even say that many ingredients
Also okay
Bone cartilage
How long
Before there's a box
Essay where it's just basically Charlton Heston going
Is mayonnaise made of
I don't know
Chickenpox the cleanest bone
What is that even
I don't know any of what you just said I don't know what he doesn't know either
What is it mean
Is there a
Chicken bones
Queen bum
Swainsboro
Cleanest cleanest
Is that a benefit
Who is just eating dirty bones
Grandma knew the chicken broth
Was important
So we're going to put a hundred times
You know how when you were like men my grandma wants me to eat the
Does Apple
So instead I'm going to
Yeah it's the same thing with like a supplement typing like
Percent of your daily intake of vitamin C because your body can't even absorb
Even want 5000 there's a reason 100
Percent exist
As a
Number listen
A5000
Scary sounds
Not going to lie to you
The 100th time what we're taking in now is just enough
For somebody who
Rave so often about cannibals
Seems like he's leaning towards
Implying
Hubert boat that's what it is
Don't lie
Call man
It's made of people
Be called caveman
It's already
Lucy
Oh yeah
The pillow.
Yep yep it's like what the great is like
We will
Spaceships in colonies named after us
Yeah
I'm going to get to the clip
But also
What are we going to
Nami this Colony super male Vitality make multiple
Lightyear
Trips
Pain pills
Phone bill
Gold
Pill
If you run out of pills
You also have a
Formula
Who make more bones
I have a leg
We're now we're now in
Snowpiercer run out of
That you get on auto-ship
Run out you always
Go ahead
Check out that femur grinded up real good
Infowars store.com sell the mortar and pestle
Colonnade
No we're not close to FEMA camps
We're going to go with I can't think of another bone
Tibia
Saturn
The Rings
Tibia ring
Tarsals metatarsals doesn't even matter
But do not eat
The coccyx that's what the Liberals herbalist would want
Alright
We got our last clip here is finally like two and a half hours into the show
Interview with David Horowitz
Write you later ends up doing interview
Maybe it's
David Horowitz
I'm sure someone has original
No one steal that desk
Have that what this is what he finally gets around to the Press
So I reckon it's a little bit longer
This is is in
Fire coverage
Of the hour and 10 minute or whatever press conference
Where he again
Blackhawk
Has personally reporters to shut up
Yep
Repeatedly one of them we played earlier about Hillary selling uranium to the Russians
He explained
How nuclear weapons work
E2n entire people
I did not need that information we already know it was a prick and sounded like an a******
Petulant 8
And now none of that
Could not imagine
Is not an analysis
Truth-teller
Bring the big news
Watch media design
He is reading a Infowars headlines because I don't even need you to tell me that
Year the Infowars headlines
F****** voice I hope all of you out there or starting
To get trained to decipher these things yourself
Bone
That's the way for a long while acknowledge
Acknowledge underscore fight tell us which Bones
Let's go
The Farms you're preparing
Total control
Make you pay more for 200 ft2 apartment than 1000 ft laughing at you
Justin
Greenwood Lake
40% of the things that he list
I mean we have supports
Massacre
Jobs in
Stock market research
Just Chicago's Park
That's bad
And you know what if the globalist
Are doing that
I will say right now
I am again
The Global Group
I am against
An imaginary group
That does exactly what
The Chicago mayor is going to do
He is against Natural Beauty
Well it makes sense
That's a good point
He only likes
You'll agree with me
What about him
Smiling face on TV
Playing really straight
Hilarious he's great on 30 Rock
You f****** liar who cares
I hope we have it like oh I'm going to take a shot at Brian Williams
Your protector if you're on Brian Williams
A real probably
Brian Williams released
Here's Williams
Didn't have any bearing on what I believe
I don't care
Nothing happens to agree with me
Whatever if Dave and it
Tells me that Trump is garbage
I'm like
Good on you Dave for my 20
And then he's like well did you know that they've never even work tonight and you're like what
I guess Trump is great now
All of a sudden
Defended their point is attacking
I do
F*** David Icke
Yeah it's so it's so better
So f****** funny if it weren't the reality destroying us from the inside
Absolute
Is a Muslim sympathizer CIA
He's got the documents
He doesn't just talk about John Brennan who he believes is a lobbyist
Because he has
Islamic sympathy
May or may not have converted to Islam
We did who gives a s***
Again
No reputable Source I can find
Any indication
Any kind of radical
Did you
Infowars
It's yet
Other
We already know
President
Would never happen
Male vitality
Mullen and the other stuff is not really about
It's not all over the news
Let's kill Trump
It's not it's
A hundred percent.
Really not
People would be getting f****** arrest can't say kill the president
Trump
Would love
Nothing more than four people that advocate
His dad
Raystown Unturned
Trump Associated political action committee was making robocalls
Yeah people trying to get Trump
Impeached
Exactly what someone crazy
It's a false flag it is
I don't know
If you'd necessarily involved
Put people who have on his side
We're pretending to be against him
To anger the people who are on his side
F****** insanity
It's insanity
Cuz you went on CNN
I think you're picking on some Iraq
Fake laugh
Economy going I mean
You guys walk down that road
It's like you're not even like
Wait
He does not understand that at all
He might have read Beowulf when he was sick
Grendel gets killed walking down the road
Going up like
The grendels on one side of the fence
Beowulf is Tim the toolman Taylor
I think we've lost I think we've lost track of the Grendel references
Mudskipper
To me that's a very
What the hell is your problem
Michelle
Boom Beach get out the way
Highway
What's going on
The way
Did he just drop
You just drop 10 hours
Got a reminder
Wait Joe
What the hell is your problem
Fitzgerald's back at yourself you're projecting on us again
Highway in the fast lane
F*** you and the show and he just got the goddamn verse
Better than motherfuking 10 bars right there
Daddy's right f****** there
Oh my God
That's the greatest thing how could you
Dropping
Hot f******
Fire right now that was just
Dumb Spazmatics
Did you see these headline I'm on the highway or oh my God
You know what
Holyshit
I wasn't there but you didn't care
That is
That is very holyshit
I want I want you to be able to see
Isn't space right now has been destroyed by this new information
Let me let me walk you through why I'm so
Bucking flummox
She does
Say that move b**** get out the way things a lot
Like Hillary in the election
Because I'm sure Ludacris
What is
I'm at a loss for words you are grappling with a lot of emotions
You never thought you're going to handle this
I don't know you doing the hippity you doing
The beatboxing
Let's do that one more time
Guys walk down that road
It's like
I went too far back
But also when this does
I need this to be clear
Is wrapping these work
It does it's not good we're not we're not arguing on the quality of his Rabbi don't want anyone out there
Think that I
Week
But you're not even like you're more like a
1 ft tall grandmother
Do not alter bike rental bulshit
Just yourself
Boom beach boom
The crowd she was pretending he's alive
She's at the run the jewels show and he is is
F****** fantastic
I just destroyed your Paradigm will like look
Really psychoanalyzing him as a child and all this
You did not know
But that's why he's a f****** like I've described him as a propaganda under layers
There's just
No more
There's no deeper to go and Alex Jones or I can never be surprised surprised
Always
Consistently surprised by Alex Jones and I'm surprised
Prepare like I said I pulled these clip drunk last night so
Anyway let's get through this and see what happens after the rapping
Genuine something you'll never have Ginuwine
The way
I just had a horrifying song
What
What if
Michelle
Avant-garde
Jazz
Talk
A performance-art jazz scat
What if
We have to
Completely delete all of the old ones
We're starting fresh from the Duke
This is Scatman Caruthers
Holy Ship
Wow it's oh my God
I love it
They were only
Esteban piles of crap
Come on anymore
Let's go ahead
New York Lottery Angeles
In particular
Very very
Obviously
And we don't talk about it
We are doing a scamander
Disturbance to the American people
Penny's Diner
It was paired with their families and their communities
So long as they weren't talking article
Power truck
The power structure
I can't listen to this now without questioning whether Trump is laying a lazy verse
I've been infected now.
I'm looking for M anywhere and it just pick one
Destroyed
Oh man
Really wish you had
God I wish
His voice were nowhere near
Yeah pitlick
It won't be too much longer
F****** crazy
Alex
Is playing just this quick because it's where he's not interacting
Question
Prepared statement
Observe
Doesn't sound crazy
Because he's not being hold on
So you only like what he just said
Comparatively speaking
Doesn't sound crazy
That's how
Through the Looking-Glass baby
Through what they have to go through
35%
Yeah
I don't fully disagree with him again government is always a mess
Is always entrenched interests
Natsu have to untangle
But he inherited
Compared to what
Inherited
8 years prior
It's Unthinkable to think that he
Do you know what I've never come out there and be like
Wow this is a mess
I've never looked at a pile of laundry on my floor
Damn it I hate this mess
You know what I'm going to do
Burn the blame.
Keep the store going to blame whoever sold me these clothes wherever they came from
Inherited this f****** meso what I'm going to
Is I am going to
What what
I haven't done laundry
So I'm going
To tell everyone who says I stink
Okay
How about start from the beginning
All right and I'm going to drop
I'm on the highway
On-the-fly way
Like this.
Home and abroad
Amen jobs are pouring out of the country
They're not be what's going on with
Definitely not
Ability overseas don't matter where you look
Cuz the Middle East
Take care of it all
How
Preemptive like
Alright when this goes poorly just know that it's not my
Do it work a little bit but I know and I'd my bosses know I'm kind
Kind of line that are overdue
I'm just starting
I can't get all of this
First realtor first rule of government
Blame the guys before
For it
Go for it
Here. You're doing what everybody else
I mean
We're killing people with flying robots
The Middle East
It's been a mess
I think it's in the Bible
Is in the Bible
North Korea
Agreed
Yeah
His thing we're going to take care of it it's the scariest part of North Korea North Korea
I am afraid of trump saying
We're going to take
Caravan
Because anytime he says we're going to take care of it in my mind I hear
Exactly
Kill Kim Jeong Hoon
Brother
And the lady who
Killed him
Thought it was a prank show
What the f***
You know what's even crazier
Implying that Kim John
Probably has a false flag
The only thing makes sense
He was a Defector
He left
Korea
Like his dad
Like him that's why Kim Jeong Hoon isn't power I didn't know anything about that
He's got it
Anyway
Getting a day when our Administration went to work
Foreign Affairs we've already begun enormously productive Thoughts with minibar and later
Ability security
Troubled regions of the world
Wichita
Yep
Really really productive
That's right we're looking to Alex
They're his words
Just to say that
Promote women
Directions
Advance Community Health
He's over there now working very hard
A group that celebrates the murder and torture of
Large sections of the world
Used to be a small group
Directions
Of the world
Can we not listen
Lovelace
Pioneering
Thank you Alec
Thank you for that
Trible's
She made the deal took the money did it
Know-it-all
30 +
Didn't
Criminal law
That's what government supposed to do
And
Okay
So Sor Boogeyman
Now
I'm your boogie man
Are the Press
Big time Big X price
There's another one Boogeyman
Now
Are we so low on Boogeyman that we're still going after Hillary
Hillary Hillary is actually directing the
The press to do what it's doing
Through Soros funding
And what have you
There's a unified field theory of Boogeyman
Me or the world is over
Stop
Shooting on Hillary
Again
Let Her Go Let Her Go
Well
Hint
Because there are so few
If know is
If there is a terrorist
Attack
It's over
Right
What Nara I mean
If if
Trump gif
If the government we have now gets it
Terrorist attack
Sentence on America
If there's like a 911
Yeah yeah
They get to end the world
Basically going
To do Trump has indicated he's very willing
Nuclear weapons
If there's any kind of justification for it
Yeah because he thinks that will help
Books on nuclear weapons when he was sick
Arthritis Alex
Now that Alex
Trump
Trump has been
Planning
Since he was 12
She's been aware
Trump has known The Game Plan
I'm
Listen
I want to go both we both ran out of gas
Immediately once the wrap
Ulta
Is just him responding yet now there's no way this is going to snow
The parts of Trumps
Press conference that are not on hinge
I'm not yelling it
Members of the press
Complete dick to people for no reason
Registering a series of Lies I think about how
Out-of-control he was how abusive he was
Two people
Israel
Unhinged a man shouting lies
Yeah what reporter asked him about the
Bomb threats
Synagogue around
No he's a phrase
His answer was
People make this claim I hate this claim I am the least racist person you'll ever hear
I'm the least anti-semitic person
Alex Drummond
Play Van
I quit because if he did
He would have to be like okay now here
Trump has no listening comprehension understand what this person is actually asking her
Trump's gold argument
He did not get a good score
Every single question that was asked at that press conference was not answered
According to the question that was
So Alex doesn't talk about
Any of that
All he does
Is her about
5 minutes of his
3 hour broadcast
You takes 5 minutes
To play the part where Trump is just talking
And not answering question
He's lying
But he's not yelling and he's not
Combative
He's like
Now the media is going to
That he's crazy
Issaquah
Is that the only part that you're actually listening to like if you're getting all of your news from Alex
You might think of that other stuff didn't happen even if that's the only part you're listening to
Brazy
If not if you actually believe there are globalist Boogeyman
Razee the media should spin
If that was all that I read on a transcript
I don't know why
Buzz Marketing
No in Spanish
The only transcript
That would be enough for me
They're supposed to
Okay
I knew
Play thoughts
When you want it I would prefer if
You put it
Add to Apizza
Okay
This podcast
John how do we how do we
I don't know
Beautiful us on Twitter
Books on iTunes
On Twitter
ITunes
Does knowledge fight please give us a review five stars
Playing with you this promise if you email and knowledge fight at gmail.com
I will send
No one's taking me up on it yet but I'm ready also I want to make this offer
Bring start montage
Famous podcast a little bit if you guys want
Support the show
I have a patreon up
Patreon.com freezing point
It's just
List of all the podcasts that I do
If you donate
You will receive in the mail
What are the wine bottles
Autograph
Autographed wine bottle
For your mantle
If you wanted to donate appreciated
Possibly imagine
Also if you donate let's say
Don't know
$100 a month
We will give you bone pills made out of
Freezing
$100 a month
A hundred dollars a month
Bridges net worth
We will make
Lock her up
Pixolotl work feeling inside this is
Super fun to do and we love you guys so much for making cool stuff
Jordan
Thank you so much for joining
As well
A couple of f****** Paula
Ewoks
Alexandra Thurston color