Alexandra Thurston color
Little bit about Alex Jones
We do Dan
Yep yep yep
What's up
So much about him
I know I'm sorry I'm not good at the two-man game
Speaker
Before we get into
Today's episode
I mean
The 121
Let everyone know a big congratulations out to our friend Jordan here
For making an amazing homemade pizza
Went over to your your place you made a great
I think it's I think it deserves a celebration of Seifert need to know about
Is my second go-around
The first one
Not good
But this one was a fantastic
Chick-fil-A hours
I got a couple of amazing Polly
To give a shout out to today
This is Big League stuff not not I'm not that other people and their donation
The show aren't awesome they're all
Fantastic
But but today
We got to give a shout out to
But for reasons I'll explain here in a minute
20 global
Just right off the bat
Damn
So I'd like to give a shout out to
Our new policy wonk
Is a globalist
As a sweet ass name
Thank you so much
Amanat Ali Aprilia someone sodomites
Thank you so much because you are broke
You couldn't donate
This day
The reason
Great music
That could be him up to globalist
Right off the bat
Is along with the donation
Can you send an awesome message
I've been listening for all the old episodes
The catch up on April 17th 2017 you mentioned buying
Fill your hand. Com
And redirecting it to your site
You didn't do it
So I did so thank you so much man
It's the coolest thing ever and now if you go to feel your hand
Which is awesome in love
The way that I am in love with you right now
Cool cuz I had forgotten that we even said that
Yeah that's the cool thing
Someone who I mean
Do you know this
Is obviously a pseudonym or maybe it's
Not in fiction is reality
Democrat
You so much
John Wick
Someone sodomites
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much John Wick
We Are Men
If that is a look
If that's like a sending a black.
Puppies with recently 008
I just got a message
From somebody that on April 12th
That's why John Wick 2 name is not true
I swear
Really awesome
If you'd like to become
You may
Do so by website
Esports Joe Biden
Honestly I'm very self-conscious about this
Yeah I know so far
It's crazy
I feel like I have low energy
You know I feel like I need a good job thinking those people
Various
You know what today
Look up and I don't know what it is
I'm not in it
I tried
It could have been the pizza to get it up
54 like the show today
Can't do it I just
I'm not interested in it I really tried to force it
It's one of the challenges of doing a show like this
Does like sometimes it's not fun
Studying portion especially is not
Fun and toys
Gotta I gotta
I got it I got to show up
And I do have an idea
The fun episode for us to do today
Flu Game is that you're under the weather and you're still going to f****** deliver is that what's going on
We'll see how that turns out.
Talk to me after the show
I really I really
My heart and soul wasn't in this
But I think it's going to work out okay
But
My heart and soul
Dammit
20 second
AR
March Madness bracket
Because I kind of
A little bit
I didn't will do a bunch of matchups on the next episode
Three guests division
Not surprised to report Steve
Botanica
Hamamoto
How I was
Religious
Division Heavy Hitters
Number for Speed in the religious division
Was that from January of
This year
When Alex Jones was out
Some of the people celebrating at the inauguration
Amanda
He said this
About meeting
Need to go pray
Text
I like those Metallum Alex
The b*******
I got to pray.
Yes infowars.com is Grace
I think the selection committee probably put that in the four-seat over some of his lengthy
What's about the devil
Because of the fake tears
The fake beers
I'm a guy yelling bulshit
Surprise
Literally nobody
The number one
From our first episode ever
It might be time
Red Alert
This is getting crazy
This is so freaking out of control
It's time to pray
He's helped us
Pray
I just love the
Red Alert
The Rhythm on that if you recall the reason that he was going into that you know thinking that it's time to
Despres was because he thought the Benjamin Netanyahu was going to get arrested immediately
Hey why I think the
Unfortunately this might be another one that's
The upside
Don't be very difficult
Any kind of first episode
Battle for the b******* Gallery at the rally
Facebook group
Go home
I'm leaning towards that as the favorite for the Holt
It's going to be tough for something else to come in
Although I have
Some surprises
I have something you might have forgotten absurd
Speaking of horses
God dammit
But you said you weren't
Just muscle memory
I can do that asleep
Jordan
Like I said I didn't care for his show today I found it very boring and didn't want to play
Games with it and I was trying to
Think about like
Maybe today
We go back and we go to 2008
Birthday
Way too much time I didn't have the time to do it
And I don't want to half-ass but I don't want to half-ass anything
And that is
The David Charlie Sheen destroyed his own life on Alex's show
Do you not remember this
I remember I remember him destroying his life I didn't remember that it was on Alex's
Let me give you a little bit of History
So
At the time
In 2011
Charlie Sheen was making 1.8 million dollars per episode on Two and a Half Men
And what would be his last
Season of the show
Also
He had to
Little bit of backstory on him
Had a stroke after overdosing on cocaine
January 1990 she and accidentally shot his fiance in the arm
Accidentally shot hernia Google
Let's just called the Burrows special
Misdemeanor assault charges involving his wife
Brooke Mueller in August 2010 receiving the sentence
Anger management counseling
His second wife Denise Richards
Accuse him of physically and verbally abusing her threat
Shooting a restraining order against
On October 26th 2010 Charlie Sheen was removed from the Plaza hotel after doing over 7,000
Dollars in damage
Just did a property
According to the New York New York Police Department
Charlie Sheen came that night
I was going to say I thought you were going to say he did over $7,000 of Coke
Warriors 2011
When production
Was forced into hiatus
Because Charlie had to go to rehab after he was hospitalized following a Coke binge
The third time
He tried to get clean in the past
Then on February 18th 2011
Charlie Sheen went on the Alex Jones Show
Then acted like a drugged-up idiot
Which is literally the reason he ended up
Getting fired from his show
Wow
All of that stuff
Charlie Sheen public meltdown
All of it started on Alex Jones
We're going to listen to you cuz I was like
Interesting Lee klusterfuk
In like later because Alex
Is the beginning of this dark
Alex goes on The View today
What might be where you getting for Barbara Walters connection
Yeah
Start screaming allowed Alex pretty wild
Cuz he keeps trying to say electronic drugs
Amanda
It just turn
Turns into people yelling over each other he wants
To talk about the bank
What have you
And Whoopi is like
Can we please talk about Charlie Sheen
I'm like everybody remembers the
The Tiger Blood everybody remembers a lot a lot of these quote
What they forget is a lot of them started on Alex Jones Show
That was proven true
The black nobility
So this is a fateful day
That it's interesting that history is Rewritten
Because the public meltdown went so much further
His appearance
On Alex Jones
On the show
Kick-started a lot of
Forgot
In the General Public
We are not ones to forget
There's not a lot to do bunk here
There's ripped
Really just we're going to end up listening to Charlie Sheen act like an idiot and Alex Jones last cuz he know that this is going to get him so much
Get me on The View
Houston says type higher than that but whatever
Spoiler alert
I thought it was just
It's a lady Dykstra
Everybody knew who Nails was I know that's
I know that the two of them were talking about specifically Lenny Dykstra
The only person
He shows up at the end of the interview
Dykstra shows up
We don't
Wait did you just have a dizzy just know when people are speaking about him in the aethersphere
They're all friends
Listen to any of that because
It just the reality of Alex Jones talking to Charlie Sheen and Lenny Dykstra
Is overshadowed by how boring it is it's really nothing is
Disappointed
He wants to be
Daddy I want
Tell Charlie Sheen on a fake
Property
That's the goal I have there
Extra
Guy awesome
Which I would argue with both him and Alex being bad friends
Anyway
Is a variable
What's going on
Absolute home
Here's your first pee test next one goes in your mouth now you won't get high
All good
Well yeah but there's only one time in the gym if you
The clipse not done but
Throughout
This time and whenever Alex goes on The View
They're referencing also after this
Charlie Sheen
Cameras into his house
And they publicly took
His blood to be tested
It's kind of interesting because blood test
For drug use
Is
Credibly
Credibly Acura
Mega Gallade it's very good
Good for finding stuff
But
Detectable in your blood the window is
Very short
So for instance
Amphetamines aren't detectable after like
Hours
24-hours barbiturates
Possibly about a day or two
Could be
Quick is
6 hours later is out of your blood cocaine generally about 12 hours
Detectable in your blood
So
I don't know I'm not convinced
PCP about 12 hours
Is generally speak
PID
Proving that he's not doing drugs
Give blood is like
That's that's ridiculous
Committed to that
Thumbs up together
Meltdown just call
Me neither
Somebody who is
Clearly
Mentally ill on
Tapas
Doing all that like now
You're not
You don't wind up doing a s*** ton of cocaine and and all of the s*** without having some underlying
Mental issue
She's going on
Clear that
Use if not of my people at least
Do the bipolar
It was like
A little bit of
You stop punching up whatever you're mocking
Celebrity
Restart real
Does the celebrity person gets eclipse
Spivey human portion of it and it's
Right yeah that whole time. Is very uncomfortable for me cuz I didn't know if
Painful
This is business really tough to watch
I think my biggest issue.
Alex went to Charlie's house
Hi everybody in French for long time
I don't know
All the time he does sometimes
Essenza playing out
He doesn't want to bring it up
Especially
I don't want to tease
Too much but the stuff that Charlie Sheen has said
Lately about this period of his life
I don't think Alex wants to associate men
Okay
Because Charlie Sheen's retconned whole bunches
Okay let's say
Spoiler alert the steroid cream
He looks back on his like this time
Friends with Charlie when he
Famous
Possibly her that he the moment he's like
I got to find
Famous brands
I think so I think
I don't know I don't know if there's
I don't know what
Gilna
Possibly
Defend yourself
What is going on
Women
The goddesses
Carmen
Good enough is good enough
The State Theatre restaurant
Description
Marriage
Yeah yeah
Excuse but but
Never has
We all have them
Is a is a marriage of the heart
Disrespected
Preppers
You nailed
Mailed
Weather
Boots with strange there
Win-win somebody like that uses
Goddess
That is simply another way to meeting with
Sing for him to like
Terrestrial words aren't enough
F*** you
Talkin about the pornstars
He's hanging out with
Hey I don't judge
No neither do I but it's just have to look at the pic
Picture of what he was doing at that time
Gazelle
Actually we'll even get to
Talk about like weather
I believe then wife
Is involved with
Shenanigans
And you're very
Spin on it
Is that where they were for
You're going to need it
And and and and we are and I don't know anyone
What will Charlie have known you for
664 South
You are now
I was really really flattered that he got it right that I'm not getting he might be nails but I'm freaking
Winning
Every second
Underwear before my first cup of coffee because
Ugly wives and children and just look at their loser lives and then they'll give me
That does sound a lot like Alex Jones
Add to some extent
Concentrated version of the ship that Alex Jones is spread out over overtime
Cuz I bet
Wanted to
You could go back
Can find a little chunk of different sentence
Then put all of those trucks
Together and it would be worth
Yeah
Alex is that same
Also I'm
Interested now because
Alex Jones
Percent of coke with Charlie
But there's a decent I don't know if we can
I don't know if
Very high
And I
Code for
Yeah we did a lot of Coke
I can't refute that I don't know I think it's
Will ever be able to prove
Entirely possible whatever
The issue here is that like this is irresponsible
Like
You suck
Attention grabber you such as you so desperate for any kind of attention that'll come to him
But he knows that like
Everyone's going to be recognizing the damage
Probably come to
The reputation in the life
Someone he considers a friend
That's bad that's not a good human thing to do like if you came in here one day you were all f***** up
And you started
Talking nonsense
You'll see some of the other shity end up saying
Lake
I would not put that out or I would tell you to
Just shut up and try and get the interview on track
George Webb
Substance
What's the matter is
Do that
Using
He's using Turnpike
Cruel thing to
That's one of the reasons I wanted to go over there
I mean not as much as it is interesting
A lot of that madness has its roots
Herein
Alex's show
These sort of Cruelty of Alex's allowing
Him to do that
Is
That's why I hate
Giving you positive feedback
Bringing the goods
Get to where things were fairly problematic
It is one of the big reason
Exit strategy
Children in the world
Effortlessly and magically appear gold
His job which is to write
Above-the-law
Dude
He's talking about Chuck Lorre
Got a little
Little bit
Quizlet calling him Haim Levine
Because his real name is Charles Michael Levine
Geheim part is
Probably just
Directly
You are a true
I embarrassed him and his Jew children in front of the world like
Chuck Lorre
Changed his name because his mother was never a fan of his father's family
When displeased with Mason Rudolph
You know what you are you're Lovin
A no-good rotten Levine
As far back as I can remember every time I heard my last name mote experience
Acute feelings of low self
Is that
Songs of take
Toll on me
Mysteries not trying to hide
Is Jewish Heritage or whatever you know like it's not it's not
And the fact that you know Charlie is
Is that using that is
Some sort of an insult
Is really the reason
But he got into trouble
From Guardian article here
Filming of the 30-minute show two and a half
Do the restart next week after Sheen's latest out of Rehabilitation
For drinking drug
Until he hit the self
Destruct button
Spectacular Style on Thursday
We spoke to a radio jock
Call Alex Jones
Her CBS
Holding company Warner Bros television
Probably most stuck
McCraw was it
Tirade
Against the Creator and Lead writer of Two and a Half Men Chuck Lorre
That's probably
You know the world believes
That was bigger
That that's real bad and probably a big part of why he
What are more innocent
Radio jock
Why Alex Jones
What Preamble in the current time
No
Title
Charlie's
Big catch phrases
Get deployed
Just Luna
Yeah
People pushing around
Understatement
I just I'm sorry man I got my fingertips
Most of the time in this is snaps
F-18 bro
Are you in the air and I will I will I will deploy my ordinances to the ground
Yeah I sat with 218 to Top Gun
Radical fire Napalm dropping Pilots
Taxi
Because they wanted to in those people working their way
And I and I was getting a tattoo
Is the
Is the Apple from The Giving Tree tears my life deal with it losers winning
Roof
What what
I didn't understand what tracks are there
The combination of the death card that is referencing
An apple from the
I don't know I don't know I mean Blake look like I said there's nothing to really debunker they
It's almost impossible to Deacon
Instruktur track
Any of this stuff like
The lines of thinking of our three movie theater
You are you sitting with two F-18 fighter pilot
I don't know man it doesn't matter
Stop the f****** Tatooine
Two artists
I should do that I can't afford to hire
This much per hour
Alex talks about
Future movies
Charlie Sheen
He was going to be a part of
The rumor Mills
I'm moving along here a major league 3
Genius
Sting
The classic
The movie called wild thing
What whatever I am I going to do it there's just one there's one deal Point than Jim Robinson wonderful man
If they don't
Glass
Huge fake laps per minute
SPM
Came out 1989
Major League
Who came out in 1994
Major League back to the minors came out in 1998
I mean I'm splitting
Here's a little bit cuz they're already in the third film
A proper sequel
Since that one did so poorly
Really bad
It's just a
It was really weird in Back to the minors whenever the
Disgraced nuclear physicist
Was murdered trying to buy
Is that a different movie
NASCAR does get thrown
Anyway
Alex
Charlie Sheen the
$64,000 Question
Which is why
Did you decide to come and do this on Infowars
A really big class
He does my answer would be
Yeah I figure the stakes are low
If you're going to do something like this
It's a
Bet that most people aren't going to pay attention to Alex
But you forget that your own celebrity in
Is Charlie Sheen's on Celebrity
Which would be down here
To another level
Have you are going to pay attention to it if they were live
To my mind what I hear there is
Alex
Who's calling me
Alex told me that I should call him
He-Man
Interviewing
I didn't really realize
His perceptions were they was not a show
Yeah I think
Timur anyting
Although
Brought up
Then
Truth
That Alec
Text John
Run Charlie Sheen's career almost single-handedly Charlie Sheen did it to himself but Alex
Has a role to play and if I
Any professional would absolutely
And then we get another one of those
A big old catch phrases from the
Yes.
Broadcast
Cuz I'm just
You can leave a warning
They should not dumb I'm just not
Target
It's over
There's a new sheriff in town
Army of Assassins
I Will Not Waste My Precious time on on on Kentucky
Curiosity
American Assassin
It's right there in the thing
Havana Cafe
Call Mariana
And nails
Darlene Arlington in my life
That we are high priest
People
Context of this episode
I know that
A lot of people made a lot of hay out of the Vatican
Assassin's game ends at like maybe he actually thought the back in the past
Sims were after him
And what have you
I don't know what that's like
I kind of lean towards what you're saying
Text I'm able to glean from this episode
And I'm decided to talk
About on air
As if something
Trolling
Thought about
While they were all doing a lot of coke together and Trust shootouts
Entirely possible
Do you know when you do Coke
You don't end up just doing nothing
Sometimes you watch a movie
Or hang out with Lenny Dykstra
Anytime anybody does coke Lenny Dykstra
Shows up
Nails
Weird breakdown of Apocalypse Now
It might have been
And so it is next Cliff we get Charlie is very bizarre take
Isabel
Also I'm getting from the chat room from Nikki gifts
Straight out of prison
Congratulations hell
Not not good but
Good for him
You can say other than genius represents wife
How to how to live inside of a moment between a moment
Because
Do you know I'm not just I'm not just
My dad and I'm heading up the river to kill Another Part Of Me wishes cards
Every character in between
Actually
My my motto now is you either love
Family
In the middle I don't live in the middle anymore.
Embarrass
That is his his tremendous focus and tremendous Clarity intermittent keys
You have absolute and total resolve about your decisions if you love with violence
Slips Pinterest
SantaCon
Apocalypse
I don't think that was Joseph Campbell
But I don't I don't think so I don't think it was a
I don't think it was like
Everyone's trying to destroy your family except your family
Colonel Kurtz
I don't
I mean I don't I don't like that
I don't like that is a sloth
I don't like that is a way to look at the world
Martin Sheen
I wonder how Charlie's doing
Do you think he's doing okay
Sort of
I don't know
Martin's on Livernois
And I was old
Yeah he's old and he's still on that show with the one where the turns out they're gay and they were married to
If they're best friends or whatever it's
It's on Netflix
I don't know I don't have Netflix
But I pretty
Completely forgot to learn
Yeah I know
Coronavirus
Very helpful
Yeah so I know Emilio Estevez is doing great
Starring in a major leagues
Turnouts
Just wondering
Like if you're if you're still Martin senour still famous in
And you're still
Do what you're still work
And your son
Exploded his career in everything about his life
Yeah how do you react to that
Like I know they don't have a particularly close relationship
I would assume
I don't know because also you have to consider Tuesday
You know
As we'd certainly doubt it very rough
Details you know certainly not a full picture
Charlie Sheen have a history of
Domestic violence dating back
89 or whatever and he's been in and out of rehab center around that time
So like as a parent you
Kind of probably
It diminished expectations
Perhaps Perhaps
You kind of have to for your own protection
Right like understand that there's just
It's just a reality gear
There's there's nothing worse than what a parent
Has to bury their
Let's
Number of people in the world who has the heads up
Abuse issues in a
Have been able to turn their life around
Through the help of the program
Right there number
People who advocate for Alta
Ternative program certainly there's you know a a is
Isn't the only way to go or an A
There are other non
Space Bass
Sort of organization
Innovation bubble that criticism
Thrown around a lot
Of the higher power
Component
Switch lot of people
Misrepresent
Understand to me and that you have
But
Frozen does not like
Charlie
Charlie Sheen
Cleanse myself I close my eyes
Ridiculous
Simple syrup
Chapter Book of Lies
Necessarily a drug of abuse
You know in the same way that alcoholic
Is it not really
You can't really do it all the time
It's really hard to do all the
Most people will never have to even
Color come close
To the idea of being addicted
New lsv
But be that as it may
The point that
Has
Have you heard of anybody who was a dick
It's something with like mushrooms
If you can't do too much of it your body that won't allow yeah
I have you do a bunch
Chevelle.
Having as much of
Given the fact you'll just naturally look
GameStop
Chemicals I don't understand
Tattoos psychedelic
You can absolutely do to it
You do too much
Some sort of a
Jeff Foxworthy's setup
If you go to manager
You might do too much ass
It's not good
Nope
I just did a bad thing
So I would I would
Suggest that
His rhetoric about AAA is
I would suggest
That based on
Everything
You did not
Cure himself of addiction Indiana
Kind of thinking
Time
Multiple times
The failed attempts at rehab
You
Here's the thing that's why that 54
Unsuccessful
Siding for AAA does have
Pretty low
Success rate as a whole people who decide
Quit on their own
That success rate
Subway
Addiction does
Require a lot of
Personal
Will
You can tell whether or not you have a program
And there's a couple pieces
That are born that everyone
Go through recovery nose
That relapse
Does a part of recovery
And you're going to end
End up failing
I'm just getting back on track
I meant Beyonce
It's anonymous
And I don't know if you're able to really get a good
Statistical
A perfectly accurate portrait
That's a good point
I think the success rate is lower than we would hope
Bye
Leaving people it within their own
Addiction
That usually leave
For prison
Yeah so
I'll take it by force
Success rate if that's what it is
Better than zero
Things like a game
And stuff like that I don't know I don't know enough about
I've heard some people
Suggesting that it's a very powerful
Cure for addiction
Sounds
Like a very heavy hallucinate
Oh okay
You hear people talking about how like you're going
Doing ayahuasca
Cured the most
I think it's possible
Servant
McLean vet
Taking
LSD is
Way of
Kind of
Lessening your symptoms of
Read a lot about
A lot of
Philip said that they
Haven't had to deal with that is
Stringent AAA
Or even like
To be helping with
PTSD
I know it's outside of
Mystery like
Madison-kipp possibility
But there is a there's a world of recovery outside of AA
I'd rather him espoused
Supposed to
These stupid assholes I cured myself in a nanosec
Yeah the guy who ran the organization
And was I
But the thing that I
Think about
Listening
Into this kind of chocolate
Clearly he's
He's
At the veterinary least having a manic episode
Throughout
This hole.
Perhaps
Look at that
What it is the
Sycophantic
Do to those kind
The form of
Yeah
I'm not just Alex but all of the people around him at that
Nails
Giving him that kind of
Ego and narcissism
And allowing that
Spread
Allowing
To be as far as
If you are
Charlie Sheen
You have a mass
The platform
To say something
Positive
Because you're surrounded by these
To tell you that everything you say is
That is a pause
What you saying is I am opening people's eyes
In the same way that
Jones is surrounded by those
Sycophants who just
Everything you do is the greatest possible person
All of the negative s*** that you are putting
Is
Is viewed by you as something that you're doing to help jump bigger
It's like all this
Tough love
Need to break you free of this concept of
Being a better
Carson Daly
AAA is trying to
Charlie Sheen
I think he probably thinks that
So you know Alex Jones fancies himself a
Classical liberal Alexa Collins
The classical liberal in the Thomas
Jefferson Mall
It is something really weird about Thomas Jefferson
Be one of us
Flashlight
Thomas Jefferson
Alright
Alright I would have thought I expect you to be like
Now we're going to get into all of the fight that Thomas Jefferson was over the years I would expect Alex to be like
You're now inviting
Important founding
Father-in-law
He has this is one of those
Alex has no actual Prince
If I want you to like me
I will a
Agree with every
Any heavy lifting at all or trying to leave the conversation into greener pastures
He's just like
Doing is fake laugh
Sincere laugh
Batman just being like anyone
Allowing him to play himself out
Charlie spray bullets everywhere
It allows them to do this
To read a note from one of his goddesses
Who's on the air is about nothing
Listen
Iran air
And it just says I'm blessed and perfect my insane life is
My monkey man like seeing my high priest ninja warlock I love you violently with the fire of 1000
Experienced Jedi Mind Powers amazing humor and unconditional love
I am truly honored
View
By your side
The capital c
I don't know why that
Should be on Alex's
The show I don't understand
He's completely lost control of the interview like it's just
It's just not
It's just allowing Charlie Sheen to be weird in public
Well yeah that's
What he wants
Controlling the
Debs
Because if Charlie's stopped
Is Charlie
Really just kind of calmed
The down was like
Let's talk about the global
Alex Wood
Pissed
Probably
Cuz that's what's going to
To notice me and it worked
Beyond Alex
If we talked a little bit about poetry
Panda
Charlie Sheen
Sure
Jedi Mind
One of my favorite poets is Eminem
Not like that sentence one bit
Eminem inspires me to stay violin
That's what I like in my power
Stop by tonight alive
Now Clash Royale
It's better that you said Eminem
I'm just a violin
Instead of being like
Emily Dickinson
She really inspires me to stay violet
After awhile Lenny Dykstra comes in
Makes clear
Charlie Sheen's got a job
Call me early
I wait
Certainly on fire my friend
Not good
No sense text at 3 in the morning
Your time
Yeah
So you may have to work on that Tuesday
In February but Charlie
I got in trouble
I got fired
His contract was terminated with two-and-a-half-men on March
7th 2011
3 days later
On March 10th
Charlie and apps to Nationwide
I tore called my violent torpedo of Truth
The Detroit opening night show sold out in
18 minutes
But a closer look revealed that at least 1,000
It's been bought by a third-party reseller and
Sold a cut-rate prices
Terribly cut-rate price
On April 2nd
Detroit show hap
Which is the opener
The tour
And it was
His opening act
Stand-up comedian got booed off stage
6:20
I am Gathering of the Juggalos
Those are the two that Giggs I don't want to
I have no idea
I knew a guy
No I think
When around opening
For Screech
It was described it as
Are you go to casinos you have to
Do 10 minutes
Plenty of money
And very shortly thereafter he was a
Party screeches
So
You're having the money part is nice
Since you don't care about all the stuff
Comes along with that
I have to drive around with Screech all day that does not sound
Violent torpedo of Truth tour in Detroit
Seems
Equally bad I want to know who that guy
I probably could have figured out but I didn't want to look into it just in case
Even if
Sing his name is
It feels pretty
Talking about the
People who were in Charlie Sheen's life who aren't named Lenny Dykstra
Because in some ways
Maybe they're
Actions were complicit in
Like enabling him
Stuff like that
But I don't feel
I don't I don't feel like it
It's necessary to point a finger at them
Just did
I think I would take that game
For the story is maybe it's a great game either way you're open
Hang up for Charlie Sheen
Losing is f****** my I would I would I would like to do is I get that invitation
I say
No but Jordan perfect for it and then I come along and I watch
Call Austin good
That would be the most satisfying booed off stage of my life
Alex has Charlie Sheen
Michelle to ramble for 40 minutes like an 80
During which time
Call
Chuck Lorre
I'm Lovin
Throws
Very dog-whistle a Jewish
Consult
Crazy person
And it does
End up going viral and it leads
To him getting fired
Community Behavior after-the-fact didn't help
Get a raise
Alex didn't do all of it but
Started this ball down the road
I guess actually probably
Be having to hold
Production to go to rehab
That certainly plays a part in it but I think a lot of it could have been smoothed out if you didn't go on
The national radio show
And say those things about Chuck Lorre and then also say
He won't do his job
Cans into gold
I think that you could probably on
The damage that you do to halting production
Because of your addiction problem
I think you could probably smooth that out
But this is too far because this is
The reason that he kept going
Probably
Everybody wants
To talk to him about the interview
Even more even a larger platform
To say his crazy
I meant Alex Jones
Love you too publicly defend him. Stokes the fires
Even further
Fired
And then almost immediately
Store
Thanks Amigos on the
I want to talk a little bit more about the Detroit show
It's such a
Like I got that his opening act
Gets booed off stage
F*** is going on
Cuz it was supposed to have a rocket
Party
Rockstar atmosphere like I don't want to hear that guy DuPont
Turned immediately
About 20 minutes after the actual show starts
The Boost are being directed at Charlie
Because he's just rambling a bunch of bulshit
You start
The show-off playing like weird video packages
And stuff and having his goddesses come out on stage
Great people are just
Not f****** Intuit
They start about 20 minutes
Pretty quick
Best route
I think that is just a
Celebrity would give a grace period of more than 20
It turns out you don't
So in response to all the Boos he says
Quote I already got your money dude
Which does not make the crowd happier
Sheen says he's going to quote tell some stories about crack
I figured Detroit was a good place to tell some crack story
This comment not surprisingly does not go over well
Quotes
A few people raised their hands
I don't do anymore good f****** night to do some crap
The audience Boos
About an hour in people start walking
Hangout is Charlie composes
The tweet on stage
Later Charlie Play the rap track he made with Snoop Dogg
They would be there but he was a no-show
Because he was performing
Nickelodeon Kids Choice Awards
Does a tragic how far how far away was that from
Is it Los Angeles
Do the show is taped
Elephant the room we've not really addressed
Too much is
Charlie Sheen came out
And publicly acknowledged
Videos HIV
A lot of the stuff
About
The chaos in his life
I believe he's
Traced some of it towards
Like they're being a
The parallel path
Like dealing with a diagnosis
Yeah stuff like that
His personal life
And all that
The stuff
It is a relates to that
I don't really want to talk
Right I feel
I feel very weird talking about any of that
I don't I don't know
You know you read about people's personal private lives
You hear something that's pretty
Messed up
Here
Their side of it
I don't I just don't want to
It's not really important for our Shout
But
He was coming out and Pub
We talked about that
Hugo on
The claim that the
Entire episode
Of his
Tiger blood
I have portrait coming out of my fingers
Vatican assassins nonsense
I was all about
Quotes
The ABC News Good Morning America
Life quotes
It's fun to kind of watch
Sometimes but also it's just a little printable
It's like what the hell was that
I was doing way too much testosterone cream
I'm trying to get the old libido up
He added
Call
Listen to basically a Roid Rage
That whole Odyssey
That was basically an accidental Roid Rage
I mean
Is that
Possible
I doubt it
Doesn't feel like
I feel like you
Probably doing it
Yeah it feels right
But also you probably was doing this testosterone Clinic
I know the reason I wanted to
Leave with that or sort of
Almost makes
As much
Because you see a guy like him
You know aging you can see his
He's going through an all that
And apparently
He got
Multiple pornstars around him at all the time with Brooke
Brooke Shields no Brooke Mueller
Berkeley
The biggest third wife
Yeah I can I can definitely see the
That he would place
Himself and then of course
Insecurities
Stuff like
Trying to
Turn himself into
Far more of a man
Thunderman that he project
Languages like
Keep using tiger blood
I think it's the title of the era in his life through the years
That is projection
Image of masculinity that adorable person
It would be impossible to live up to
Especially someone who's like
50 55 60
I don't know how old
You probably
Anyway the other thing that I want to point out
Is that maybe one of the reasons that Alex Jones
Doesn't want
Necessarily publicly
Talk so much about them being friends although I agree with your
Yours
Ascent method
Throw him under the bus what do you mean you said you were suggesting
As good friends anymore any
Like that
He does still bring him up from time
The reason that I think he doesn't go around
And like
Flaunt
That like
I had Charlie Sheen on and that caused all this
Was because of had negatively it all played out
And because now
In present day
He's blaming it on artificial
Testosterone boosters
What is Alex Jones's name business
That's a good point I think
That if
Charlie Sheen is talking about how cringey it is to look back at this period of his life
Because of testosterone products giving him Roid Rage
That kind of undercuts
Super male vitality
Indicates that ik maybe Alex's behavior is do that sort of thing too
And I think the parallels
Are shockingly easy
AI
Piece of Alex Jones history
It said was
Little more uncomfortable to listen to than I expected today
Like this
Reminds me of where we were whenever all of this stuff
What's happening I just remember
Remember
Couldn't
Couldn't partake
Like I feel the same way right now like I want to I want to have
The distance to
Start to find this funny again
But this really just makes me
Smithfield
Burning Stimpy
This is Amanda
Drawing himself
And the fact that a lot of people laugh
About it is
Like at the Liberty
I don't give a s***
Intellectual
You and I both got a good laugh out of the
First one's a piss test the next one's going to your mouth
That would have been a great line for the
Detroit
The next one's going in your mouth
And it won't get you high that's a keeper
That would not have got the opening act booed off stage
So anyways this has been fun
Alberta Indiana
Also ultimately
Comfortable
Knowledge
Tagline
You can find it at knowledge site.com go to
You can go to iTunes
Twitter knowledge underscore fight on Twitter
And we are doing the March Madness bracket
We can vote on the religious sound bites
We had today
Facebook group go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
And then I supposed
I mean there's really only
One person
I had a hunch it was going to be
Nails
Alexandra Thurston color with your Japan I love your work