Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
I am Joy
You were trying to sell the show
You were not talking to a tank
Michael Corinthos
Okay
What would you describe
You should get into Tango Court
Podcast
But I do know Tango
Anybody is not a tangled cord enthusiasts
Have you heard about Chris
Flights
And that twist makes things
Absolutely
Like at angle
Episode for a while
I thought you were leaving for a month
Where can I go
I told you before the show I got
Confused cuz you're doing the month at Zanies
In the future in the near future and you're going on vacation now and I combined the two into a
I don't listen well
It is only because of Jamie's month coming up that I'll be able to afford the vacation I'm going on now right right
This is our last live episode
Or two like possibly fit into be a delightful time
Before we get going
I'd like to give a shout out to
Strong people
Affect
Like to give a shout out and thank you to do
Natalya brilliant someone sodomites Italy a bucket of poop
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean
Loser
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Go to our website
We would appreciate it mean a lot that I wanted to do
On Thursdays and then are broadcast on Friday
These are the week episode figured out
That we should do a wrap up
Episode
So we did that was last time
Towers in
That was a disaster
So what I was badass
I was up until 5 or 6 in the morning editing effects
So I was kind of hoping to avoid something like that
Who is do a
Top 10 things you missed this week on Alex
I f***** up
I wasn't keeping track of anything that's just
No you are not on 10
No sir
Nor like
The pro wrestler
Gimmick is the number 10
20 about it a little bit
And
Interesting and other things
Some of it is very exciting to start with Tuesday March
Meacham
On the show trustworthy
Is the guy from the United Kingdom who got in trouble with the law because he made a video of himself
Teaching his dog how does Zeke heil
The dog was trained to Heil when everybody Kyle or gas the Jews
Right
I know one that bothers me
I think
Especially the Jewish organization
He goes on Alex Jones a show and they try and cry all this first amendment nonsense
American Constitution
So that argument
In the sixties
He would have been on Johnny Carson
That's true
Gravy out of Alex's argument I wish I had this clip now regret it
The craziest thing
He's like
Angel comedy
He's better than
I mean
Now that's when we get into what. John Cleese
Towers I'm going to murder you Alex
I'll be also said that he's funnier than Chaplin
Because Chaplin The Great Dictator B and
Necessarily
Straight up comedy
Pretty sure that was actually incisive satire
Use a lot of that nonsense I'm just really work
And the other thing that marks defense
This to annoy my girlfriend
Cuz she doesn't like Nazis
I'm so I sit back
And I think
I think there's first of all this isn't a great relationship
Break up with him
Well I don't like
But I am okay if my boyfriend teaches
His dog how to fix
He was teaching your dog this as a prank
On the girlfriend
Respond
How is that ever going to
The payoff when are you going to just casually say gas the Jews another dog Hyles
When you walk in the door in the the
The
Singing waterfalls on your head is just like that
Like she walks in the door and he's like
Need to leave you now
Now you've turned this into
Not on the dog
Raining on the job on the girlfriend
Certainly
The point that I'm trying to make is if I train
My cat
Suzy Kyle every time
Sumit said gas the Jews and you and I were sitting around I was
Just waiting
It would never happen
Hayward
Do accidentally coincidentally come up like
We're doing the show and talking about Alex Jones anti-semitism
Just got to be like if he said gas the Jews and then
That would be not a prank that would be the most
Terrified
Where did you accidentally get a nut to cat neutering cats
Here's my other problem Mark meechan defense self
It's terrible and stupid he's appearing from the UK and there's someone else in the room
And that guy's name
Is Tommy Robinson
Another guest on his show that is a little bit more
From geopolitical perspective that is a gentleman by the name of Alexander
This guy is a former and I put this former and quotes
Possibly heavy? Kremlin political advisor
You generally don't get to be one of those like
Former anything near the kremlin's are dead
It's working with the Russian
For approximately 20
Even like before you go
You know they just let you retire retire there like hey look I get it you don't want to do this anymore
You know a lot of secrets that other people could find out if they talk to you
But no big deal
About that he's written
For places like Al Jazeera another publication
That jumped over the Russian
Marine Le Pen is awesome
How it's no big deal
Ocean Bank gave her like $40 in The Lego Movie
Everything Is Awesome
Written by Alexander to dress up
Alex has him on Pharrell has a lot of weird friends
This is the sort of Journalism
Do Russians love Putin so much
Great great
You know what's interesting
That's actually a very complicated
Good question because
Strangely enough does enjoy
Largely favorable view amongst Russia
That is something that is true like if
The weirdest part about that election that they had that was
Clearly f****** rig
Little later
Still want one
If possible
What I think is more interesting is
A little bit down the line with interview
Explains what
Used to do for the Russian government
ShopRite
Alarm bells in everyone but Alex Jones for some reason
Oh my God
What means that's a murder
No he's talking about being a public relations
Foreign media fixer work behind the theme
He's a propaganda
He just admitted on Alex
No I was going to go in the media
Putin and his associates would do things the International Community
Dab or in the loop
He was a he was a media dark arts master
You will
Another just like embarrassing example of Alec
Either just being completely oblivious of the people he surrounds himself with
Or just
Epicly revealing
What his game is
And I mean I don't think I don't think it anyway that he works
Anything like that but
These pro-putin Tendencies are in
A big fan of how little respect this guy gives Alex's show
Is he's just like
I'm going to lay it all out there yeah
I would go
Especially media quote people who ask me questions
Tired tired
I like it let's say you were
What I would do
Before you ever even got close to talking about Putin
I would go to you and I would assuage your fears
So you would be more Pro Putin
Alex
I would never do that to you
Absolutely
The show our Alex gets a little bit in
To the Cambridge analytica situation
I assume he does so very hard with a lot of
Data behind the bad guy
Perspective but
It's it's correct
Public
But that's
MMA
Also on the 20th the day before or I believe in the early morning hours
We sure exactly when it happened
Antonio
Yes
Tries to pretend
That this doesn't undo all of his narrative
About his secret sources
About the author
Because all that stuff by like
It's built on the porch
It takes 20 minutes on the porch
Weather
It's all that stuff is
Famous FedEx
The FedEx hang out on the porch
Sit on a rocket
King chair next to the other FedEx porch guys
Imallexx continues a little bit of like that we got to use covert action
Actually advocating
Sing for Trump like working behind the scenes to like
People out a little upset
Batshit
Language
The video uses
Possibility politically
The 20th
21st which would be
If you're nasty
Before we get to that
Witness day
Before we get there
From the 21st
Well you can be sure that you're going to be
See if you like it
How's that sound
Oh no
I dude started sucking up there
Is that a is that is Ruth Bader Ginsburg
No that's
But I always like
Opportunity is SNL real
$1000000 to say that audition
That's closer to the acceptable price
A couple years in the ground
And Lauren just kinda was like
We're just going to give everybody I would watch that audition
Type so fast
Xenophobia
So good
On the 21st
Piece of advice
Alex
We got a red wine
21st
I got to say
I did a lot of talking
In explaining over
The 20th because
It's not that
The 21st
10/22
Feature some
Hi and bulshit
Like
Like some of the stuff
This stuff is like it's kind of in
The league of
Stuff that I've liked
I wait for
Bulshit like
Because it okay
It's just it's
The kind of b******* you can think
Your teeth m-28
I like
What are you doing
And it's the kind that made you read six different book
Very kind of stuff where you can
You can look at it and you can do that
He knows he's lying
And then you can look at it and be like
Which is about two more inches
Easton conversation Orange
Interesting like
Train of thought
Is he lying about the hello do you know he's exactly
Really been lacking in the present for us for so long it's just like
He's just pathetic pathetic lies about like strawman versions of his lawsuit
Yeah of course you're doing business is too transparent self-protection Ray
So Alex is found a story that's a couple days old
Are you shocked that he hasn't heard about yet
He delivers it with the most immediately
Anyone has ever told me stories
Are you know what I want to do
You know what I want to do at some point maybe you know who don't do this episode
But like
You rattle off
Like
Things that you think Alex should cover that like it's coming up or nope
Cuz there's a classic like
Yay or nay
OK Google
This one
Is going
It just gets crazier
Daily Caller
It's a footnote
The top investigator
Murder was shot
I want to hold off because I I wonder what's that mean
I'm already wondering what top like the best
Team right
Washington Post
The top investigator
Was shot twice in the back
Once in the butt actually
He got away with his dachshund
Badgerhound in his arms
Yep over
Submarine
When the department of energy
Downtown
Yeah, that's that's what they are
A marine with the Department of energy and so
It's just that I want to get this individual lawn
But now the rewards investigating doing all this the family
Real quick will get back to Albany
Not Mountain
Conflated number of things could Seth rich and his ferret
I guess I've reached
Didn't his parents did
He was that at the time but his parents put out a reward
For information about people who killed him
Analysis
Conflating the two trying to pretend that they're the same reward as they're different
Cover option
Why Jones
Was in the ass
Body was in a document pickup
Under the orange cone
Documents
What is dog in his arms
Didn't stop for that run over him
But between cars that were being rammed twice and lived
Screams about this narrative for pretty much the entirety of the show
Keeps coming up and he's like that's all the information he gives on it
Screaming
Like Groupon later and he screams
This is nonsense
Stories of scary
If I understand correctly
The top investigator right which is a nebulous idea to begin with
He was shot twice in Spanish
No
Don't even work for the police
No God no
We have his private investigator's license I don't think so
He's a lobbyist
He's a lobbyist and a hobbyist
It's not
And Alex is trying to pretend that he's working in an official capacity
He's not you just someone who decided to take it upon himself to start and
Investigation into
The problem
Is that now we go from
It's a conspiracy to you getting shot
Twice in the back to like
Hey dude you're probably f****** pissing people off
Maybe you have getting shot in the back
Combination
I didn't look into that cuz I don't really care
I don't know man
I don't care
He's not involved in
He's a crazy dude
I know that because these
A guy named Kevin Dougherty
Pretend that he's an assassin
Kill him kill Jack burkman because he wouldn't stop
Investigating
Okay
However
If you actually read the articles about this it's not a political hit job but
It's a case of one crazy person attack
Another crazy person
Here is the arrears the quote about that
Jack burkman told the Washington Post that he had hired Kevin Dougherty to help him build a psychological profile of Rich's killer
Birdman fire Doherty in July 2017 investigated the FBI
In February
Andrew McCabe
Spoiler alert
Information
Is awesome
F*** it f*** everything but this story they told him my favorite I told you never had
Alright
Now instead of the top investigator getting shot twice in the back and running away with his Docs
Now we have
Who
Was hired to look up information on Seth rich
He was fired from doing that and then later
He was given a contact
Who said if you meet with me I'll give you information on Andrew McCabe yeah but it turns out that the guy who
Hired him in the first place
Was the guy who is sending him that
In order to murder him
I think you're some of your pronoun reference were generally
Decided to investigate Seth riches murder
Yes and he will
Might have had a reason to do so I would will get into in a minute
Hired Kevin Dougherty who probably was an ex-marine
Be at some point
But he's now a crazy person is beyond all that
Employed by those people anymore
They get to a little bit of a beef
Well they're working together
Who is Jack burkman
And thinks the Kevin Dougherty is trying to turn the project
Into being about him
Himself he thinks that he's grandiose
Interviews and stuff like that is taking over the project
So he's seen out that something completely grandiose and paranoid person would say
Never investigate
Because they thought the other guy was getting too much
Right
That's a normal thing to do so that comes to head July 2017 and Birdman fire
Because there's not much
Do this that's rich
Conspiracy nonsense
A little bit down the road
Might as well take it all the way to stop
He gets contacted by an anonymous source
Spoiler alert
That's what's going on
Jordan what we call this is the cost of doing business in the computer
SeaWorld
You're going to end up working with dangerous crazy people
Might want to kill you at some point
That is
I don't I don't know the story of baby feel
Look I got it
I'm against people getting shot
But it's pretty hilarious cuz he lives in them cannibalize each other that's the only has like a
Broken wrist
Or something like that it's not even a big deal
Do you know what all the stories I could find
Don't even really confirm that he was shocked
Biggest say he says he was shot we can confirm means he was not shot
It was like a BB gun or something like that or pellet gun
I don't know I don't know it may not even have been a murder plan
This guy I don't know
What's cartoon
And I love
There's all sorts of unknowns about it but what I do know is this has nothing to do with Seth Rich the petty squabbles between
How do you get
Named a top
Investigator
TV sets in the news Alex Jones I'll call you that
Alright so I told you the lobby
Yes
Important
Okay but it turns out the jack burkman is a trump connected lobbyist
Who in the past
Has raised money for Rick Gates
If you don't remember who that is
Is Paul manafort Trump campaign manager
The United States
So
Hoverboard
Yeah
The most
Trustworthy people involved with a story
I don't know I don't know 100% if that's
Schenectady
Like that
It's certainly interesting
This point
It seems that seems like a
Like
How many stories did you read about this where they went in
Into how
Insane and Ludacris
This is detailed
Oneida piece
Together from a bunch of stories
Is how I abbreviate washing
Engine poster
Befriend
Story that was like
Crazy people doing crazy s*** like that
I'm f****** read that all day
We got to figure out how to do clickbait
So I agree with you
This story
Banana
Juicy
But unfortunately I don't really know how to make this suspicious
Because he can't
You keep you don't get your friend in a narrative if you've got guts
Because the reality of the situation
Point fingers at Trump
But Rick Gates
Why is this Trump connected lobbyist
Being a
Top Seth Rich investigator in the first place the craziness
Between the two you kind of come to a damning indictment of the mindset that drives you down that road to begin with
Now here we go
Let's Go reverse reverse engineering
Let's rewrite the narrative for Alex Jones
False flag
Alright
The guy who is associated dachshunds
The guy who is associated with Rick
Clearly being set up
In order.
Reddit anybody who's ever
Hired anybody who's ever worked
For Trump in the past
Narrative to go down
This is a fascinating
What you can do with your other narrative
You might be close to what he thinks
You just can't really figure out how to work
What your version
Here's his
WikiLeaks
Not good
Re-bag
Julian Assange and said we don't know why sources but yes you should look at him as a source
Doesn't sound like WikiLeaks
He didn't say you should treat him as a sorcerer
Julian Assange did try to pretend videos the source
Political trouble
There's an article that came out literally just
Before we started recording where
It's very
Clear now that guccifer 2.0 was a GRU Russia
Intelligence
Albuquerque
They went over all of the time
Clear-cut no no there's an article article in The Daily Beast
That just came out
All of the times the emails were sent or any IP addresses world
Every time
It went to VPN
Server that would Lodge
In France
To get around IP address.
But one time when he logged in
He forgot
To use the VPN setting
And that IP address link to directly back
Pgru
So
Yes so
It is now
Entira as long as that story is accurate
Right it seems like it is
I don't know we'll see how the reporting goes in
Couple days
But if that's the reason
Then guccifer 2.0
Is a Russian intelligence cutout
Yep persona
Rodger Stone
Interacted with gusto employment very clear about it
The crimes have all been commit
End
The emails directly to WikiLeaks
A tweet that WikiLeaks
Themselves
Retweeted
The case then Russian intelligence
Gave the emails that they hatch
Text from the DNC
Directly
To WikiLeaks
Which Doug kind of complicate things
For Julian Assange
Nah
So people write the histories of Art
I've said this before but
Unqualified
Well I'm absolutely
Discovery that we can realize how great a job they did it pulling all of this s*** up
Like this is crazy this is movie levels
Tri-level
Committed
Treason
So forth
Like where at
Like
The more you learn about it we're kind of at Hot War level
Someone who has
Actively said the United Nations
Doesn't exist
It is much as we want them to our last
Live episode for a while every single episode
Insane person without
This is one of those
More f***** up staff decisions
You could have possibly made
Because I I can't imagine
Steve pieczenik won't be on the show tomorrow
Steve pieczenik
Furious
Oh yeah hates John Bolton's
From conversation
That I've had with with folks
Pro friend. Simpson
We Believe
If it doesn't have to be a Breaking Point
If Trump is in bed with Bolton
Hates John Bolton
So this could be
This could lead if there's one thing I've learned
Indeed
Past few years it is that
Nobody
Underwrite believe in anything
He's chaotic
Unusual
He could be I believe that pretty wholeheartedly
AAA been convinced
Guiding principles are being
Violated
Behavior the Trump is
Using and he'll have to
Steve will have to turn on Alex
I can't wait
If he's not on tomorrow going to be
.
But anyway
I was trying to leave this
If you brought the WikiLeaks
Sparta now we've discussed why that's pretty stupid
Line
Maine discovered spinning a yarn
Shot multiple times in the back
Once in the bus
Family
Held up pictures
You want to find out who killed our son
Very suspicious behavior for a family
Oh yeah
From this week
Headline Fox News Alex Jones
Z
Set a rate ducato
So bad but he's trying to
Compare
Inflate the to reward
That were offered
Family
Parkman
Berkman
Berkman Jack Burke
So they are you saying
I'm just loving his rhythm of speech right now
Bassy
He's like a beat poet
No idea
Nothing
He's trying to figure out a way to
Call
The time
It'd be very annoying and I hope you stopped right now
Like they came out and offered this reward people started investigating
Investigator
I would argue that people give rewards
They give rewards for information that is already had by people
Not as a coal for investigative vigilantism believe actually they hired
It's not like
You know it's not a call for amateur sleuth
You guys want to make your name in the game but I can get out
Chords for going to be fake investigators coming out
So ridiculous
People start looking into this
Get the family.
People change their stories
Because who you're talking about is Rod wheeler
Who was the guy freelance
For Fox News who has been
Fox News
He sue them
For using quotes
That we're not
From him
The Heat
He they falsely attributed
Information as to coming from him
And that's why his story changed because foxnewslive the first time you've got
Got legal action
Why are all these people who were finding evidence of the clintons being involved in this
Story with a f****** lie
Investigating
Thousands and thousands
Right
Completely within their legal rights
R.a. Petoskey
Mooyah Zimmerman and Executives at Fox News for a
Conspiracy that they
Nearly engaged him
You know
Priest on email
The lawsuit that are jamming
If you are
One of these Republican
Right
Number of lawsuits being filed against you kind of like
And look at all of the people you support
How many lawsuits have been filed against them
Recently
Shouldn't you start to think
Maybe
You're an idiot
Okay you said it's a good defense what you should do you should see that is proof that you're in the right direction
Call the time he uses like the analogy of
World War
1 bombers
Didn't have a radar
And they would only know that they were above the target whenever they're getting shot at
You know it's like the payload whenever I'm getting shot
You said this in so many different ways like whenever people are attacking me that's where I know I'm doing the right thing
Sometimes because you're way out of line
Interesting fact
Do you know the whole carrots
Improve your vision
Spirits of rabbits
No it was put out by the British government discovered
Started using radar
I'd like in order to make sure that
People know in order to kind of so doubt into people about whether or not
Radar actually existed
Planes they said that their best Pilots were eating a lot of carrots
That's why they're vision
Fastenal
I appreciate it
Such an ass
Has your farewell show
Especially
We're sort of done with Alex
Two separate bulshit narrative
It goes on throughout the show but then I wouldn't
Took care of it up top
Into a narrative
He has
Stick with that
Like there's so many of those narratives
Just won't go away
Genuinely
Nothing
Like literally have nothing
They have so much
Nothing
Can't even come up with a new fake narrative
Because every narrative back to the reality of
Wegotsoccer
There were spies
Everything is Jerome corsi Style baby
They made
Running with the band
Mem
Alex jumps to another man
And if you ever listen to our show or ever lived Alex Jones Show end
You will hear a lot of familiar stuff in this
Pretty much every other week or so Alex Jones will start screaming about how the globalist
Airplane to their armored redoubt
Here the 21st
No exception
Here's the deal
What
I should be in Montana or something
Digging in with transmission
These are going on a rant about how if you can't afford to get to New Zealand or Kauai then people are going to
Montana Utah
Alex
You should not be in America
If you are if you are at all worried
Go to a place where there's poor extradition laws
Urban chaos
Weaponized diseases and stuff like that
That's fun
They talked about
Weapon X
Or not Weapon X
Jesus
They talked about disease X
Nicked my Fred dad
Do you know about disease X
The World Health Organization
Morning about
Breakout
Doctor group says he's on a lottery
Chiropractic
Does alot of research
They have a bunch of conversations
It sorta leads you to believe that they think it's a thing
When it's not it's
The designation for everything that's not on the World Health organization's radar
It could be a deadly they put out a list every year of life
Yeah playing the field
By the way
Whatever
Oh
Yeah
Unknown unknowns yet
Rumsfeld
He's such a he's one of the most
Evil Psychopaths I think of the history of the
World so I agree but back to disease X
Sorry about that chief executive of the research Council of Norway and Scientific Advisor to the world
Explain these acts.
History tells us that is likely that the next big outbreak will be something we have not seen but
Before it may seem strange that adding an X
But the point is to make sure we prepare and plan flexibly in terms of vaccines diagnostic
We want
Plug-and-play platform
Developed which will work
For any number of diseases
Systems that allow us
Create countermeasures at speed
So what they're just talk about is the ability
100 / 6
These people are so bad at naming
Now it's perfect
This is we're planning for we don't know cuz historically humans don't know everything
Well now it's also talks about how like clearly there's like vaccines and like you're going there trying to create a superbug
Human Habitat
He's jumping from animals to humans
It's a natural process
Is vital that we are aware of
Probably the greatest
Yeah of course they go on to explain that like be
Because of the way the climate's changing because the way the thing
Becoming more comp
We run the risk of
Being much more
Contact with animals
Diseases that
We haven't
Experience before mini Bolas an example
There's 100 examples
Terrible diseases that have jumped over from animals
You think about
Most
Currently
The one of the
There was a
Doctor
I can't remember when I can't remember his name because I am
But he was the first doctor
Kind of started doing re
Why it is
Eye doctors
Killing somebody
Legitimately directly from
An autopsy
Going directly
Other s***
And he's his solution was like hey
Guys
Wash your f****** hands
Now
That
Of course
Destroyed his career because doctors
We're insisting that no you don't need to do that and you never need to worry about it because doctors are the best
People in the world
And so they spent their entire f******
Like his entire life was destroyed
For coming up with the single best idea and Doctor maybe has ever come up with
In history about something like disease
That's that guy going to be like
We know
We f***
We know that there's something that we need to do because something is coming around the corner
Always
So maybe plan ahead for what
And guys like Alex Jones are the same guys who are like
Don't worry about it
Put all your bodies in the same thing and then poop
Next to where you live
Well well said
Now back to the part about how the globalist
Do I them off on keratin
Sort of sidetracked started with talking about doctor group and disease access
Explaining that Alex Jones
Pretty convinced
That
Weeks
The globalist
They're going to then foment
Comedy
Italian police station
Social civilization breaks down
Bomb going off
We told you was it all coming
Wilson pool
Holyshit
Cam
What do they know that we don't
Swiss Lakes
Is links back to an article in the Washington Examiner
It's just one of these
You see these articles all the time if you follow such a huge fan of but what do they know that we don't know article
That's probably the Infowars headline I read over this and it's just basically
Describe it as
Buzz Marketing
Peace
For this guy's
What's it called
For the name of his
Place but it's some place where they sell
Studio
They sell bug at
S*** you know like her like a yeah yeah
Yeah you see this over and over
You see this over and over again if you follow
Some people have in the world to get free tanks
Just about it
Them stories will pop up about hey all the elites are buying a brat glows under the ground
You saw it with
Way back there now
She saw Alex pushing these narratives over and over and over again through the years
I read the articles exact same thing
The idea that
The officials are leaving
Based on the article it says
Have a vest
Inflating the importance could be
Could be any people from unnamed
Three-letter organizations
Are coming in
Spu
In the absence of any real information
Take this one
Before
Copy and paste this
Basically
But
This time
It's real
Something is different
What
Timing
I wonder where he has
Obama is in New Zealand
Golf no public docks
A2Z meeting with
The Lord of the Rings tour
Barack Obama
Caesars
Official welcome ceremony Thursday
Citizen
Why would John
And to work with the Obama Foundation
Foundation Building
As an escape
That's right it's not exactly that is not a huge leap at all
He's working with your bottom
Who is building him a huge
Escape water in New Zealand
This is really popular in the conspiracy world
A ton of land in New Zealand
As a murderer if you're a mass murderer article
You should not have.
I will not be allowed to run for any kind of off
Stephen alderman
Relax
No
Vlone
A huge plot of land
The New Zealand and he said that it's as a sort of backup Last Resort kind of thing
Society collapses
This has become sort of a man
In the conspiracy world that everybody is making
Bees
Fortresses
I find very little
Compelling evidence
Is behind it
Other than this one story about Peter
Teal
Well I drank paranoia
In all honesty I have
I have asked myself the question
Of like
The massive disaster is
Regardless massively
Structure of the war
Regardless how bad you think it is going to be
Right
I would want to figure out where it is that I would put my
Doubt
So to speak
And you want you want
Freshwater
You want
Good
Pizza delivery
Absolutely
Yeah that's fine though
Find an Aldi in New Zealand the matter Amazon is drone delivery
Those two die
Madrone like deliver me the Pizza Hut
Ingredients
Look
But my position on all that stuff is
I don't know I don't want
I get too deep into this but
As all that stuff comes becomes more and more
Importance that people who are
Be around
Don't run away
So I don't care about all of that
So the conversation
But where are we going to hide
Re-hide in the shed of it and try and help you
That's kind of
My perspective
And I hope
When things get bad
I can walk the walk
That I'm very casually talk
I don't know
There's no f****** way for me to know what my reaction will be but I pray and Hope
That it is
Help people that I can help
Enfield community
Where I am
I'm out cuz everytime somebody's like
That b*******
Incredibly different
Galvanizing in unifying
Because climate change is not so much a like
It's not like
If you get hit by a rogue wave
Like an errant wave you know it's not like that
Or is it
I don't think so I've been hitting an undertow before
Terabyte
The 21st
3 hours long. Posted
I'm sorry I'm sorry
On the 21st doctor group
I only threw that later cuz I wasn't saying it reluctantly.
Our boy
Daddy
Eddy Group
One of the things
Is some crazy
Not hot fire
He's on there talking about how
Your pineal gland
Has a crystal in it
Cuboid vaccine
No
Fluoride
Your phone
That's not good with everything around you
Pretty much
Crystal
It hurts that Crystal but you know what can help
I'm going to go with fake bulshit pills
Iodine
Colloidal iodine
Now he says that iodine is
The only thing
They can help the pineal gland
Harrah's buffet
The new age World lot of that that sort of stuff and I know
From going to all of these websites
Researching all this.
No one says the iodine is
Can you use its turmeric
Turmeric is within your pineal gland
Is your fake correction of his fake Bowl
I just want to be aboveboard about all day
Thank God cuz it's more important
Peter in doctor groups appearance they start
Call
And they get viscol which is
Buckwild
This is Mike download
Attorney
California
I'll talk to Alexander
In California are on the air
Hello Alex
Graduate
Doctor for Brazilian to the public
The fact that the pineal gland
And that is our unique
What's Siri's phone number
Pineal gland we could be communicating
We Are Spiritual Beings we are very powerful
And other 1% is trying to deny that ability.
And you're helping us to that I want to congratulate you for that
Don't work that you do Alex
And one thing I would like more stories
About the Sandy Hook
Oh boy
Doughboy
Operation
Really hard
I'm an attorney.
Telepathy
Count the capital empathy
San Diego Spectrum
Nobody
Take the 147 boxes idea
Yet
Right
I mean
But just wait by the way I'm starting a new line of Crystal called the pine Neil Brand
Crystal I mean like let's
Just
Blue sky this
This idea
If it is the case
I am hearing a if then state
Meant being sad
How blue-sky thinking works all right there about Edward group
Noted chiropractors ideas
And keep saying that your cell phone
Modern technology
Fluoride in the water
And vaccines
Are the things that are inhibiting your pineal gland
Then
What we should see
Is telepathy in human
In the 1600
We should see telepathy you're out your luck
Of course it is
Pictures of the phone
Where the guy was in the
17. Was
I retract
And I was not from 1700
Earphone
Argument
Splat for me because
Maybe because I've gone down so many of these stupid New Age Road
And I found
So much
Asterism
I found so much
Con man
Behavior
There are so many people are trying to sell you on these like super human capabilities that you're able to achieve
You weren't being held
And I believe in human potential I think our conscious
This is way more powerful than we think it is
I don't think
Didn't we
Washed off our pineal gland Crystal by not drinking water not being around Electronics
Having a cell phone not taking vaccine
Scores odds and somehow we be able to
Telepathy
Ethically communicate
It is Muddy in the water is like
Fun new age
Stuff with new-age b*******
Is the the bodhisattva like ultimately when you get down to all of this
End up being a
Rehashing of
The Buddha went to the f****** Mountain
And meditated
A 6-month right my favorite
For so much
This s*** it just all goes down to that
That guy who goes into the middle of nowhere and cleanses himself of
Humanity reaches Enlightenment and then so on and so aesthetic
Lifestyle
If that's what you want to do
F****** fine
But if you're somebody who is doing that and then coming back to other people
There's no explanation for why you would come back
Two other people
Right
Like that's the thing that always breaks it down
My favorite
My favorite Buddha my favorite boat is off of my favorites guy who ever reached enlightenment
Weather in Elgin
Who
Famously
I reached enlightenment
Whenever
Crow dropped a rock
In the middle of a lake
And then was given the head of a
Buddhist monastery
And after nine days
He said f*** you guys you're all corrupt
You can find me at the brothel
You can find me in the woods
Brilliant poet
That's that's Wonder
That is my man
That's my guy
Jesus Christ
Could be
So Jordan now things are going to get
Mercure 21st does not end well
54 l
Because in one of the commercial break
Towards the end of the show the article where he's being called a race
For someone
Mets that he's made about
How
We've covered a lot of it in the past but what it boils down to is a lot of these ideas about how white should
Police South Africa and let the blacks destroy themselves
Of course he has that idea in his head
He's been weaving in imagery about Black Panther
About like this
Very good this idea of a black
Utopia happened without the whites there
A great-aunt
But love it
Publication
Have been taken
But out of context but also
Again it's what we deal with all the time it's like when people take him out of context
Generous
They don't actually deal with the reality what do you think
And thankfully
In responding to this article that
He says
One of the worst f****** things I've ever heard him say
Might also be on lockdown
I was just reading during a break
Blackstar
And then they don't tell you that the same
Eclipse on the Communist leaders number three in the government Market
I'm just saying that's racist
That's stupid
Zimbabwe
Play the clip
You didn't
This goes back to Cliff misrepresent
He played a clip from it was like 1
South African
Julius malema the leader of the radical Marxist opposition party
Fighters
In the clip
We talked about this already in the past when he played it
Yeah, says
Specifically is not calling for the slaughter of white people at least
For now
I was going to say
That was talking about
Slaughtering White
Marxist opposition's
But they're talking about an equitable redistribution of land that didn't happen after the apartheid state was ended
South Africa we've been over this a hundred f****** tonight
Now the reason that this clip to me
The most fuc
Nothing I've ever heard Alex say
Whites are being exterminated in Zimbabwe Rhodesia you name it
You name it
You name it there's so many f****** problem place
Rhodesia autoplay there
Not another place
Studio
Persia
Do you know Rhodesia is
No you don't
I know
But I don't know if what I know is then going to be revealed to be f****** stupid
Reveal myself to be f******
I'll tell you a little story
Supposed
Recently come into the Public's
Because
Dylann roof
After he shot up the black church
Killed nine
People pictures of him
Came out burning American flag
And also with
Flags
Of the apartheid government in South Africa and Rhodesia flag on his shirt
That's one of the reasons
Brought to the public
People don't know what Rhodesia axe
Actually is
Rhodesia is an internationally
Ignited state
Hasn't existed since
It's a literal symbol of the white supremacist White
Nationalist
Exist to this day
Okay and there's a reason for
Because I
I was legit terrified that like when you started when you started saying like
Do you know what Rhodesia really is I was like
How do you spell white
Is it is it a real place like I don't I don't
Zimbabwe
That's why I got scared I thought it was a very simple and straightforward
So in 1965 Rhodesia broke away from its existing
Status is part of the United Kingdom
UK would not record
Denies their apartheid government
We're 32 4% done clear exactly where the number was
Population was about three to four percent and they control the entire apparatus
Controls the government
Wars with black liberation group 2 broke out all over the place
And the regime incredibly horrific means to stay in power included
How did article from the 60s in New York Times
Describing some of the torture that they employed Electric
Electrocuting people limbs
Extremes
We also engaged in incarceration to Black leaders
Never heard of in 1979 the government collapsed
But the racist myth
This white supremacist utopian state of Rhodesia remains to this day
Idea that they have is
Communist
Horses
The black people who are like why are 3% of population oppressive
Lee governing over us
Create
Assholes
Have been like
Then they could have had a white supremacist Utopia and rotation
It's unfortunate because you end up with
Picture
And that's not right
And
This is this is something that I put a lot of thought into
Because
That's kind of what we need to happen here
What do you have an oppressive government
The people it's the French Revolution
Over and over and over again
Historically
You have this
Oppressive
B******* f****** government
And people are finally like
We can't handle this s***
And then they wind up making the same mistake that everybody else does where they go
Will this guy will help
And then
Democratic well-meaning leader who became the dictator himself
Yeah you get your you get your Castro out of a
Your f******
I would posit deposit first of all that Mugabe
All that terrible to begin with but he got terrible
But I would also say that you unfortunately
He serves as a tool of the white supremacist propaganda about Rhodesia because it like if he hadn't come
Buddies
An overthrown the white
Great government
They could have been doing great there and because he is so terribly
Props up their argument
Right after the French Revolution
Revolution
You f***** up and eventually paper like we need to f****** solve this problem
And a charismatic leader shows up
And then discovers that
Powers
Really f****** great
Big
Problem
Is the Alex Jones
Drops Rhodesia
Like it's a real thing
It only exists
Two white supremacists
And white National
The idea that
He is bringing it up
Whites are being exterminated in Rhodesia
Is one of the most
Dammit
Possible sentences
A person can make
Because
Like
Even if you thought that white
We're being exterminated in Africa in someplace
You wouldn't say that no
You would never say Rhodesia well but let's put you in the position of somebody who
Isn't a hard yes on white genocide
The show reason that it's f*****
Is this
Rhodesia was never
It was
Literally never
Accepted as a country
It existed
From 1965 to 1979
And the entire time was
Sickly just
Small white minority
Beating the s*** out of him torturing
Black people who demanded right
And then stopped existing the only
Any reason to ever have it in your head
Is because you identify with that
You are a f****** white
Supremacist
If you bring up Rhodesia in a conversation if it's a thing
Alex Jones
Played himself so f****** hard there
It's embarrassing
And you know what's even more embarrassing
Media Matters
Rightwingwatch
All of those f******
Chicken places
They don't talk about this
They don't talk about the how he brought up a rope
Asia
I got no response
I don't think we've ever said before
Is it confirmed white supremacist
Call for calling him a racist
Write a Tom hit up your boy I'll get you right out of that lawsuit
Absurd
At this point Alex
Get really defensive cuz people are calling a race
Cuz he's a rank
We're all under attack and there's.
Much more with
The syphilis vaccination all the different vaccinations blacks have been used for
Multiple top-secret testing projects which we expose
All all
Are you kidding me Alex.
Black urine
You got that
What's the reason why we need to control our stress levels
Alright that's
What is the weather deck
Okay
What is the black KKK
Farrakhan maybe it's the Black Panthers
Black Panthers
Historically
Hung
Lynched
Murdered
Did everything that they possibly could to
To destroy
Black before Thor run them out
Created a program
Breakfast
Two people who couldn't
Now we now we have our equivalent
Caloric balance
On that
Scrambled
Toast
Nailed it
V
Target
It's the Providence
Problem light not Providence
Providence
It's like weird where the
Like what is in response to what
Black KKK groups
He does this about
Skins with like La Raza
Separatist
Racist organization
Translate
Like he does the same thing with like historically black fraternity
And stuff like that
You're not looking at
Is the dees organization
Only exist
Because of
The history of violent exclusion
By the way organization
Those things
Would not exist
If we had a history
They didn't have
Violent
And murderous segregation
So
We're not saying
Every white person
Should be punished for that history
But everyone
Well you're not really
Your debts that's for comedic
Perfect
Alex
Everyone should be aware of it
Absolute and if you're willfully obtuse to that
That means that
That you have some sort of underlying belief
There is much more than just I want that Bruce out
I want everyone to be fair it's more that you're like
Cannot deal with
The fact
It's someone that looks like me
Was so awful
Two people who didn't look that good
Exactly
This situation where people who look like me
Had to create their own resources in order to
The situation
There is that
Defending it and denied you are tattoo
Simply admitting
But yes it did
Happened
And you are guilty
Let's jump off
I think we've nailed that he's a white supremacist
Nikki
Exactly
Yeah he plays himself
Like a fiddle
We have one more clip here from the 21st and it's really funny and consideration
You had this
Russia
Fixer on his shows
The media fixer on his show
Cuz at the end of the show Rodger Stone comes on
And even Rodger goddamn Stone living the best life he can possibly live
Knows that flat Amir Putin's stole that goddamn election
And Alex cannot handle it
He's been briefed by the
Leah
Rig the election which he most certainly did it's a choice.
It's really popular
I guess what I'm saying is that
Really
Frozen in jail has their supporters
Petition carriers beaten
So this wine Alex Alex
This is really fun, again
Just
It's just f****** Loki
He's just sowing Discord
There is absolutely a piece of it that is like
He does.
Give
Bengal
F***
He just driving
Is it is amazing
On many levels
II
Everybody knows this is this election is rigged
Otherwise
That's so great because
God I
If if Rogerson was never allowed anywhere near power and was just allowed to give interviews
He would be the best
No because he got kicked off of like Fox and CNN know that for
Want to race
People equal opportunity hires insurance
REI tent gloss over the worst of Rodger stones
Is a terrible monster when he is working again
What his
Wendy's
He's the funniest f****** human cutting through the bull
Because he's not
Damn well what's going on
No so this brings us to the end of the 21st
Right we will get into the 22nd
Here in a second but I need
To reinforced my belief to anybody who is
Rodger Stone
Should be f****** but headed butts
True he deserves the death penalty
Almost as much as Joe Arpaio 25 years of the past
Exactly
Cuz I got to open up that window
And I got to go to the bathroom really quick
Open up that
Show me back in about 3 minutes
The memory of oppressed people is one thing that cannot be taken away
A such people with such memories
Revolt is always an inch below the surface
Achievability boban jalebi go
Being afraid of blushing
So when does it begin
I'm going to faucett AutoZone
I walked into the lobby
I got like two steps into the lobby
When the the apartment door open and I sorted
He did one of these
Please
Back against the wall
Inhale reloaded automatic sweat dripping heart racing is flooded with static I got a bad habit The Shining
Grocery stores like motions for a thug holiday closing the courts are show my thoughts on paper tikka masala violin
So if you find it you know what to bring when you come and get me the stuff that bit me never hit me but still I feel it in me
Cell phone
The eye of the storm I'm not dislocated finding the coin patient waiting for something to happen stop
Right Place Wrong Time
Open Facebook
State Route never planned on finding the way I got plans and none of them involve dying today it's not a Warcraft
If we must die let it not be like all confident ending in Inglorious by
Like a man will face the murderous coward attached to the wall dying
Massachusetts Massachusetts
Influence
Appetite for Destruction
New World Order
I Too Sing America I am the darker brother they send me to eat in the kitchen I'm trying
But I laughed and well and grow strong tomorrow
Hey Rebecca everybody sorry about that
Fitness on that break we fix bathroom
So Jordan like I told you
We're getting into the 22nd
And this is Thursday if you're nasty
Thursday if you're not
Cuz I know you need that
Nope
The 22nd
Is a delightful day
This
Boy
You said a lot of stuff that's not true and a lot of stuff that is very easy
Poke holes in
But
Unusual for him
He also ended up spending about an hour of the
More than our possibly
Of the show Jessie
Talking to his gun Buddies
A lot and we'll talk about here in the Sun
They have a lot of company
First gun Buddies
I got somebody's back in Missouri like shootout guns
You just never been to the range
And it's fun I should
Because I'm going to need that scale eventually
I don't like
This uncomfortable position that I have
Have to live in where it's like
I guess I get all of it
I get all of it and you know what the right answer is done
Control
I get all of it though to
And I think that gives unique position to be in where I think I can call out b*******
More capable
It's Direction Story whenever it's like
Is this actually trying to the oppressive or is
Just trying to
How is this benign
Or whatever like
You're very much on the side of Hemet
Like I get that a lot of people likes you.
Recreational area
All ready to do this right now
Unnamed people
That's a good place to stop right there a little bit
Cuz you've been filing the serial numbers off of yours I don't have any
I have a vacuum cleaner over there that I could
Turn into one though cuz I'm crafty like MacGyver
Richard Dean Anderson from his bed
Alright
Absurd
Because the varsity narrative Alex Jones
Is him misrepresenting
A new rule
That YouTube
Has put out about gun video
And we will hear his take on it
Tell you what the
The truth is
More
Here's Bloomberg
YouTube videos
The First Amendment
Hollywood Runner trailers of all the shoot'em up
They're going to put out
Three sponsors
Also on Twitch
You bring my sweater
Incredible
First Amendment
People playing video games
All the other games
Play some street names
Death wish
Trailers
Arm shan'l doesn't even sell guns
Hold on The Military Arms channel with the guy who runs that channel
Later
And then
These are showing firearms
All selective attack
On the 1st Amendment
Assault
The war baby
Sprawling like crazy over there
What's up taking a lot of notes
I'm just thinking
About how Alex Jones
Conception
Of what
The First Amendment
Isdin
Apparently aunt
What freemark
Interesting
Okay
So first amendment is the government
Cannot
Control speech
Yes
Free market capitalism
Especially the journalism and you're allowed to gather together no matter what
What does not understand that those parts at all gather are paid together
Actually
Which allows you to regulate
Speech
Exactly the way
He is again
Stem
Those
Amara
Tackle and he doesn't understand that they are
They are the reason that he's angry but one of the things like if you just want to take it to a dumb
F****** way to resolve this argument
There's no p*** on YouTube
P*** is legal well I know it when I see it
Right but there's no there's no point on YouTube like pouring is legal they've decided we don't want that on our plan
Do you want a cup that Free Speech battle
What is it
No it's not
Gun videos are still
Cool
They're still totally cool
From Bloomberg
The problem is the
The title of this f****** article
Guys named things better
Think I had one of the article is YouTube and Firearm demo videos
Entering the gun control debate
And that is an absolutely unfair title
Based on the reality of what YouTube has done
So here we go I'll just read to you from this article cuz Alex Jones didn't make it to the second paragraph
YouTube will ban videos that promote or link to websites selling firearms
Accessories
Including pump
Which allows semi-automatic rifles
To fire faster
Additional YouTube side of a print videos with instructions on how to assemble fire
The video site owned by alphabets Google
His face intense criticism
Frozen videos about guns
And other deadly weapon
Basically what the new rules they've come up with
If you sell gun
You cannot have videos where you
Advertise those guns
If you don't sell guns
But you were supported by someone who does sell gun
And linked to them for direct sales
Can't post those videos
Also if you are putting up videos
Where you show how to
To create a silencer
How to create a higher-capacity magazine
You can't put up those videos
My personal take on this
Is
Good
This is going to be impossible to enforce
Good that isn't that is a good rule to have you should have had the
Long time ago
I don't I don't know what realistic
Steps UK
Can take
Now Alex has two guests on the ship is.
Right
You're not going to e.r. you're never going to be able to
Plug
Once once a week starts you're never going to be able to plug all the
And pretending that you can
Is
Lip service
Do I get ice like I support
The idea that they're trying to do it but they're never going to
To do it the first amendment argument is absolutely out the window cuz they're not being arrested
You know like that again
The First Amendment
Control what the
Government
What a private organization
Can control which you should have a boner for you would think again the first amendment is antithetical
To free market
Capitalism
And somehow he believes he's
He supports both
Song to talk about this
And these are the gun buddy I was talking about for about an hour worth of
Show David murderbox
Skeeter
One of them
My notes were not pulling up there for
The guy by the name of Tim harmison
Who runs the YouTube channel Military Arms
Channel do I mention
The interview that
He runs a gun store
So that kind of put some afoul of the selling gun provision of YouTube's new rules
Conditions argument
Also you goes into a pretty big argument about
How is the Southern Poverty Law Center is a radical far-left
I'm bored you hate to see that
Can't handle it
Other guests
He has
Kitco
This guy runs this
Most
Southwestern
Villain name I've ever heard
Skyrun
Colt
Fourteen-year-old that
Quick Draw better than anybody else
Gun maker and seller business
Auto Florida called
Spiked
Tonasket
Alex just reference them is having their YouTube channel taken down
During the day while the steps was going on
Google dich
I found our YouTube channel is it was up
Also the Military Arms channel
The issue the bigger is that
Spike's Tactical is an advert
Kaiser on Alex Jones
The show
Yeah
Fox say
The whole thing just turns into a commercial basically
No
It's just a
Sharia law
There probably is making up a law that
Restricting
Advertising
4 and they come on your show saying
They're restricting
Even though there's not a restriction what I said they're not allowed to say that there's a restriction on it I think there's not
SEC violation because he doesn't
Hide the fact
Is there a sponsor like even plays a commercial for them in the middle
Of their hour-long argument about
No absolutely it is
It's it's a it's a hot load
Is that in the middle of copse interviewed explained
Flames eat behind my eyes
Burning in the middle of
Kerosene on you because in the middle of his interview
Expresses
He believes that most
Mass shootings
You specifically said
Yeah
The thing that I was just pretending that he doesn't support one of his sponsors comes on Aaron says I think
You know what it's not even the shootings that we know of
It gets even more of them
That's what I said
Crazy
Also this is
This is really fun
Beyond the I'm beyond like
Oh you shouldn't Advocate that
These guys
On.com amazon.com
To this you can find it there
Skipco
Kit cope
Skip for a second it's kit
Kickoff
Kitco
Piece of s*** I will never do that box of things but
Doodle
That's
Whitlock with your issues
A kit of coping
Hot water a little while back
Because he created this
For his business
I don't like
Say
He presented it as standing up to antifa
Already bad slogan was not today
Antifa
And I
The picture was for white dudes with guns with
To the camera it's not it's not a picture but like
To the
Whatever the lamb
And then
Steve guys in math
Like we're going to shoot you down
And then in the corner
That has
Boston
I get my buddy other ones
Charlottesville
What is that one of your four in the list we had to use
No
Christ
People
Nope
What are they what is it
Doordash it like there's a genuine part of me that wants
Be able to experience a level of a
Eeyore or understanding but like
And literal empathy of
Can I see through there
And I have
No ability to see the world through the way.
Created is
For Alex
Video game the video game
Created a literal
No one else does and I want to be able to see it I promise you
Stamp it out with a
Giant f****** boots I promise you I'm going to explain some of it at the end of this episode
Alright
But I think they're actually created by part of the reason they
You can't emphasize
Is because I can't
Well no I mean
Difficult
Cuz
What you're trying to emphasize emphasize with is
Weebly scared
And come
Pleakley externalize
Worldview
Like everything is
Red
And all these threats are connect
Is very difficult
That's sure any of the movies
The thing is
If you don't fall under the sway
I actually think you should emphasize a little bit I think you need to look inside yourself a little bit deeper
Because
What were looking
With a lot of these people are people who have fallen under the
This way of very charismatic conman
They use politic
As opposed to
People who was abused
Necessarily
And it's the same game
I feel like
You should be able to
To take a stab
It might be difficult but look at it from that prism
I'm see how
Done protectionism
White supremacy
A lot of those things are there religion
That they've been
Abused with
And they just haven't escaped
The church
It doesn't it doesn't
Come voronin
You're right
I see where you're coming from I think
The reason I still rather laugh
Because I didn't come from a desk called
I just came from a regular
Kind of situation
Problem in translation
Everything
And then they kill themselves right
Or others
So you
And and or others
I would like
To explore this more but I'm not entirely sure.
Episode
We're going into for our territory a 9-hour long episode of just you and I
By figuring out called
She wanted to do episodes not about Alex to that I say
I don't eat enough Jordan F have a job and then we will
And then we'll go right on into a radio show
Abbott Jordan I want it I want to get back to this idea that Alex was spitting about
VR like video games
Stop
He really tries to make hay out of the idea that like
All We Do
People using guns responsibly
Hollywood as people using guns responsibly
And video games of blasting people away
I'm not trying to say we should
Sensor
And I agree
But the problem with the comparison
Is he's responding to a
Fake version of YouTube's rules
I meant comparing it to
Fiction
Makes it all meaning
Yeah I'm saying
Ansel
I don't know it's a bummer it gets worse in this next clip where Alex Jones talked a little bit more about video game violence
It's like he's
He's creating a straw man
Comparing it to a virtual man-made
Yes
I agree neither of them are real
What is a straw man
One is art
What else is a virtual man made of
Tearing up
Anyway it is night club Alex has some
Weird f******
Sing ideas about the history of video games
But
Haven't the 60s
Do you have any idea as a video game
Like they were inaccessible to people
Two projections
What developed
For the military wasn't developed developed for the military
Instinctive shooting training Edge
All of that
That's the dumbest
Let that
That dumb
Like
I hear like
I just think like
I wish I was in
Sketch comedy
Cuz like that character Leah will cuz that character right there is a good like
Professor who's about to get fired
Character
All of that is so off base in Turkey
Monster bull facts about the history of video games
When did when did humans
Computers were made
What if
Which
Can you think of
Ultimately
Bring Me Back To Life
What is heat
Even think of
Computer
Rocky thinks the computers were created by Thomas Watson in order to help with nausea
Alright Google says that
He's not a big fan
Also by the way
So
It's a little bit of a problem
Yeah maybe a little bit though I played donkey
King Kong Country cuz I like to jump on heads
I like cartoon
Tune violin when was like
Even then
First video
Was the 1962 video game but it was
Computer
Game where you go
I believe is named!
It was
Giant computer energy like
Circular
Scream
It was just a boy
And then you move things in life
I guess it sort of a precursor to like Space Invaders
The arcade
Sure
Is to dehumanize
Okay
Good good stuff
Bingo if you are playing towards
Alex's
Clearly older
Rural audience
Where in you
All your butcher video games cause violence
Doing is just another version of the like
Millennials
Millennials are ruining this
Marilyn Manson and video games
It's a fun game
Play Alex is smart enough to know that like I can't play this game I have to play the I'm not playing this game
And then play the game
So
Cuz if he was a Call of Duty Black Ops
Do you remember that where you kill all the Nazi zombies
Oh man I would kill
Maybe got decent
Can't speak to this
From my own experience
Cuz most of my gaming
Life has been
10 doz.
Skyrim
Ezell's
Jesus
I wasn't thinking
Underground
What are they called
No
They don't exist
Who are the people who are all around it though those shity assholes were all around it were they called
I have
Play
Alright
We can't stick on Skyrim for the next
If you could come up with that race
Skilling
I think I might be right I think they were called
We got to quit the show
Alright
Over exaggerate
The volunteer for Revolutionary War
Infowars audience
10% of the United States
30 minutes
Denver Center sell worldwide
Percent of the world
So that means that like
Roughly a billion
Alright
Exactly right
I agree
Literal lunacy
And you heard that soft
Guitar playing in the background
Cuz this is
After the Revolutionary War
Also it Bears mentioning that is
Fifty-three percent of the population was involved
In the Revolutionary War
Is a specific reference to a group called The
Be 3%
I bet it's cut ties to white supremacy
Might not
Not
God on the 22nd
Alex spent a lot of
The time on his show talking about
How Trump
Is putting these tariff
On
China
That's a really
Important things to talk about whether or not
As as husband
Reported
Whenever China says
Put a tariff on our porch
Sale
China own
Most of the pork Market
So really what their responses is a
Yourself when you talk about terrorist
If they are responding in such a way as they know that
It's not really going
What is that mean
Two trumps
Saying that
He's going to
Pateros on there
You know
That there isn't really a
Tariffs are
I'm sure Alex
Cousin incisive
An important
This
Facts but we're not sure what this really mean I actually think that you generally speaking
Figure you're right on butt
In this case I think we're dealing with a
Entirely too
Situation
He plays a bunch
Eclipse
Streams live Trump
About this putting these terrorists on China
I would say to know that anything Trump says live is going to a disc
Desi's going to disavow his own
Actual
I would say
From
Unable to read
Angeline
This is
Probably going to cause a trade
U-Haul
Glasses
America
Incredibly hard
Hooter
That's going to be a disaster
I can't imagine doing that would hurt the middle class in the lower class
I base this song is
When it was
Coming up
To the point of making this amount
Kind of like people were talking about maybe Trump is going to do this
The Chinese State newspaper
Chinadaily War
Quote
History has shown the pinpricks of
Protectionism
Can ultimately lead to the Shoppes of War somewhere down the line
Great that's not subtle
Definitely something that you want a state-owned newspaper to say
Yeah as a warden
Awesome also Jordans
This is so gay
God dammit
Less than a month ago
Z champagne
Declared himself supreme leader for life
What is a big move
And wait
Anybody declaring himself dictator for life
That's just a regular that's the course of human events
He can't afford to look weak
Oh no
Is Levi these tariff
You have to assume
But he's going through
Respond
Now the fun part about this is the
The China has
Options how to f*** with us
Without doing anything
They can just slow down costumes
Sforno Reed
I'm making increase security inspect
Slow down trade that way they can Levy export taxes
Just random like they can do that one
Paperwork
Screw up
We lost my paperwork
Where do you get these sort of like
Little tiny things
And aren't illegal
And only f*** with us
Are the reasons that we Arkham
Completely outgunned
In terms of a trade War
With giant
They're much bigger
Some of them sold most of our business them overtime
But I would also a regulator
I would argue
The most likely what Trump is doing is posturing
Shoestring
Negotiating that will eventually end up leaving us back to exactly where we
We started
He's doing that
To use Alex Jones
To Virtue signal
To his base that he's hard on China
He's doing all these things
Comes back to the beginning
I think that's probably what's going on
Is the other possibility is
True of
You don't have a lake
The same is true of G-Eazy
Insofar
He has
Appear to be the same strong
His dumbass
I think Trump has to be
That's what I'm talkin about with you I just called myself supreme leader for life
Present himself
And I don't I am not going to go down the Alex Jones root of saying like
They got together and figured out this was the best way to both look strong
I would say it's more like the
I don't think
It's one of those things where you talk about
The difference
Collusion
Working at Mutual benefit
Like I'm sure they talk to each other and they were like
Hey I have
To do this
And he was like
I have to do this in response to that and they're both like
Okay cool well then we're going to do that
Thought about terrorists
Trump is
Islay
Varying Lee reported as 50 billion
60 billion
It's unclear
But
Take on it that I find
More troubling than any ideas
About China
.
Industrialization
Post-industrial era
Tucson weather
Agenda 21 agenda 2030
Do all this before I was ever on air
Was a huge dumpster John Birch Society
His lawyer
Boykin was the head
Both of them
Best friend
Throne
Am Healthcare
Everything before the contract
It's a classic
It is just mind-blowing right now
So before you agree
I agree before you leave it's just mind-blowing right now before you respond
I just want you to keep in mind with Alex Jones free
He's the opposite of a Russian agent
Where you at
All of the stuff
He said is the most
Damning stuff you can say about Trump's dick
Look okay was a f****** b*******,
Like that is where they f***
Can come from their entire existence
Just add in that timeframe being a large donor to
To the John Birch Society Society was founded by Fred
Who built
The third large
Oil refinery in the third right
He has a literal operator alphabet
Yep
Mikey is
His children are the Koch brothers
Created the Tea Party Movement
Now
About
The house on American
Nothing but great things
Jordan
The Bedford
They got rid of all
Do you know the house on American
Went down in history
As being the most
Great
Committee
Do you know how the the McCarthy version of the house American Onyx Havanese committee started
Square
It wasn't McCarthy
Strongarm
Joseph McCarthy in the house on American Activities Committee grew out of the McCormick dickstein special Committee of
Automatic connectivity
Which spent most of its time harassing left-wing organizations
Unions in particular but also trying to drum out Nazi influence in America
There's a little bit of good
Stuff in there possibly
Death started in 1934
According to records released
By the Russian
KV
EB the precursor to the KGB
As early as 90
1837 Samuel dick
Spain was literally a Russian spy
Taking in monthly payments
That by 1940 had totaled $12
$133,000 adjusted for inflation
The Russians had a code for dickstein
It was
Crook
That sounds from the Auntie nkvd files quote
Crooked
Completely justifying his code name
This is an unscrupulous type
Greedy for money
Can send it to work because of money
A very cunning swindler
Hey
Hey if your code name is crook that's
If the people who codename do crocus like
This guy's a crook is a swindler real
That's really bad
Special committee
On American activities
Through into the house on American
Have you so much I remember that quote he grew into the Martin Dies
Joseph McCarthy
Person who was
Jet Li
Literally a Russian spy
When the house on American Activities Committee landed under the leadership of right-wing Bart
Dies
Sam dickstein on the outside
He was no longer useful to the Russia
So they cut off payments
5 more years in Congress
Service New York
Really American history is filled with s***
From an article in the guardian
Courtyard
Yes
The committee itself stumbled on until 1976
When Congress finally killed it off
The Damage Done to American society is still visible today
Sample
In the almost almost physical horror of socialism and social democracy
After all these years if somehow fitting
To discover that it was the brainchild of a
Traitor
All of the root Coffeehouse
And set it on American Activities Committee
Comes back to
And so that's why it makes it funny that Alex is like
This guy was McCarthy's best friend
And you think he's a Russian it well I mean literally
$33,000 from the
Note to mean figuratively
No literally in the sense of the word literally mean
Literally he was a Russian f******
And as far as I can tell
Barring whatever might come out about Dana rohrabacher
Dickstein is
Legitimately the only Congress person who is
It's proved
Was on a foreign governments payroll
Like acting as a foreign spy
For the house on American Activities Committee
The history is a bit problematic
Quote in the book Harvey
Matusow
You wrote this book called.
Witness
He claimed that he was an FBI agent who's been paid to lie about his former friend
And some of the people
But he knew who used to work at a communist bookstore back in the
Back in those days
Some of those people were in prison because of his testimony where is others were black everybody
What books they could
In return
Received what books
Is a communist
Book Hangout
More than anything
So some of the people that have testified against were in prison and some of them
Because of his lies
He also named Joseph
McCarthy
Android
To give false testimony
Madison was a paid Informer
Who'd want to
All of his testimony
Mostly because it was all bulshit
He claimed to know 126 common is to work for the Sunday New York Times
Although they only employed
100 employees
At that time
His false testimony LED
Do union workers being wrongly imprisoned
And the blacklisting of
Many
People
Including folk singer Pete Seeger
O'Mara
Waheed at 1
So
Involvement that's the that's the worst betrayal
To hear this eager was
The traitor
He wasn't
Heartbreak
The traitor was dicks
Dickstein created the Committees
It became the Witch Hunt
Committees
Yeah of McCarthy
Under the tutelage
Complete monstrous a****** reykon
You know it's not Gradle nobody knows about this
Yeah
Ignore it
Yep
Show it
Did the
Is because
We won
To believe
Yeah Leggett
Heartbreaking
Ultimately
When you get down to it
The history of America
The history of the
Worst
You don't want to believe that it was just like just like with white people and
Concept of
You don't want to believe that
Every part
Of who you are and
Led to you
Dominating
Envy
Free p
To the murder of millions of on Billy
Ultimately what it is right like isn't that isn't that what
Isn't isn't being a white dude
Every morning you wake up
If not conscious
At least
Beneficiary
Of the fact that you have destroyed
Millions upon Millions upon millions of
How do you how do you say to yourself in the morning
I deserve what I got
Before I learned anything
Kush Collective response
Possibility is b*******
Nonsense
Like did you didn't
Do any
You are not responsible for that
So
You can work
On that
Bye
Killing all white people nope that's the wrong approach the wrong approach
At least number to you can work on it by recognizing
The argument
People in underprivileged
Which positions are making
By understanding
To help
As best you can Elevate their voices
I think is the best
Duke and
Recognize the places where your
Antisocial
Advantage
Because of coincidence
The other stuff
The guilt
Do you like I should kill myself because I'm white that's what all these minorities want
Those sorts of things are all just
It's the equivalent of taking an argument to the wrongest possible
Conclusion on the roadway
Too far and you end up in
In Steubenville
I don't know
I brought up stupidville for a reason
Vista has like a great transition about to happen
Our next
We're in the middle of a great transition happening Dan we have one last guest Jordans
And she
Is
Absolute resident
This
Person
Here we go
She's a
She's not a collar she's about Seussical
She's on to talk about that good sign
Is the
Boy she's a problematic figure no matter where you go I'm in the alt right
What about the West
The alt-right doesn't even like her
Alright
Deceive I found a bunch of articles that I don't
Laura Loomer I know her name
She's been on before she's talked about all Muslims are terrorists
SD
Monster we deal with Sean everyday
Hillary Clinton for a little bit too dumb dollar book signings
Butthole
I found a bunch of articles that like
I don't suck
You know how to eat
But like
Cassandra Fairbanks
And Lauren Southern
Work using
Laura Loomer of raping a dude
No idea how to engage with it
Because everything is to like
No words
I don't know what's going on
And not because it's a woman
Being accused of raping man that's absolutely
It does happen
But it just because
Characters
Like
I don't know what to do with
Whatever the reality of that stuff is
Is absolutely outside of the scope of our
Is pitchy is a
Monster
Islamophobe
She sucks
So hard right
Hitter now
I'm trying to
To research the
Las Vegas shooting
Research
And those are bad words
No no
I got to give her one tip of the cap
Like legitimately
Cheese
Set a bunch of balls
Absolutely not true
But she
She did make a video that demonstrated that
She could get into
Freight elevator
At that hotel
And
Great
No it is good
No it is it is telling on some level because
The people at the hotel had said that
No one could get access
To the elevator that would lead
From
The ground
Florida employee elevator to the 32nd
Can floor where
Play okay
You could that could be
Beyond the other conclusions that you make
Other stuff
Is Wild Bull Shake
Conspiracy
Alright
That's it
Should send that to
The hotel
Come to Beef It Up
Secure
I've always wanted to do this as if I was like writing a tweet
It's sweet on air I've never been able to do like meme stuff to play out of me
I I don't like the way you pronounce
Pronounce
Bubba
So today
Laura Loomer comes on
Talk about
Coover investigation
22R listeners who are not watching the livestream
Looked at his
Hand the park ironically
No
Parkland
Real quick
Laura Loomer used to work for James O'Keefe
For project veritas
I think she got a sub
From him
Organizers here in Florida
Liberals just gathering together and dc2
Giffords Foundation
Foundation
Gabrielle
The former
Nope
Gabrielle
Giffords that the lady who was shot in the f******
Head Start in Arizona
Chrissy's
All right sounds
Forget about that event is
Shooting
And remember that the federal judge
Killed four other people beyond that
6 people total
Gabrielle Giffords
Song of miraculously survived
Oh and since then has dedicated her life to
To trying to figure out a way that we can have more sensible gun control measures
Yeah
F****** real
Good wife f****** love Giffords Foundation would be involved
With these Parkland kids
I also it
Bears mentioning
That the guy
Who did
The
The Killing
In Arizona
He was a guy whose name
Jared
Lee Loughner
Broke I don't understand
He's a guy who also
Unfortunately last
Bunch of blog post
In his wake
Jeffrey died
Is it carry a bunch
Infowars
The rhetoric
He says stuff like quote the government is brainwashing
People biking
Trolling
Sounds great sound
Marion
It's weird at all that
Foundations
Involved in
To help out
Provide grounds
Support for children
Don't know how to organize
Interstate
Rallies of Their Own
It's f******.
But this
I want to just talk about that really quick
I think that's more an issue of
As a parent
Students
Who are 60
17 years old
To know
There's going to be people f******
Here are the talking points
You don't want to go on TV and act like an
Masshole
And then become a laugh
This wasn't a concern do people need to have 20 years ago 15 years ago
But now there's such a manipulative
You know you'd better to stuff with the Sandy Hook people who were like this guy was laughing right before he
He came on and gave his speech
He's fake
Like you don't want to have those bad
X moments
I don't think it's
Debbie Miller is her name
Future
It don't matter
No
It doesn't
Responsibility
It doesn't matter what reality
It doesn't matter if every single f******
Thank you say
Israel
Because they're going to even if you say everything perfectly
Perfectly they're just going to create a hole
Separate
F****** reality
Pretends It Whatever It Is
F*** you said
We don't live in a world where reality
Matter
Reality
Jordan
PR f******
Gill's whenever they don't even
They don't even realistically matter for the bath
It doesn't matter
It couldn't hurt
In their f****** hands and then
And they be like
F****** b*******
It doesn't matter it's not going to change it like why are we putting it on me
Children
F****** knowing god damn
Adult should f******
Adult showing up
Everybody is wondering
What you're screaming about
Why aren't
Parents and adults showing up
Is the Giffords Foundation
They're showing up
To try to help
Because you know I know and is trying
I know right
It's just
I don't understand.
I'm not trying to quell your passion I just I know I know
The Giffords organization
This
Laura Loomer
His caught on video
Or manifestation
Of adults
Who are trying to
To help these kids
Express themselves
Accurately right
And in a way that's not good
Here is the only thing
That I
Feel about what's going on
With
Especially in regards to
All of these kids
Staying very
And it doesn't matter
It doesn't matter
My point
Continue
Tubi
Why are we
For what these people are
You mean the the right
These were
Why bother
Why bother acting like
We need to have a
PR strategy
What is white matter
Okay
Because there
Who cares
No no no
Because
They have the rest of their lives in
Who cares
Don't
No no no
This meeting
Ostensibly easy
The teacher in Broward County
Talking to
Two students
Write better going
To go on this
What I would assume is
Field trip
Flash
Protest
Rally
They have a responsibility
Adults
I don't
Think of it when they're talking
Think about talking
It's like
Used
Right
More like
Stay on message
Reggie you agree with this
If not do this
Keep your dog. Make sure you know
Escape now that there
Play it on the show
In one of her Undercover videos
She's like
Broward County
Teacher Debbie Miller
There should not be any kids
Alone
And I would say even if
Where you're going
Ulta
It's a field trip Bass
Physically
She might as well
Use the buddy system
They want to make
Supported by
The Giffords
Innovation
The Run by a woman
Here's my argument against that which is that
Who
I'm sorry
Argument against that is just
F****** care
It doesn't
There is no right there is no longer a conversation
That is not a thing better
So if you want to if you want to say
We should get rid of all guns in the history of ever
We should go back in
During the American Civil War
Or the American Revolution
People who care
About Gunn
Are going to
Twist and turn
I forgot to tell you one of the most fun things about this
That that whole YouTube and
What's going on
The gun videos of it
Slingshot videos of Germany
Slingshots
He's concerned it like his
Brights are going
I'm construct
Could you say this in a German
Accent I would make me feel better
I'm not Alex I don't do shity accent
But his was stopped
Is
Something and his
Response to it was
We should Union
Yeah
Which is a reasonable or like idea
World collide with Alex
Could never deal with a guy who makes
Gun
Construction
Contact your creators
For YouTube we should unionize
We should make a union because they're encroaching our ability to make gun videos on YouTube
Now think about this
The only arguments that Alex
And his ilk
Have at all
In terms of REM
Either
Unionizing
Putting regulations
They have to go against themselves in order to
Anyway
I'm sorry I'm furious 4 sucks
It will cause us to get off track
Jordan is.
You're so much
Jews control the politicians in Washington
She said oh this is super off-the-record
Literally
Students to break the law and storm the White House and March to the
Lighthouse Inn
Raise Hell
So
Permits and permits are
Really important
Where are the really important
But the people shoot people
Ahead
Really
Just messed with it being shot
I had a little bit
Tulsa
So
I watched a YouTube channel if you want it's
Very boring
It also is very selective
Edited in the same way that
James O'Keefe
Project Veritas videos are
I will give Laura Credit in as much as she allows.
Supposed to happen I won't sometimes they end up leading into other senses
Or unrelated
I don't give her
Goddamn bit
Credit address
First of all permit
Permits to
The First Amendment
Permits are huge
This part of the first time
Understanding of civil order in if you want to organize somewhere
And I'm not I'm not coming down
What Debbie Miller
In this video it's a
Is that
They were unable
Fire app
Not that they failed to
Acquire permit
Given one
Different it's slightly different
Can understand
But they have a permit
To have a rally
So what they're going to do is have a rally
And then she says
Winking voice
If we all leave the same direction
That sort of thing
But
I would argue
I've been to
100 goddamn Rally's in my life
That's how they all go
Everyone
Kind of just
The real
It's not the right to
That's not like a left right thing
If you
Permitting
Right
I and I'm not I'm not I'm not saying that like
In Sumter
Kind of like
Flippant
Defending
This protest not defending other
Waze
Like
When
The KKK has a permit
Rally
Alright
Good luck
I think I'm fine with that
Is
Teacher in the CPS
When she was
Sing about the
Walkout
That the students
We're going to have
For the Parkland
Weather like
Everybody needs to f****** do something
The administration of
The school dance
Okay
It's already going to have a walkout
We're going to do 17 minutes of silence redo the whole thing
Well then
Spore
So the people who are complicit in the shooting happening
Are going to lead a
Pointless meaningless protest
And then everybody's going to go back to
To school then
F****** care if I think that's the grander conversation
This conversation is
Do you like
Your student
Your school is Soros operated
You're fine with The Rock
Your conversation is real conversation is
Why is anybody going
Mario
Everyday you go to school
Your school gets
Everyday your school gets money
Your school is more susceptible to
You getting
F****** shot
Everybody should f****** shut
Shittown
.
Like Franklin like I don't even want to go to work like a real thing where it's like if we all
Could just f******
And we can't do it we can't do it because
We all have to
Or we could we live with it
That's called Market live in a world where a union
A real Union
Is fuc
Wow and that's not a world that we can ever that
Comes back to
The consequences
Goddamn Russians
Traitor
Created
Visceral disgust
Let me have
In the name of
Patriotism
And protecting America
He created
Unintentionally or intense
Internally
A complete disgust
About the idea of social
Democratic
Socialist democratic
Lingers to this day
We just got to f******
Find a way to deal with it
The worst
Part about that clip no the listen to what they're saying
This teacher Debbie Miller
Proclaimed
The Jews run the politician
Who hasn't
Batshit
Flo's off me at this point like this point I'm like
Run the politician me see if I can cut back too and find
Jews control the politicians in Washington
Amazing
Riddles
So I went and pulled the clip that
She's actually talking about
YouTube when she clearly proves that she
Said that the Jews run the politician
Lowe's in McDonough
That's what Debbie Miller said
You heard that story
They say the Jews are in charge of the weather but the
Clear Lake
No
That's not what you said that's not even what she said
Good job
She said
I would say something
I'm saying about that
Politician
The Jews harp
Right
Trayon White
A DC council member recently said
It started smelling out of nowhere this morning man
Y'all better pay attention to this climate
Control man just climate manipulation
That's a model based off of Rothschild
Controlling the climate
Create natural disasters they can
Paying for their own in these cities man
Be careful
She's making a joke
About this guy who died
A week ago
Silica gel
It's at the salad it's a salad
She's playing to the crowd
This is why this is
Is a great joke
Why is it a great
When Debbie Miller made that joke that meeting
It was a air
It's
There was like you could hear laughs because people had to read that story
Response would read that story in the understood what she was talking about
Yeah it's
Funnier
Because Laura Loomer was
There
He was not
She was at the meeting secretly recording
That's how she has this audio
She was secretly recording all this
So she's secretly recorded all of this
Then
Took it
Then misrepresentative
On Alex Jones Show
Where they accuse Debbie Miller of making anti-semitic remarks about how the Jews run
Which isn't even
Close to what
She said
On a show
Alex Jones
Absolutely accused the Rothschild that haven't weather Rapids
Fix my
Doesn't matter why coach know this guy trayon white absolutely was inspired by
He's whether it's Infowars. Or a Infowars
Surrogates
He's inspired by his head like it let me make clear what my point
Is that
Why bother
Pretending
That there's a world
Coach
PR purse
Phrases saying something
Let the right-wing plan in a perfect world
Cheetah nails in a perfect world no explanation
Give a f*** about the
These people need to be left
Ain't nobody should ever know
That's what I get serious me about the idea of a Centrist
Democrat
Everybody
They are gone
If you are somebody who is concerned
About what
Misconstrue what you said into thinking
If you're somebody who's like oh well the Southern Poverty Law Center said this
Who cares
Take me to go
Put forth
Actual
Progressive
F****** idea
End
Go
Say it real
Say it loud
People should not
Pretend that there's a
Third Way people should not pretend that you need to
Say things in the middle there's no middle there's these people who are f****** trying to murder it
There is a fuk
Rectify
The middle is trying to live
Survive coming
F****** Apocalypse in the middle
Bill
There is a compromise
Between
The idea that we should
Find a middle ground
Compromise doesn't exist
When the other side
Compromise
Cuzick
With
The very very rare people who are
Shopkins
That compromise.
But
Play we live in a world where
Praying are we talked about the Alberta
Window so much
So goddamn
How far to the right
It's basically compromising
Yes
The battle
Compromising with
Orthocenter
Where to actually identify
As
On the right are
Fairfax
At this point
And you do what I imagine that
There's a hypothetical world that
Exist where
Things went a different way
That maybe thing
Or something like that in our country
We had a
Yeah there's
Like
Leader
Who take
Alternate reality
I'm not saying that
Always fighting fascism is great
But
Right but
There is a way there is a way that liberalism and leftism is exploited also
Like with Communist governments in the past it like if we want to go back to
Alex Jones is shity Rhodesia metaphor
Like what
Mugabe went bad
Like there is a point
Where
Like things are going
That way
And then I imagine there are people
Who are on the right who are like
I'm only able to compromise with
Epicenter I can't compromise with the
Right actually left
Exist now but unfortunately
That is not our reality
That is a hypothetical reality
And that's
That's my
I have a long-standing
With
Anybody who uses
Is the word popular
Right cuz
Is not an
Is always
Associated
With that fashion
Just leader that shows up
May not always begin with but becomes it
That's what you're popular
Associated with always always want something.
Lake
The personality
It's that nonsense
It's
The I care about you but
The two most important
I care about you
What's up
Like we talked about
Those
Those Concepts
Sonos ID
The destruction of them always wind up being
Miss associate
Might be a way
The association
With populist to the dictator that are right
Right leg the idea
Bernie Sanders had won the Democratic nomination
Become a be president
He would have been become Mugabe right like that's the idea of populism that
Associated
And
It is
Always
Always comes back to that
People doing f***** up so bad that they're willing to do
Anything other than what's go
Like the idea of a populist
Trump is not up
Parking
Like our entire show is a demonstration of him being a victim of a con man
It is a
Concentrate
Enforcement
VI
Diaz that we should let
No we shouldn't
We shouldn't know I kind of think they should
I kind of think we should
I think we should drag them
Because there's
They're not there
Alright nevermind
I'm going to let this
I just I don't I don't I don't know what time we're going to come tonight I really don't even think I can
Incoherently make my point let's do I apologize
Southern
But also Laura Loomer
The same first name
The first like 5 letters
But you can
Like
Your boy got it alright alright
Here's my dismount
So that's that
Website knowledge pike.com we're also on Twitter
You can also kill the rich
Go to Facebook
Where you can kill the rich group go home tell your mother you're brilliant
Lot of people get killed by the ridge there
X over The download yes
Absolutely
And a lot of fun
But
I want to I want to give him more abstract
Shout out at the end of the step
Episode
No
I mean they should go f*** them
But
I would say
Alex Jones's beholding
To his
Guns
Answers
Can go f*** itself
That's not good
It is actually very good
Bugatti
Alexandra Thurston color