Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
As a replacement California
Madrag
Hello welcome back to the show
Thank you it's been awhile it's good to have you learned anything about Alex
Just stuff it's been in the news I remember
Michelle
But I know a lot about Alex Jones you still know very little about him
Don't know if I told you every time I usually leaves
This time might be no different
That is something that is one of the listener sometimes
I like the show but this is depressing
I know
Sorry
It's not so much he's just in the van like a Rush Limbaugh or whatever just
A character spell announcer
Since we can make money today more there are out there that believe like I knew a guy that
And there's no conspiracy
Diaper
But a fluoride
Staffing hadwin
For your mind
Okay you can have it
It's something that I struggle with
But you know you got to keep moving forward
I think I think that there is plenty of stuff that's at least
I can't make an argument.
Fun at all
Yeah you do a lot of the older I get the more I'm kind of like I'll just find them
My little pillow and whatever is going on and just
Until I die
Sure
So whatever whenever the ship comes take a nap and go out with the world
Whatever is fine.
Yes
I don't know what you
Can change the I hope
I hope you can
Look here's the deal whatever children
I will say that
I had a thought
Google's always good
Very much appreciative
I'm a policy wonk
Appreciated
Yourself you can go to our website
Do it the simple deal
I know I've got a lot of friends it's
That's great
Is that right
I don't know if you do know I just guess I had some
I don't think so
Never met
It's pretty cool on this episode were going to be talking about today
Nope nope we're going over
Friday March 23rd 2018
Conociendo last weekend
I usually try and move on to a note
This week
Is this episodes coming out on Monday and well in the past
Does last week
But there's nothing important news that it come out that it
I think it's relevant
How much is he still talking about yeah
People people in like to know what beverages its Sparkling Ice Mountain black cherry
Don't like it
Xavier not right now
I hope you like it by the end of the bottle
You and Jordan are anti-life mountain and I do not like it
Cuz I'm not a fan
Fizzy water that's fine
A hundred percent
Daniels will not come up
What have you
He did make a video that came out on Saturday over the weekend
Turning on Trump
Because he signed the Omnibus spending Bill everybody being like
Alright
The Fox News Andy
I appreciate
Any glimpse
Love reality.
Those people want to shall I was like
When troubles like later
Eddie's like if Obama said that
Why have you not heard every person say that for the last year-and-a-half
Alex I take on that was that it's a Machiavelli and trying to lure people into the open in order to
Gun registration
Gun laws
These guys are good
They're pretty good yeah
The ability to do backflips
With reality
But you know what it is review might also have someone pitching impression
Like it with the comedy show
From today's show that says show some of that
The games I play
Apologizing
Yeah that's
Do it we just like the catalog every time you break that is Bernie Sanders impression very important
Big news that happened on Thursday and that's why the Friday show sort of important cover
Sweetwater
That's that it might be
Just your perception
Are you a beast
What happened on Thursday the most
Important is that they announce
The HR McMaster was going
He's going to be replaced
John Bolton
Big Red
Flag for Alex
This should be a very like I'm out kind of moment
Because John Bolton is a
Notorious
He is someone who is very in favor of the Iraq someone who
Intelligent
He's also still in favor of the Iraq War
Very publicly made the argument that
The problem was we didn't stay there long enough we weren't aggressive enough
Yet his
His president
Give me Donald Trump
Is that there's an article in the intercept
Just came out
On Friday as well.
Who started the break
It's disgusting
John Bolton 8 months ago gave a speech
To a group of Iranian exile
People
Call Dee people's mujahideen
Mainly John Bolton
Viable alternative
To the regime
That is in power in Iran
And
Basically
The eridian revolution
Ayatollah Khomeini Revolution
1979 will not last till its 40th birthday
Which would be
The beginning of 20
Telling this separatist group
Working-out topple that by the end of 2018
So Alex should be thrilled with any of that you should be very against
And now we have someone
Security advisor
Clearly in favor of war with Iran
Among other places
Sin City is great
Water roller coaster Park Tycoon
Sure surprised
John Bolton
Cuz they're all just b*******
We got Rodger Stone popping in to give us his take
On Donald Trump's New National Security advisor
Mister
Bolton
A lot of people really don't like including
The word is on Bolton
Interstate Department in the UN in the Pentagon
And that he will be a nap or a
Cool
Munchkin
Edwards
The carryout
Policies that the president wants carried out
He won't sit there and information
Cool cool cool
So this is Rodger Stone telling Alex
All right here's the talking point
When will people realize that the person leaking the information
Is the guy that
Some of the country of
He's the one that's he can't stop telling his friends everything and that's how the information together now
That might that might be part of the game
Exactly there'll be it'll be sort of Palace intrigue
Not games being played instead of important issues
You'll notice Alex uses the word ratchet
I don't know what that means
It's just a function area
I use you as a
Instrument of my will and it's only interesting because it's a word
Use of that later when talking with Rodger Stone
That's a Rodger Stone words just repeating
Use people that way like
Bring people that have
To use them
Is there a
Apple ratchet ratchet
Sure
Knox
Blissfully
Obtuse
Oh wait
Jesus Britney's bring this guy in at 2 to
You know get
He's sleeping.
You're bringing a John Bolton
McMaster
Isalita
He's leaking stuff
Explain
On
Congratulate
And then Trump
President again
Some people
Call the Communist Chinese
Is appointed by the Communist party and now for lot in life
By the politburo
So
Tired of the lies
Is not addictive
I love strong man
What do you mean about food
I do not believe so
Well in our 2015 investigation into why Alex join team Trump
Concurrent
Very strong pro-putin Santana
Quite a while
Hate him saying that
Congratulate
Privately
But also that was in 20
12 different time
Hacking election
The Game of Life
Hey why didn't you call the Chinese guy dictator like that a point the finger at bankwell
We could do that
We can say that
Sure
Point
That's right
Jai
Sneezing
I'm not that involved
In this next clip
You are a little bit.
But
Jordan
It is a boy
We're now we're going to get to something
Does a little more familiar
Is mad about him,
Spell because
He thinks that they're coming at him inappropriately
What you think about it
There's been an attack
Why
And the main
Mint represent
Impersonal
Thomas middleditch
Middleditch
Cover of the magazine
Okay
Covers
Because he believes it has to do with making it cool
As he would say
Thomas middleditch
Made fun of that idea
More about this weekend leave that aside for now unless you have any immediate responses
Well I just know he's very anti Jordan klepper
Some of that
He doesn't like being made fun of
He's a little bit of a little sensitive
What's interesting to me that I find Most Fascinating is that whenever he gets made fun of
He creates a fake version of what people are making fun of and then gets mad about that
Instead of like
You hurt my feelings
Which is really what he's saying
There's a
A child
Intuit
Do you think Thomas middleditch has a fake name
No I don't
IMDb
Thomas middleditch
I know that he came up in Chicago that was his name when he was here
For he was on
TV
I don't know
I got two strong
Feeling that that maybe
Are the neighbors actually
Chicago
Dan Friesen
Jordan
I think we have an aversion to b******* Alex's pretty pretty
He's one of the larger voices of b*******
Jordan klepper
Exactly
Some of the people that your mock
I think any of those types
Shows are you know with the satire that they're doing
Some of it's been real
So
I think there's some pieces that hit
Some babe
Kind of missed the point
Generally I don't know if there's enough
To make a show out of
Yeah necessarily without getting a little
Cuz some of the pieces that I've seen that have been posted as you
YouTube videos
I like yeah right
I do I get the game
What's going on
Can make fun of him yelling a bit
I think too that you open up the possibility of
Like playing into his hands
The tiny bit
Okay because when you have a dedicated
Show on Comedy Central this about him
He's got to be like
They're dedicating
Millions of dollars to attack
Sure that sort of thing
There's a complicated
There's a weird way that Alex's brain works that I think a lot of people don't understand
I think
The most
Scathing attack that can come from hell at him
Is from
A bedroom there frankly I think that's cuz we don't have any
Don't have Comedy Central.
No Soros money or anything like that is just
Play Hold on I I was told I was getting a check for
From George Soros
Colorado
Check the Foreman grill
Secure package
4 minutes
I take a grill
Get all the juices out of my meat
Yeah
We get in the next clip
We get a little bit more insight into the bolt
Narrative
Bad receive
I clearly that it's coming from Rodger Stone
Rodger Stones relationship
What what about Rodger
We'll get to that in a minute
Rodger Stones friends with
Senior National Security advisor
Whiskey and play poker together for
30 years
He says Bolton is an apple
People follow Trump's orders and will not leak in his dog light is loyalty
The present
I spell apparatchiks
Not even close I don't believe now
He has a guy on Francis Boyle
The professor
Just keeps repeating Rodger
Gaston kind of line
How we both don't like Hillary
But then
You have you have this Rodger says he's an apparatchik
Just get back to you like all those were the narratives coming from
What's up
Apparatchiks
Oh
Interesting
Well that's news to all of us
Where's the narrative come from
A character reference
For this
Crazy warm
Anytime anyone thinking something bad about that
Just come talk to me and I
Probably
Romeo come talk to you in 20 years if we're still friends
Still alive by poker in awhile but
Chaotic
Play every hand I'm just lay off I'm mostly played
Me a 25
We talkin
We're talkin to sneak attack baby
$10 game
I don't think I do that
Burroughs
Okay thanks
Directions to Naperville
Girls f****** stop it
Sure
Absol
This weekend
How did the March for our lives
Around the country
Tons and tons of people came out to protest
A gun regulation
I have you
I should let everyone know I am an NRA
A Boy a Gun
That no one will know whose kids are did you hear that I heard that argument which is
Kind of callous
A little bit little bit rough
To hear
I think like a
I think that the gun question is becoming a little bit muddied
I'm strongly in favor of what these kids are pushing for and what have you
But I think it's
Need to get the perception that everybody wants all guns
Destroyed or all guns
Confiscated
And I don't believe that that's necessarily the conversation
I think the people on
Some people on Twitter think that's the conversation
What's happening pushing
Instead of actual having a,
Translation Leicester way of pushing back
Just last year with the Democratic
Text Heather
Uniforms
No no
Interpretations that have been done by the evens
Supreme Court about
The Second Amendment have said clearly that
Second Amendment
Does allow for
Some regulation that could happen
Regulating what appropriate sales of guns are and s*** like that
Does
Wake Campus
She's really mad
David Hogg
Particular in this episode
Here's a really funny clip where he complains
About David Hogg
Amanda where Jose is fun
Hog
So he's running around
Horrible things about me
Wonderful person
Angry with him
Thank you for teaching me in America how we should behave thank you David
It's so funny to me the repayments to an ad for super male after complaining about how a high-schooler is treating him
If that's what your f****** stuff does if that's what your supplements do for you that's the level of
Strength
Yeah
That is a mess
Also I love the presentation to the beginning of that that's like
He's not getting attention anymore so he's got a lash out at me
Legitimately that Bart was
Overflowing Street
And that's not just him
No
That's the
And he's going to keep getting attention while we do nothing
Just they're not going away
That girl's going to Long Hair By the time
Yeah yeah
David Hogg
Eclipse
You goddamn motherfukers apologizes
He understands was not appropriate because being interviewed at a dinner table
Not a not a professional operation at all
And he's just saying like
His conversational swearing other hoes to Alex's
8 year-old who just learned about the word sock
And stuff like that
If David
Some criticism
Swearing like a human
Squares I don't understand I feel like that's the thing that
I don't want to put Christians on Blaster like morel
The people that think they're the morality police
But if you would talk that way I can't believe you would do that
Yet you allow other people to get away with the worst things in the world
Who
Like we play enough I'm not that bothered by the fact that
You know you got it
He got it or whatever
But don't come at me like you're a great person and you're immortal
Personally that you're cool with that.
Aspect to it I think zip
You know pain
People off
Do not be no they're not lying about
That's x-borg
Because he didn't want the evangelicals or whatever to think different of them or
Right
The train Jeff
Earlier
I apologize for derailing the
No that was on the rails
Weave back onto the
Clip train
We get back to
The Thomas middleditch beta male narrative
Okay
Explain
What keys
Talkin about
Computer stuff
Comes out of beta
Beforehand
Understand why I talked about the cover of The Hollywood Reporter magazine
The triumph
They made fun of that
What do you mean
Star of Silicon Valley
And
It's amazing that
Impersonal
I meant that guy
Sxsw four years ago
I've been shooting with basically the whole cast.
Call Jeanette
Videos about Ozonics
Is that a brother Rodger Stone in 1 minute
That's how they turn this whole thing around
Pushing pushing
Round robin
Everybody's getting cancer
It's an agenda
Hollywood Reporter
Criticize the push by the government
Oh that's what it is
Is a person
Alpha male poses
I just type in Hollywood Reporter
Typing.com
The triumph
Hollywood celebrities
And then it is a subliminal of gay men
What are all putting their hands are pocket behind each other
Is they have a
The name of that
I'm not going to say it on here
Alright thank you
Interesting analysis
Yeah I think what he's trying to come up with is either a daisy chain the whole situation
But they don't take it the ladder Martin starwire
That's
That's been that's interesting
I think I think
Of the
Set up a
Necessarily
If you're watching this live
Check out
Do you think this is Buzz Marketing Alex's doing
He's getting a little bit under the table from HBO there buzzed Market as we've been talking about Barry at all
Another show
He's from SNL
Stefan
Bill Hader oh yeah
Every TV
Resume surprises not been on
Talking about he's everywhere
Very strange
It wouldn't surprise me to Terra Blade
I don't understand like what don't you understand if you watch the show
The whole show is there all just kind of f******
Deeks
And dorks yeah
So
Totally fit the whole
Profile
Why would he ever watch the show
Other than his good
With the whole cast
Is friends with Mike Judge
I understand they are actually friends
TJ Miller doing that I think about it
I don't know if middleditch
Fascinating
Zach Woods
Oh God to be a fly-on-the-wall for that
I got arrested
Is professionals all right I'm sure he'd
Yeah that checks out
Government trying to push beta males
Because they want to destroy the family the trying to feminize everybody right
Frog stuffed we're going to discuss towards the end of this episode
Alex Jones doesn't understand
To weld up the headlines of things and then decides to extrapolate them to
Irresponsible degrees and that's what he's done
More or less
No
I'm so the government pushing beta males in the trying to make
Thomas middleditch
I am Stephen Colbert
Beta males
On the show in order to make fun of Alex Jones
For talking about the government's plan to push beta males
Through this article and headline
It expects
No sense
You should be a cop
Like the way he can just twist things around in one night
Going to get a lot of kids
Are huge and people up so hard
So many false conviction
Speaking of
Rodger Stone
I have spoken
Into
The people he probably shouldn't
Have in the past
Surfer 2
Well Circle article just came out
We talked about our last episode of The Daily Beast
Eyewear they've demonstrated that guccifer
2.0
Apparently does crack back
2 Russian intelligence
What are the times that he signed on
Alaska server and IP address
It appears that it is actually Russian intelligence
Rodger
Has been like
Russian intelligence
Different
Because
Going to jail baby it's his position is slightly less defensible now
Sirius you always have a lot of stuff on your radar what else are you looking at right now
Well there's a big move today because The Daily Beast which is
Credible news organizations
In the country
I believe that they have proved gustafer 2.0 is a Russian
Which allows them to revive the headline
Trump associate Rodger Stone
With Russian hacker
Perfunctory
It is an Oculus
Haha
It's a smear so the point is my conversation with him anyway
For the DNC material I bet Subway
But it gives the left an opportunity to recycle that headline
Trump associate Rodger Stone communicated with Russian hacker
It's fake
Alex
Well I mean it's not it's not big news strictly speaking because
If
Reporting about guccifer 2.0 is correct
Rodger Stone have contact
That is not fake news as a real headlights
Doesn't necessarily mean there was coordination between
That's not that's not that's proven but the fact
He was in contact with them
I've some of the messages
Why that there was some sort of
There's one message that guccifer sent him those like
Paying you back
Or something like that
There's a lot of questions definitely need answers now
This development is
Come back using terms like that's ex post facto out trying to use legal terms
He knows he's got to protect himself a bit
Re-up
Of course
Rogersbase
A part of the investigation for a long time
PU
I mean I'm not pointing necessarily like a specific finger
But I'm saying
Before being like before
But that's still kind of like
A little bit
In this next clip
We get some fun
So
During Friday's
Episode show
Donald Trump
Is going to give us
Oh about the Omnibus spending bill
Sure thing of the day Alex
Convinced
The Trump is going to veto it
As demonstrated in this clip
I will give you the extra battery
He's going to send her some good things and spending bills bad things
The border wall and because of spending
The swamp
Is delivering a giant
So that this take
Is Trump
Start speaking
And then we're going to get onto this
Ridiculous situation that took place over the last
Week so
Okay
Sorry
And As Trump keeps talking Alex realizes
Oh
So we have
Hi boss
Tilda Swinton from the Fox news feeds or the white house because there's this better
I don't like that too much in a dozen
So he's like
I got to figure out how to land on this list.
Flies
You don't have to go to
He's not honest
Buc-ee's on radio station
I feel like he
You showed some cards
There
He was expecting a veto and it didn't happen
I got to figure out where to land on this
Everybody coming back
Playing the press conference again
Say something
Very not into
And I don't know why he allowed this to not like
Whatever
Something inconvenience Alex's narratives happens usually just starts yelling over it and hopes people don't hear it
Like whenever they do the debates you just yell over Hillary
He should have yelled over this
Our military equipment is the best equipment in the world
2 days ago with Saudi Arabia
And with other country Saudi Arabia
Hundreds of billions of dollars
Then we're getting
Therefore is a matter of National Security
Budget bill
He is literally saying
What is the consideration
Was that we're selling
Millions and millions of dollars of our
Stuff to tell
I thought I was in a billion-dollar it sounded like you said billion
Well but to be fair
A real red flag for Alex
Billions of dollars of arms sales to Saudi Arabia who Alex is not in favor of
Shirley took
Our
Deep state
What have you
ISO
I don't know why you played that
Let the
But he realizes that
S*** you signing the bill
EXO
Trump keeps talking
Mustang
They must end
The filibuster Rule and get down to work
We have to get
Legislation approved
It'll happen just like magic
The president is right behind here is the brace
And I
Because I have no way
I think that's something the present really should have
Okay
Right on my board
Yeah shut it down
U-Store-It
That's not good
So
What's even worse
Did you rather Alex Jones come out again
I don't know I
Auto on one level in terms of like I'm always
Not pulling for Redemption cuz I think it's impossible at this point
But I'm always pulling for like that
Voice that's got to be in the back of his head the remembers who he used to be
No
Yeah stop putting up with this s***
I'm always pulling for that to happen but I know it
Did you see how much of his
The pastikan retcon
Iot keeps
Accepting whatever Trump does
Yeah like what's Trump
Suspend the midterm election
Algebra like of course
The Democrats are trying to steal all of these election
He's just trying to protect America
Heat that's the level of
Nonsense that he's capable of
It'd be a lot less
Commercials auntie
CBI depreciate
That's one consideration
Entitled
Hellboy
Yeah we're all sick of that
It's back to the David Hogg
Situation
Lake
I know there's a little bit during the campaign cuz jumps out of yelling
It's all through Rodger Stone
Do you think Trump rolls around
Every four years I go come around
Reruns
A hundred percent
I think I'll show up if he's running again then
You know we're still there
Be there like I have to
Yeah but I think most of the interaction if any is through Rodger
And I even have questions how much Rodger is necessarily speaking
I don't know
That that's all speculation
We can't pop
But what I can't I do know the truth about is that Alex
About to lie
About David Hogg
We can't we can't have it both ways you know like I don't know if I do
I don't I don't know that the ideas like
Labeling my child when it's
Convenient
And treating me like an adult when it's
Yeah I don't know
Anyway
The truth is Alex
Taxis a child
And also his mother thought
I want to hear that
I'm going to air the profanity Lake
Sparta High School senior who is a public figure
He wants to debate
What's keratin
Bullying
No
Alex was getting bullied
You hate to hear that
You just
I mean it is just what are you doing there
Okay
Hutterites
I don't know
I think that
Scale of bullying
Not very high
Very high on the scale of bullying
Consider people's
In-N-Out
Position
Alex Jones being a
In charge of air
Quite large media Operation Ivy
Probably
What about
Ice cooler
Friends got murdered saying he's a scam artist
Yes
Using profanity when
You called
Adam Schiff
C********* beat his ass cuz you're drunk on air
His statements
David Hogg
A little more palatable
They don't really
Poster child A3000
Where the mass shooting happened
To go out with
So what are they going to do
Stromme
He's vicious Tyrant cussing and yelling at gun owners.
It's all
Coming up
At the bottom of the hour
He's it up baby
Coming up at the end of the hour.
Couple more my pill commercials before we get to it and then you'll be disappointed
But the thing is when you saying
People are saying that I said they were crisis actors I didn't say that
All I said is that these kids are in the drama club in their actors and they work
Clearly chosen
With talking points that they're being given by the powers-that-be were clearly paid by Soros
It's like
You're just describing basically what people think crisis actors are and not using the term
To I don't find that argument
Super compelling
You know what every time this happens
Alex's tournament
You can tell by this lady I just threw
Cuz she thinks
That's the most forward positive thing that's ever happened on this podcast
So
Did Alex get bullied
You could set your sights
I'll take it off at least drawing I just made
Buy ice cooler
How old is 40 Alex
Same school buses a child
Getting bullied by a f****** seventeen-year-old
Another complaint
Operations
It's pretty hilarious
How does he treat
God continually misrepresented
Facts about
Continue
MPR pieces this week
MSNBC eclipse
No one died
Then
Works with
We visited before the shooting ever happen
Lobby Davenport were shut down YouTube
The organization
That's that's super
Interesting
Oh no
A couple months back
Alex Jones had Mike cernovich on
And they started a contest where they were going to pay people
Thousands of dollars
To go on CNN with is Isis
Yeah
It's Deanna is Isis shirts talking about how
Uncivil
Needed that
Okay
You know it's not necessarily 121 connected
Inquiring minds are very fascinated by the
Tire contest was going to give out like
Like a hundred thousand dollars
Two people who would die
Yelling
Yep they're complaining about allegedly George Soros paying people
It is kind of interesting
Well they didn't
I think so yeah I mean you did a contest where you pay people to go on TV and interrupt
Clinton rallies yelling
What's the paycheck
What's how much am I getting paid today
I think it's either a thousand or $2,500 pending on what you get on TV
If I got to be pretty nice
You just got to go find live television and
Do you think you might
Amanda Pann
Depends on what you do
I don't think you get arrested for just yelling at Auntie
TV
I feel like they don't have to
The pay anyone
People who called said they got the money but I don't know how much I trust a vet
I don't know if you know this but there's a round
Did the United States allow these radio program sure about that
I think both of Alex's calls are real just cuz they're so dumb
Like I don't think
I don't think you could
Specify
Like an improv
Park at sketch actor to be this
Yeah
This demand and right in line with Alex
His beliefs
I get real
Isaac Moses
These calls are real if only because
Well first of all you hear the same people call pretty repeatedly
And then they just mirror bat him back
Difficult
Not on this one now
I need to get the
I need to get that cord
It looks up the phone my old one broke
But I'd be willing to do that especially if you willing to do that with like people
Disgusted with them maybe once a year but it's up to you guys if you want to
Talk to Danny Jordan
Make it happen them calling a brother to people who like
You know you want to talk to him make it a patreon exclusive
$500 donation
Use olive
Everything is an opportunity for a fundraiser
Play
Idea I would like to play the
Profanity-laced
Tirade the David Hogg goes on
Well you just a couple times he swears like the politicians don't give a f*** about us
And stuff like that
I guess it is
Technically profanity-laced
Expressing themselves
It actually to me is evidence that he is not
Crisis actor
Because if you want
People would
Teacher like
Don't
Where you don't want people to attack you for that
You have a much more polished media
Happened to be on the news
That that I don't know what you're talkin about on TV before cuz they got saved by a lifeguard
I have no idea
I don't I don't know this I'm resistant to all of those
I've looked into them in the
This Virgin of stuff
From tragedy
Arizona waste much
A little bit of David Hogg on CNN
Bigger ion C-SPAN
Because I think it's important
And brings up
Alex's
The fame
Portico
Gay frogs
You're 17 you'll be 18
Text Mom
You online with a video
Attack by the Infowars crowd was that like
I only mention his name
Statue Asian that I don't want to name the name of but
Agitated from Infowars
Keeshond
Advertisement
Scaremongering
I hate and Division in America
Example
Tap water is turning the frogs gay
The advertisers water filters
Interested
Trying to fertilize eggs and don't exist and then the species dies
Okay
He goes on from there to do about a five-minute commercial about his water filter
David Hogg point
The term Lakehead arosexual or hetero
Article out of Berkeley
Betty references
Flashes it up on screen so I can tell that it's
Exact article lady talk
I'm about it in this article they found that frogs
Highly
Exposed
Two level high levels of actresses
The chemical atrazine
It is mostly byproduct of like
Plastic
Production
And pharmacological
The pharmacological
Call farmview
Okay like it's used as a weed
Killer
A very good weed
Killer 75% of the frogs that were exposed to high levels of atrazine end up chemically castrated
10% were shown to be comfy
Quote the 10% or more of the turn from males and two females
Can successfully mate
With male frog
But because these females are genetically male all their offspring are male
So that Pinterest
It's pretty wild thing
Cool yeah it's in relation to this guy from Vice
Decided to look into it and talk to some
I'm just about what the ramifications
Who's this
If there's any reason for humans
To be concerned
Neuroscientist from the University of Nottingham
Told this reporter from
Frogs and many species of fish named Ali the Nemo fish
Clownfish
Can spontaneously change their sex anyway
Fish are not human
Then humans don't spend their lives living and breathing water
Due to their natural sex flopping characteristics
It's likely some fishing frogs are very susceptible to the actions of the pollutant
But there's still no evidence that can influence the development of sexuality
Until I read this from the Centrist
Disease Control
What are the primary ways that atrazine can affect your health is by altering the way your reproductive
Studies of couples living on farms that use atrazine for weave
Control find it
An increase in the risk
Preterm delivery
These studies are difficult
Interpret because most of the farmers were men who may have been exposed to several types of pesticides
Inconclusive
Light connection but you can't really even do that
Atrazine has been shown to cause changes
Blood hormone levels and animals
That affect the ability to reproduce
Some of the specific effects observed in animals are not likely to occur
Inhumans
Because of biological differences between humans and these types of animals
Atrazine also cause liver kidney and heart damage and animals
It's possible that atrazine to cause these effects in human although this has not been exam
So you can find that are kind of interesting
We were like what about this
A thing that Alex brought up earlier
There's a study is 2008 study alabado is the name of the person
Who led the research
They found that atrazine stimulates aromatase activity and human ovarian cancer
Enzyme that converts testosterone
Is produced by the adrenal glands by some cancer cells
Cancer patients with estrogen promoted cancer
Primarily breast prostate
The class of drugs
Designed specifically to block the production of Roman
Thereby decreasing levels of estrogen impatient
So
Alex is trying to make the argument
That aromatize
HD that activity is stimulated by
Have therefore will boost
The estrogen levels
People that end up dating
The problem with this
The first thing you find
Is that the people who made that study
Have retracted the study over concerns that they have a good enough job with the study
Do you have a retracted study
You have another study that was done on people who lived on the farms that showed
Premature delivery that's inconclusive cuz they're exposed to too many other things
Don't have a good
Control group there
All you have is this
Study of frogs
Definitely doesn't relate to humans 121
Because frogs
Fish to have some
Gender
Changing it like it's good that there should be
Stuck in the water and stuff like that but
Legislator they change sexes
Right but can reproduce
Well I think I think it's because they aren't they end up
Changing into
Males and then end up breeding with males
And that triggers our
Go because they're females
Internally
I don't know I don't know
The article doesn't say that the frogs are gay it says they change
I guess would be sex
So also from the Centers for Disease Control just in case you're worried that this is in all of our tap water
I had well water I want to see what's going to happen to me
Interested
The Environmental Protection Agency identifies the most serious hazardous waste sites
These sites make up the national priorities list
And are the sites targeted for long-term Federal cleanup activities
Atrazine has been found in Italy
Of the 1636
Current or former npl sites
So that's not a very high number
Atrazine to taken up by all plants
Butt implants not affected by The Afters
Sandwich Arby's
Target
It is broken down before it can have any effect on their photo center
And therefore it's not in the foods that come from
Atrazine treated plant
Supply isn't the natural
Concern that you could be exposed to it
Most people are not exposed to atrazine on a regular basis
People live in your areas where the atrazine was applied to crops maybe expose through contaminated drinking water
Atrazine has been found at about 20 Superfund Site
Supposed to be
Npl site
In the United States
People living near those sites may be exposed to higher levels of actors
If you're a factory worker who works with atrazine
You may be exposed to higher amounts
The government has estimated that approximately maybe expose this way
So the numbers of people who are actually
Damaging lie or dangerously exposed atrazine
Massively
Over-exaggerated
Sure
And that the other thing that's even more f***** up is if you really want to talk about
You know the problem
Do
You know is there are these couple of farms
The farm 20
Well 20 site 20 hazardous site but could be more Farms
That aren't nearly as polluted but could still affect groundwater somehow
You know what would solve that
Regulation
That's not good that's that's the end solution to that problem
I've been documented happening
Two frogs
Because because of pesticide and groundwater contamination
But this is not
All applicable to humans
And Studies have shown that have been retracted
5 people go down them because they
Yeah
It does make me wonder what I drank
Because a child
Cuz I did drink well water in
So I could have been
Could be Mercury could be a lad
I'm crazy about that mercury
Earlier
Alex
Yeah
It's interesting cuz what happens next album
Cuz I told him
He's trying to save it like whenever he's like I don't want to say his name
Because
He tried to protect himself from a lawsuit
When reality
But also when the interviewer is asked
You were the target of Infowars like group
That's because
Spiraled far beyond jump Infowars
Alex
Owen Shroyer
Is people inspired
There were
Sorry but I'll get what they want to start rolling
Lawsuit
We're going to say
And then
How do you murder the truth
Jokes
David frog
You're 17 you'll be 18
Text my nephew online for the victim of a conspiracy video
Attacked by this right Infowars crowd was that like
Replays the CNN's with his face blurred and that modulation
The guy who created
I also I thought it was just going to be like
Ribbit ribbit
Yeah
Go to the f****** at least half mile still halfway there
To be funny not funny
It's not expensive either it's just nothing
Entire thing with the voice modulator
Advertises water filters
Interested
Interesting
Beer commercial show girls in bikinis you're going to get the girls in bikinis
We're going to find the woman of your dreams you fly to Cancun
Marshalls
Almost all well water has Racine
It has mercury it has around
So deep.
I have a feeling that
You need to buy a filter
Well he's accidentally
Pointing a finger at himself cuz he's comparing his ads
2 beer commercials that depict a false reality
Entice you into buying beer
Leading a baby if I buy this beer this hot gorilla like me
Doing the same thing
Hey maybe if I buy all of these products I'll be safe from the onslaught of globalist attack
That are trying to get me through the Water and Air
I mean
This is very dumb
Gift cards
To Infowars store
Come on man
Don't get me a
Don't give me super male vitality
I don't like
I'm hooked
I'm sure it would work
It is much as like it would make me feel something
Yeah
My level
Here's Alex just lying a little more
Oh yes
Do frogs indovino
There you go ladies and gentlemen
No.
Berkeley study
Anyway no
Just read a headline and I'll your golden
You're good to go
I want you to watch
Spore how
He's collectively edits
The appearance of middleditch on Colbert Show
Alex
When the media edits his clips
It makes it seem like you saying something you didn't
Say
And watching do the exact same thing
To this tackle their show
Implying
Email
He was bad
He brings it up a lot
Thomas middleditch
He doesn't want to work mother know this is just
Oh man that's never going to play again
Trudeau I don't even know if it came directly from him
But the Canadian government was trying
To get people to use gender-neutral
Words whenever whenever it would be appropriate
Instead of mother or father
Just to be non-specific about it
Anna
Who cares
Yeah
Mother
Someone else that's not why
Stephen Colbert last night
Ruffled feathers
Alex Jones
Controller
Do you really
Eating a cheeseburger in shooting a gun
Announcer when I heard
Google was right there
Beta male
I'm calling the cops
And he just jumps
Alex
Cut it went completely different conversation
So it sounds like it makes no sense
Essentially catering your searches based on algorithms
Minions
Friends when they don't even exist
It's out there so maybe people
I'll buy it
I noticed this morning
Chemicals in the water
They are so worried about that
Because it's a fact
It's because of the terrifying underlying assumptions
There's things underneath
The statement
Especially about the idea of
You know this thing is that they are putting in the water that's the first thing
Runoff
That's really the place where it comes it's not like there's a massive Global it too or just trying to poison the groundwater like it's Batman
Begins some s***
Then the second part is
If if
We go along for the ride
They're inducing homosexuality
People
And Alex be saying
Myproducts
Will help fight back again
To some extent
Uncomfortable underlying
Peace there
I believe
If I stop using my brother
Start sucking dick
That's a possible I think you could take
Aqua-pure
I will again I am more than happy to suck a dick
And I'm talking Romeo
So you got you got that
He added that clip
In order to make it look like it jumps to nonsense about
About Trent
Google searches
Probably
I think that most people don't pay attention to do Echo
Yes
What is life clip
Alex ruminate on
On their other interview
The show
The way he always
Celebrate
Cowardly chicken
Superstore.com
Huge discounts on water filtration air filtration system
Yeah
So anyway
He brings us to the end of February 23rd of March
I feel like based on your doodling
Throughout you didn't
You didn't enjoy this all that much
Baby I'm so sorry that I wasn't listening
I do I did I wasn't listening
I'm self-conscious
I always feel bad when I have to bring someone else into this world of unpleasantness
Sure
I was thinking I don't know if people would want to buy this either we should put it on a t-shirt okay
Excel the original print
I think that's the best way to go about it
Half of it goes to this podcast having to go to the artist
Be happy to sign it and be happy to record a podcast about why I drew it
I love you God
Don't screenshot it
But just have it
Though that's
Dirty pool pay your $500 like a good American person would amen
I told you before we went there and I might have said it on the pocket
I normally they're sad
I'm not sad
No cuz it was all just stupid
Yeah that's fine
But anyway people can follow you as the mattress also I have a fun podcast
12:30 characters comes out once
Samantha
We'll be doing more of them
Website
Kids.com is not my website
The bad news
It's very okay
Vinyl area
It's a 7 if you want to come email actual Murders At
At gmail.com
Thompson
I'm going to buy two drinks
We are at knowledge fight.com
69 is too many characters
Sure
It's also weird today
It generally at the end of this these episodes we tell someone to go f*** themselves
Really
Fairground of us telling
Specific guy to f*** himself at the end of every episode
And then
Decided to give him a break and now we switch
The fill-in Jordan I feel like I should give you the honors of who from
Today's conversation would you like to tell the
Why do that I do like the Red Sox
I just got the shirt for
Start up
Anyway
I got a I'm sure he's
Been told many times before
David hockney
Rodger Rodger
Galaxy color with huge fan I love your work