Alexandra Thurston color
We are
Easter Sunday knowledge fight has risen from the dead that is our
Easter's best
A peanut butter eggs
All you need
The Cadbury Mini Eggs of the best candy of all time
If you see that there
Have you seen that they're starting to f*** around with that Reese's egg format
No they have the regular Reese's egg
Cadbury eggs
Is Reese's peanut butter
88 semester
Perfect candy
There's nothing I did anyways you know a lot about Alex
You were sorely missed
But
Go home and tell your mother
For keeping me company
Yes that's a good point Dan without without me you have no other
That I can bounce this stuff off
Discuss the phone Alex Jones related issues
Give me the ignored in La by all and anyone who
Everyone possible friend doesn't matter
Brutally
Also like to give a special shout-out to listener Darren sent me an email about a book
About the rides
Russia
And I started reading that
I always like that always like a nice book recodo
Looking for that which
Which rise of totalitarianism most recently
Seamlessly
Susceptible to authoritarian
I listened to the episode with rags and the whole time every time you did a transition I was like
Rick didn't say anything
What's going on
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Thank you so much if you would like yourself to our website knowledge
Click on that little button that says support the show we would appreciate it we are
So thrilled with everybody
Who's donating weary single person you are heroic
So if you have a business
We will do it for
Anyway
Bingo bad stuff today is bad
What we're going to be doing Jordan today is we're going to be doing we'll have a two-part episode
To right now
Part 1
Of that in these two episodes will cover
The last week
Gotcha from the 25th of March to the 31st of March
And
Aggressive
Play bad stuff that's going on this week
Great fantastic
All right you might have seen a lot of
Stop the news about Alex Jones this week with him
I don't know
Well but I read the other day that was awesome
Some overlap
Stories about like let's say Alex Jones
Comparing the park
Little kids to Nazis
Worse
Everyone's ignoring
Much like last week
Weather report
He has said that whites were being exterminated in Rhodesia and
Attention
Could be most compared to the Nazis are the Israeli government
Subway
Thanks Israel
Not to be believed
Hey
Definitely not mad about murdered over and over and over again
Weird weird how they would react negative
Don't know everything about
Very long console
But I would posit
Taylor's oldest time
I would say the even if the Israeli line
Shooting protesters
Was
Wrecked
Donut saying that it is
Bad Optics should be like
Oh boy
Test from a year ago
Wizard wizard actually
Are you sure wasn't like rock salt
Have a gun at somebody else's
I'm going to consider that shoot
It's not right
But also everyone's always.
Today we're drinking IBC
A nice red wine out of
Sonoma County which is close to where you were over the gation total wine, Napa
What not interested you know what I like wine I don't want to stop and taste wine
I've been there it's not that interested
The Scott Brothers grapes
And some other stuff happens when you get drunk
Part 1
There we go
Who starts
March 25th
And on the Sunday show Alex
Who's hosting with Owen Shroyer
For a little while
Theater disappear for whatever reason any left Owen
So we won't be discussing too much have went Owens gone start something on this episode
That is really fascinating and goes through the entire week
And that is he talks about how much like the
Halloween Hitler hat
Absolutely
Daughters and five other friend
Mom hotel at Six Flags
Whenever filter
I love Beth
Quotes
Also
Two high five in 4 minutes I love that Mama.
Love you
Also
I look
I'm not saying
You can't be friends with
Alex Jones's daughter
Sure they're lovely
You are
Being taken to Six Flags
With Alex Jones
You have to be the most miserable person
Six Flags
I was friends with a lot of people who would look at that
Not necessarily
Maybe some people who support the
The Confederacy actually all of them
Missouri Brewery outside
The bigger cities now there's a lot of
Very pro-confederate
Trouble
Batteries
Six Flags my man
Multi-ethnic people and a lot of the Yoke that you use
The young people as he explains in his neck
Clip
Conservative
Generations
Audiology that's the next wave is like their final
The Establishment was the NRA The Establishment was the conservative
So also on this show enjoy your suggest
But it's just a phase
Cars that David Hogg is going through and rebelling and whatever
You have no heart if you're not a conservative when you're old and you have no brain
Right
Really love protecting money
That's not really even the stat
Maybe he's drawing on
Shown that
Most of the young
People are
Trying to become
Unaffiliated with party
Maybe because
They attribute all of climate change and income inequality to both parties
The entire baby boomer generation
Who have f*****
The world over
Smart thinking
I was trying to study by the British marketing firm called
The Guild
Gild
Also what we talked about blofeld was he
I mean it's not it's just clunky
Pacific methodology
Z from their study
People who looked into it and she'll be like
Either way you got other data
Could not possibly lead to a representative
Example
Survey the people take on the internet stuff like that
There's literally no answer
The questions were asked in a very biased way
People are paid
I think these were just like open
Like almost like Facebook
Quizzes
Proposed
We're biased which everyone knows
Statistics
Advice results
So even
The American
Conservative publication wrote article about that
And in that article
They talked about the guild
Understudy
Even they have to admit this
And I quote
On the other hand Northwestern University shows the Generation Z is about as likely to support gay marriage and government involved
Lumberton Health Care is millennials
Add more likely to support transgender right
Atheism Rises by 5 percentage points among generation
Despite promising signs of increasing religiosity
Teenagers are taking a less traditional approach
Christianity than previous generation
Christianity is also garbage
Now I rather Huffington Post article that cites this Guild study
Great
Findings from other study
A recent study that they sight shows that 18% of Millennials go to church but 41% of generation
Members do
Most of them
That's not that's mean
Decided to eight out of ten members of generations
Considers himself
Fiscally conservative to which I would reply most
High school or college
Let alone I haven't had real jobs
They don't really understand what the economy is all about
Also
They were sucking little children very impressionable children during the worst downturn in modern
History in 2008/2009 in a probably
Impression on them watching their parents lose all their money
Understand a certain amount of
Perception
Of fiscal conservatism what you don't understand what that actually means
If your parents are in anyway
Giving you that b*******
You're like
Well the government should be run like my family is
And if we don't have enough money
Then what we do is we
Tighten our belts
That whole thing
And that makes sense if you are
A bigger picture makes perfect
I'm also on porch
Problematic for this conclusion the generation
Envy is going work
Conservative
Post article
But 75% of generation
Envy members
Support gay marriage and its 76%
Concerned about climate
So
Well that's just the number that is about this point
Even if you're 9 years old you're like Cheese's
Make it to 20
I felt that way too but that was just because I was at traumatized
At this point
Taking away all that stuff
Your assessment is probably the most
That the generator
Regency folks
The shoe label
Much more than
Previous generations
In the same way that they support transgender rights
Permeability
Of people to
Define themselves however they see
Apply that same
Logic to the political Spectrum
Conservative
Anyway
It is next clip Owen Shroyer
Imagine
People who believe that bipartisanship is the way to go
I don't think they're like
We'll get to make it 2:30
That's our generation
Really soft version of the the loss of idealism of 6
6th generation absolutely
BFDI
No maybe we saw a blueprint for how did not cooperate
Succeeded and instead of doing that the Democrats were like maybe
Even larger
That's true I'm is next clip
Owen Shroyer says something
That ends up kicking off
The
Event of the entire neck
Is very important
There's a void right now Alex and David Hall can easily be defeated we need to find a high-school student
I was in a car
With six girls today
Way more.
Guns don't kill
A conservative that's all you wanted to feed a chicken neck Nelly
It is present somebody that's an alpha male that's all you do what do you think the youth is going to do
Or pick some guy who's the captain of the football team
So
History correctly
It's generous an 80s movie
David Hogg
Is a chicken neck
Nerd you need a bully
The trick to defeating these people
Is to be monstrous
Into the probilling camp
I honestly think it on
Might
Unironically agree with absolutely
David Hogg
Seated right
That's your plan
Well
A teenager
Punching down little b******
Well I mean you got to you got to consider the worldview that they are espousing and what they actually believe
Even that is that Soros
And his people
Are scripting David Hogg
Redhead groom Tim
Which introduces
Incredible problem
Becky was
Recording video during the school shooting
Talking
Two people
In his class
So
If they would have had to groom him
The school shooting slant the school shooter
Is pushing that narrative one of the logical conclusion
It has to come from it is
That he believes was fake and set up by the global absolutely cowardly.
Like people saying you believe that
Unscripted by the globalist
Again
Like I said there's really literally no way for that to be the case without it happening before the school shooting
Which what do I say
Literally every school
Has somebody who was Gru right
Because
We all know what school shooting is going to happen that's another that's another possible outcome of the red
Possibly say that
That is called Forever
You have to plant
Schools
Columbia Missouri 100000
People going to college with him session or not
We had
For high school
High School Chicago hat
High School's New York has New York
If you would have
To have someone
Pre-planned and position ready to go and
Mysteriously none of these kids have spoken out after like
Hey you know I was put in a position where I could
Could have been even consider that
Either the
Every school shooting
Is a false flag invalidate that whole argument you are still calling them prices
Or
You are saying that they and everybody else realize that school shootings are random
Problem
Migrate
Google outcome of that conversation that isn't f******
Stupid
Proving that
F******
Stupid it's all very dumb but most
Important
Is their own young hot
Person
To fight back
Against David Hogg
And we'll see where they're nervous or whatever
That plays out but now we go to
March 26th
Alex wants
To talk some more
About going to Six Flags
Antonio
Also Ted Nugent ends up showing up on 10 later shows but I can listen to it
I only bring this up because I ate bears
Mentioning Alex Jones
Ted Nugent
Call Michelle
Talk about San Antonio
That means
I cannot
Not think about
How
Ted Nugent has said on stage
San Antonio
So
Anyway
Good work
This weekend I took my daughter's in some of their friend
Which car do you want to be in there
She's baby
Hotel Riverwalk at Six Flags
Play Randy ages
Got mob in Six Flags
I got my outside I particularly had
Particular
Buster's
I saw the video you shot today
I'll check it out
What do we do if they're really making a move
Feel so good
Those people Adam
I know what to do I don't know what to do you know don't know what to do
SRP
Alright
Don't need to bring that into stick
Six Flags that energy
People just like to go for the ranch
Screaming at
White-collar Hispanic
Great way to go into an amusement park
Negative energy
God so far how do you feel about this Six Flags
Dollightful
I think
The person who gets Google Alerts about what Alex Jones puts out
Is the status
Human being in the world
But that
I didn't do anything to
But sometimes I'll get updates on my phone from YouTube
Broadcasting live
But yeah these other people they don't
Google algorithm really is great
Rentastic stuff
Outside of
Ouch
Everybody everybody
It doesn't
It's not real though but at least it's pretty on track
The stories are similar and everything
White people are not mob
Bro only Mart multi-ethnic people
Minorities
He knows that you know it isn't saying that
Minorities would talk to him at all
Mexican guy looked
Yeah we got a Tuesday
He told fix bike story
With six girls
He said it was 5 or so
The daughter in Pfeiffer
You don't walk out
Bowling
By the teachers and people
Walkout
Organize
Two of the girls by the leaders
They're only freshmen they're already
Stop.
And you're super smart
They look like supermodel
Was Dynamite
This trip isn't.
Supermodel
Alex
Look at those kids
The Clippers are done but
You can already tell that Alex is in
Internalized Owen Shroyer
Suggested
Girls come on air
People that right
People that are against
The wheels are turning in his head look like
It's a good idea
And those girls that wasn't prompting that I was sitting there
Listen to loud music and stop I'll listen to him
Hungry hungry
Hungry
Well good luck
Funded by George Soros
Red-blooded devices
What is a worth
Oh my God I thought they were conservative and then I gave him a
See little girls
The fuc
So if you are if you are Soros
In his world
Absolutely
That's the way you got to do is that was actually think it was happening
Here they're like I would use my own daughter
But that would make my ex-wife get it
I don't know if you've been following
What's happening
Alex's ex-wife
Disconcerting
As we've narrative plays out but just
Know that year on March 27th
Alex is like I want to use my own daughter but I can't cuz my
Get mad
Which is important
Anyway now we go to March 28th
Which is
Alex
Tell the
Current kind of story about going to Six Flags
How many Chicken Express the owner was a western
Thank you
Broadcast
Interesting Lee I did a bunch of research this week
I read your piece on how many radio stations actually carry Alex and it is
32 less than advertised
United States play Alex Jones an only about
I think it was 6
American Life
The other a lot of the other ones are him at midnight to 3 a.m.
Right sort of shift
He has almost no exposure on
Radio terrestrial radio
He pretends it is very large
You can go to our website knowledge feit.com and find the the right up with all the proof
Send links and stuff on that
Butts
Suffice it to say what I did is I went through every radio Market
Eli's well
Sound
Radio markets in the United
I found all of the broadcast
Enzo's Market
270 miles outside of town
Is a pretty reasonable estimate of how far a normal radio station would travel
Can't leave again
No this was a delight
Waterworks
This is called research
Fact-finding
I went through all of these radio stations found their schedules and found
Skyrim
I still played a little bit of this week
Anyway the point value with my legitimate
Concern concerns are legit
It was exhausting process go through
More people would Guam could every single article about Alex
Uses his own
Any Zone claims
Like whenever you hear something about Alex it'll say
Without
Variation base little bi
He's on 100 am and FM station
Around the corner
They'll just use his own thing without ever looking into it
And I think that's
Good I can get the problem
I can demonstrate that it's not true
Never have
Like you are the only person I can think of who is actually like
How many stations he is on willing to put up with the mind-numbing chore going through
Which is understandable why they would just be like
I'll just take his word for it in Texas that Alex is on his name
Amarillo
Am 940 kixz
He's on Monday through Friday at midday
So the idea that this guy is a listener
Yes we listening online and he owns
The chicken joint
I don't know how that's possible you might like be aware of who Alex's
Probably not a normal listener
How to dress to get back to the circle put a button on anxiety I was worried that I might have missed
Spoken
But I was able to find them
The country that are Alex
Eight of them broadcasters show live
Ten of them broadcast him after 9
P.m. including
Most of those being
Midnight to overnight
Yeah cuz they couldn't afford syndication of coast to coast
Essentially what he's doing is
Well that's why you broadcaster shortwave radio also
Yep they're also three breaker Alex nine
And eight of the 32 stations emanate from
Cities with population
Lower than 5,000 people
And probably don't have the strength
Text to hip normalcy
Like largest city also is not on in Austin
As far as I can tell he always says that he's on
590 a.m. KLBJ
But he is not
That's all to save it
I don't know I just wanted to bring that up cuz you mentioned thanks to all our affiliates
Yeah thanks to all 32 of them
Including only three stations in the country that pinpoint David night
The country
Plays Owen Shroyer
Oh yeah
What station is that that's the one that's in Elmhurst Illinois
It's the one that sells
It's the one that's owned by Matt do ba
Who's that timer
And so you know
If you look at the real world version of Alex's reach
It's all online
And that's what I wanted to bring up
When we talked about like
Alex treating his YouTube channel being taken away as an ex
Existential threat to
The first
Existential threat exactly
In the in the
Investment World USA he's not Diversified
Because what he has is that Shoreway for truckers right which is a very limited market
He has
Did the online platform
Through Facebook and through YouTube which could be taken away from him
32 Station
If he was band
From YouTube and Facebook
He would he would go away
He would
It would be more conservative he would have almost
No penetration to large markets
The large audience
Does the people to run his ass
But he absolutely would be
Crippled by
He would turn it he would go full Lenny Bruce
At that point
My plate is your plate first amendment by my Victim right all that stuff but it would be an interesting transformation
Ibid inter
Seeing what happened
But
Even knowing all of this
I still
I'm not advocating for Alex.
To be kicked off YouTube
42b kicked off Facebook
If it happened
Not going to defend him on a 1st Amendment
Fart
The people who are like
That
I just think there's better ways to attack him
Mabley pointing out that he has almost no radio station
Talking about
He keeps claiming
He's on there I did not reach out to any of these stations cuz I was like I've already I've done
To watch looking
Irib Institution Ohio
Would be like
Hey
No we don't
Please stop saying that would they send
Would that be possible I don't know cuz I I don't
He doesn't say it very often
I can't pinpoint the last time
Reset it but I know that I've heard him say it about
Like
There was an instance where Darren mcbreen
And
The other reporter
They were out on on
Assignment
Trying to get it fixed
About how the police bought a new boat
Or something like that
It's a huge scope
And they got hassled by them
Right
But again I don't know
LOL
Desist would do
I don't know if you'd have to bet you wouldn't have to make an on-air apology
Alex
You know what it is
I've never claimed it our audiences
Anything compared to Alex
I've never claimed we are big
Or anything like that because we're a modest show and I appreciate our listeners greatly but it's not like we're taking over the world
Yes very small business
Discounted rate
Probably a lot less
The things that gets in my craw
Is that Alex is so caught up in his masculinity
And everything is like I'm much bigger than
He's got roughly 2 billion
He's running a commercial currently where he's at
Conservatively 10% of the world listens to him
60 million people absolutely first of all if you break that demographically people who have access
The internet
Google count the China
Accounts for
A whole lot of the world's population
Not a lot of our listening to probably.
Of the world's population
Under the age
It's just
It's cockamamie.
10% of the United
It's just
It's lunacy
Huge in Venice
Acoustic
It bent me out of shape
I was so motivated
I'll look into it
Is because it really bothers
When people over egg
Exaggerate
Very important
Clearly
Because that's what's going on
Here there is like I have to present myself as being
100-200 radio
When
I'm on
Stocking
32 including 1 in
Tioga North Dakota population 1230
Including Loris South Carolina population 2000
I'm loving this including
Delta Utah population
Kind of
Well I mean I did the costume
Beatbox
Anyway fuckyourself Alex
I say that
Save that in
Recognition that I know what
Here's the next clip this one is also from March
Pretty mad at David Hogg
And then I we get to
See where this is
Over the course of the week Alex's narrative is pivoted from I hate this stupid March for our lives
To little bit
Couple days later he's like
Darren mcbreen told me that David Hogg was wearing an armband
Matt Redman a little bit later in the week
He decides to bring into the narrative that David Hogg didn't
Heel click
Noi
Dissolute
Interpretation
Soft a little bit.
David Hogg narrative that involves over the course of the week
Any luck if you meant that you would have just started where you went you know you wouldn't have like
Mad about this but I don't have anything
Complain about her choices
There's a ton of noncom
An armband
Their lives
Wiiware
Pink ribbon for breast cancer
The real thing
That's fine
Anyway
I'm allowed to say that
My son
Tell me this morning
No
Oh you know
Couple Junction
We talked to lawyers right judge on that but they're not
Constitutional
Anthony
Sup
Ecology like the people who leave Scientology
What time I looked on the internet
Alex Jones's kid was allowed to read the regular internet
Don't know if it would matter
Because
He's been brought up by Alec
And like you've been doing reports
About other stuff
What's a past global warming one whose dad was
Leader of a white supremacist
Who looked into it and was like
This is bad
The hope that that would be some of the end
Result I want to be clear
I know that you and I have slightly different
Views on this
Because of our texting but
I believe
That no matter what Rex
Is doing he is off limits
For criticism
Because I
Speed
What's happening
Exploitation
I absolutely see
His behavior is being
With a kid
From a chaotic
/ abusive home situation
Right where he is trying to
Exactly what the authority figure wants
Seem to be
And generally speaking
When kids
Do that sort of thing
Because they
Have an ingrained belief that if I become what
This authority figure wants me to be
All of a sudden these feelings that I have about being deprived ignored
Whatever will go away
And that's a misguided
Heart of therapy
John Dewey
Alex Jones kid
Could become a
Great comedian
Because daddy issues
Huge thing as long as you get out of work
I struggle with this greatly
Because
Where we are right now in the events of the last week
Necessitate the
To talk about this
But at the same time
I'm still not ready
And it never will be ready
To criticize
Rec for his behave
You know I
We we did talk about that and I did have a different take on it and the more I think about it the more it is
Just the same thing as
Alex being like David Hogg
Pencil Neck
Whatever whatever it is along those lines it
When you're an adult and you're like this
Stupid
What are you doing
Right what are you f******
Well there's that
Was never going to
To be good for Alex
Absolutely
Because he's putting him out as would I would
Describe it as
You put him out of the lightning
Whether or not
In his
Intense desire to make Alex
Believe in him
And congratulate him or whatever the
Particular flavor is
It whether or not Rex thinks
Is choice or not
Alex is using him as
Kind of
Deflection
Like when I was when I was that age
To get my father's approval
I got so involved
The levels that were on
Fashionable because I thought it would be like everything will be okay when I first went to college
Became a religious Studies major
Because I wanted to follow in my dad's footsteps
I've somehow I kind and let me be clear my dad was not abusive
Or anything like that
He was just
Withholding
Yep you have to assume
There's some sort of
Worst version of that in the the home to older brothers and one younger sister and
I was given of course made me feel like
Well if I
That I will I will receive that
Attention if my dad will treat me with this kind of level of
Respect
Don't treat me like a person
I'm projecting
Anything onto Rec
I just
I totally
Okay Rex I understand
I believe in you from my will escape this eventually everything I've been able to glean from
Alex's Behavior both on and off air
Things I know about him from research
And that sort of thing
Thought that
This is
More or less
What's going on
Can you imagine
How
Like
This is one of the things about Alex that I think would be worse
Is a
If Rex
Was
134 radio station
Oh my God.
I'm so over the course of the last week before this Alex and put up a video that had racks on
Kelly
Alex's ex-wife
I got in touch with YouTube
And have them take it down
Because I don't know cuz he hates
Well I don't know the full text
Store anything of their Court
Proceedings and their divorce and cuss
Debridement
Because I
You can't I don't care
But according to her there is a
Injunction that the judge
Made the tracks in supposed to be on air
See the miner could cause
He's being interjected
To a very
Aggressive
Public
You know like
When we talked about it a couple
Months and months
Alex had a report that wrecks
When he was
We was talking about global warming
Hanging stuff like that
And to me that's not
A defensive it's bad
I'm not for it
But it's not nearly as a fence
Is this because
You put your kid into
Incredibly dangerous
Disposition
When you inject him into this
Gun debate
And you injecting on the side
Like
I know that Alex
Isn't saying that these people are crisis actors literally
But he is insinuating that
What does 15 year old
Into that world on the side of things
You can't possibly understand
Along with all the
You know 80 somatic
Implication
The globalist narratives that Alex Jones pushes
Completely lying about
All that's when you do that you put him in danger
You put him at least you're not
Texting your juice
Unacceptable
It's absolutely unacceptable but the reason Alex is doing it
Is 1
Because Owen Shroyer
On Sunday
Said we need our own version of a high-schooler to fight back
Yeah I'm second
Because Kelly
Got one of his videos removed
And because Alex is a f***
Child
He's doubling down
Oh
Yeah
You know what Rick being on air
He's going to be on aeroflot
And if I can
Advice
Don't listen to God damn
Owen Shroyer says if you're taking ideas from him
We've given you a million times better than one radio station
So anyway in his next clip we jump to
The 30th
Is the 29th
Does not
Not all that fruitful
High For This
This.
Until we go
Where Alex is at
This morning
His offer Easter
There's One Direction
I see George Soros
Isn't terrible
Had to go out and
Interview people on the street
This is all about
He's comparing himself to Soros there as well
Like if Sorrows gets to use people why can't I
And that's that actually touches on one of my reasoning
We're not attacking
Inasmuch as
Alex
And everyone in that world attacks David Hogg
It doesn't make it okay for us to
Rationalizing
His faults version of
Soros's using it
A child why can't I that's really bad
That's it that's it
Better exploitative mindset to have
Now I would also posit
That
From everything I can tell
David Hawkins acting out of his own volition
His friends got
F****** murdered
School
So that puts him in a position where he was thrust into
The national conversation
Right
17 as opposed
215 which
Like a
Small Potatoes
Huge huge
Potatoes
I think I think it is
I think it is but I could understand why someone would say it's kind of a thin lopping
To draw but I do think it matters
I think the beginning of High School versus the end is relevant
Beyond that
How hairy your pets are
The other thing too
In the past when we seen Alex Jones's kids
Pop-up on Infowars
The times are exactly his narrative
Or
Him doing that video with his daughters that was super transphobic where he pretended
How to be a dog
Really
If there was a history of
Life's a George Soros making David Hogg
A subject of those sorts of things
In the past I might feel differently about David Hogs Behavior
Right that's possible
I'm just trying to find ways to
Like
Frame this
It's very difficult
To come down on
Come down on exactly what the problem is
Is it is
In and of itself
Putting your child out
As a as an advocate
The worst
Abuse
Like. The only thing that I would say it was
He's doing that
I give
At Markham
Really
To that argument that I think
That
I mean Alex Munoz he's a liar and a propaganda
But his son may actually think that what he's doing is right
He might not think
He's a part of
The worst
Right to that gives
Absolutely
Hartke doesn't
The level of bullying
A child gets online from
You know being alive compared to the level of bullying
You better child like
I like Rex
We get for is getting
From
Is is
Brutal
You and I can't possibly
When we were fourteen we didn't have that level of
Social media
AOL Instant Messenger
You know that was already like Facebook was the Facebook when I was in college
Like maybe Myspace or Friendster exist
When I was younger and I was not on
Amazon
Yeah
The amount of
Pressure
And
And being judged
It comes from
Articles being written about you in Daily Mail Right
I don't
Think like what what is what is 50
Freshman in high school well as we all know like just like any child
You wind up
Fine
Right from that development
At all
SMS
The drinking problem he is going to have
What is going to be a star
Well special is alcoholism
So it is next clip by Alex G but how you can't criticize
David Hogg
You're not allowed to
Twitter Facebook
Criticize
Dirty
Play
Images of Mary Jane
I hope Michael Buffer Suzhou right on that
Adele
Next Level stuff
You know what you can criticize David Hogg
If you disagree with his principal if you disagree with his
Principal live
You disagree with what he
Are the
Solutions to the issue
You're not disagree
With David Hogg
David Hart
The person calling him
Maze
What the f***
Child
And
Creating elaborate conspiracy theories around a 17-0 like
To the point where like none of its proven that you can't prove
Single goddamn things
And
He's embellishing all of the things like
There's that video that came out where David Hogg was talked about like politics
A f*** about us
Stuff like that whenever Alex
Play Oregon
You're lying about a child
And again
I think it's
You went to school with David Hogg
You would be suspended
That's at least you would get a sternly worded talk
Perhaps
Forgiveness comes down to Alex's beliefs
David Hogg isn't acting of his own volition
He is he is a globalist puppet
Witchy spells out in the
I should take that's not Alex speaking for himself he's quoting an article I believe in the Austin american-statesman
Yeah so that's not his own words
But in order for me to have had this
This clip include him explaining that you'll be like a minute and a half longer
Have nothing
Yeah you can get a career
Hell yes.
Yep you nailed it
Sick life
Bricklayers Midland
Justice bottom feeders
Even
Texas
He's going to be is
Even if you was groom
Even if he is a puppet deserve sympathy
I'm not your violent attacks are used
Suggesting
Even in such a world
Where he was groomed
Shooting he deserves sympathy
Yes
Yeah human being in that scenario which isn't the real
Then he's as much as a victim as lexic
Because he didn't know a shooting was going to happen
He was just planted there by the globalist
Every made and even even if he was groomed for it
A shooting still have
I was pretty thrilled to shooting the messenger
Conclusion and
Action that Alex Jones has taken
Only incriminates him more
Even if
Is living in the real world even if his version of stuff is Right still bad behavior still
I'm suing this next clip
This is Brazil in March 30th
Which
Is
Believe that was Friday
I do
Where's that leave you a
We're still in the 30-year and this next clip we get to
Feed
Alex talking about the
The Providence
Of rex's
Material
He said something in here that he thinks
I don't like it when he uses the word I used it
Sexy wife
Alex says something's that is
Sort of
To save
Like
He's doing that
But accidentally
You kind of reviews
My wife are they cloud
He's a man now
Still
He understood the talk last night
Use a condom when you f*** a globalist
He wants to go down this road
How did Gladiator win the fight for liberty
Que maldicion nice gentleman
Newspapers
They don't like
My son 15
A few ideas I had
That's sad
Two ideas
Nordstrom
Even if
20%
Does Alex
Spiritually
Cyborg
So
I don't know I don't I don't believe it's a really good argument
He's doing it
Jewish Jewish people have a Mitzvah at 13 but even they are not there like
Yeah
We're having a party
You're still not allowed to make your own
It's something of a Rite of Passage
But you're still develop
Mentally not
Whenever everybody lived
You're halfway home
Alex's
Just talkin about how
Excited
This video
The Friday the 30th
Show sort of wines down
Marisol
Gross
Back to this really quick I would argue that Alex's near exist
Yeah you know like your living evidence
Right now that you can do
Right so go f*** yourself
Warthog
Love you guys so much but I want to be able to go to our gas
I want to play that so I want to get that new video
Legally
No
Where he says basically
And why are you responding and why are you calling the first men
Sounds like Alex
Call Ford
Hosta
It's just a word
Really feels like Alex
Cuz not in character they're so much as
Psychodrama
This is a whole lot of mess yeah
So where you at Whitwell
Calling for the cancellation of Laura Ingraham show is not the same thing as pointing out to sponsors of her show
Do that
She's a monster and maybe you don't want to be associate
That's that's not quite the end result might be she gets dropped from the network is sponsor
Don't want to get behind it but that
That's pretty much okay
That's how the market works
Sponsors staying behind who they
Not
And if someone that's that's kind of how
Your show Alex is kind of heavy Overton window
In terms of mass media should
Maybe
Maybe I don't actually
This is how it should be enforced
To some degree is like
Is this something we can get away with
Supporting without losing our bottom line
That sure seems like the least
Vet Canby.
Blake is this something that week
Can get away with is not necessarily A ringing endorsement
The capitalist
Is Mexico a Latin
Is the last one
From the 30th
And it's Alex reinforcing the idea that
Dude
This was Rex's idea
I forgot you also sings along with country music at the beginning
I guess it was Wednesday night Tuesday night Nisha said man that is hog jobs
Debate
The real quick the timeline of
The David Hogg did say you wanted
Bait Alex but then he gave an interview
Know anything about Alex and I started to realize
Yeah which is a very rational
This morning I got up at 6 a.m.
6 a.m.
He wanted you to do
Did you before school
Rabbit over
Is is that
All the Publications are coming out saying in the same article I talked about hog
Express my son into politics
A terrible father
That that that has done this
Alex Jones turns his fifteen-year-old son to defend them from bullying
By David Hogg
So
Headlines
Any
Way I agree
And anyway if you if you agree with that
Petillo riffic headlight
That at that email ostensibly
Support
Alex
They are a garbage
Group of Public Aid
Certainly a result of Articles like that is only furthering exploitation that Alex
Subjecting his son to
Like they're there is a journalist
Ethic I believe that don't
Yeah and the only reason we were poor idealistic
Well the only reason we're doing this is because of what we're about to talk about because
We're a podcast about Alex Jones taken up a lot of the last week and it would be remiss of us
Discuss it
In the way that we
We discuss out
It's not like again I mean
Stress it over and over again
I've anything but pity and empathy for 4 right
Again if David Hogg were a tool of the globalist
We would have the same level of pity and empathy for that
Spoiler alert I have a lot of sympathy for him as is
Yeah
Yeah I mentioned
What my life would have been like
Had at
16 or 7
I was
In the position of
Leaving
Spokesman
Leaning
Participating in one
But leaving a movement that all of the adults I know
Are unable to
And you have some people who are on your side you know somebody else who are like
I get it
I get it reflects things up
See what you can do
I know there's some people are like
Globalist
Be difficult cuz one Creator like
Do the adults are like you go ahead and take care of this pressure
And then there's the abuse that comes from
The globalists
And
That world
I can't imagine
Have literally
All of this s*** to these children
It's not like we talked about
So many times
There are no adults
Does a backup
People
Doing their job belts are coming but only if we all
Call Mama.
Just going to happen
What is Generation Z
Probably true blue Jordan now we getting
I'm trying to not talk
Alex went into the studio on Saturday
On 31st
Okay Special Report
I'm not liking
The first one single Special Report we've ever
Recovered has been the worst thing I've ever
Is probably worse than the first one first one
So
Paul Joseph Watson
You found
A Reddit account
Is David Hogg
I really think you're wrong
It's possible that he's not
I don't care
I'm already on the he's wrong tip
If Alex confirm something absolutely not
Alex
Confirmed it was literally impossible
Reddit isn't a person first off first off and second off they don't give out that information
It's illegal
Illegal for them to do so
I mean Reddit
At its core outside of like when people get doc
And stuff like that
It's a community that
A hundred percent based around a nativity
They wouldn't
Give that information up to
Weirdo alt-right a****** from Britain
I'll be that as it may
The story that he's pitching is about how David Hogg made a joke
In 27
Eonon Reddit
Mosquitoes killing Millions
The human
Well there was an ass
Reddit Thread about what Miss
Mosquitoes water positive things
It was for them to exist
And our account
Write more people than anything else and so Alex is at the point of almost
Crying about their about like it as evidence that like
He's clearly lying about
Caring about a school shooting when he's making a joke about mosquitoes killing millions of people
John P holdren book ecoscience which he's lying about on the global
Hypno's waypoints he says
Literally the beginning of it that
John P holdren and the Rockefellers
Have a plan to put HIV in mosquitoes
Disseminated
Literally impossible
Yeah I don't think you
Mosquitoes
Bloodborne
YouTube and one of them
Saliva into you to make you itch
And make you numb well they're biting you and the other one only is an opera of blood
Sirius B
Conception people have because
Began
You know Transit
Malaria
And stuff like that.
Crazy fear that people have
And Alex's
So f******
Stupid
That he's also
Malaria is more effective
1294 it's very treatable
Swimmingly
Second Special Report
You know what
HIV isn't as effective as I'm sure the bacteria are the
Call C.
Give him give them any better
Speak now you are at
Smallpox whenever you could turn it into a f****** gas or whatever
There's nothing available
My life in inches
Nothing idea
Listen
Have you ever
Watch the Andromeda
This is just you baby outbreak
This is just you channeling that doctor Pianka
From the endgame
Go conspiracy theories
Write like your research on
How to kill people on a mass scale by Design
Orchestrate stupid
Disappoint 90%
The other special report
Hour-long
Special Report
With him and Rec
Sitting at the desk challenging David Hogg
Imallexx fans trying to be like
That's again anytime Alex says I did
Absolutely did it feels very uncomfortable
4-bolt there are multiple points in it where Rex
Is literally repeating Alex Jones
Narratives that he has no business
Being inter
Christian or knowing about one of them is
Here get ready
Complains about any clips of him talk
Cuz I I believe it that's it
Inappropriate
But at one point
We are in agreement
Complaining about
Salon
Cuz there was an article in
Salon about how he's been brainwashed
About
His mother
Making these claim
And about how she's concerned
It's not
Interview with Kelly
Is lashing out at
Salon
Clearly
Also
Doing some sort of like
Mom shut up
Stop Riders a weird family relationship psychodrama
That's playing out and it
Any part of that I only bring that up because he's complaining about the law
Organization to normalize pedophilia
Alex Jones normative
And
It's
Articles
That were written
In 2050
Team fire guy name
Todd Nickerson
We've been over this
Yeah but he was
12 Windows key
There's legitimately no reason you should be reading salon at 12
Right
Cling to his dad
Because it's misrepresent
Taste of reality
Exactly in the same way that Alex.
There's a bunch
Point where it's
Clear that he's doing an Alex
There's a bunch of
Things that are
Either literally
Or very close to Alex catchphrase
Really really
Stabbed so f****** f***** up
Thanks comfortable
Yeah
That's a bummer
Comfortable is there's a park
Towards the end of
Special Report
Where Alex
Is trying to prove
That it's not scripted and there's no teleprompter
Syrex is sitting at the desk
And the camera
Hands over
And Alex is standing which would be watching
Yeah
He clearly has a
Isn't that isn't supportive
It's it's just it's just a glass
Disposable cups
The same way
See them drink out of in the past
So many times on the show
Faces
You can make the argument that
Well this next clip should do some of those
And keep in mind
Well you're listening to this
F****** stupid ass
Very clearly drunk Alex
His son is there
Sitting right next
Silicon shop
So good
30 yd
Coco
Colt Python
I mean that is
Dog show you that now me doing that kind of stuff
That's what I'm doing baby I'm boom
Talk like that
You know if you got it
And the people claimed that my Americana
Straight-shooting
Holy Temple in all this crap
YouTube the establishment's why you're so successful
The whole control left
Is so pathetic
And so scared and so
Free movies.com
We're going to put you up on TV
Criticize that we're going to be
And I'm private jets with George Soros
Bring a private jet around here my son was mad
Heat
I took took my daughters
About their friends to Six Flags
Wow
That's not what I
Sad
The only reason that I deemed it necessary for us
To even
Dip into these Waters
I think
Alex adjust
Posted a video where Rex was like
I'm a kid two or something like that if you like this is f***** up but I like and we can get past this and the sake of DC
Escalated to the point where he on his day off
Brought his son into the studio and was
Drunk
Wow they did a f******
Video about how I'm not forcing you into this
And Rex
Repeated a bunch of Alex Jones narrative talking points
Like it's beyond the point where we can sit back and not be like
This is
Crazy
This is me
On the level of Alex Jones Behavior it
This is next
Level
Really
What type of ship in the in the
Shittown that I grew up
This is the type of s*** that I would hear from my friends who lived
Been there in the country
Enter data
Thrown around
The word it like
Not Looking Back
Your dad would sit around the fire with his three Buddies
And they would be
Drunk just saying the worst
And you're right there
Any rain next
The story of light bulbs
Whenever all my friends there and they laughed as I as I
As I drink all of this
Your likes
That's cool when I'm twelve and now as an adult some like
Text fuckedupshit
Fuckedupshit
It's not treating a child as a individual now
Yeah and that's a really damaged
Park
You can do severe damage to and upbringing
Cuz
The process of becoming
Adult involved individuation
Involve separation anxiety
Look into like
Can talk about the various crises
You're supposed to go through
As you mature
I don't I don't sit here
Say anything.
The effect of Alex.
Love his son
Or anything like that
I'm not
That is what I am saying
Is that
The way he's
Treating him
He's a prop
He's not a child
Yeah it's on
He's not that's not okay
Is a thing
Italics
From everything that I've noticed of Kelly's Behavior
Ron Twitter
I don't fully support her either
But I think she's much better than Alex
Just by virtue of
Simplistic explanation but I go even deeper than that
Recognize that a lot of the
Complained
She's making about
Are things that have existed
Since
She was a part of it
Infowars
LLC
OU spits out this hateful rhetoric of a
Like he was doing that in 2014
When you guys were married
If you were a part of the business you didn't have a
F****** problem with a backpack
Now granted
You can change
And I accept that
But I also I also see your posting stuff about like
She knows
About Rodger Stone
Cambridge analytica in Russian business
And we know from investigating 2015
Timeline doesn't work
She divorced Alex
It's Beginning
2015 Rodger Stone didn't show up
Till November
There's not
There's not behind-the-scenes information
Can chicken have about
Alex
Liking Trump cuz he didn't
Immediately showed up right until December 20th
A behind-the-scenes information
She can have about
The business dealings
Which I imagine
She does not want
No
But she wants to pretend that she has information about stuff the people want to hear about
Mutually exclusive
Try not have that information
I don't either
Family Show
Exactly. A f***** up fam
Your
That's f******
On the issues about Kelly I'm saying I support her in a
As much as
I do believe that
She was mistreated and what have you playing things
Plays right into Alex
Because she's pretending that she has information that
No I don't want you to believe that
Pretending to have information
But you can't pause
Implies that Alex is a Russian
Something like that in reality
He's not a Russian agent
Comes out invalidate
It works against
Like she legitimately the other day posted
A picture of Alex
Having a Russian
A Russian
He posted this picture on
Twitter
They got f***
Ron Perlman retweeted
Great but you know what
On February 1st 2018
That place was first tweeted by Daria
Infowars employee Daria
As a prank
It was a troll picture
That she reposted
As if it's somehow proves that Alex works for Russia
No we are trying to work towards
That bums me out but I
Don't think she's probably a better parent
Conflicted
I don't know what
It's like you said
Family s***
We shouldn't be involved in any of that but as we are a deeply and intimately involved with Alec
We can't ignore this
At the same time
If we're only talking about Alex
In context of all this stuff insane
Kelly gets a free
Pass
I don't think that's fair either
So
Nothing I got nothing no this is f***** up that's my response to all of this is like
Thank God I'm not wreck
Well thank God
Immediately after that last clip
Alex told you stories again
Heat
I took took my daughters
About their friends to Six Flags
My wife was in one car
Babies
Unrecognizable
Older daughter again
Farmer Fran
I thought
I thought Ted Nugent
Are these girls were like
Who I was
Wasn't
They were dial.
And they were all from your high school
That's what I'm getting at is globalist
And those girls
We're both hurting
Smart beautiful intelligent
Then he doesn't have a right to be on here
That's brainwashing
That's deeply upsetting PID
He is drinking
Sitting on the air next to his son and being like
What is these girls spoke out loud he's having his fun for him he's discussing the idea of a
Better prop
Yep
Go f*** yourself seriously
I regret that we talked about
I hope this resolves and I wish Rex nothing but the best at
Immatures
And grows up I hope that he doesn't
Too deeply involved
Good luck kid when you grow up
God Bless you that's right. You're welcome to have your own position
But I think the idea of beef like
Comedy scene in Austin dude whenever you're ready for a fall again
Are in one day
I want this is the crystallized point that I really want to make
I don't want to 50
Senior old ever listen
Absolutely
If you consider the
He's been doing Special reports for Alex if he was 12 13
I don't want any 12 or 13 year old listening
They do not have the emotional
Maturity
Understand
Where these ideas
Come from
Cuz some of its kind of attractive
Some of its kind of appealing
You know this idea when you're a kid
The world is scary
Because there's
Chaos there's disorder there's like I don't understand why this happened
And what do you have a conspiracy theory that ties everything together in a nice bow
Oh it's these globalist that are doing everything
It gives you a shortcut to
Maturing
In some ways
But you never asked
You end up having the appearance
More less
Because you believed you could read college books when you were
Exactly and if you're curated
Information like if you're if Alex clearly if he's
He was reading adult books whenever he was 10
That is
Pressure that's put on you
By Alex Alex Alex
Like let's be
F******
Super clear about this
That's Alex
Reading Rec
Like
You are mean
Because it's the exact same language to use it
Speak about himself
It's whether or not Rexes
Yeah I don't give a
Flying f*** about that
What I do care about is Alex's behavior in the things that you can trace bro
When a parent
He's their child
Extension of themselves
As opposed to an individual in an of them
Themselves
What they do is not allow them
To experience
Separation
That individuation
So important
And upbringing
Haddad Electric
Unfortunately
Pretty clear
Based on the way that I would speak
About him like you bring up with me
He's reading adult books
Yep
That's Alex being like you are me
Think about all the
Rhetoric that Alex
Bentley employees
I will live on through my kids because
My ancestors Army
That is a shortcut
To mental illness
Right
What time this weekend so we can do a slightly more fun part 2
Thank you all so much for listening if you want more of the show we can
Go to our website knowledge fight.
I don't I don't plug this enough
I've started at
Calendar that's on the homepage
Acknowledge flight.com
The catalog
Alex Jones behavior on everyday its comprehensive and disconcerting most of
Is filled in
And also if you go back to
There's a lot of episodes that are filled in
I am building it up
As we go along
I keep trying to keep up
Present and then also filling in all
The stuff I have from
The past
It is broken down
Guest
Buy narrative there's a lot of
Debunking
It's in there and I really think it's a valuable resource
And if you guys were
Want to check that out
I think it's a lot of fun
Ryder.com homepage
Call the Alex tracker
And that is calendar
And each day UK
Can click on it
It open up at 8
Tire essay
And I guarantee eventually Dan and I will have a conversation about active versus
Passive voice
No no
Cuz you don't like the subjunctive fear you have some problems with
I think there's a stylistic aspect here doesn't hurt to some of the passive voice
You do a lot of a lot of a fourteen-year-old essay writers think that things are stylistic as opposed to
Where is that to be
First of all
Tell you to f*** yourself
Go back to California
We are on Facebook and tell your mother you're brilliant
Super Funland
You can share you can do all that kind of
Stop leave a review least episode is slightly less fun except
Six Flags stuff that I want
It's very clear you're the one
Go fuc yourself
Holding
Alex