Alexandra Thurston color with your Japan I love your work
Part
It was last week of the week of
Mark
March 30th
I completely understand
Listen to part 1
Watch the taste out of your mouth
If you are listening to this immediately after listening to part 1
Let me tell you something
Go go get it
Jacob is promising me this will be
The most fun I've ever had
You going to write my feelings on California
Immediately after
I would like a new donor what's going on
Absolutely if you are Kirk Cameron
Weird that you listen to the show
Very disappointed very disappointed I thought you were going to go with Captain Kirk
Fictional character
I was hoping you would go a Captain Kirk cuz then I was going to Pivot that
Tri Pointe
Master P song on the ghetto D album
Called Captain Kirk
Featuring
Fiend
I can't believe the other feature is might have been big at the
The Assassin
But it's about how Mass
Master P of Captain Kirk
Andy's eyes
Put up with these hoes that will happen
You will have to put up with her
The chorus of it I don't know who was it might have been
Next
It might have been one of the other ladies
You didn't really have album Beals level that is
Can you
Captain Kirk I want to have your baby
The good thing is an elaborate metaphor for how
Master P now that
He has
Record ended
Success can be women out of the ghetto
I just need time
But at the same time I enjoy the creativity of a metaphor because
On the level of No Limit Records
That was unheard of the level of extended metaphor
I feel like this is way better than if I had let you in anyways
You really left behind
You can by going to a website and I was right. Com
Pizza Port
Amazon body left behind I don't know I don't know how
Wherever record stores still exist yet still better than the last Don
His follow-up CC
Bymaster
Terrible
I Miss my Homies
Anyways
Let's just see how far this goes unfortunately
Entire catalog was by
C-Murder who end up murdering somebody
Like
The definition of not Irish
He has a lyric literally that is
You take the key out my name in your left with a homicide
We just followed up by the ghetto makes me crazy
His lawyer his lawyer argued in court
That he was
Incapable
The crime Bahamas my name is
C-Murder
Catalog
If you disagree please send an email to knowledge fight at
Gmail.com
Don't do it
Don't you don't want to you don't want to open that can of worms add an also mr. Serv on to the next level is a great album
Also like strong as articles
The email that you will get about No Limit Records
Will be
400 pages long
Respectable work
The game is to be sold not to be told by Snoop Dogg was kind of disappointed
Yeah I think it's
Remember how we spell
Despite your Everlasting knowledge of an element
In terms of that misspeaking I would like to say
It ain't my fault
Alright
What did you do
Did we already say that you know a lot about Alex Jones
IPhone spoiler alerts the Shocker and Mystikal.
Thank you very much
They did two versions of it ain't my
My fault
But unlike unlike a lot
These assholes
I'm talking about Michael McDonald and Kenny Loggins
How dare you they would make you are not even allowed to put those names in your mouth Sir Michael McDonald Kenny Loggins
New versions of like
Taking it to the streets
This is it like they would write them together
Just ate like
Beyond both of their album
But it would be the same song
You just finished this is exactly
My point is disgusting shocker and Mystikal when they did it ain't my fault
The Shocker cares all right
Do I need it ain't my fault my fault
Totally different songs just like this part 1 and part 2 of
Metaphor
It ain't my fault
What is Alex's fault
Entirely on the last episode of the Sunday episode
Better transition than
So we talk
Come on Dan I expect more of you
Episode where
Owen Shroyer introduce the ideas like we need our own David Hogg
Alex
There wasn't really anything else all that interesting that happened so that will be the last off of today's episode
Also left off of today's episode
Monday 5:20
There's really nothing all that much that we need to talk about
Except that
Mike cernovich
Shows up
Accidentally reveals
No
Actually straight up being like
He's doing the
The move that I'm going to call the Paul Joseph Watson
Which is
Just call it D Mike cernovich
From six months ago okay I'm done with Trump
Trump doesn't care about us
You stupid motherfukers
You got played by a pro
So he ends up
Expressing on this episode
And that is mentality really reveal
Only cares about money
Listen to that really
Alabama
Unplug my videos
I would sell a thousand copies plug it and sell none
Did There's zombies watching its background noise
It's elevator music
And actually NBC wanted to do a big interview with me and I told the guy who seemed like a nice guy said
I'm just bored with people coming in and trying to bring up irrelevant stuff
Because it doesn't move the needle for me being on NBC
0 blocks
13 hours
But when I come on your show
Mindset has over 1000 reviews on Amazon and also 100 just like that
That's one Theory
Snowboards QVC for unemployable pairing
Threat
Sailfish
And that's what he's doing there
Extending the sale for exactly 1 hour
These are sales as for the for the first time in a year
That joke is probably relevant
Simoniz
DirecTV
Also the rest
The show is just
Lot of nonsense a lot of him yelling about
David Hogg
Still Thursday
It's not really all that into
So we do not need
Fascinating
People recognize
How sad they are
Attacking
David Hall
Like they'd like
Like they're so
Green in this concept of
Viciously attacking
Anyone who disagrees with them
That the moment like they don't
Get
And this is a child
Who has survived trauma that they will never understand people never even be able to comprehend that buy something
I'm so much
Just attack people suck
The consequences
Regardless of what or who those people are
It is
Kind of an interesting thing to realize that their defense you do
Alex Jones is like
He's
Motto
Should just be
F*** the contacts
Because that kind of behavior is
Nubian like fuc
Suck it
Always have the same
Mode of operation that is attack
Why
Is there was a nine-year-old that was a lie
5 year old baby with a YouTube video where their parents were like
He would be like that
The f****** globalist
He would start getting into like
Some people are
Shockingly advance that young ages
He probably an indigo child
Start flipping into Project Camelot yet
Two things I needed
Yes
It was my
Sincere intention
To surprise you with the Project Camelot episode for your first episode
I'm disappointed
Well here's why
I listen to an episode where she talked to
Lady
You talk to alien
She mentioned
I had just gotten back
From talking to Mark Richards
Yeah okay but
Wife cumming
But it hasn't come out yet so I got it yet
Did do
One of them is about Parkland
How much worse
She is
Then we thought
No we can't
I wish you hadn't even told me that Robin Alex
And then
She didn't episode about the guy Delight in ruining the world
These two guys who wrote a book about
The real Cowboys & Aliens
Yes I do remember that movie Harrison Ford
And they wrote a book
Smokers they wrote a book about it it's so boring
Such a boring
Interview except for one point where the
What are the geysers
I can't lie
Me and this guy we met each other in federal prison
Fusion of methamphetamine
Alright
Tavares he was selling fake methamphetamines now is to differ
So do I get into Tuesday
This that this is where we get actual Alex Jones
Popping back up back into it
Call Steven
Calling for the repeal
The Second Amendment
WYD
Complication we've got his editorial
New York
Infowars.com
Now here's the problem
John Paul Stevens
Rhoda editorial
New York Times
Called
Headline
Repeal the second event
Yes
There's the problem
Yeah now it says reads
And so if you actually read
The the argument
He's making
All laid out for those who have not read it that he's making is it until 2008
Not really understanding that
The Second Amendment
Provided for
Protection of
Individual ownership
At that point there was the district
Columbia vs. Heller Decision
And that created the idea
That
The Second Amendment wasn't about a well-ordered militia
And it was about your right
Right to carry guns
For that the
Corvette stolen election
They would but it was not like a across-the-board the Supreme Court everyone agree
Amendment was more or less understood the historical
That the states
How to write
To keep a militia in case one
The other states attacked them or the federal government attack
Them yeah
Real intent
A he did was he wrote a an editorial
Was based in
Legally
Essentially
He wasn't making an impassioned like ideological argument he was making a historical League
Legal argument right
Admittedly
He's a piece of s***
But
It was a good day was good argument
But I think my favorite part
The article was when
Talking about the NRA
In in pushing the narrative that the Second Amendment means that everyone has the right to
And carry guns
The NRA was perpetuating quote
One of the greatest
Pieces of fraud I repeat the word fraud on the American public by special interest groups
That I have ever seen in my life
Which
Is
Incorrect
He's a very old man
But that doesn't take away from the fact
The thrust of what he means
This is bulshit
It's weird to come down on the side of John Paul Stevens whenever his
Many of his
Decisions in his boat
I have been
Silver aggressive towards racial Injustice
It's been it's been an issue for me how how many of these people who come out and
Are suddenly like
Here's what we should do in this is awful in their lifetime
Prior to being retired or quitting
Right
Truly horrific
It's so strange writing a novel that
Talk about that I can't do it
Sinnerman
Stop
You think you're helping but you're not
Turns on Trump
You'll be like a I can help
Stop
Like
The thing that the thing that got me about when Hillary Clinton was asked about
How
People have told her like go away
A response was
Well none of the other presidents none of these other males
We're told to go away they were tacitly allowed to do all of this b*******
He was like yes
Totally have a
Reasonable argument
About sexism
Howard has
Destroyed you should have gone away to
Yeah like I'm 40 you're right you're right
Big should have been told to go away in the same way that we're telling you now
Like that is that is absolutely true
And and not allowed to do that is undoubtedly due to sexism
Also
Go away
It's it's more immediately after his
Presidency so many of those speaking engagement
So many of those
Lobbying issues where he's being paid obscene amounts of money
To just be like hey guess what I'm the president
Pretty great
Like I totally agree
More the fault
Is that weed
Never told other people to go away
But also I would argue
Kind of a measure of sex
Because no one got up in arms about how like it up before
You were being a little
Totally
Totally recognize
Involved
With this
This situation
However I have also said that Bill Clinton is a rapist
Best others that
I don't know what to say I don't know what to say like maybe the only president who should
Continue talking
Is Jimmy Carter
When he was president
He was a pile of garbage
Building houses for the homeless
Appreciate atoning for his miserable mistake
So I want to talk a little bit more about this John Paul Stevens thing
Because sorry for derailing you weird
Ignition
Here's the issue with the John Paul Stevens
Because he's talking about.
DC vs. Heller being
The issue where we come into like people having the right to own guns as the ins
Interpretation of the Second Amendment yes
It's all meaningless
Because
If you actually read DC vs. Heller
It's the Second Amendment
They ruled is compatible with
With gun control the second page
DC vs. Heller the Supreme Court decision
Quote
Like many rights
The Second Amendment right is not Unlimited
It is not a right
Keep and carry any weapon whatsoever in any manner whatsoever and for whatever purpose
For example
Concealed weapon
Prohibition
Have been upheld under the amendment or state analog
To cast doubt
Unlock daily prohibitions on the possession of firearms
Fallon and the mentally ill or laws prohibiting
Firearms in sensitive places
Such as Schools and Government buildings
Or laws imposing
Conditions
Only come
All of that
Everything that Alex Jones
Complains about everything that Aldi
He's gone right
People are super afraid of
Even in the decision
The Second Amendment is being you ever right scary
It and that
Passage ends with
It's compatible with laws imposing
Conditions and koala
Vacation on the commercial sale of arms
Which is
Registration
Harder background
Which is legitimately
That the
Rational minded
People are asking
The only people who were asked
Looking for like
No God
Before Alice's Boogeyman
Except
Gun
They were regulated the same way as
Roller coaster
Like that
You're not allowed to build a commercial Road
Like I'd rather just fine recently a kid died
Like
Huge elaborate water slide and the guy who
Ed and the guy
Alex isn't talking about that now
Hey David
The same thing like I'm fine look
People like to shoot guns and I respect
Probably super fun
You're probably go shoot a gun I should learn how to shoot a gun in order to obtain water I will probably
Why dig one of our listeners actually
Jacking off right now
Agreed that that would be super cool
If that was the only place where you were allowed to shoot guns as a private citizen
That would be awesome
Lego guns were part of an amusement
Like a larger Music Park where people were
I would have to get a permit to build a water slide in your back
I would imagine that
You are allowed to build a water park in your backyard
So I think you probably would have to be
Subway license like you can take care of this man. Going to hurt people
You shouldn't be allowed to do
Just walk around with guns
Sprinkler
I don't think law
I should be allowed to walk around with
So very responsible
Drive
Like they they
Hit that woman
What is like to lick you and I texted you literally said
Law enforcement is now is
Always has been
Hey
An inherently white supremacist
Defense of a white supremacist
You see that through the way that I saw operates
You see that illiterate away that
Here's the cow black
People
Anyway police officers are white supremacists but it is to say that
The system that you participated
Is white the reverse of a composition fallacy
You are a part of a
Therefore the group
Is the same as you
It made the reverse of it is to say
This is the character of the group therefore you are exactly like the dark
Yes and it is it is the same thing
It's the
Just because law enforcement
To be about defending white rice
White property
That doesn't mean that every copy
System needs to be
Here's one place
Which is that
If you are if you
Do you want to run
You should
First submit to
The death-penalty preemptive
It's like if you become president if you do make it eight years
Route whenever you're terman
You should
Willingly submit to being
Only way to accept the responsibility for what
Interesting
I think I think that's
The dystopian view but I also dig a little
Exile
Exile whatever you like so long
But the ideas like you make your changes you rule is Estates
Your f****** gone
Strategically
Even if I were to
Like ice
I kind of think
And this is something that I might wind up
Elucidating
Further
Through
True right
Is that
I think I
Could
If I were elected
Supreme leader
With complete autocratic
Eyebrows
I think I could
Fix everything
Before I would ever do that I would submit to
I am going to be murdered at the end of
We are too because that's the only way that's the only way to avoid becoming guy autocratic
Dictator that's so many communist
Socialist
Countries have wound up having
Like that that's how you get the Fidel Castro
If Fidel had been like
We're going to
Complete this revolution
I'm going to do whatever it is I need to do
And then you guys get to murder me
That would
Creative baby
Staples
Or wouldn't
But you'll be dead soon
And then another dictator would show up and take over
So we should be removed
Speaking of God
On the 27th
Alex Jones one of his gas
Jack Purcell
Talk about it
Because he went down to the March for our lives
And he saw but he saw a bunch of buses
Quiet
Great so I don't know a bunch of
Disparate organization anyone guy
Who cares about that stuff
Alex has another guest
I'm thrilled that you showed up
Ben Garrison
Do you know about Ben Garrison
Cartoonist of the alt right
I'm going to
Reject
Sprinkler head over here this is one of his political cartoon right here
This is one you can find on his website it's about California being in a
Shoot off with Jeff session
If you look around here you'll see
The Golden Bear Saloon here with that welcomes
Immigrant
If you want to see this picture it's also on knowledge fight.com we have it
You look into salute no ice
That guy right there
Gang written on his head
Label
Sanctuary
Governor labeled California to be a
Nickel cartoon
Perhaps the cartoon
Itself should be representative of what it is you're trying to say as opposed to you just right
Writing it out there that would be
For what is style is
Overlay ballistics
And if you look at his cartoons it's almost comical the extent
To go
Do so much work
To make it make sense by like
Which means he's a bad cartoon
Craft
But I will
He shows up on in Floresville
Do the cowboy hat cowboy hat have his name on it
Because that is essentially what he does is a cartoon posted in the Facebook group this is not a drill
Ben Garrison is on Infowars
The clown Donovan the group before
Jim chimed in is
Labeled there we go
Alright
Just keeps talking to him about like
Your work is perfect
And all this picture clearly cuz he wants to sell
Coffee table books
Of his cartoon
He makes it clear
You know what the best part of graphic novels
Is that they never let the images speak for themselves
Never
They always over label every panel
I would say that like
The Pharcyde
Left you up
There'd be the caption
Not like
Bear
Feel like explaining
Somebody holding a basketball and then a label thing
Basketball play
Sport
Exactly
Tortoise
The only thing that's interesting about this entire interview is that Alex Jones
Equipment
He's trying to go to the interview with Ben Garrison
Break salt
Even though they're trying to talk whenever Alex
Can't hear any
I don't even press on
Blisters and viewer
I've got a broken arm
So
So when he gets another ear
He doesn't need to impress this on the listeners
And then maybe
20 seconds later is like
I'll say to you
And they've just has Ben Garrison
Okay alright
Talking about
Can't respond to it in the middle
Alex
Turn his mic on and you can hear him yelling at the
Mark says a democracy
100 hours of driving
Well this dumbass hole
Dumb assholes trying to talk about Karl Marx
It's Brandi
Amateur hour
I'm a big fan of
Everytime it like whenever he's like oh I don't use a teleprompter
Because you're
Broadcaster
You don't
F****** have any
Professionalism
Whatsoever
Also it's not broadcast on any radio station
Yeah I'll miss episode also
He starts doing a lot of Star Wars talk
But he feels a disturbed
The force nuanced look at
Tastic
Do everybody have
Hopefully it's no good let me tell you something
That looks Skywalker
Interesting
I'm not as excited to see this as of the new Jurassic world movie which is not much
Number for dinosaurs
Does doing a lot of like
Kind of stuff
Rather I know something's, it's like when the first attacks
Rebellion
He just started the war detectives
Joke
You think this is
Hardcore criminals on top with a bunch of
Dumb down mindless alone people that are scared and desperate
But I need money
Always
About 27 to talk to Jack
So back
Ben Garrison
I wish it was more
It just revealed to me to Ben Garrison
Bad
That's all I got
What else you got
Burke Bradford
No he did that bloom County Kerry Carol
Very true.
I love dub
Boone County is very
Have you been reading at a harrow County
It's a great graphic novel
I've Loved ugly
So good
Episode of knowledge Pines Dallas was the best
So cool
Flawed
Terrible character
Move on to the 28th
Yes is Wednesday
And Alex has
Some other narratives he's pitching
First one is about
Craigslist
Is he descended into a dictatorship because I feel like he's on board
Like this is a
Natural
They're going down very similar to how they have been
A while
Well Percy is kind of edgy
Alex
Complains about China not because he
Who cares about China
Providing cover
What's going on in Russia
It's always like
Everyone says that
I won't touch that poop
Dictator
What about the Tricom
It's just his mom pretty sure we're all on board with
Dictators becoming dictators
Both
It's not one or the other
Anyway here's
Control
Call the numbers
Everything
I told you about that years ago is finally in the news
They have
Exports to the kingdom
No it's not
We talked about this already it sounds like that's what it is in reality what it is is a Google gave the encryption
Some keys to China of chow
Chinese iCloud
Customer now
Let me tell you something
If his listeners
Have seen the movie Elysium
I would be
Just by going off box office receipts
Not a hugely popular film heard his review
I like it's different all just a lie
Like that's all
Projecting whatever you learn from that movie
Onto his version of reality
Like that encrypt
Monkeys that
They gave two
Vagina
Between local
Company in China
It will
But it's not giving encryption
The entire world
The Chinese iCloud customer
Telecom system
Russia hat
Interesting
But it's just it's just the way of Alex
Not really giving him
Information for what he does do
Episode
It's some solid whataboutism
Alex Jones
We love Bass
That is
Doing impression
Smelling
Cuz he got winded is is his Bernie Sanders also a siren is this
Weird does Bloods come
Is actually a new one
On the 28th of March
Chan Wednesday
To do with that
Who got in a new narrative
Not really cuz we got the John Paul Stevens narrative
Yeah but
No bad news this one does too
But it's a really interesting
Information
On the other side
This one
Isabel Isabel
Alright
Muslims and suites.com
For Muslim
Because I guess
Releases brochure for migrants legitimizing child marriage
You just can't make this up
Yes you can so I can
Find this brochure
Because
The only thing I can find on this is article on Infowars written by Paul Joseph Watson
And that they only have
Tweet
From a guy who's talking
Forget about it
We bring you the latest
Tweets from a guy
To be is that the brochure talks about
People who have
Married
Underage folks in other countries
That have a record
Acknowledge the marriage
But also recommend that people don't
Adult
Don't live with or marry anyone under the age of 15
That's f***** up
Yeah that's a weird place for Sweden today because
They are
Trying so much to understand and respect
Everybody
Almost to
It did
2A Andover down extend
That of course they're going to be like
We are trying to include everyone
And yes
Culture is weird in that way
But also
Please don't do that what are you going to
To do
If someone was married at a different age
Then you deem acceptable in a different country
Say invalid or implication
Like I don't I don't know
Statecraft
International
I don't know if you want a broach that subject
Because if you are doing that
What you would like if you do say if you come to this
Validate
What you have done in your other
Country that is another way of saying you're not allowed to come
I do think
Marrying people who are minors
Is wrong
Super Wrong by Ted Nugent did it
So that's fun
Right on Ted Nugent married a girl who is 17
In order for her parents not
Complained when he
I have sex with her marry her
He adopted her yeah that's one of the weirdest things not married
Also Courtney Love's husband
She blew in one
So also spoiler alert
On Thursday
The moral High Ground
Many of these people who have committed so many sex crimes often take the moral High Ground to appear as
Pundits on Alex Jones Show where they talk about Muslims want to have sex with your kids
They're starting to appear on CNN
Not really good point I regret that I don't remember who it was and I can't pull it up now but on the Facebook
Ted
The right
Is buying into the
Mythology
Ignoring
Reality Fugazi
I can't imagine the right ever doing anything
Did the draft
Austin Banks kids
Who would never accept somebody like that
They would never elect multiple people like that as president so no back back to the Sweden
I want to ask you if you know about this
You know
The girls as young as
Quail can be married in Uruguay
14 in Venezuela
14 in Belarus 14 and Bolivia
12 in Columbia
14 in
Cuba 12 in Ecuador 14 in El Salvador Guatemala 15 and Lithuania
14 in Mexico 14 in Nicaragua 14 and Panama 14 and Tanzania
12 in Trinidad and Tobago
None of these are Muslim countries
These are just
Countries that have different cultural
Values
I think there's developmental problems that exist there but yeah when you play
Play the game that Alex is playing any Trice presented as a Muslim issue
King of child breiding
What if someone immigrate to
Sweden from Colombia
Yeah they married someone who was 12 right
That is a high priority male female
That's more to the point
As I've said before
It dude
It's not religion it's not all of this other s*** it's
Dude it's men
Anytime you have a
The patriarchal system
Scapegoats Muslims for a threat
Decides
Men like to talk to you about this also in the United States
Spy quote
Most states allow marriages at 6
16 and 17 with parental
In some states also make
Exception subject
Judicial provement
Or cases
The pregnancy
When all except
Taking into account
25 United
What states have no minimum age requirement
Not okay
In Florida
Thousand
400 children some as young as
Have been married since
Which is the second highest incidence
Child marriage
Texas
Well not just that but it's also one of those things
Where many
Of these cultures
Groom
Children
Is nose
There is still like
You're 12
We have promised
And so even if your
14 you're married to this guy
You're not living with this guy
And now your dad is telling you
How to treat your husband and all of that shake and it's important to point out these aren't all Muslims
No they're mostly
Chris
You do fine
Is that
Like Everyone likes to point the finger at like I had a buddy
When I was growing up
Indians
I guess his parents
For Hindu
Used certified
Call Discount
Is good dude
And his parents were very insistent
The he want they wanted
To arrange Merit right
Debuck's back against the
You for them
Someone
Choice
Weird
And everything is fine
Everything's going to actually had the marriage
In India
But there are cases like that that
Well recently recently in the news
Somebody who
It was a woman
It was a young woman who rejected her parents arranged marriage and they threw hot oil
And they abused her in so many different ways
That is the actions of
Insane people
That's why it's
It's new it's not the actions of the religion as a whole or the people as a whole
Most of the people in that culture would be like
Hey we get that arranged marriage is part of our culture
Still f***** up
Episode Alex
Give a Gaston who wants to talk
Turnabout
Muslims
Too much of it
Enneagram
Into what the Quran
But if you look at the what the Quran says
Islamic law
They don't
Support that
It's not that the Orthodox Islam does
There is a verse about circumcision
Very specific about how you
You should not do harm
Further because
I need to drive home
The point
You really acted like
Like I was about to
No I just want to drive home that point
400 children
Florida
Since 2000
Have been married
Is the second
Highest incidence
The highest
Is
Texas
You know what's weird
That seems low to me
Those people are
F***** up
The data shows that
Girl
15 or younger
Who cannot legally consent to sex
In Florida
Or had a baby
And then married an adult man
In each of these incidents
Because the girls rapist
Marriage license
Going to prison
In most cases
The exploitative practices
Takes place inside families or hitting
From public View
If you Brave women have spoken out about being pushed into marriages
His children have shared horror stories
Notably Sherry Johnson
From Tampa
Teletubby
Pushed married her rapist by her parents
She was only 11 years old and then being trapped
Abusive marriage for men
Their situations like this and has nothing to
To do almond has nothing to do with religion is nothing to do with the culture
It has everything to do with the idea of
Not
Bringing shame to the family and that's not a Muslim idea that's just people ID
That idea of looking at your children
An extension of yourself
Laws allow for a man to rape a woman
And if she get pregnant
He is given
Custody
He is given visitation
That's crazy
You're forced to now have
The rapist
Who owns
F******
Destroyed your you're
Life
Regardless of whether or not you can rebuild it
He destroyed everything
And he is now a part of your life
Ever
So
Alex also has an interview with
Arranged marriage
Is 18
And she talks about the
Female genital mutilation
Like in terms of that
Lucifer campaign
I do support
She is
From the United
When is working with Tony Robbins
That's not good
Appears that
There is more going
You know what's weird is that
5ive started
Yeah just as long as gloss dollar
Dr. Abbott
Aslan out
Northstar
The person the life and bodily sounds
The person
Is a legal necessity
Anything that compromises
Is it legal necessity by Brick
Harm to a person is unlawful
This is an interpretation
The prophet Muhammad said
And I quote trim but do not cut into it
But is brighter for the face and more favorable
For the husband
Which is still misogynistic
No I don't like it either but also
I don't like
I just don't like computer
Religious bulshit law
In The Raw
Just
Wiring somebody
Constantly
Accurately be wrong
Let's move on
Anyways organized religion
Today that Alex Jones is wrong
Child marriage happens
Under his very nose in Texas
In white families all over the place
It is an issue that has to do
With
Patriarchal
Do do
Jerry Krause
Are guilty of it too
Hey tonight it's not just
And maybe there respond
Going to
Pressure from their husband
I don't know if it's fair to say that it's
It is
A traceable historically from the mail
Purity
Yeah that sort of idea
Diabetic snacks
The current manifestation
You could find
Like let's say a single mom household where she behaves this
This way towards her daughter without a mail-in
I think it's possible but I do agree with you story
Anyway
Who cares
I would I want to talk to you about is how I grow out
Alex is getting on this
Episode he's getting
F****** Fury
Here's the first clip
Really
Really messed up
Amazing silver products
America's wealth
So that's the first one
That's a hard way to get out of it
That's it that's one of the weirder add pivots in generally speaking we get the screaming about nonsense
So loudly and then the ad paper
Turning into screaming about.
Yeah it's kind of
F****** mood
Here's here's my question
You only you have a
Point of view that derail
The situation I think this one actually is
We have
If not
Conclusively proven
Proven to a
Very solid
That the larger portion of
Responding
Has to come from
Dark money not his
Listeners
Listeners that only listen to him online
I think that's entirely possible
Why
What was were referencing back to the idea that he's not on any radio station
Yeah proper YouTube channel
What you'll see
In terms of like his actual long
Inform shows
Those are posted on the real Alex Jones Channel
Clearly
Natural and that post all of the long-form videos
Like
Maybe
Maybe 10,000
20000 people
Watch the actual show
Now the numbers that Alex gets for his
3 minute Clips are higher
Have you might have like 50,000 people who are watching
These clips
Maybe 100,000 if it's something like really salacious
That doesn't add up
To the millions of dollars in gas to run the operation so is he aggressive
Covertech
Or is it
Because it's not I can't figure that out
Possible for him to obtain the amount of money he has
With the listenership for the viewership
That we see
So
Like
Yeah I think it is getting money from somebody
To bolster the operation
Yeah I don't know who that is
Probably the mercy
That's an attractive option the Koch brothers in
In the pasture very attractive option is Sheldon Adelson is interactive option
Related Think Tank
The center for American prosperity freedomworks
Are attractive
Possibilities
Approve any events
I don't know
But I am
Based on
Kid needs to pee
Hey to make of this
Happen
He must be paying on that studio space
Sound
Figured out
Roundabout
He's paying in rent
There's no way he
He's doing it with the audience
He has
So why is it then that he is so
Aggressive
It's possible that he hasn't allowed
Or whatever
From whoever's bolster
Okay
The money that comes in
Boat
Yeah or whatever
Yeah
If you're accustomed to a certain lifestyle
Woodshed
And you're like
Sugar daddy
Is like we're going to give you
Going to keep you afloat
Ride him with
That's
Six Flags money
What I'm guessing that's the best way I can sort of
Contextualize it
What VR mathematically impossible for it not
It's just what the facts on the ground bleeding
I'm I'm looking
Dentist office
Hopefully we'll be able to figure some of this
Because of
Ways that
These
Think tanks
Foundations operator
They don't have to report who they
Give money to and s*** like that so
Yeah
But
Absolutely
Fantastic thing that happened to Arkham
Alex Jones
Who's the spirit fully downloaded
Empty zombie
Sounds great
Botanica
Metaphysical
Alright
Cool cool cool that's
Violent at all
Don't think a zombie once brain
Because they don't have
Baby
Hunches
Because we don't have our own
You know I have good huh
Yeah but I would eat them
I still have them I mean it's all just horse
It solves violent rhetoric
The average leftist is the anime
The average
Whenever high-level whenever we talked about
The enemy
It is not
Average
Person the average person is
Usually
At the end of the day like a good
I do way out of my way to make that clear
Yeah the average conservative is just
You do
Easily influenced
Send an
Kind of dumb usually wealthy usually realize how far the mainstream
The right has gone
Right towards this
Cambridge analytica
The Koch brothers
All of these people not the average well
Billionaire
This is violent issue
I didn't get pushed around
Confederates
Michael Moore's all the Glorious times everybody else has been covering up all this crap
You better know this
I know you trash
I know you're totally fake
Garbage
Bill Clinton Hillary Clinton
Listen up
You garbage
Is
The most
Progressive projection
I've ever heard I mean I don't know how else to describe it
Talking by yourself
Dealing with the fact that
Kill yourself a little bit
The other day like a week and a half ago I wish I had the Clipper this season
I'm miserable
All I got is my kids have this fight
Vistaprint
This supports every argument we've made about his
Is transition the overtime
This is not this is this is Aaron Stone that he could go back to the highwomen
This is
God
I don't think I'm a good person I think I might be evil if tomorrow when I'm listening to the show
He comes in from break with Eddie Money
I wanna go back yet
If he comes back then don't know
Already telling enough if he comes back
A break with Tarzan
Oh no
Call
On this here 28
28th episode
What is a Note 3
Remember boring as hell this one
Debbie and Nebraska
Call Zan
I feel like we heard from Debbie I'm not sure I'm really on the other
Radar for the guy with the house phone
In Wyoming
I only know his voice for sewer
Debbie and Nebraska make
Really
You f***** up
About women
Carry guns
Here's the first
I mean I have one conversation with the woman and she was just curious
She said well why don't you conceal that
Why don't you have it under your coat
And I said well let me ask you this
I said if you and I were to walk out in the parking lot right now
And there was a psycho nut job in the parking lot that was looking for a woman to kidnap and rape
Who do you think he's going to pick
And there was this long hot
And you could almost hear the click in her brain
And she said well it's not going to be you and I said exactly
I only need to be a harder Target than one other person
I was actually kind of on board until the end
That's so f***** up I was like maybe if women all
Carry guns and we would have a whole different
Picking on the tail end of all of the violence right
Maybe that's a different story and then she ends it with that old like
I only have to outrun the person that's next to me while we're being chased by a gazelle
Exactly cuz you don't have a gun
I don't understand
Like I'm not judging her too harshly but
Lionism
I have a gun so I can protect you two
Seem like she's interested in whether or not her friend lives
It seems like it
It's the same argument that she isn't means baby doesn't
Give a f*** maybe she doesn't
Give a f***
Is that Alex pivot
Time. Does this maybe she's more like a like a
Jesus care
Teacher woman to murder
It'll murder Waters
No no murder weapon
Chicken burger Aldi
Hey go but Alex
F******
Hornet
He gets hard as s***
I don't like that it's called here's what ends up happening
I am talk to one girl she came up to me and she goes well I have a restraining order
I'm like baby.
That's just his paper it is not going to stop a gun or knife
You need to get a gun I said you have a gun and she goes no I'm like why don't you have a Dutch because why don't know how to get one
Troy-Bilt 30 minutes explaining to her how you get your purchase permit
Curious how you get a concealed carry
Here's where you can take classes
You need to protect yourself because the police
Are not going to get there until
Also you could just spend five minutes going like
Look you can get all that permits yet
But you go to a gun show
Does f******
So gross
Anytime anyone is like I'm not hitting on you but
I'm not a racist but of sexual assault
Exactly in the way you sexualizing this call is
She didn't call for that
Evan Grant
Women
Are there are there p******
Videos of
P****** alt-right p******
Second Amendment Hub but like that yeah probably
The way that they like that call was not sexual in any way
And the way that he introduced you at
Well he wouldn't she was a male
Disagree
That was
Violin
Which two Alex is sexy
Guy saying like I want to teach other dudes how to shoot
He wouldn't said it was admirable
Patriotic
He's only doing that because she's a woman
Yeah I mean you can only ultimately sexualized
In the same way that you do he has
To describe them as women are being put on a pedestal right because the power thing and I'm glad you brought that
The West worships women
Ono
Women are worshipped
The Holy Grail
Women
Caught in power to the West because they worship in
What's a fun
Respond
Let me ask you a question
Did women get the right to vote because they were worshipped
Feel like it wasn't that 140 for years after America was founded for that to happen
F****** worship
Maybe it was women coming together be like
This is f****** b*******
I'm not even all women like I smaller
Percentage of women really f******
Cuz they were worship worship worship
Gave them the right to vote
For the right to vote
Gave it to them
Because of their worship of fear to talk about the right to vote I want to talk about a couple of more really fun things
That people don't talk about all that much did you know that until 1922 women lost their
Citizenship
If they married a foreigner I could do was just assumed that they would take on the for it
Status of their husband also
Women
Completely do women contain
And
That was until 1922 and then get this
They continued until 1931 if the man was Asian
Because we hated Asian
Also did you know that it was completely legal to not allow women to practice law in the United States
Till 1971
It was just
You could just borrow women from getting her their bar exam because their women until 1971
Supreme Court
The law would hurt their brain
Photo on the right side
That's crazy
Crazy levels of like a
If that's worse thing that's not good not allowing women to know the law
No they couldn't know it
Pratt
F****** Christ
Until
719 set
What
What's 71
And also did you know that
America was
Founded in
And then 172 years later
Right
The Supreme Court
Refer to case
And they decided
That women could be barred from being bartenders
Add bars that were known by male relative
Because quote
The profession of bartending
Potentially lead to moral and social problems for women
I mean hey
Argue with that
It took 172 years to get to a bad decision
Also at it till 1970 it was legal for airlines not to hire stewardesses if they were married
Until 19
Scene75 it was
Completely legal to exclude women from juries just because they were women
Really think 40% of men
It's insane all of these weird like things
It took whatever people talk about women's rights
They only talk about the basic thing
Ya basic
Yeah
But
You talk about the right to vote
Suffragette
Stuff like that we don't talk about like the ability to work in various profession
To abortion was guaranteed before the right
To work on Apple
Well unless you weren't married cuz they wanted to
Single people who can be flirty and fun
It's pretty crazy man
The same thing is still going on now
Arthur Arthur restaurants that can
I reject women who aren't attractive anymore
Because
There there
Classifying their waitresses or or
Performers
I believe that you risk
Getting in trouble
For that I think I think that there are laws on the book
From my understanding
That you can you can run 1,000 w
Instances you might be talking about like strip clubs
Them stuff like that is dependent contract
Your your Tilted Kilt
Sir or whatever like those b******* like
Your Hooters or whatever
They they classify their employees as such and such an order to get away with
Lose 5 lb you get fired
We're talking about a secondary issue
I'm talking about Lex
It's not like that is
Entirely gone but I'm more interested in
The broad Strokes of like
Women were disallowed
From all this s***
Horse
In the interest of
Texting them
Wow
Talking about insurance
To the West
And I don't think anybody got it
As a b*******
A lot of
Call Darrell I think it's just that
The the type of person
We are
Dial
The 29th
Alex is sexually harassed call her and then yelled about how the West worship
Get onto the the 29th
App screen mostly about how I Islam wants to suck it
Unfortunately
On the show
PS3 gas but two of them are Ted Nugent
Who became
13 year old girl's legal guardian so he could have sex
The mayor may not have gotten a b******* from Courtney Love when she was twelve he was 29
He was twenty-nine when Courtney Love allegedly blew him in order to
Have sex with the murky gray area especially
But it is a key area seems very difficult
For me to deal with
The garbage and he has
Famously
Try to pick up on a
Couple fifteen-year-old girls on Twitter great so
Great
Wants to do this whole like
Basically
About Muslims
Choose better guest
So that's most of the show
And then
He has a guy on named Mark Moreno
Choose better gas
Because the only people who support what it is
Your b******* things are the people about but that's the thing they're the only ones you were going to come out
Save it the thing that you're talking about
F****** sense
Sears another Gangsta on a mark Moreno
About climate change
Climate change denier do you know about Mark Marino I've heard the name before
Aransas
The website called climatedepot.com
Free shipping if you
Spend over $500 robley
Exclusively
Committee for a constructive tomorrow
Witcher believe it or not return always name something
Sing like that
They received
$500,000 in funding from ExxonMobil
Grace is always the case for climate change
Start running back to oil companies or Coke related foundations which is also the case
For committee for a constructed tomorrow they received a bunch of money from the donors fund
Andy Charles Koch Foundation
Supreme leader for
Subjected myself to
I would really probably just egg
Execute all of the
Like I would just start from like or or Amanda
Family would be even remotely related to the Koch family
All of their finances and I would just
You don't need murdered
You don't need to
Disease finances
All you have to do
Is correct
All you have to do is
Put in place
Sensible regulation
Sensible oversee
Good things that they the way that they get away with all this stuff is loophole
In terms of
I don't have to report
Giving hundreds of thousands of dollars through
Shadow and secondary sound
Towards these goals that would be
Very easily debunked
If you drink for all of it is that there is
That's what we
Been dealing with for so long is that it
Really hard
Write laws but I'll also
Kill everyone involved with the Koch brothers
Maybe we do
I will be getting rid of it
Woodforest app
Sure
Also also Mark Moreno was one of the first people to
To publish about
John Kerry in the swiftboating
Of course because he used to work for Rush Limbaugh gray taupe suede
Housing for election
You know he's a winner hatchet man
For hire
It's a really boring episode
This guy named Doug Hagmann who's
Super boring
August 4th hour
I was going to turn it off
But I'm glad I did
Because
Hagmann
Yeah he's just a
Fields
He's a boring ass dude
F****** but
When Alex and Doug Hagmann were having their little overlap
Before Doug took over the entire fourth
He was talking about Maria Abramovic and how much
Doesn't believe in pizzagate
Will Conquer America
I'll admit that was for Crowley Magic
Will crocheting
He's got the Elixir that will empower the people behind the behind the veil soccorso
Intercourse
Yuba City
You're busted
You are so busted Alex
You f****** literally believe
Yep
What idiot
He is on the same f****** page
Every time every time they
It's so it's so incredible to me that every time they bring up those
What you would expect is a metaphor
The Elixir that's going to take us to the next level
Then they wind up
Making it
Clear that they believe there is an elixir
It's literally literally
Yeah
You clearly like we've gone over this
In
Exhaustive detail like
Mcmillions
Even going into trip report adrenochrome and
It's a very
Bad High
Highbridge is a week high
No one really
Overdosing
Adrenaline
Really
Fun Buzz
Even even if their worldview was like
This address
I think we got to scare children to put their blood that we convey
Drink
Even if that was true
The end result of it is
The elites like a bad Buzz
That's worse than just
Weed
So go f***
Yourself Alex
Extra hundred dollars in donation by the end of April
We will do what episode where we're high on adrenochrome
And we're highlights
What are sites you can order it from
Easy to synthesize you don't even need kids to do it I don't need blood to do it
We've been over this to the amount
You could get out of
Like
Maximum adrenaline production
Would be
Not enough
Getyourpet crazy
It's insane
Higher doses
The trip reports are
So you're only Tallassee for this next clip
So now we're moving on to the 30th
Which is Friday.
If you're nasty
Socket
Sukkot
Jordans
Yeah
Yep this is cuz this one is
Frey f*****-up
Okay
Very fact
You're judging people
Yes your horses I have
I got four children
My lucky stars every time they're healthy
And they're born
Just
Hi I have serious guilt
Think about global km
About the children and I have no fear
Juicy
I mean
Because of what I did to my children
Money
The difference is I'm sorry and I know I'm wrong
I was young and stupid
Most girls want a divorce has a couple of them didn't
I think about those magic children
Judge you
God judges you
Holy
S***
Holyshit
That's crazy
He paid for 10 abortions
At least a song that research
Pull out
Rhythm method is not
It's not reliable love unprotect
Bruh sound effect
What you're doing is hitting on I think what is
One of the more important points and that is that like
People make
Things happen
That's a behavior
That's not that's a
That's a pattern of behavior
And I have known a couple people who have
Open
Who had abortion
But haven't talked
But I know a couple people who have
I have spoken about it and generally it's a wake-up call
It's generally I like OSHA
Okay
Absolutely
G'head
An abortion
Crazy
So I did some research into this
13 / 600
Fifty thousand or so
Reported abortion
In the United
Yeah
There were about 151 million
Mail
In the United
Assuming
That all of those people just
Spread the abortions out evenly
You have a
24% chance
Of being a male Who's involved in abortion in
Any given year
Alex Jones was
That
Which is crazy
Like
None of this is just none of this is to judge and then he knows about
None of this is to judge
Wrong
But that's a
Hi number that's a f****** huge number intentional
Now the other problem that I think is even more important is when he says
That's not great
That's severely f***** up
Pressuring people into getting abortion
That
Wow
And
Him pretending like
He's just this guy didn't know any better he was a sucker to the propaganda of abortions
If he was reading adult
Textbooks
And super mature reading
10000 books about World War when he was 10
Vig person
He better when I got
Women pregnant
When I was
Deal with that
Like I don't like ideological I'm 100%
Right
At the same time
Sequence that is what is is Alex Jones was almost
Intentionally trying
Reconcile I would argue
Tension
Might
Be
You might want to take that away I would say
I would say compulsive
I would say at 4 likely explanation is that he was a compulsive Behavior
That he really enjoyed
I was able to get away with
Inasmuch as
Sometimes they wanted to get abortions on the other times you can pressure him into it
And it
You just avoiding
It's so f***** up that's because f***** up because also the idea that like I learned my lesson
I'm so sorry
Yeah that's not
Why did you learn it the first time
Why didn't
Pattern
Of behavior the first time is it
As real
Until they're like I really got to change this
I don't I don't
I couldn't be more pro-choice at the same time I think everybody who's pro-choice
Is not
Up for 10
Different women having
To have abortion I think what it comes down to is generally when you're pro-choice
One of the most important elements of it is
Women's health for sports
Seeing here is
Alex
Haven't an abortion
Which probably with 10 different
Women
And that's more him at least like 9 p.m. be a wildly response
And I'm not judging him for that either he was young and stupid and what have you but like
I think I am going to judge
I'm going to judge for the parts of it were he's like some of them
Want to have
That's pretty f*****
And then I'm going to also judge
Like legitimately when we
When we hear him talk about
Pro-choice people being satanic
To kill their babies
All it is is that clip
But you just heard
Being projected on them he's guilty about his past
Behavior
Wanted to
Maldives
I don't know how to deal with 10
I don't think I do I don't think I
Ever
I don't think I've ever heard of anybody in
Involved
I imagine is a lot
So many
Mystically
You shouldn't have it nothing was judging if you do but it's a lot
No
I don't know I don't know how to
Man that is a f***
Conundra Brown let's cleanser palette by
Checking out this next flight for Alex Jones
Gives his thoughts on Depeche Mode
Alex Jones radio network
Depeche Mode
We cannot possibly like their most recent album
Because that was
Victory anti Alex Jones is b*******
Playing he chose to play on his own program
I am involved Christianity taking cues from Islam
I need screams about how like
Hey
It was 600 years later not recognizing that
Paul
What he wrote all his letters and stuff
600 don't worry about it
Pretty worried about it
Don't don't think about the timeline Paul created
Church
Very bored organized religions
I bet song is a banger though
In the next
So now we get to Alex having a gap
Okay it's a new guest
Do you know Katie Hopkins name before
Where she's from
She's a former reality star from the UK
That is why I know
Now I immediately regret knowing that
She's most notable
For being a brutal islamophobe
After terrorists
The tack you got on Twitter
Call Tori
Final solution
That's not great after the Manchester bombing
Gray's promoted hoax narratives about the Muslim no-go zones
She refers
Constantly
Cockroaches and rats
Don't
Shiro tan
Anti-immigration calling in the Sun
Was titled rescue boat
IG was gunship
Stop my gray
In June 2017 she appeared on Fox and Friends and advocated
Internment camps being set up for suspected Islamic terrorists
Added you kept conference the UK Independence
Party
Northridge
People who are into
Brexit
Hopkins gesture that would be okay if he House of Lords was quotes
The people
Always
But
Criticize their enemies like like
Whatever Alex Jones says David Hogg is
Clicking his heels
Together and salute
God dammit they don't love nothing
Tactics
Huge fans of genocide they just don't like the uniform I guess like I don't know
I don't know what's wrong with armbands are out
Do they not
Ever hear themselves talk
Probably not
We got to keep moving
Keep distracting
Israeli government
Naruto
Look
Genocide
So Katie Hopkins has advocated for a final solution about Islamic terrorism
Great I keep that in mind as Alec
No
Censorship
Mode
Congratulations here's the next Clipper Katie Hopkins
About to
Conservative
I don't like this
White supremacist
I think
Is this kind of ray of light he's kind of mine
My Carnival
Whitewright
Wide soda earlier
On March 28th Alex out of nowhere
Turn die
Conversate
Sexy
With a
Would someone who called into
See where this goes
Hopkins
You got a boner
Women voting conservative
Husband
Awesome
You like that house it go ahead and then immediately started screaming at like
Enjoy what you have to say
Has nothing to do with the kids because you agree with me
Exactly
F*****'-a
Disaster
Notify
They were awesome
Why do you think I'm sexy
Iraq
There's so many layers to that there's so many layers that the first is that
Like first of all f*** Katie Hopkins
Terrible she is appearing on the show
In case you were wondering
Cheese for bread
She is appearing on the show I voted for brexit
Nigel farage
Actually he's even like
We are not
I'll bet you
Weird
Be there as it may she is
And she's appearing on the show and if yes
And she's appearing on the show and
Professional capacity
Now I disagree with literally everything she's saying but she's not there for Alex Jones to be like
Pocket turns me on
I'm married but you're sexy
LG
Completely fine thing to do
Henry and ideology that is entirely built
F*** you
I don't give a s*** strongly disagree
Strongly disagree
At what point do you become complicit
And in fact
Your own subjugation as a as an object
Principles
I try to
Fail
Play X but
Principles are at least
Believe principles that are on
Are Universal
ARG
This must be true
Otherwise
I don't know alright and one of them is that kind of behavior towards someone is in Pearl
I don't care
I don't care what she advocates for that does not mean that she deserves to be treated
Okay
I don't understand
I don't I understand where you're coming from as well that she is propping up
The system fed
Mantu out of nowhere in a professional capacity
Professional interviews be like
I'm going to give you a sexual compliment
Yeah out of nowhere
I understand
But at the same time
That doesn't matter to me
It matters to me that that is an inappropriate way for a man to
Behave towards a woman
And you can tell from listening to that clip is deflect into a self-deprecating
Didn't comment where she says I'm if you think I'm sexy you need to check your eyes and Alex responses
By interrupting her
Insane
I don't think you look bad
Or whatever I want to deal with
The thing that clearly is inappropriate cuz you wouldn't have said
If you think I'm sexy
This isn't what I'm here for this is what the conversation
She tried to deflect it with
A powerful position
What is that self
Deprecating
I
Humerus position
Yeah and
Work
She does not deserve to be subjected to
Just because our positions are horrible
I do not believe
Here is
Here is my
Okay
I agree with what
You are saying
Annabelle
In nauna world that we don't f****** live in
I agree with you in
Entirely
At the same time my printful
Time
F*** her
She is
Let's go let's go let's go let's go
Really on your side and at the same time
I think she f****** does deserve well let's go back to
Actively accept
And actively says is the right way for things
Mitsubishi going to pretend she clearly something that she is not
Participant
She clearly doesn't accept it on some level cuz otherwise
F****** don't do the s*** you're doing
Wow
Time
The problem I have with that
Is that it reminds me of that argument of
Dress the way you're dressed
Expect
It concerns what it seems like a similar argument time
It's not 88 don't dress the way you're dressing it's a rapist
Be allowed to rape
Right it's the same thing that befell the alt right
Community
When Lauren Southern came out and said that you didn't want to have kids
And everyone got on there and everyone started
Everyone turned on her you are right
Sort of thing
I don't believe that just based on Lauren Southern
Other awful position
She deserves to be treated
Like that
By the terrible community that she's Court
You know I don't believe
I don't believe the Katie Hopkins
Who I hate
For her position deserves to be treated like that
By a guy who invited her on the show
To talk about
Admittedly
White genocide
But
I can't
I cannot agree with you more
Like I genuinely agree with you
What what does
Is
I think you and I are on the same page on a lot of
But I don't know if we're a hundred percent
On the same page in terms of my foot
Defeat
About this
World
And that is that
I lost my train of thought
I'm coming up again
I100
Percent agree with Odin
As a human being
No one deserves that I found the TranStar
And I agree with you I don't think she does deserve that
At the same time if you are saying
This is the world
That should be
The one where I am treated like this
My sympathy for you
My empathy for you
Disappeared
Will her behavior underlies if that's not what you
Yeah because they don't f****** make it a reality
She's not I don't know I don't know
F****** know here's what I was trying to get to a second ago and I lost my train of thought
And I don't think we really had a full conversation about this
Cowardice propaganda stuff
This entire world
Sometimes
What's required of you is doing the thing that feels unnatural
You know like it's very natural to attract
He's saying stupid s***
Feels unnatural to give a pass
To it
Because you understand the context of it that
He is a victim in
Is being exploited by Alex
Push these narratives
Respect in the same way on a different scale and it certainly is not a one-to-one
Comparison
It feels very natural to say f*** you you brought this on yourself of course you behave this way Alex is going to sexually harass
Or turn a sexual compliment out of nowhere red you want to call that harassment or not is your business. Not for me
It feels natural to dismiss that
Interstate like f****** who cares
But I don't think that's
I think that the unnatural thing
Looking
And realizing
That she did not
Ask for that she's there in a profession
Capacity
And imagine
World where she's on a different news show
And I don't know where the guy is like
Imagine Alex saying that
Gerald Celente
Getting like that like imagine you start to get a picture of like
This is inappropriate behavior whether or not the
Open is
Vile monster
Yeah not that that part is
Important it's feels like you
You should say
F*** you to all these
Right and now
No let me let me kind of like the more I think about it here's the here's the reality
1%
She does
She absolutely does not deserve that
I think
My issue comes from
The world that we live in now
We're in this
Minority of human being
Is
Somehow the strongest
Overarching
Dominant philosophy of Art
So exactly
Here's where I'm coming
And I think this is my altar
I'm listening
How
Less less what
What does anybody
Deserve
What day is what is
Good what is
The correct way to
And more
How do we stamp
This bulge
I am coming from a place
I think you said it I think you stamp It Out by resisting
The easy Road
How does that work
How did that work for
How did that work for Hillary Clinton
You know when they go low we go high
She went but that's just a catch for
I mean I'm not
That I respect is the actual
I entirely respect that as well
The actual work
It's actually wrestling issues
Dealing with reality on reality term
In reality
Katie Hopkins
Is a f******
Monster
Bought
Human
She doesn't deserve
The pier or anything that you've done in the past or any positions that she has does not marry
Her coming on Alex Jones Show
Talk about how bad Islam is
She shouldn't be doing
Yeah I design treated like a sexual object
For Alex to flirt
Is
That is more
My point and it's f****** it's f****** tough
Because
I mean
I don't want it I don't want
Putting you on blast cuz everyone has their
Their position
Tanzanite
Yeah but in the
In the Facebook group go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
We had some conversation
Particularly about rack
Yeah
And there were people who were
On the side
Yeah that's like that
I understand
Where is that voice come from
She brought this on herself
Trying to avoid that entails this Behavior
That's what you're saying
Exact
Maybe the cat
But
If
I believe
She had this worldview
That was beckoning
This sort of behavior on
Her response would be
Then
A self Depp
For kading deflection
If you clearly.
What you want to talk about is how
There is a play that's being put up called the assassination of
Katie Hopkins
And Alex has to
Interrupt
In order to
I think that her world is you
Wow
Korin
Stupid
It doesn't
It does not imply that
She should
Or
Is Cool Whip
That sort of
Because I'm sure I I don't think you could ever talk to her
Like
I just now in fantasy booking
Yeah I meant afterwards
Okay
Let me try and get it
To it this way
I think
That my position on this is becoming
The reason that
We Are Who We Are
Is empathy
Bright empathy and understanding
The recognition that
Human
That is
Part of our beliefs
And I think
I'm I'm
Wrestling with the
The fact that
For not fact
I'm wrestling with the concept of
Maybe that's
Why were Luke
What up losing
Where We Are
We will Arnold
Nobody has ever lost as hard as we are losing right now
Knowledge
Losing
I mean that
I think you need to adjust your definition
Lucent
Climate change is out of control
Income inequality has never been higher
Civil rights are being destroyed at every possible f****** oportun
Naruto
That is just
Purely
Little
Be empathetic
Big picture
Terrible
OurWorld
The only things that we have
Control over our
The show
Yeah perception
AR
Prince
Right
I think that no matter what happens
In the bigger world you have an opera
Opportunity to speak out against it or accept
Those are the two starters like Waze
You can
You can live
And it's your decision whether you want to in
The moral decision or anything like that some
But be that as it may
The reality of the world is not
Are choosing
We are
Mirror actors on the the stage as it worth we don't get to
Play weeaboo
Yes and we have to
Figure out how to get
Through it
You and I
There is not much we can do other than
Express our opinions
And try and put out
The best we can do it in this context
Yes we can
Convoke
Protests also we can
Encourage people to
Active in
Yes but beyond that
It is not our fault
Fault it's
Even
Arnon listener
That the world as it is
Exist
Yes but it does
We have to exist within it
I would argue that just
Because all of the
Big-picture stuff
Real bat
Just because of that doesn't necessarily mean
We're losing
Or is it everything is
Is terrible
Terrible but doesn't mean we're losing
You only really lose when you give up your
Your principles
You only really lose when
You are not
Fighting for
That which you believe in
Yeah
Because cuz all of this stuff could get turned back
All of it could be fit
It would be a fight
And it'll take a while
But all the stuff
Is really terrible is not undoable
It'll just
Take rationale
Calmer heads
That's
And a beating down of
Great voices and Nazis put them back into the corner of the internet
But then the question
And this is
This is something that was was wrestled with during the Civil Rights Movement
Intensely
Is the difference
The effectiveness
Total pacifism versus
Violent Acts
I mean
Yourself
Slavery was intended by pacifier
Slavery was intended by
Slavery was intended by all of those things how slavery was ended by a f****** War
No I'd like Martin Luther King wouldn't have existed without Malcolm X and Stokely Carmichael
He wouldn't even have survived as long as he did
Killed if it wasn't for the complete
Psychopathy of the people
And
Spoiler alert
Look those are related to this conversation
Agree with you I have to give up that that idea that I
The forces that are
Pacifist
Philosophical
It's just you say
Baby imperfect
Perfect example
A bunch of people who realize that fascism ain't Great Britain
Do you have that certain
Continuum
Yeah that exist
I don't know I don't have it
Going to play out I don't know anyting
But the only reason this conversation is going on this long is
I'm
Going out of my way
Defend
Someone
Yeah
I'm
I think you're a better person for it
Thank you and I
I mean melatonin Cal Expo
I agree with
Thanks
That's the end of that set
I have another pack but it's this was an aggressive conversation and I see
I think you are right
We are we just f***** now we need a cigarette and now let's smoke a cigarette in
Enjoy
This clip that will undo all good will towards Katie Hopkins
At one point Alex Jones I guess
Take a call
You just let her host
Entire segment
Trade-ideas what kind of s*** she's pushing
The white Farm in South Africa is outside with the white rhino
The only difference is that because it's a white
We've been over this
God damn time
The the white farmer murder narrative
Very clearly about something
Play Nelson Prior Lake
Cuz if you look at murder rate
South Africa
Right now what you find is
Young black
Being murdered
Way more
Always anyway she who's who's
Young black women are young white
Who won the
Faygo
Spears
And Alex Jones
He was doing
On the other show
All the world went to Russia
No response other than
We're going to end up with like so many Clips like that
There's like
Noted
F*** you
You're wrong
And you're lying
So at the end of the day I don't give a s***
The March 30th episode
Alex Jones
Realreal Soros have
He's really into talking about sir
He does a bunch of s*** about how like
He helped the Nazis all day thing is
18 his Memoirs absolutely started reading his memoirs
Alex is
Whole bunch
From that just cuz I was like
Santa Rita
Reinforces the
You had nothing to do even with his godparents
The things that were taken away from Jews in Nazi Germany
Quartz turns out most the time he
He was playing
In the field
Anyway
Alex
This is really funny
He is insisting
It's Taurus
Keeps trying to reach out to him
And this
Is the
This is almost the equivalent of a lesbian
TV is talking
It's not alright
Lawson State filed
Always have a quote about
Jones claims George Soros
Do
Georgetown and nnn to others
As a message
George I know I know you're coming after me
These guys don't get it
I'd kill them
Jersey
Your movie in theaters
George Soros
Had to do what he did
Would you ever want to talk to George Soros
He seems like an interesting guy
And I'm sitting there
Know what you want
No and then
I had another
TV released are on one time
Is not that bad
Tori Spelling
Cam
I will
Ever
Refused
No such number
Not ever selling anybody
No it's not
How do you spell glad all the guy
All the time
Dear your careers
Brutal
In this clip
Alex's
He is operating under that like that dumb
He has that like
Whenever there is a
Mass shooting the people are talking
What about right owners are blame
Crisis at which is dumb
Dumb
He believes
Furthermore
Once again
The majority of Guns is owned by 1%
That's very small
Tiniest amount variable
Who we are blame
Gun owners
Generally speaking
Define
I hate guns more than anybody
Has been proven by all of the things that I've said
Most gun owners are
Totally
Alex
Is projecting a lot of guilt onto himself
And then he spins
One of the
The stupidest idea ever had
Cause celeb
Child killer
Gun
Scheller's
Turn in Georgia
Yes
Somebody stab somebody
Every knife on ursulines
Your car
You didn't know that
Porter Chevy
American Ford and Chevy owners
Mercedes truck
You have this vehicle
Hundreds
Portal
Vehicle that was associated with number 277
So real quick in nice
434 people yeah
And 87 people died including the driver
Then what do you think actually the the real world of what he's talking about
If there was going to be like this field
And let's say
Like let's make it
Like sort of an analog of
Controller
What's going on
It's specifically designed only for killing people
Right let's write like the DeLorean where are the monster truck
Alex was going on
The Destroyer 5000 be allowed on Road
Everyone know and it's not
The version
This logic is so f****** stupid because
On one level
Everyone who drives
Car is
License
Get in trouble for
Part of what people would like to
Steve Gunn
Secondarily the restrictions
The people want
Speed on guns are things that are like
Do this gun has no
Legitimate real purpose outside of killing people
And if there was a car that was like humorously brought up
Ventrac even then
Immediately
So anyway
Hilarious idea
What are those
I can't wait.
Arguments
Makes sense
If you never think
If you never think critically about it in the same way that earlier we were talking about the baby was on the last step
Episode we were talking about this
18%
Of Millennials go to church 41%
Of generations
Perfect sense if you never think about a critical shoot around helmet
Right now
Go to the second
Stephanie realize like this
Logic does
Work like if
If
Yes
Intimate conversation that people were having
Which
I understand why they might have it but I don't think it
The idea Village
People should not be allowed
Is that was the conversation that was going on
I'd be much more sympathetic to Alex
In the in the sense of like
I get it
In terms of gun ownership
For like a rifle
Do you want to hunt
Or handgun
That you deal with responsibly and have locked up
You like those sorts of things
If people were saying
No one can
Can own any of these
I get it
We on the side of
But I would be served
Pathetic and much
More it's like engaged with the ark
But because the argument
Isabel
Semi-automatic weapon
That it is about a psaltery
It is about
Modifications
Can be made
With
Very simple adjustments you can do on your own
And things like that or little modifications
You can buy at stores because that's what people are talking
I am
Unless the pathetic
His logic called for complete disarmament
.
But if
Autopia
If we climb
Good point
Alright alright
If guns were only Recreation
If guns were like we talked about only recreational
You could go to this
Place and shoot
And they have their gun
You get to have your perfect or some sort of like a wildlife refuge
Animals for hunting or bowling
Are those balls are for you today
I'm totally fine with that granted even that analogy doesn't play work as a lot of people have their own ball
Yeah
You can't murder people the ball
You know like that. How you could help murdered with a bowl
You're a little bit at fault as well
Or you're living in a cartoon
It is madness
I love that Alex is like
I'm going to put make the
This video and it's going
Spell all of the
This s*** like
Like 45 different logical problem
What your
You're trying to espouse
But like we've got to the end of this you just explain conservative
You have four or five different logical problems with which shoes
Bolt clip
Podcastville last another 45 minutes give or take I'm we're going to discuss whether or not reality is valid
Like to talk
About the Gambino family to talk
About I want to talk about skulduggery I want to talk about
A Carlton Fisk
Other rapper other new living room
Let's bring in nails
Throw it all in the ghetto
One of the best albums
Buy Beach
Had the song bling bling on it that I wanted to love back in 1997
Really stuck in a
Pacific resort my taste
It just things I know from that time
Holy triumvirate Dirty South specially Louisiana
Anna in Memphis
Stuff that was really famous back when I was
Ralph
And did you hear
Almost immediately for no reason no one can think of any reason somebody survive
Yes he did
And no limit survived on
Very bad leg
But then the two of them and hypnotize Minds
Include like Three 6 Mafia
Project Pat
Those guys
Like it was a lot of I did like other stuff like A Tribe Called Quest in
Brand Nubian a lot of other stuff too
But the movement of course who doesn't love that
Like I got
No Limit and cash money
Apologize for it
I wasn't trying to argue
You always take
Upstairs whatever you say that you love this music is like any response to you being like
No Limit was the best I didn't say that
Mr. Serv on CD
You'll pry it from my cold dead hands
Back on track
On the 30th
Here
We heard him the only podcast that will get you
A sober and serious gun-control debate
Directly to
Is no limit as good as Danzig sit is
Even
I've got to push back on
You're misrepresenting my feelings on it I don't think it's good
I don't think it's good I just listen to it when I was 12
I just
No it don't like it although there are a few songs that are pretty good
Cmurders talented
That's the Alex Jones at pivot
EBC probably still be relevant
I'm going to go with
No
If you go to listen to life-and-death or bossalini some of those early albums
He's very very talented
He has a smooth flow also
Can pickup is also very creative
Yourself anyway
On the 30th of March
Rock You
On the 30th Alex Jones by the way
Good to be bad
I love you to all the 30th Alex started the show by talk
Talking about how many abortion
And I didn't even bring this up
He immediately fix a phone call
And plays like
3 Special Report
Like the show this is like
I don't know maybe it was a real phone call who knows
What you gets off air and they just play a bunch of
Anti-islam
Big play bunch
Anti-abortion
The next 20 minutes of the show
And then he has
White supremacist
Nationalist
This
I'm in at towards the end
The show he's like
I had a lot of clips
I didn't take pictures
Just tickles me
Yeah
That's what it is like
Are you going to drop them off pretty much dropped the ball
Big old pile
Bulshit
Yep punch a******
Nonsense
Find a signal
Yeah you can follow us on Twitter that knowledge
All the time is it
Bossalini was underrated
Review doodle
Oh God damn shebang
If you know any advertisers
Send them our way we will do it for less than your nearest
Competitor full-service No Limit Records still exist and we're ready to adapt
Do a lot of adverbs
Respect the Cardinals
What about no limit
Before we close this out
Fake
Military hierarchy
Getting all
For no reason
Because the tank was there their logo
All of a sudden
Everyone just
Decided
Here's my rag
Groupthink
Mr. Serv on
Has referred to himself as a colonel
Across-the-board always referred to as a colonel
Call Cole
Ideology often involves group and everybody just buys into the same concept
Other than weird
Little bit
No they weren't cuz after
Fiend
Servan
Snoop they all left
They all laughed and did the albums on other record label
Silkk the Shocker I'm not sure what he's up to these days really mad that you keep calling the shocker
It's an honorific
He also did a great song with
Trina
The baddest bytch
Slip and slide records a little bit further
Talk about Trick Daddy and his crew
Very well but this is too much
This has been fun
Jordan I'd like you to choose someone from our Cadre of weirdos today to tell to f*** themselves
You know I know you do what I
Perfect Masterpiece number to throw this microphone at you
Covert
Probably really exploitative dude
Like if you look at his business model from
Like when he started there were a bunch of really talented dudes
Like back in 93
Like I'm trying to wrap it up a bunch of guys
As you probably deserve a lot more money than
Lagos from the album sales
I think Master Pete might have been hoarding some of that
In the same way that slimming baby did with money cash money
Yes to somebody if it's master phf
Go fuc yourself
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color