Thanks for holding
Alex
Novelty beverage
Talk a little bit about Alex
Zaroxolyn
I know a lot about Alex Jones
I don't know anything about Alex Jones and clearly you don't know a lot about
Bringing the heat some emotionally deflated because I opened
The door today and Jordan had brought over
Hard cider
Myxovirus
Alcoholic beverage
I don't know dude
This Is A Dangerous Game
For AAA to be engaged
Is it the most
Seltzer game is
Is a real real dangerous things
Information
You can catch me on the street freaking taquiza catch me out there the Bartles & Jaymes
You know I used to f*** with eczema
Whatever that metal phenomenon
Why is this a punishment I love this delicious elixir
That last part's not true
We are we're doing another episode
Wow
Wow coming out
The gate
Do navigate with energy you know what I'm just I'm in a position where I'm still a little bit rough
From our
Long recording last night afterwards
I'm going to get there
A little bit of I got some Rust in the gears
Today my brain was
Dying on the inside but
During the show man I got it
Yeah for my friend
Unprofessional professionalism
Hey we're going to be talking a little bit about the April 2nd 2018 episode of Alex's show and then we'll have some
I'm fine afterwards I don't like the way you put that was inspecting like
Talk on
On the Facebook group about like what's his April Fool's joke going to be
EBay the best of episode and played it on the 1st
Hilarious
His Monday episode here on April 2nd and Sabine look really interesting on a couple levels
Haven't really boring for the rest of it
Start off texting your professionalism
Little boy
Your professionalism out the window
Sarcastic
Steve people treating him when he was younger
He wasn't supposed
Can you sort of saying it in the voice of the people picked on him
But still
So on a episode Alex
Does a lot of talking about
How's cell phones are going
So you the lot of that everything all of the s*** that's coming down on
Call Emma's hardest
Possum or less
He gets in
To this
He starts
Talking about the Parklands
Survivors
David Hogg
Course
In the past Alex has had like a really
Awful but sort of defensible position in bike
Hey everyone saying that I said he was a crisis actor I didn't I just implied it very heavily
People who did say
EXO
This is where things take a little bit of a
If somebody says
David Hogg is a crisis actor in your life
That is saying the David Hogg is a Christ
If I were to say
Do you
Hmmm you define the term
I kind of think you're saying that before
But this is where on this April 2nd show
Turn
A bit about David Hogg
Is trulieve
Disgraceful
This weekend
Article about it
Headline
David
Shooting
Not just a little Clips but the longer
It's not out of
I wasn't home when the shooting happened
Androgyny
He does
I was at the school in the class when the shooting started
What the teacher said we heard the shots we close the door
Other
Closet
Away
The shooting
In class when the shooting starts you close the door
So
This is a real big problem
I don't
Okay around on the world
Particularly on redstate.com
Sad
This news about the interview with David Hogg
CBS
Piece of paper together where you says
That's all
You got on his bikes
From his house and went to the school to shoot dinner
Okay
How is it
There's no way
School shooting
You heard about it
Then it couldn't be happening during the
The shooting itself there is no
Oh okay okay I got to figure that you got to tell me more about this this isn't.
He was talking about the evil
Alright
Perfect
How about I was at home and then I went
To the school
He's talking about after he had already gone home after the shooting
He left his house at 6
P.m.
It's very clear the timeline is
Incredibly consistent
Throughout all of the interviews that he's given
Interview after the shooting I took my camera got on my bike
I wrote it based
Twilight
My bike 3 miles down
Find my way to
The school as I've done in previous years
All the way I was making sure my camera bag
Is it a certain way
A falls out note
Be destroyed
I start shooting b-roll and ice
Sea Fox News over there
I knew I wanted to talk on the news and make sure there was ads
Especially with so many people from
The NRA
Different gun-toting Americans who watch Fox News
I went on the day of the shooting and said quote
There cannot be another mass shooting
I think that's partially why but I also but also other people started saying that
It's insane
The fact that there's more bullet holes in those windows
Better been proposed
Impastor
To save these kids lives
So
Alex is taking the CBS
Completely out of context
Fit during the day
Right now
Problem
Because now is Alex's pushing this narrative
Think that
He is a completely fake
Implanted
Realized
I'm supposed to be at work faking being a rectum of a crime today
And this
He's a real real serious problem
Continues down this road
He will be
Very very deeply into the crisis actor
Wow bundle
Or whatever
Interesting Lee
I mean to work
Does that even f****** matter
Even if even if this were the case
It's unfortunate
Even if Alex
Veritiv and these these f****** alright assholes is 100% correct
Then the school shooting still f****** happy
But that's the larger
It's unfortunate if he is saying that he was there whenever he was
But people were there
Who gives a s***
He's right
Interesting
I don't know I don't know how I would address that but I would say that red-state
Their story
And I've said quote I am sorry for the error and have updated the post according
GPS included a very confusing
Without context
Not really you guys just don't care
Define pecan
Ready to say I want to act
Super fun Alex goes with it
We got an article I mentioned it
But I'd already been banned off YouTube videos block
I realize why they were so scared
What went on
Didn't want you
Defraud
Yes you at
Paul Joseph Watson found his Reddit
Not
To-die-for depopulation
The perfect globalist leftist religion
This whole program
So he takes this
These two pieces of information
Are both either
Completely misrepresented or not true
Like
The school does inconsistencies in his story is just not true
The Reddit
Things that
I don't know
It's joke
But being willfully
Misrepresented
The two of them
To be like
Of course
He wants depopulation
I imagine these globalist
They also want a population
He's
Perfect person for them to have groom beforehand
Not good
Again
I'm the only person
Legitimately
Cauliflower
You should attack you
Also on this episode of mad because the pope has an article about he said that they are
Angel
The hell does
Exist which
You're going to go with a biblical
Interview
Eugenio scalfari
And he said
They are not punished
Those who repent
Forgiveness and
Take their place among the ranks
To those who
Complete him but those who did not return
Cannot be forgiven disappear
A hell doesn't exist
The Disappearance of spending Souls
So that's the quote that Alex
It's f****** hot and bothered about
Fart
The Bible more than
But hold on man
The Vatican
Denies
Did this interview even
Took place there's no recording
The guy is notorious for not
He's a 93 year old journalist
According to the guardian Eugenio scalfari
His quotes to Pride himself on not taking notes are recording high-profile interviews
Right that's that's a weird thing to take private
Sodapop
Stefan
No one knowing if anything
He says it's true
It's like Michael Wolff
The Vatican
Comments were quote the fruit of scalf Ari's Rica
Construction
And not a faithful transcription of the Holy father's words
Suggested he did do the interview
Confirm that
For denying what they just said was
He did do the interview any use
Creating that hole
Yeah
So so the Vatican did confirm that
Bro alright
The Vatican is denying that he said these things
Isn't that it's not accurate
To the vet their beliefs
Or Pope Francis
This belief
That is not stop Alex
From screaming about how he's the devil for
About how very elite
Oh no
They love to do DMT
Speak to little beings that they find on the other side
Somebody bringing
Some rationality
The little bit they talked to Dee and Ayahuasca and in their hallucinations they get program
Instructions
From the Otherworld entities that are running globalism
Listen to Regal for being somewhat
So so not even the bad guys
No. It's the little beings that they contact
They're the ones who are coming up with the sort of game plan of the globalist
What what happened
Railing against big guys from the
I don't know man
Discovered the issue is like
You're stupid
Because
She's not you
Alex
Super good friends with Joe Rogan
He is literally the biggest DMT proponent in pop culture
Hosted a documentary about it
The cult The Spirit Molecule
You're right
He is a big advocate of Colusa
The gym
Probably
People
There's a mention below and above
Whether it's real or not
You have the Spirit guides
Mescalito and all this
Okay Alex
I do like wait
Whether it's real or not you do have spirit guide
I don't know what that
Mathematics believe it or not
I don't know you're saying but I do
If a little goat man comes up to you
She is not your friend
Cool
I mean
Is that what's going on later
Mr. tumnus
I like
Alright
You got to work on your too babe babe
I don't I can't take Kenny Rogers and the first edition
I thought it was going to
As I started saying the name of the band I thought it was going to end eventually but it's Edition
Look man I'm right
Give me a higher.
That's it for the 2nd
Alex about the pope and Alex
Launching fun what will become a
Potentially
Slanderous narrative about David Hogg it will turn into
You're committing life
What's another guy to now
Man
Give us a call dude
He was one of the guys
From
There whatever
Alex
Mischaracterize as the shooter
And Daniel's article that was on
Infowars
It's doing Alex
I don't think
If that's going to work
I think it's absolutely
Will you take
The stand and testify
Cuz that's not a crime
Adjusted bad reporting
Depressed
Is protected assuming they're using good faith
You know it
Hip roof
Fly in court the ability to be like
To say intentionally
Did bad work
The reason why I like slander laws
Very difficult
To prove intent
In terms of slander cuz he want to err on the side of
Awesome amazing honest
Mistaken we don't want to punish them for it
Alex uses
Abuses
That leeway over and over
This will be another case
The case will be thrown out
I don't know I think if
You can establish a pattern of behavior
Then you can
I think you can generally prove intent in this
In this Arkham
Difficult
You can't improve
You can't prove it
Intent against
This guy
Like you can prove his intent
Deceive
Yeah prove his intent to destroy
I don't think you can prove that he even gives a s*** about this year
It'll be tough to prove malice directed at
Who knows
Now to the fun
Okay
Burbot mouth
The right around the corner
To get to the matchups
In the drop bracket
Any moment
And I realize I was telling you about this
What are the parts
To the bet
Of my old bracket
But I did
Was I intentionally didn't do them in March
Because I
Thought it was really stupid how somebody
F****** blogs
Alarm
I got a I got to push
Is this off until April
So now we're in April
April and so far
The matchups
From the guest
Division
We have
Giving Alex Jones Mariners last night
To the next round
And then also we had for Alex
It's time to pray
Versus
Alex saying he has to leave a rally to go pray
There's a lot of love for the big guy in the back of that rally screaming
Showed up for that
It's time to pray has made it onto the next round
And I should say that we are doing this
And we will
Only be going over the first round today
But I am ready
The entire
Yep all right and I am ready
To reveal all of the
This podcast that we've done in the last year-and-a-half herself
We've looking through a lot
They actually
They were very very polite
They had some bad idea but you're not a friendly character
I think if I did DMT
Hospital
There's something wrong with my subconscious clearly I'm not going to listen to a hallucination that's telling me to kill people
Kind of
Hockey
How big
How big do you think is a little GoPro
Some size would be
The little gold personal beast for four-and-a-half
Lucy and children
Wasn't that much taller
Well that's
True but I think you had a hunch
The f****** dope guy
Look if you can't if you have
Reversible
Reversible nieces that truck
Flamingos need for the doctor's call it
A little goat guy for
I would say
I was a little goat guy to me
Almost almost pocket
Hi Nico.
Episode
I would like to
To keep them in a little bag
Like a like a Paris Hilton dog specially if it's broken
My girlfriend
We got to go into parties
Number one
Pieczenik manners license has moved on to the next round but now it is time for us
Closeout
The division in a reveal what the other end
The number 3 seed in the guest division
Is
Rodger Stone interviewing Rick derringers wife
Infowars
The real American very proud
It sounded 280 estime so I told Rick and
He said it's to 80s and then I came up with the idea of having
Space Oddity
So alright controversial choice to be in the number three seed but let me explain
Why does selection committee put it in there
Here's why it's 3:00.
Alright
It's possible it should be in the number one spot
Or whatever
The number 3 seed Rodger Stone interviewing
Rick derringers wife
Is deserving of the number three seed for two reasons
It's absurd
Yes second claim to come up with the most important part of that song
Like it's 280
But the reason is because episode where Rodger interviews Rick Derringer and his
Is the episode where
Jerome corsi was supposed to reveal all of the stuff
But he had learned that would have gotten him killed
Rodger Stone shows up half an hour late
Just for contacts that is that is gorgeous
Unfortunately it's going up against
Incredibly strong competitor
It's all we spoke
Into it is Larry Nichols
And they were they went to a church
For witches
Lady that was trying to run sometimes
Place where they did
Wichita
Hillary went to a church
Worship
Which also artery artery meditates the three witches tickets babe
Linda bloodworth-thomason
Which Hillary Clinton
Delta Burke
Three witches of Designing Women honorable mention also to Larry Nichols
Focus was based off
The song Hocus Pocus by Focus
Honorable mention
What are nickels
I wish there was room for all of his stupid comment
But President Obama
Is about as ready
Leave office as I am
To be a duck
I would almost throw in our interview where he says
I felt like our own stuff and Project Camelot stuff
Larry Nichols going up against Rodger Stone featuring Rick derringers wife rounding out the force
Received
Of the guest division
Very exciting
The natural
All about it
Soap
Clips
Those come from the religious
Right before seeds in a religious division
And he's already moved on the ones
I'm here are
The other entry
Now you know we have
Alex
To clip saying
It's time to pray
I got to leave this f****** place
So it might surprise you
The
Number three
Does not pray everyday
Strong
Strong review of Prayer
It seems to help me
Is there a
Four out of five star right right
The dessert place
Maybe because of how contradictory it is to
All the other
Prayer clip
But that will be going up against the
The number to seeds
Is it like
Does he think he's still bragging about doing I think he is
I don't do it every day I still do
Which is better than you
I just did it
Yeah so my little girlfriend
Tiny little Doughboy
Like a little Jim Breuer
Definitely not your friend
M4u
The number two seed
I can't help it
I'm picking that one to go to the cemetery that's not better than it's time to rise
That's true
Red Alert Red Alert
Come on
I didn't feel better until I called the pope a devil wears a great I had a headache
But I called the Pope the devil worshiper and
Jubilant
Just B calling the popo
Can Hugh you much like juice
Therapeutic
I don't know
People think I think that's a that's a pretty even
App Store
All right we'll see who see how the people vote
So in the neck
The next
Division division
Stop
Is a 16-seed bracket
Quips and all the religion
Just Clips
And that brings us
To the next division
Alex
Swearing
So it is the first matchup from the alligator wearing division
Where he talks about
Somebody pissed in
You'll notice
Where can I get
4th Street excuse me
You will notice I think all of these do ended
This should be literally no surprise to anybody
It's going up again
It's number one seed
Fill your hand Adam Schiff hell yeah
Okay I love the gray fox
But Chef looks like the ark
Archetypal c*********
With those little deer in the headlight eyes and all his stuff
And there's something about this fairy
Bossing everybody around
Tell Congressman Schiff
And all the rest of them
Hey listen a******
What sing Rodger and I never use cussing in 22 years without the gloves are off
What's inside of a b****
You want to sit here and say that I'm a goddamn f****** Russian
You get my face without I'll beat your goddamn ass you son-of-a-b****
Listen Buckhead
Get that through your goddamn f****** head
Pushing your s***
You're the country over
Yeah
From the first moment we heard it
Poetry
You son of a son of a b**** you piece of s*** calling me a Russian feel your hand
It brought feel your hand into our lives
There's so much
Going on there
I mean it's over a minute for him screaming obscenities at Adams
It's
Poorly poorly
For Lake
She's really bad it's where
It's tough man
It's time for anything to
Be a number one
Is in the
Consideration
In the swearing section like
I don't know what you're going to do
Might have a chance know what I'm going to I'm not going to lie I think that one
That I don't
I think that one is going to go that far
I do not think it's going to get beat by your bucket of rotten pissed
Filter whatever
That's the first matchup that's
What's the number one verse
4C
And that brings us to the number to versa
The number three
Who's better
Conservative
That's not the best
But it
It's fun cuz of the b****
Feel like Alec
Do you like
Conservative
About how I think of him
Almost
It's almost
You would say that like that seems to me like something I would say
Brightright
That's going up against number two seed and swearing division
To unsee
I feel your hand
Adam Schiff but that is
Because this
This is profound
The Andersons of course
From a very drunk Special Report
American flag
Yeah
About the reason that I think of that his
The potential to eclipse
Refill your hand clip
It's because like
There is so much more real anger there I think
Now I think he was he was doing is Dianne Feinstein
Right
Then his Italian mafia what's going on here
I think
The
Like I don't think
Especially every form of the time that we've been doing it we don't have any other clothes of Alex just directly
Q
And that's pretty wild
Yeah cuz that's direct whereas
Iceman
That's some championships wearing right there
It's amazing how bad he is like
F****** piece of s*** f*** it like the drunk at a bar that makes you feel
I swear
But if I was at a bar with a guy swearing like that
Grow up
Yeah reaction
Are you a child
Is this podcast we decided to move on to something else
Alex
Tragic
State of delay.
Yeah that's what's going on is that of a child
That's why he doesn't understand anything
So you don't understand anything he reads
Yeah we got a f****** tell him about the rabbit
Brutal thankfully can't read that book so you didn't get the reference
Otherwise I'd be really mad at us
That brings
Division
This last division
It was incredibly difficult
Figure out
Should be laid out
And so I decided
It is it is a miscellaneous
There was there were some other thoughts I had but like
Legitimately the idea of the amount of work it would take
To do a 32c bracket
Just beyond what I have bandwidth for at the point
So here we are we have these for seeds in the miscellaneous section
We will start
With other number for versus the number one
Number for
Yeah
Do you want to do baby
I don't know how to
Steve the miscellaneous
50 how you seated it
Because
Is gold my friends gold
You rock and roll band it's gold as a drop I tried to Wavy like
Drop versus like
Weird
It's difficult
Sort of standing in place
A lot of the other times you saying
The best example of him singing something
It's immediately unclear that he's trying to say
Cat song
Is that hot
He sounds a lot worse
You bring back a
Did you bring back our ludicrous
No
No I should have
Whataburger amazing listeners
Play student it's too regular
He says it all the time
Think about that but he doesn't even sing free-for-all all the time
Decagon
The Rhythm
The rhythm of it was perfect
If I if I had this all to do over I probably would have an entire section
Yeah but yeah that would be
But
Nova delay
Chatroom the
Embellishment of his listener numbers
This next turn
Is actually 2 clips
Depression Bragg
I feel like that's actually grandfathered-in
In the
Don't tell your mother you're brilliant
I feel like that's been
We come
I took stuff out of context
Jar Jar Binks thing in the the policy walk drop
He's actually saying
Isn't that funny
Like it's just commenting on the character of Jar Jar Binks
Exactly what the rest of it
I just imagine backlash
Jar Jar Binks
It's drop ulcer what makes it fun is the way I cut it
Together to make it sound like you
You saying the Jar Jar Binks baby
He was yelling about Colin Kaepernick
Them together
Splice together
Are funny but the actual things that come from Arkansas
That
Technocrat
As a
We'll see they take him out of context
Isn't a single bracketeering is.
Before
I respect that but
There's reason
Eclipse
I couldn't decide which was representative of
Valve
Really
So there's that event here is the second part of
He's doing.
Suffrage
There's a different flavor of it too I think
I think the number one seed is Oliver
What I do
Liberal Liberal
Soap
Flipside of the liberal coin
Like Smeagol or some s***
But that also we are also going to add a
Bracket
Chirp
It's important
To remember to that like that click you heard of the beginning there was
Opening a switchblade
That should do
A boat
Liberal vs number 46
Navigate to number 2 and 3 seed and this was difficult a little difficult
The parameters of
The miscellaneous
Division is
It's wide open
Not just religious
Foursquare ringer
Gassed up your setting this up
I'm trying to get my cell
IPad
Here's number three Alex Jones talking about making a startling confession about his sexuality
Contacts
Belongs and
Partially because of the end
That clip is never going to end
This joke is never going to end because that's almost a cry for help there
If you like the o.c.
Alex
Please
Well yeah
Julia something
Capitalist
I believe he was also hitting on her
Shuffle look at things without that prism very flirty
I think he actually lets her house
For a good
Couple segments on that shows
But so that's
Number three
What's the number to Z
And it's probably is in the number two seed because it's
Gross
Something that doesn't say
If we talked about this I'm not sure if we did
It doesn't get enough
P***
Please
You know what I like
Girl
From the 50s
Women
Like a waitress in a
A representation of Alex being gross
Boudreaux's
I like just sitting
For an hour and looked it up girls
Like multiple or just
Just the one
Probably
Multiple I think he likes
Selection
He has to have the calendar that had like 10 up shots of me and McAdoo on it back and
Find
Swimsuit pictures of her on the internet because of that kind of takes away from some of her
Credibility
You know I don't know I'm not judging her for it.
That's a tough question to ask
Who has no journalist
The credibility via their own journal
Go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
That would be up on Wednesday
What do you think what would you pick as your winner
I don't know how things are going to break but I mean because
Your personal like
Can you dance
If you were going to vote for the ultimate winner
Kind of
Flavor of
Alex Jones
I don't know but I think it's
Tumi
I can tell you what I think is going to
We should win out of each division
Let's say
My prediction for these final four is
VR
Screaming f*** you
Act liberal
I think is a religious vision
Probably Pope
Compact
And it get to the point
It's time to pray
I think that is
I meant from the gas division
I mean I'm biased
We talked to him but I got to go with Larry Nichols
No
Weather
It's just like it
In the brick
Well that's
I don't know I don't know the reality of it not really particularly care
I have a soft spot
For Larry Nichols photos gone
He's up there is my favorite crazy
Going to be tough
If it makes it to the next round
Steve pieczenik manners lesson versus Larry Nichols
I don't know how that's going to break
I know
I thought you were
Going to ask me how I'm doing
I know what about you what are you what are your
Wood ear pick
Make any impression that he does
Automatically kind of something
Think that I I like I don't think
Italian
The only reason I'm partially his Impressions because there's nothing I love more than
Making fun of his impression
Then calling it something else I don't know how I can enjoy that
So that's that's your pic
Yeah
Little Goat
I was outside of the time frame
Imma go with us
I'm going to go with that as the as the ultimate winner
It's a really perfect encapsulation
Alex is about
So those are those are the seeds my friends
Visa that get the voting I hope everyone
Not Furious
About something
NCAA bracket there is always going to be
We respect that
Email gmail.com
Reflections
You can check us out at knowledge fight.com
Trick where people can download the drops
I'm stuff if it really makes you want to make an electronic song
That is not now I've never been
That's knowledge fight.com
And there's a bunch of drops already up there and I'm putting more up as time goes on
But it's exhausting process
Look like
Finding these clips in my archives
CD version downloadable version of all of the songs
Better be great or copyright
Hey your copyrights
Whenever you upload
You can
It's been hard to get a flavor for who should die
Rick Derringer I don't know
Let me listen to his wife
Thanks for holding
Alex