Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Quite awhile
I just made what I gave you ever heard before.
Inspire people to listen I would say the people find a dynamic interesting between a person who spends all of their
Time studying Alex Jones
First person
Interesting
Plan for y'all's to enjoy tonight before we get into
To the show I need to make a public apology
Daniel wanted or please me
We believe it is it when we get something wrong
And we are aware of the public
I put out an article and I went and investigated the radio station
Come to the conclusion that I came to I found 32 stations
He was on the United States
However I accidentally stumbled onto another list of Alex Jones Affiliates last night
And I went through all of them
A bunch of them were not accurate they've dropped him
Great a couple and I found 10 additional stations that Alex is on
So I can read
I can reasonably say at this point that Alex Jones maybe on 42 stations in the United States
And I would like to I would like to apologize for the inaccuracy of the fur
First version of the article the article has been updated
But
Again
It doesn't matter
Pictures of Sean Hannity is on 500 something
Glenn Beck is on 500 something radio station
Rush Limbaugh's on 590 radio station 1340 is a very
In those extra 10 radio station
Is that you
You've discovered its 10% of government
The other 30 million were a we're hanging out on all makes
Yeah yeah
Hard seltzer
Which I discovered
Hard Seltzer in the world which
Do not understand.
I also don't think it's a worthy thing to hold up on a pedestal purity
Of Seltzer is that
All of these have a promise ring around them so that it's better
Good I'm not super hungover
Last time we tried to drink These Eyes they tasted like s***
Now I'd like to give a shout out
A couple of new donors what's going on out there Kevin
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much for joining up
Kevin Hart got defensive of Kevin
Yeah
I also would like to give a shout out to someone who did donate bumped it up
Very much this lady is a delight
You are now a technocrat
Someone sodomites
Set me a bucket of poop
Thank you so much Sonia
If you
Would like
Thank you so much
Sonia
You can't buy going through our website
We would appreciate it very much
Hey look Soros incoming
Public declaration
Let me be honest with you if you just want to see if you just want to put a dollar bill
Inside of an envelope
Don't
Don't put any address on there
Chances are it will show up at our
I want to make this public declaration because I think I've been wrestling with this
Okay
With depression I have no great great show sad to see it end
Is wrapping it up
But
I've come to realization that I would reject Soros money
If it was ever offer
Let's be clear
Nor will it
But I realized it just based on how easy it is to attack that I wouldn't want that to be
Piece of
Who We Are
And what the perception of what we do is
So I make this promise to the audience
We will reject Soros money if it's ever offered
And it is not there
And it would need to be to be a lot
Needville
Far out is getting really smart in the chat room suggesting that
We're just trying to beg
If we could offer us like 3 million
Dollars I would put that into a CD and let me tell you something
I would live off the in
Well that's a whole different issue
If I have enough money to create a good Financial strategy
I would do that and then I would get voting Republican operating like 60
Capital gains tax on 1.5
Have to get but I would say to point
Anyway
Got it
At $3000000 would put us up for life
True I like it.
You couldn't afford a guy got a yacht on Lake Michigan timing
We will be
Going over the April 4th
2018 episode
From Wednesday
And the boy family known as April Fool's Day
Yeah
Are you doing
Has not found
No
This show is
It is super messed up
Really stupid stuff happened the day right after the shooting at YouTube headquarters
Okay and weirdly Alex
Does not talk about that very much
He would make hay out of it but he doesn't
Except to sort of say like
Hey it's interesting that no one's talking about
Petered out a little bit
But I think that's because no one died
Except for the shooter herself
That makes it a little bit less severe we have more pressing issues
Articles
To think about how
California's gun laws
Actually probably prevented this from being
She didn't have an AR
Statistics of shown that it doesn't
You can't really stop someone
I'm from doing something like this
But you can
Limit
The number of people who
Get killed
Consistently
Is counter to his narrative about the shooting
I think it's going to infuriate you
How we start
Our investigation
Great-aunt
But this is
What happens as
Impossible
Revolution info
What do you think about that how's that grab you
Even say that
I don't I don't think that's I think he's misinterpreting and missing the club
And the f****** quotes
No
No not at all
Dubstep
He's pitching this
Is that like
YouTube's the f******
She's got
She had her videos demonetized when YouTube
Structure
I met something that's what they're well within their rights to do they didn't Banner they didn't sense her they just changed their business
This model in such a way that smaller channels
The revenue when they
Don't have ads
Videos anymore
So that
I mean it sucks for
For people I get that I have the size with that
And I think it's probably
Of YouTube in some ways but it's not
Ethically wrong it's not
Home Depot
Something that we've just accepted is corporations to do
Not necessarily exploited
Small channels that don't have ads on their videos
That you were just giving a place where they can put them up
Sure your overall traffic Rises
What is infant asthma
Compared to the big
Channels that have
Millions of subscribers and
Hundreds of Millions
The views on their videos
Exploitative in terms of expectation
Because there
Pitching this idea of a world
Where you put videos up on YouTube
If you play your cards right and your interesting
You'll make money off at a small minority
Posting videos to YouTube that make
Any reasonable amount of money of course they pitched this idea of like
This is a way that you can build an audience and build an income stream
Awesome babe
Did a lot of people are disenchanted by the idea of
Even that fantasy
Taken away from them
Yeah
It's like being in the Alex Jones sales paper mitski member
Sell it hard and then
It doesn't work out
Admittedly
Don't understand everything about this shooter or their motivation
But I will say that I was saying
Alex's pitching a stupid narrative
And she used it to shoot
Yeah there's that
That's probably a foundational problem
And the other
I'm really I'm just uncomfortable with Alex's like
This is what happens
Like
I mean it's not okay
Frankly at this point
Alright I do I understand that
Like I understand that reaction
Not given his prior comment f****** anesthetized
Constant
Unending stream of gun violence Earth at 4
Bring going on for
What
All of America
Play it's it's something that
Will not be addressed and the craziest thing is I think
There's a
There's a serious chance
If we were to
F****** do it
That we could repeal the 2nd Amendment
I bet we have more than two-thirds of states that would be willing to look at the f****** governors
I don't believe that
The legislators that have
To vote on
The governor is it today
No the governor's whenever it's like
Did in the chat room almost
Immediately
Amendment
There's no other way to repeal them
But you can't get that one off there
You have to now come up with another amendment does what that Amendment
Witch hazel
I believe it's been done
Before I has
I'm literally or literally repealed an amendment
Yeah
Sure I die just groovy I don't think
If possible
Necessary
Maybe the Supreme Court RI
Looking at
Where We Are
Which is of course and of course that's what you get
There's no real Avenue to correct it
I agree
It's mess
Always talks about the victim
Disarmament Zone
Beware shooting
Things happen
You're like school
There's no guns
School
So that's weird Shooters go
This is work
This is your work play
Yeah is are fairly common
But also
It's just a matter of people are disarmed
This Google headquarters
Security
That's why she shot through the back door to get in
Funeral
Because there's heavy security
Yeah
And so I mean it's not a disarm
RedZone it's not like a
A situation where
Hey
This suggests
Let's armed teachers
Stupid into
Disastrous world where
You're teaching people with
Thread of a gun
Go to work without
Maybe people
Your boss having a gun
Yeah it sounds like the solutions that are
Realistically proposed by either side are
Hey let's
Limit guns
Because
Where the other side is
What if everybody had a gun nobody be shooting anybody
We're legitimately pushing ever closer to the day
Deep Space 9 m m
Video becoming real
Everyone
In society in a Mexican standoff with each other
Alex talks about a new initiative
It's probably
Maybe thinking about my
I have no idea
I think this is bad and anybody else
How to be super again
He's got a sport
Resources at my other sources in the house
Uncle months ago that he's been talking to Peter
Petersfield the power garbage
Napoli's Facebook Twitter
Google
He does say oh
All these channels amplify ham
He's been briefed
Face-to-face by three people I know in the last month
Doubt this is
Volume from 11
Ouch
I have the midterms are dialing everybody
Congresswoman running for congress
And Facebook
There their they're
Yeah those milquetoast poor shooting their false flag video
And so that is the big enchilada
So it's fine cuz I look says everything's a big enchilada but also right there at the end
Trump is pushing for regulation
Big companies great idea as long as it supports
Or benefits conservatives regulation is great wonderful
Whenever it helps you
It's odd that you're not for regulation
Whatever regulation is good for you
It almost seems hypocritical Dan it look frankly
Doesn't want to put up with my b*******
The government wants to save a emission standards
Because
You know some cities are
Exactly
Some cities have unbreathable are really bad at Monopoly
Is an oxymoron
Red is not a possible thing
Well if you are a leftist
You are aware that monopolies are in
Apparently
Damaging
2nd function
Society movements
Beard
Towards bad
Economic
But that's as baby came
Authoritarian
Systems
You know it's not if you are a foreign Authority
Insist
Principal at stuff
We're going to get more into this in a minute
In a fun way
It might be fun it's fun to me
Trump
Because you love torture
I like reading things
A lot of
Text to read to you
And it comes to a head on this episode
I want to clear the air about some
Right before that episode
It's not I don't really care about that
I'm kind of sick of that too
Alex Alex Jones
Announces that
He's going to be in wash
In d.c.
But why why
Ahead and make for everyone
Infowars
Dot-com
Democrat plan to repeal 1st Amendment discovered
Alex Jones to hold press conference
On Tuesday April 10th Alex Jones
Questions from the press in Washington DC
Yep I before I can't wait to watch that
He's also going to be
3 hour press conference he's just doing his show from the Press Club I can't put it up so it's going to be amazing
But also I want to be
Be clear about this
Cuz this is something that I had to look into because of the Larry's
Sinclair research
Wheatley lunatic individual
You can just rent out the Press Club
That's why heat press conference
The Press Club to rent out a room at the Press Club
They don't have editorial oversight of like who comes
Press conference
They just allow people to do it so
Congratulations
How much does it cost
It's not it's really not cheap
Yeah that's a good point
Think we should
I think we should definitely Prescott
I'll look into it and give a Prescott
That will is Emma
Look up numbers
Free Speech lawsuits targeting First Amendment rights
National Press Club in Washington DC
Ginger room
9 a.m.
Eastern
3 hours I'm also
Press conference
Prestamos RSVP via email at
Medial infowars.com
I don't know why we
Weird weird email name for that I want to change that
And a change of the press release about their we should have like
Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious
How do you spell that is possible
ImmediaDent I do I do I just want to change it I just I just read this here I'm at work
Lompoc
Email subject line
Reno Reno
I never learned how to read
MEP what the end result of this is going to be is like
I hope someone slips through the cracks
Lincoln asking real question
But it's going to be like Jerome course he's going to be there at the question
Yeah it'll just be a Roundtable a dick
It's going to lose weight
Alex
I've heard
Your dick is huge
Can you,
No,
But yes
I have sources that excuse me
It will be understand you're the smartest child
We might have to do an emergency episode next week because this is on a Tuesday
Like we might have to
Cuz this is going to be a zoo
It's going to be the most ridiculous
I know she's trying to make it as hard as possible for the media to RSVP apparently
It we can watch it for the Press spoiler on Thursday
Thursday's show this
Cute outfit is that at that press conference
He's going to name the first
Two people he's suing
Quote on quote
Enemies of the Republic all right
Hey Tammy the enemies of the Republic I also hope we're one of them I hope
All that was a letter by now right
I'd love it
They're going to because I think it's probably the
Justin Bieber suing
I assume
Just all countersuit
The pope is going to be named in there
Because he thinks the pope is suing him
Depends on what you think of republic
It's a great restaurant
From it is a book
Anyway
In his next clip
Alex is talking about
Damn life.
The leftist
Their scourge of the world
They are
With their monopolies
And they're very repealing the First Amendment
Which you know
Peter teal
Love the First Amendment
Absolutely is never tried to infringe upon first amendment that demonstrated his commitment to
Yeah it is next clip though Alex's
Probably I guess he's
Fluent
And often
And I believe
Nope not little girl
And then I just walked all over Austin and cut stone
Knossos CCP or whatever
Shut up Grandpa
I want our bodies kill the Midwest
Reorganizing a giant bloodline
You are self-sufficient
They want to rape your wife
Whoever they want they want authoritarianism
And your children
Their religion is pedophilia
And starving you to death and murdering you
You talk about George Soros
This is troubling
If true hold on hold on
You talk about George Soros and he's like that's why they're God is
This guy but list
Is this really quick
Nazis when he was 14
60 minutes
And you would do it over again and he's not ashamed
Alex Amin
Accidentally just said thesaurus help around up Nazi
Because
He's he's just written
He's just doing his his thing
Boy that's intense
Can you imagine living in a headspace where you believed I was
True like how how much that would make an impression on
Like if you lived in a world where you thought Alex
The credible source
You thought he knew any
Hey do you think he's up there screaming about like our enemies want to watch
She would starve
And rape your wife and
Children
And create an authoritarian state
Like
That's if if that's if you believe that
Existential threat on a level of
Yes of course you would grab a gun and go to a f****** Pizza Joint
Politically
No I didn't have any choice
Like if I believe that somebody was actually trying to do that
Then the only rational
With
Guns
Whatever
No.
What do you think
It's a mess
That's not good no I think this rhetoric is incredibly dangerous
Rape your wife is incredibly dangerous
Evans next Calypso Alex Jones gets in
He gets into thesaurus
And he gets into
God stuff
They're wild Electric
He has a little bit of a breakdown on air and I think
It's really funny
Buy in some ways but it's also super not funny
Another way
So this is Mike down clip cuz you got to enjoy the
The nuances of Alex freaking out
For his stepfather and help round up
He would do it over again and he's not ashamed
If somebody else didn't do it he would have done
Another version
.
Killer
Worship
And I just think
Dark that's fun
It's enjoyed it's fun cuz of the growling and how stupid is a big fan of
Sinners in the hands of an Angry God
I mean business
This is neck
Next Level just a crock
Gosha
We've talked about Soros a bit
In the past
About how Alex is wrong about him
The collaborator
We have but we haven't talked about him
Enough
Quite frankly
Because
I just think
Look
I think that anytime you're a billionaire
You're probably a dick
There's no way around
I just think I definitely don't worship any billionaires
No as you know I'm very strong actually anti billionaire
Violently so I think it's worthwhile to always have
A default position
Skepticism
And suspicion
Of people who are tremendously well
Netflix
Sad
I think that there's more we need to talk about
As it relates to
Soros because it's not enough
That we you got you got your
Paragraphs
Right ready now don't you
Memoirs
I knew it I read some interviews with him and I have
Really important things that I think people need to know
You know people digest things better in a
That's true to make memes
Adam DeVine
The issues that I come down to is that literally everything that Alex Jones says about
George Soros
The only thing that I guess
Could be said is true
Is that he has worked
To overthrow
That's true but they were
Soviet
Revenant government
Free
Society they were oppressive regime
That existed in the crumbling of the
The Soviet Union
Do you have people like Slobodan milosevic
In Yugoslavia
That he funded
Bunch of youth group you don't want to try and take him down that's
That's bad student groups
And like
Pro freedom of speech
Which groups and pro-democracy
In Yugoslavia
He would give
He sent
Billions of dollars worth of Aid and photocopier
So they could
Create publication
Could put out
In order to
Elevate
You thought
Hey hey
Genocide Allstate
But Slobodan milosevic
Was Russia
And Alex is
Speaking the truth in some ways
That he has worked against
Government
Right but they are consist
Across-the-board
Not democracy
Now in places where are old Pals Kissinger in
The entire United States
Worked tirelessly to overthrow democratic government
If you want to go into f****** Iran
We are the ones
Who made that dictatorship
That is all
Democratic Republic
Think that
It's telling us all of their oil with such a great idea
Trust the United States
What hundred percent right
Right there
Because I thought
There is that
But if you look at cirrhosis history
That's not the
Necessarily that he's been involved
Have you opened
Yeah
I'm not saying all of their history is perfect
Rebels against a
Evil dictatorship
I'm kind of Envoy
The reason of my chair looks the way it does is because
Celine climbs on the top of it and tears it all apart
So if it bothers you I'm sorry
I'm having a very aggressive cat
Hey happen
Back sore throat
When Alex is talking about in that clip
He enjoyed that
He was under Nazi occupation
Yeah when he was
Perhaps 13 years old
It's really important
Contacts
Now it's never does
And when he's in that clip threatening to
Play the entire sea
60 Minutes interview
You know God damn well he's not going
Because it would reveal the contents
I know I want to further elucidate that context
Because I
The really important
To speak about
In the face
Of this
Aggressive
Buganda
Also really quick one other really important
To consider is
You were talking about the
The crumbling of the Soviet Union
Funding initiatives
For democracy and free
Free speech
Freedom in Ozark
Doing a lot of that stuff
About Russia
I am.
There might be a correlation
Back back to this other issue
Soros is talking about the best year of his
His life
It relates back to how much
He loves his daddy
And I want to talk to you a little bit about some comments that he made about
What is that in an interview
That I think are elucidating
I am very
He volunteered in the first World War
He was promoted to Lieutenant
He was then taken prisoner of war
On the Russian front
Concentra Siberia
You still very ambitious
The editor of the newspaper called the
It was written by hand and nail to apply
The Authors Hit behind the plank
Listen to the comments of the reader
I remember seeing the collective copies of the
The blank is a child he brought them home from
From Siberia
Then
He was elected prisoner's representative
Some prisoners escaped in the neighboring
Camp in the prisoners representative was shot
Retaliation
He decided to be better to escape than
To be shot for other people
He selected 30 people for their skills
Carpenter cook doctor and so on
Because he had no practice
Call skills
And they broke out of
He had a plan to build a raft
The drift down to the ocean mistake because his geography was somewhat deficient
He didn't realize that all the rivers
Siberia emptied into the ark
Ocean
They built this wrapped
They floated down the river
And it took them quite a few weeks
Who discovered they were heading for the Arctic Ocean
Finally they realize that they would have to make their way through the wilderness
Civilization
That took them several months
And because the revolution they were caught up in the turmoil of the region
At that time
A check officer ruled Siberia from
Armored railroad car
There were Reds and white
And they kept on killing each other and killing the population
He went through some horrendous experience
The talking the value of
Being alive
So now
To the point of this specific
Piece of
I'm talking about the best year of his life
Being that gear
Is that
And forged papers.
To live with this guy
Who went around and catalogued
Possessions of
Not rounding up
Is that party completely
This quote is
Is relevant
The German occupation came in March 19th
I was not yet fourteen
That was my father's finest hour
Because he knew how to act
He understood this
Situation he realized that the normal rules did not apply
Obeying the law became a dangerous at
Flaunting it was the way to survive
Having experienced the Russian Revolution
He knew what to do
He made arrangements
For the family to get false identity papers
Found places for us to live or
Where to hide
He helped not only his immediate family but a fairly large number of other people around
I can truthfully say that he saved us
Signs of live
This is a. Of exciting Adventure
I could go on and on about it because it's
Etched into my memory
Although I rarely talk about it
The importance of paradoxical point
The 1944 with
The happiest year of my life
It's a strange and almost defensive things
To say because 1944's
The year of the Holocaust
But it's true
I was 14 years old
I had a father whom I adored
It wasn't Commando
Do the situation
Who knew what the
To do and who helped others
I was aware of the danger but I felt vulnerable
I was aware of the stuff around us
But we did everything we could to help others
Just to give you a small example used
Stand in line
A cigarettes
They were Distributing five cigarettes
Per person and then give them to Jews who were
Restricted from Jewish houses
Current lineup
Perhaps the only time I was physically affected
It was immediately after the siege of Budapest
When they were lots of corpse
Just lying about
There was one
It's call Bash.
I felt sick for days after
Phuc yea
This is
Absolutely
And part of it was
Because of his
Experience
Do you suffer.
Repressive
Russian regime
Goddamn so that informed
His father's life
An intern
The entirety of Soros
George Soros
And
It's really really bulshit
To try and claim this
Soros is trying
Create some sort of
Authoritarian state or is it
Communism
Or anything like that
I have pulled up some quotes of his
Cuz now not only is
Like prior to this I just assumed that
I saw roses.
Yeah I was just trying to go along to get along
And
Alex's of course as is exploiting the fact
That his dad was just trying to
To survive
And keep the sun alive
To learn that
Alex Jones is
Literally
F****** destroying the accomplishments of a genuine hero
Anderson
To any of this
He knows it
And he's willfully misrepresenting
The alternative
Which is more like
To the point of Soros being in favor of communism
I will redo some quote
I'd live through Nazi persecution and Soviet occupation
Poppers book Karl Popper
Surah study
Philosophy
When he was in high school at
He considers himself
Philosophy
Kind of quiet
Alright a book open Society
The force of a revelation
It showed that fascism
Communism have a lot in common
And they both stand in opposition to
The different principle of social organization
The principle of an open
Society
Hey my philosophy
Open Society is based on the recognition that we all act on the basis
Perfect understand
Nobody is in possession
End of the ultimate
Therefore we need a critical mode
We need
Tuitions and rulers that allow people with different opinions and interests
To live together in peace
We need a democratic form of government that is
Pictures that the orderly trance
Power we need a market economy
That provides feedback
It allows mistakes
To be corrected
We need to protect minority
Respect minority opinion
Above all we need the rule of law
Ideologies like fascism
Communism
Close Society
In which the individual is subjugated
Society is dominated by the state
Anastasia's and service of a dog mother claims
Anybody else
In such a society
There is no freedom
I knew the Communist Dogma was false
Because it was a Dogma
If Noah if one could Foster Alternatives open the door for other ideas
The falsehood of that Dogma will become obvious
By undermining the Dogma one would
Inspect weaken the regime
I did not expect its communist system
Collapse
But I did want a week
From within by making Alternatives available
And supporting critical
Right
So that's kind of couch
To the way that Alex
Resent
His philosophy
Pretty much
And the same time Alex
Will suck Putin
For sure because he's a male
Strange how that works out
Yeah
So I read an article from the early to
About Georgia
From La time
Sources efforts in Yugoslavia that's talking about
Student groups fighting against
Slobodan milosevic
Football off of it
Just a small part of its enormous Financial
Support over the past decade
The first time zone
The first
First
At first tens of millions and hundreds of millions of year for democratically Mighty groups throughout the former communist world
This work which got its branch in Belarus expelled from that country tonight
Has helped strengthen the thousands of nonprofit organizations
In countries where 1989 communist parties ran almost
Soros help
Find Independent Media in Serbia
The dominant Republic of Yugoslavia 2
Powerful State television
Which function
As a mouthpiece
For milosevic
As communist country is communist control disappeared
Resurgent nationalism ethnic
Intolerance pressure
On free speech and authoritarian rulers
I threatened hopes for democracy
Soros.
The antidote
Strong citizen organization
Respect for civil liberties in minority groups
The rule of law and the growth of Market
So the little bit frustrating not
Doing it
To the same extent
It's in our
Essential
Fascist
Capitalism
I think it's trying
In some ways
This is not a Soros sucks
It's not it's just to say that
This perception that Alex is
Creating of him
Wheatley wrong
On so many very intrinsic
Level
Enjoying
Will being a Nazi
Collaborator isn't true cuz he wasn't a Nazi collaborator
And the parties talking about enjoying
Is
Getting to
Experience
How capable and heroic
His father was
And how much he loved his father's heroism
In the face
All the totalitarian system
To murder them
And how his father went out of his
His way in order to help
Strangers
Help other people
Will Survive
Now to tid of it
Like
I mean Alex
Also talked about that he wants to overthrow Israel
And you talk about habits in the Wikileaks considering Israel is a
What
Tomorrow or Friday going to wind up killing hundreds of Palestinian
I'm kind of overthrowing Israel at this point is real is real government
Fascist
Can government wants to overthrow Israel and it's very important
Come to point out that
Misrepresenting
What'd you find
If you read the actual
Text
That got leaked emails
That were hacked
Everybody knows that
Recent years the radicalization of public opinion
Attractive Israeli right-wing government
Has resulted in more restrictive measures
Palestinians
There have been numbers
Successes in challenging Israel's racist
Anti-democratic
National Arena
Influencing
EU
Is real bilateral negotiations
He's talking about is
If you want to
You push for
A knot
Racist state
I am
The issue is that people believe
I think
Vet
Respecting Palestine
Would get rid of these
The Jewish character of the Israel
Israel as a state
I don't know what to say to that
I would say
Stop
Stop killing people for the longest time it was always a
Loaded
Kind of conversation to
To be like
Israel but I don't like what they're doing and at this point is real
Government
Not these really people although
V Israel Israel's government is very popular with you Israeli
Three people but they are now a genocide.
More
So
F*** anybody who considers it a complicated question
Write that but they don't consider Palestinians
Within is real they consider Palestinian
Every single Palestinian
To be a rogue sticks
And they are treating them as though they are at War
It's like I said Friday there's going to be a demonstration
50000 + Palestinian
And the Israeli Army is going
2 kill
Hundred.
I would that is a guarantee
We can't predict that but it does seem
Like it's the most likely out to the high probability
Whatever whatever the case is there I want to
Focus more in on
Thesaurus claim
Because all of them are
The crashing economy stuff isn't
If you look into it one of the big things is
Is nickname is the man
Who broke
Do the bank of Europe England
Yeah and that's because
He recognized the situation where
Sitting made a billion dollars
Everybody's like
Aldi's market
Trend ahead of
I would bet against whatever it is America
Economy is doing right now
Going to collapse
Let's go hard
So hard
I have a lot of
Weird protect
Seems like sort of thing or you'll have like a really bad fight
Little
Who knows we're not economic experts.
Be over
We're throwing government
If you want to take that very Loosely UK
Conseil
That
Yes you did work
To try and help democratic
Organization
Within
Former Communist States
So that's not really
The crew said about it being a Nazi collaborator isn't
It was the best time of my life that's not true
And I want to read this last quote because
I think it really is important
And that is
Quote
You may consider it weird
But in my view it is an essential feature of an open society that not everything
We should be to my like
If I tried
Control the content of every program
He's talking about things that I would not be creating an open Society
So right
There's a well in our
Is as
Something that is
The seemingly impossible
For people that
To understand
It is not
Conservative
Or anything along those lines
The point is that there is no conversation
Whenever you're not admitting that there's a problem
Like
If a conservative voice wants to come in
And argue what the best
Way to deal with climate
Changes
That is a conversation that an open Society can have
Sure about the best way to deal with this problem
But when you deny it's a problem
You are killing me
Add when you deny it's a problem in mysteriously
You work for an organization
As $500,000 of funding
ExxonMobil Koch Foundation
The jet like that
When you deliberately mislead people in order to make money
You are a bad person on a
Genuine love
Mary goes back to the
Impossibility of argue
Man who is coming from a place of
That's some of the stuff I wanted to talk about about George Soros
I'm not saying you're defending him but like everything he's done is been ethical and perfect
Jimin FF
She has a
You know I lived
The very difficult life
Beginnings and
I was able to become
Really good at predicting
Financial Trends in Mayfield
And have given
A lot of it back to
Two causes that
Most right
Yeah but be that as it may Alex Jones
That he wants to jack off to help or you are in
And that's what our next Play Store
On purpose this is what they do
Because they just want to murder people
Good people
And I get to have their way
Once you understand that then you understand
Pharaoh's wants to do one thing
Overthrow countries destroyed economy
Sandstone
Skid Row
I don't know how that relates anything
I don't know it doesn't
I don't know
Trying to create Elementals in the lake
The pretty f***** up stuff but like if you
But yeah yeah
I've done it say Emma is
Boils down to do what thou Wilt that is
The whole of the law right but it also
Good provision
About like
You can't just do thing
Thanks people
That that
Violate variability
Duet
They will
Well currently the Satanist churches the best Christian organization out there
Yeah
They're the only ones
Skip this next court because it's just Alex pretending
He's going to play the entire sea
60 Minutes interview
I'm a dozen
Because of course he can kind of experience
Interrupt
It doesn't go cuz he's not playing at all
No he plays a cut that they made
Between different interviews
Referring to
Something that you
That the endgame territory
2007 S10 dimensions
George Soros
Terms of
Politics in America since
At least the 90s
Joe Alex says that when he was a kid
His mom
I would be watching TV
Sing about George Soros being evil and s*** like that
So according to when Alex was a kid
According to Alex
His own version
His own life
You should have been aware of Soros
He was a child
But mysteriously you not in his
Documentary that he made about the globalists and the game for society
Weird
Maybe it was because it wasn't
More on that in the future
Teaser
Looking into that a little bit
I can't
How many times have we talked about the pointlessness
Appointing out the Hip Hop
Of these f***
Being assholes not about hypocrisy
About like
To destroy infrastructure
He wants to keep you high and and pouring all of those things
And you look
Literally
Policy decision that the current Trump f****** Government is made
Bears out
Line by line
Lego
Infrastructure issues riding like a works progress administration
How many of these f******
Thinks he's going to describe
Globalists are doing that you can draw
Parallel to what Trump is doing
The best globalist
See what you what you don't understand
You stupid
You sir are a fool
That's a good pointers why I didn't consider that you do not understand
The infrastructure sure we've got Bridges collapsing
We got a lot of problems roads if on the road
We got a lot of those problems
Exist some people are Christian
Weird
Conservative Christian ideals
And that is a f****** problem as that's what the globalists are real that's where you really need to fight the globalist
Because
Look dude
As long as women don't have access to healthcare f***** Bridge
You're right
Priority
You have to understand
I feel like I'm a big enough man to admit when I'm
I appreciate that
Try to get in the Waterfront
People like that
I have a financial incentive to do it but
Believe me
It's just
Let's listen to this again because I think it's no fun either way his
Not on purpose
Almost like he's ashamed
The waterfront
Whataburger
So Alex has
This is very much like
People
People of the ratings go up when I do it
Chinese f******
Subaru I don't think they do go up
Even even is a shame is alive
I think what he's talking about is the people scream about like whatever he screams people posted
Adorama
Just like that
He gets a lot of you gets run off traffic from people
Will Faking outrage about it
Alex
It's going to be hateful
Who knows
A the worst they have all these but Alex
You know Facebook snowtorious for its Lefty policy
Absolute interesting theory about that
Where they come from though
Authoritarian
Shut up
Understand
Did it
They can't
High School
They all want to end up
Being cool and so the system
System creates a system
Wait I don't understand
What.
There's more to this clip but he's saying that these leftist weren't cool in high school
They are because
Alternative if you are cool
Neither of you seem like great Prospect
What's the best
What's what's the best thing to be
High School I don't know bang out 150 women in-depth an abortion
Crack a couple times at a beach
I don't know baby
So there's that
Or just moderate levels serving
Sadistic
You just making stuff up
Dominic
We're really
Celebrate
Possible
Young Thug
Wish.com
Talking about
I don't even know what
Give me
An example of anything near what it is
I think it's just
So a runoff from like
Pick-up artist
Website
Men's rights
Right like I don't know I don't know what that means a real Alpha is that gif
Body trying to create bigger systems
That doesn't make sense
And if you were if you were if you were treated as a beta male but in reality mentally you were in Alpha
Randomly throwing
He seemed drugged up a little I think he's just
Took too much Super Mario Land had a little too much
Testosterone
When you have a freak out that early
You've got a lot of show left
Yeah sorry I think he's going to places like
I can feel time
He calls in
The helper
Ranger Michael
I will never not love that he's called the health Ranger
Does not advocate for a lot of things that are like
Help healthy
He's a vaccine
Right
Either either nonsense
Copilot
He said something a little bit
Made it to Ranger
He doesn't have to do
He said something a little later that is
Very troubling
Applications you need to become a park ranger
I think it's just a pain I think it's a
I've been becoming a to have a f****** degree you have to spend it like it's incredible I was
Looking into it cuz I was like
I like Mike Adams case I think
No it's just a fun nickname
And that is in how to butter Alex up
And make sure that this interview goes totally fine
This is something
I didn't even mention I was going to mention this but
Reasons that you're on
Awakened
And so able to process information is because your Health Products
Actually
Greatly enhance
Neurological and cognitive function
This leads to a half-hour influential
Your products
Make you our audience
More pliable
That is healthy
They make you susceptible to repetitive
The other reason that
One of the main reasons
Mike Adams is on the show is because he his
Yes he's the only Infowars guests with a non stupid name
Boy howdy if you want to know about natural news and like Adams you could look into it a very rich history
Birtherism Lake website
For some reason they're posting articles about
The Boston bombing being fake and
Calpers
Unhealthy to not be born in America
He staked his claim here that he is really Furious
Where you going after David
That sounds right
He has made a website called
Dot-com
Now
He had to spell it with two G's right
Because
Regular right I would assume
If you go to this website it's basically it's basically a
News websites that are all written by a couple of his employees for natural news
And if all I want is a live web stream of whatever it is David Hogg
Website that's created to harass
Remember the park battle whenever those eggs
I want the same thing
Unfortunately this website
I'm going to read you some of the headline
The hard-hitting news that's being done here on hogwash
If you enter the public Arena of ideas prepare to get burned
Great
Great good article
That's a headline
Another headline yet more proof that universities are social justice terrorist training camps
Another headline
Dear David Hogg you're a lying opportunistic insufferable little toe tag
A headline
NRA board member Ted Nugent called Parkland student activists
Liars quote have no soul
Hey bro you adopted a seventeen-year-old so you could f*** her without her parents having anything
To say about it
He's probably calm down
Nugent
The Rockstar lifestyle.
What's going on here
This guy is created
Entire website
Faced on harassing and
Calling out
Bulshit
I'm putting those articles their headlines I don't care to read the f****** content I don't even want to know what's in there
Weather headlines
Personal insults
Or I hate
You're getting little boy twerking to f*** you up
All that succeeds in doing is
Is not
We throw shade at David Hogg
This doesn't advance
Either side of
The gun debate
Poop face
Distant
Possibly endanger David Hogg
Like really
If you think about it
The only thing that this can do is radicalized
People who might
Hurt him
And I don't I don't think that's a good thing
You can come up with some pawns like
Really really lean into it
Stuff right there
On this on this episode
Phil come on
So pretty much the rest of the episode Alex is talking
With Mike Adams
AKA Valparaiso
And
Alex makes
This guy
That you wants to be clear
Only you can prevent vaccine
Alex
Global is the vampires
Everybody wants to be clear by
Not literally
Movie zombies at the bottom
Some of that
Animes about vampires above that
So
We got zombies Gremlins G Pires zombies
Want to eat your brain
Gremlins can't feed him after midnight
Unfortunately last week on Alex Jones Show on March 20th
Night he was sitting around with a gentleman by the name of Doug Hagmann
I replayed it on the show already
You can find it on
Bestbuy.com
ITunes is glitching
Play it
Explains that he believes
That the
Elite
Want to put
People's blood so they can drink it
Narrative
Right
They need this is a busy need to spike it
They can't they can't just drink it straight Dan
Baptist East vet like
We have two situations
Going on
And I just did Alex
Smaller things
If you want to talk about
Look like
Literal literal vampires
You can go down the literal vampire Road and then you are a
You're a f****** idiot
Because you can look at
Science about
Weather adrenaline in blood changes
Your effect
Happens when you drink it
It's been done and doorbell doesn't get you high
Hunter S Thompson wrote about it
Made up book made up a lot of
The adrenochrome stuff a bunch of other
Literary fix
But it doesn't it doesn't
It doesn't work out
Hogwash
Mature hogwash you got the literal version
You f****** stupid
Right
Metaphorical vampires
Go to Vegas
To even being any
You're not staying s***
You're just talking.
Mischaracterizing people in trying to demonize them without actually making a
Antique lamps
You can go
Directions
Fascinating but Alex
Smashing
Is Alex doing
They're both stupid but I was like
I don't want people to think I'm doing both
I kind of
And that's what he does
Dip your toes in the boat world
So
Is beta website
About David Hogg
As we discussed
Complaints about
People bullying
We're standing up to bullies
Our fourth amendment rights
You don't think that we have a right to exist and I say
Do you tie rented nbcnews
We are standing up
High School
Condor Summit High School
Of even our Riders
Receiving death threats
BBC News
Controlled who want to take us off the air
So you're saying that
You haven't received
I'd like to read to you from an article
This article
Just become one of the most recognizable faces
Cuz of the Parkland shooting
But it's famous
Into a dangerous
Situation for his
Received numerous alarming deathreats
From individuals both
In and outside of the country
So is Mother Rebecca Baldrick contact
The FBI after she got it
Disturbing message
She should have had enough
According to p.m.
You should have had an abortion one user wrote your son is a psychopathic douchebag
Drive the whole family over a cliff
Just admit failure
O'Doyle rules
Another user threatened her saying quote never change your face
Your whole family is
Suppose because of your peace
The ship kid
By the way his whole plan has backfired on
I'm sure his birthday celebration
Interesting event
F*** you and him God bless the NRA and the right to bear arms
Rock crab
Stuck with idiots
Styx
So you saying it's the next step removed
From getting a death threat
And the reality of the
World
Promoting
Creating a website entirely about harassing
Bowie David Hogg
Memes like
You don't understand
Tale of the influence
What's your playing with
Like these people are pathetic
This is
This to me is inhuman
Behavior and it's absolutely
Before anyone Compares me to Alex when he
Literally says people are human
I don't mean that
I mean this
Is
Intrinsically lacking events
It is intrinsically lacking of
Respect for other people's autonomy
Their individuality
And the fact that they exist
If not as a thing
But as a person
Android like
You're complaining about your imagined
First Amendment rights being trampled on
They aren't
Can you compare that to
At the same time
You are allowed
I have a website
Specifically
Casting aspersions
On a seventeen-year-old
Who is literally getting hundreds
The death threats
All the time
And then bitching
About how you feel
Right it's the softest s*** in the world
Yeah it's very pathetic
I don't
That's your first instinct as an empathetic human being
Is to then lose empathy and be like
Like that's
That's my first instinct is like we don't want these people in
Living
.
You were child
Because the child is like
Hey my friends.
Yeah my friends were murdered
The death
Murdered
It's just
It's not
It's not acceptable to them respond to that with a complete lack of them
Because these people are our goings I've like
There's something wrong
Something very seriously wrong with somebody who is okay
With typing off a message
That says
I want you to die
Yeah it is not okay
We've not done
A good enough job of
Not dealing with cuz I don't really know how you deal with it we stick it
We should have years ago
We probably gamergate was the
Well know that wasn't
The beginning other than that was the warning shot
I think that what it is
I don't know you want to take things seriously
We should have seen this coming
With the internet
As Services where you could
Anonymously example
Play a character in
Stuff like that
Asthma
True back on AOL
Screen names on messenger
Friendship
We evolve
To quickly from a technological
And we didn't recognize
The Reef
Repercussions of the ramifications of it
4 Ardis
And
Absolutely
Flipside is really biting Us in the ass now
Kind of
On it on a macro level
Understandable
Because when you think about it when you think about previous generation
You do you go back to talking the greatest generation
Their lives
Material
Work
All that differ
From their parents
Which word
The
Acceleration of differ
It's to the point where
My life is completely the
Thousand percent difference
From somebody who is five years younger
My life is completely different
Growing up in a situation where
I think someone is 29 is probably pretty close
Well you and I are very close
Yeah but consider somebody who grew up
When Twitter was Domino
Like as compared to grow up when the internet was exactly
Even the same thing as like
I don't know why my mind drifted to p***
The difference between
You coming up when the internet was just like you could
Slowly upload pictures on it
High-speed capabilities into
Tube sites and stuff like that
Like even fat
Now you now
You apply that level of difference
Munication
Absolutely
To the wrong place I don't know why but
The driving force behind so many
Spreads attack not like one of the things that
Occurred after
Like shortly after the invention of the printing press
What are the main reason
Isn't that so many people
Like that was that was one of the ways that
That's those so many of those intellectual books were spread through the same Underground
Principio Mathematica
We spread through the same underground Network as
F******
But Alex would stare at 4 hours was around back then
So Jordan
First long-form films
That lasted you know you've you go back to the 1910s
Well it lasted eight seconds and that was a miracle
Simultaneously
Like simultaneously the other films that last
We're a dude f****** a lady in a
SMS
We got to move on to this neck
Sorry
I don't got a long and storied history and if you look into it it's
Really very
No for sure
Can I see a cigarette from you
Thank you for a perp
Yeah I would like a cigarette but also I'm asking you.
Because cigarettes
Are carcinogenic
And they cost
Cancer
Mike Adams
The health Ranger
Had some thoughts about cancer
Guitar
A little truck a little troubling thoughts about
They know that you have cancer which is usually a fraud
Medical Health
Therapy is chemo brain
The damages your brain function
Damages your heart and your liver
You undergo chemotherapy
Which is why by the way one of our Supreme Court Justices
But she underwent chemotherapy
Chemotherapy which is based on chemical weapons
Yeah she needs sheep she's just trying to hang in there so she can keep you know the liberal agenda going but
Oh boy
Ruth Bader Ginsburg
Has
Written
Recent absolvement of guilt from from a police off
Officer f****** acting with impunity when the Supreme Court to be like
I didn't know he was breaking the law so that's
Ruth Bader Ginsburg
This and any was brilliant
Truly brilliant writer
Read
Chemotherapy
And I mean it is a poison
You know it is much
Cuz you have to write it's a drastic measure it Italy
And that's the issue with a lot of
Medicine
It's like that famous bowls
Health science articles where they write about how
People use a scientist doctor's used malaria
To help fight HIV
Like that kind of level of
Sometimes in order to kill something
You have to
Use something that kills
It reminds me of the show House m.d.
It's a far more relevant
There was a commercial For an upcoming episode but I'll never forget
House by the way
I knew that from your smart
From your Harrison 40in smart
It's a great show episode
The preview was
In order to
Favorites page
Overdrive
Adelaide
I got it I got it
Hugh Laurie is so good
The only podcast
Now cuz I'll be God damned if I know what's going on half the time for importantly the issue that I have
Okay so
Now
Mike Adams
Introduce the worldview where
The opinions of
Anyone who's gotten chemotherapy are disqualified because they can't think anymore
Usually actually just as something to convince you you have
Scam
Amazing
This is the level of stuff like when I said I don't want to get into like
The natural news
Mike Adams
Probably because I knew that clip
Who's coming up right and partly because it's
Medical nonce
We would have another hour of the show by when
His f****** resume audiology
Putting people with hearing aids
And I remember when one person came in and they were like
Well I'm not going to see you for a long time we're going to Florida
If we had a my daughter and I asked
Have Lyme disease
And we're going to go see a
Ternative medicine
Therapist
And I was like
No
GoNoodle
Are you idiot
It'd be good
Even if you don't trust him go and then go to the other guy too
Well but they're going to convince you that you have double lines
That's what
Yeah so you know
Mike Adams a talking a lot of bulshit and
Running websites
Fiscally design
Harasses 70
Funeral
Low super adult about why
My people are attacked
If they were really strong they wouldn't mind our voices being out there because we would be unconvincing to people
The reason
You are making so much sense that you're awake
You are a danger to their agenda
I would posit that the reality is
Is it yours Spitta
Propaganda
Appeals to
Bass
The people are very worried about the implication
Ofsted proper
Buganda and how it seems
Have its roots
Sandwiches and white nationalism
Christian identity movement those sort of thing
You know generally when you look it up
End result
Is generally
Murdering minority
I'm so that's really it and end your argument is persuasive
Because you play on their fears
Is it the same way
Do you know you present yourself
The populist
I mean they are able to
Trigger people
Reality
That's not who you are at all
Say this all the time I absolutely dis
Despised
The word
The pop
Yeah it is it is a
Disgusting moniker that is
Thrown about in order to
Invalidate
I really really don't
What what we should use the word we should
Use it
These guys
Case is
Fascist f****** moron
That's one word
Okay I made it
Will get that into Webster's
I love that line though the the idea that like a tech
What happens
That was true
We are in Desperate days
One of the reasons that you're stupid
The next trip is going to be controversial
I will take on it but I think is actually all
Alternative
YouTube
My
Like the Smashing
What a lot of people have a position on this
Attacking Alex
I'm going to
Unpopular League defend him
A little bit afterward
Classic Denton
Be the guardian of everything and
Somebody keeping people on Trump
That's not what happened
Border
Which is exactly
Supposed to be
Visiting inside baseball
Real quick
I'm going to go ahead and
Just deal with this ahead of Alex
Seth bullshitted
But
He's talking about Trump
Troop
To the Border
It's in response to a national
Yeah it's in response
Service ideas
Does a caravan have like 1000
Central America recognizing
Pretending
It's a group
The does the to raise awareness
Of the plight of people in Central America
And they've done this
20 temp
It's a it's a
Dispersed
Caravan
The idea that Trump is
Responding
Intuit
In a way that's so opportunistic
So
Triggering of races
That part I'm really again and I'm again
The idea of putting military On the Border
In order to
Defend against
Immigrant
Or what
But
I need be very clear about this
Because a lot of people
Tons of articles about this
Happy birthday saying that Alex is such a
F****** hypocrite
Because he would scream about the Posse Comitatus Act
And about how the
Military
Supposed to operate
Plastic soil
In terms of domestic
Operate
Right hand.
Enforcing law enforcement
Stop in the United States
Rubicon Crossing
To the Constitution
It says
In terms of the armed services
Quote to provide
Calling forth
The militia
To execute the laws of the Union
Suppress interact
The repel invasion
I think it's insulting
Statement in an Uber
Insinuate that these immigrants
Coming up our
Invasion
This is not the part I'm just
Yeah the part I'm defending
The Posse Comitatus
It's very clear
Then what they're talkin about
The army
And the Air Force
They are not talking
About the National Guard
The National Guard
Very clearly
Can be called a
If
The state Governor allows
The state Governor has two welcome
The used
Of the National Guard in their state
And then it's okay for them
To operate
In terms of
It has been done in the normal thing when you when you hear
They called in the National Guard right that's exactly what that mean
I took the idea that Trump is sending the National Guard
Enforced
The border is
Troubling
But it's not hypocritical for Alex
To be okay with that
And not be okay with
Let's de Jade House
Even though Jade Helm Osaka
Stupid now is wrong about that
It's not a
Complete contradiction
Of his principal
The way a lot of people representing
Because it is the National Guard
It's not
The same thing
Also I understand but and strongly disagree with his idea that
The South the people to protect
But if that were the case
Dushyanth does they the military camp
And then further
The Posse Comitatus Act
Does allow
The presidents
To unilaterally
The federal laws are being broken
And they can use
Is the military it has been done in the past
Like the white eyes and
An hour
Bringing in troops
To allow for the segregate segregation
The school stuff like that
The president does have unilateral Authority
To break
Comitatus
Now Alex would never give that leeway to any other president
And so it's hypocritical of him to be okay with the sort of thing
It's it's
Trend against
He stood for in the past
But if we're being totally fair to him
It's not
It's not what people are making it out to be
You are a scholar of Alex Jones
And I would bet
All of the money that I've ever made
And have
That he that if you look for it you could find a clip where he said bringing in the Nash
National Guard
Is
Illegal or whatever we look through all of the years that Obama was President
You would find that
Yeah and in that case yes
We could point out the literal of hawk
But again as we've gone over it
Matter
And
I don't think could you sing this based on Prince
But
We
To be fair
Our mission statement
To paint him in a bad light for things
He doesn't deserve
And I'll defend him against
Bike
These like articles that I've seen
Post that I've seen
He's abandoned Olive
Is Prince
Because he's okay with
The National Guard
His principles
This is this I think is
For real
A little bit later bike Adam says
Is it because of
So many immigrants
In California they should
Have their senators and Congress people taken away which is Adams is the dumbest motherfuker I think I've ever heard it's not good
This is insane
Next clip
Let me ask you a
Academy
Sell a product of some sort that he claims
Will
Cure can
I'm almost certain
I can't confirm or deny that but I suspect
Yeah
Send a text with
Alex Jones
The liberal meme
Oh that liberal media
Very specific way
But I'm actually eight
I know exact
Actually what are you talkin about
Pretty interesting
This Is War
21st century
Coffee
Alex Jones and Sean is a captive
Squash
Start in Sinclair broadcasting is that whole thing and never been on one
Not one Sinclair station TV station
They just pushed
You saying that the leftist media is saying
The only person
Who is made both of those claims
Is his ex-wife
He is trying to say that things that Kelly has
Quit it out from her own account
He's describing them to the leftist media
She tweeted out the towers got his start on
Sinclair radio
And I do not believe that
No that doesn't
I don't know for sure and I will Cop 2
The fact that
She was around then
You may have a better awareness that I do
S****** f****** signs a contract details
To come out of my position would change
But from everything I can tell from the Reeser
Search that's available
Alex Jones
Existed on
JFK
Sponsors
Network
And then when he got fired
He got picked up and syndicated
Play home radio station
He was running
Aunt Jen
I don't know if there's any
Sinclair
Influence that I can
Confined
In his
Early days of radio
Did learn about it
But it does
Like this
Is more capitalized
On the fact that people
Complaining
Sinclair come up
Now of all time
Right because there was that video that of all the people saying the exact same thing
Jump on it which again
That video
Exact same thing it was on John Oliver like a year ago
Think everyone getting like
Massively
Retweet this good good
Let's get more awareness about that but don't pretend
Is the first timer
But be that as it may
I think it's very disgrace
Things that is
Ex-wife is tweeting
Liberal media
Well she's been compromised by the globe
Well I
Now
His son has probably been brainwashed and is used as a
Probably not Sinclair Sinclair media behind that
That's another thing I don't have this clip there's another point where
Hitman Mike
You're talking about the YouTube
YouTube shooting
Heather talking about how they
Hey was YouTube taking away all these people's channels
Did you know they're putting their employees at risk
Shootings like this could happen with people who have had their livelihoods taken away
Do you not see the 121 parallel of putting your son on air in Aiken
Contentious gun debate issue
They're the way you're putting him at risk
But I don't understand because
Dissonance
It's their butt
Who knows
Should be the name of Alex's
Attribute tattooed on his f******
Can forehead
Called cognitive call cognitive dissonance
We have a couple clips left
Yeah in this next clip Alex
Pretend he's going to DC they only do Highwaymen
The great is there Alex McCabe
Covers of covers
So that means talkative isthmus
In this in his neck with Alex pretends that the reason he's going to do
He's going to do a parlay
Stringer Bell
Call Will
Either going to keep trying but I I know
And being here in person with you and it being on a similar
Battle pass
You cannot be bought with money or so far
Liberty bar country with money
Doesn't matter how big the weekend by Mac Miller.
Art operations
I mean I know nothing's for sale you know
We know you think you don't
Like what
Everybody knows those aliens are from a different planet
The CIA told me the story
Play right there
Launch into the bet
He's about to launch into that old Street
The CIA goes in there and they're like you have to kill your wife
And she pulls the trigger and she finds out it's a blank so she has to beat her husband to death
The old B
Is it older the doctor was
Yeah absolutely I don't think by the way
Noah, can I can't remember his
Dave Jake
Lozes with that great job
Also he's
The transfer I will never work with him again
Big
Big-name
Comedian
Close
Big Show
Bertha Street joke
One time I was like
Who was it
I am I going to say
I would say as to that
Clip
That's not what I
Alex's doing he was about to try and launch a
To some fake
Story that he is
Sound like a you know I'm going to give you the inside
Hireright
Yes he couldn't get the details of the bluff
He was about to
Better to make this
Conspiratorial
It's disgraceful
I'll leave it there so you guys think I've ever spoken to a CIA
Robert David Steele
Child Slaves by the globalist
It's the other aliens that we need to be worried about
We can take you to Mars come on man you know what's fun about a lot of Alex
Gast
Their past
Are unverifiable
Superfund
Fitbit super f*** the way they even like doctor group says he's involved in secret program
No way to confirm that
About everything huge fan of Alex just
Anytime somebody says something absolutely crazy they all just sign off overnight likes
Just like
This delicious
I did this piece
Of
Good
S*** what was it
No it's gone
Keep track of all the thoughts and therefore sometimes
Something about the globalist
Stalin
Who's that
No it wasn't selling it was a
No no it was the Italian
Dictator who always made the report
Was it Mussolini locksmith
Auto Care
That's terrible
I'm sorry Goodrich
Certainly made up
Burglary
I appreciate your attempts to somehow try and save me
Forgetting what I was trying to say
To do with
Appreciate you immediately
I'm happy about it
In this next clip this is our last
Alex Jones
In the middle of talking about how the globalist
Not recruiting George Washington
Because he was one of the best
He was
He was one of the best in the business
That's just for contacts
Because of what I just said is
How far
Global Sumerian times
As far as I can tell
That seems like a good time
Transdimensional demon idea that Alex is telling about like that's how the globalist get their marching orders
Then yeah you could go back to like reading stitching
And thinking about you
This dumb idea about the Anunnaki and what happened
I didn't start all the way back
But because they have time travel and can
Communicate with inter-dimensional beings
They could have gone back in time
And got George Washington
But I'm going to go with Bill and Ted's
They Coulda got George Washington to go to man
Is not a great guy is about
How Jeff Bezos has sort of a googly eye
And
How to breathe
A little bit of a cross-eyed man I found this to be
Marine creature of the deep with iPods
Agenda
So Alex says you can Google it and you can look up a VR wrist
Socratic I I did that
If you Google you don't really find anything
From England or Britain or anything like that but you do find that in Mayan
Realization
Highly desired physical trait
Cross-eyed
Suspended
Between the eyes of theirs
Artificial
Desire cross-eyed traits
It it wasn't
Some favorite and have a good for
Haven't
Was considered
Knish
The cross-eyed Mayan sun god also known as the
Sean Lourdes
In order to appease in his favor
Because of this it was also can
Consider god-like
Is well
That's the only reference I can
Confined for
Cross eyes being valued by fidlar
Relationship
All religions go back to some weird dude that people are just like
Seems right to me
Show me religions are based on
It's this whole thing where oh course your God is cross-eyed what would be
The only the only one that doesn't work for is in Grecian
Society like looking up
Hephaestus
Cuz he had a limp
He was physically flawed
Endearing
Able to create any magical piece of
Armor or weapons machinery
Like
You know the Greeks
Certainly didn't
Admire physical deformity
The thought their gods were assholes
Wow amazing things about the Greek pantheon is
It's like bottle
Well very few of the Greek pantheon was always like
Cheese's guys would you
Cut it out you guys are killing us
Throwing
Lightning bolt
And you're an immortal app
When you f*** that lady is a swan
That's where the history of the idea of God
Referring as a
It's not judeo Christian
You consider Grecian
Being a part of that but it
Super Bali
Theater
The other thing I want to bring up his Alex at the end says it's called the aristocratic I and what I see
Pinkie Pie be getting confused
Pinterest
If you look up
If you Google the aristocratic I
It's just
Two bunch of articles about Monical's
It's Alex
Using that love me and Monica people who are upper-class British war
Give me a Monopoly man every possible that's where he's getting
Brings us to the end of this episode. Triggered I'm not offended by him making fun of cross IP
Because I have a lazy eye
Entrepreneurship
I'm over that
I grew out of that a long time ago
Grown out of
Stupid
Stop
Gilbert Gottfried roast 911
Are you making a bad documentary
I will never grow out of Alex Jones is misrepresentation
End of the world around him
Grow out of Alex's
His lies about George Soros I don't have any vested interest in defending
Other than
Just I hate this sort of s***
I will never grow out of Mike Adams
Being stupid all
And Alex a known vampires
Mike Adams
Really f****** dumb
We are presenting
Crazy how stupid he is a mess because
Xena I don't know
With our constant stupid
Hastings
It's f****** stupid though he's evil
Here's one of the reasons I know that
Yeah all of his articles that he wrote on
Universal Credit
All the Articles you wrote on naturalnews.com about how the Boston
What is the boilerplate website
You know I wrote These when I was a political activist today
Then that is all about hell
He doesn't say hey this is embarrassing
Sing for me to have up on my website
Stupid sorry
Rice
This was from
Back then I'm now a different person who's on a health committee
On a different missive missions that idea
Requires intentionality
And ice
I think it makes
Anyway
Website
You can go to check us out has helped spread the word about the show
Please keep doing that we are seeing great
Growth
In our Facebook group go home and tell your mother you're sorry about that we really appreciate it
Thank you so much please keep that up
It's really helping I feel like a bracket
I feel like we got a lot more votes than I was expecting
Second-round will be coming soon
Have a lot of close races
It's me
But I will see
Close the show and I'll tell you why
Acknowledge underscore fight
We are on
Describe like all that stuff I think it's very clear
Wright Avenue article out today about Syria I have a cow
Calendar where everyday is Alex Jones Show has been
The Gatherings at Aspen Hotel.
When the when the fish-people write our history
Put on Spotify
I think at this point
You know
Mike Adams
Please go fuc yourself
Alexandra Thurston color with your Japan I love your work