Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
I'm not going to ask you a question about the whole lotta Israel
Where's a good
It's been a great deal
Which is very little yeah probably not
I don't disagree with that
Situation
In Reverse though if you're going to use that same logic to apply doordash
I apologize and I know a lot of
Different because I've got to watch WrestleMania of course
New Orleans tonight
Single wrestling pay-per-view that you ever told me about his either been immensely disappointing
Facebook never been like
This was amazing it's always been
Storyline
I mean I like the
Like the actual in-ring storytelling in the athletic
But I like imagining what could happen more than Hitler
Evan Weaver
Collapses into
As much as
People may think
Be that as it may
Alright the guy who's about to watch 7 hours of wrestling tomorrow doesn't like wrestling as much
Writing articles
I'm going to be working
I miss you
Because
Saturday
Recover from
Since we recorded on Thursday
And then Friday
Episode again
He had Paul Joseph Watson
Studio
He was hosting for a bit
Any plate
Really long
Video that Alex
Made when he went out
Ted Nugent
Farm
Show on
To go over
As always I was
Classic situation where you got to scramble
I'm so I remembered
Why is that so crazy
It was very difficult
I remembered in 2006 is this is adorable
Particularly interested
Name some of like the more formative
Alex Jones
Remember that one of the biggest ones
Date with a guy named
Aaron Russo
And you know who that is
Nope
But Alex is sort of used it as a foundation of a lot of
His narrative
And I realized
Alright
So I went back
7 hour long interview
Why won't they tell us about building 7
It's not
It's not all that fun
To talk about anyway
Okay
You do yeah
I don't know what you mean by Inside Job
Exactly
Weather
Perpetrated by the
That
Reset the whole thing up in a in a
Zodiac style po-boy zodiac 70k
See that's what I think is going on
Dick Cheney
Ephraim 70k Merica for their sin
So that is one of the deadly sins
Everett's no I was just going to go with Bill
Seven deadly sins
You could say that
Aaron Russo
To be he's guilty
No maybe since 2000
70 East
But pretty lazy Prince death
He used to be a Hollywood producer
Hey came out before then as
Prominence
Is the producer for Bette Midler
In 19 in 1978 Primetime Emmy for
Special comedy variety or music for his work on Bette Midler
Or older red hair is back
Now that
Seminole
Do for me I remember growing up
Bette Midler
Johnny the award that
Has his IMDb credit
Although he did also produced trading place
Which is produced that but the rest of his resume I would call it
Glutes
Wiseguys now
Hold on
Yeah
Not good
Threat
Because then I would really respect 1989
Cheech Marin but not Tommy Chong
Stoner movie rude awakening
Which he also co-direct
I don't know if you know the plot of that one but it's
Cheech Marin
And someone who is not
Play
Who has retreated to the woods
Anime come back to society to find but all their Old Hippie friends are.
Classic fish-out-of-water tale
Exactly
I don't know I haven't seen
Have to take a look I want to see how scores on IMDb
Not positive
4.5 out of
You make it 7-4 director
Sure sure
Generously
In 1991 career
A b political
What I would call a film
In quote
Called mad as hell
Which I cannot make more than 10 minutes
Listen to when I tried watch
I thought it was going to be one of these documentaries
The people like Alex Jones
Screw make
Keyboard like a one-man show
Bitterness of a 50-year open my car
It's him out on a stage names
No but
Play you a little clip
For mad as hell.
Give you a taste of what
Energy he was bringing
A 49
Freedom
Back and forth
One second
Waiting there isn't why are people applaud them
I told you it's like
People applauding
That's a bit, is it doesn't go anywhere or have any
Intuit
Even have a
Alexa
I do I don't understand
I really don't understand how any of this
Dlisted
Infringes on the rights of the minority
Especially speed limit
I guess
Yeah that's the real
History of
This being was just like
Some people say one thing
And other people by saying different things
Right
Conclusion from it
Or have a point of view on it he's just observing people disagree on stuff prescriptive quality to
Trees like at least there's
Thought
The fact that I had to turn it off
Prescribed
At some point
Where Cheech Marin goes into the woods
Wiggle wiggle
2006 Rousseau wrote and directed a documentary called America freedom to Fascism
Which of the foundational piece of Alex Jones's
Philosophy
Sprouts on the Infowars
Prince's it all the time
He claims in the film the film
International Premiere to Patchogue
Film Fest
The daring part
The film was not on the program that can
However not even for screenings made under the festivals
Without being in the competition
Mr. Russo the film's director writer and producer
Just set up an inflatable screen on a beach
Photographs posted at 1
Mr. Russo's websites
Audience of fewer than 50 people
Spread out on a platform of
Guerrilla film yourself gunship
I respect more than a lot of the people who were in The
It like that shity market
Smashables
Conspiracy bulshit
But it's mostly about how the federal income tax
Is b******* always comes back
Don't like
What a quarter of their pay
Check going somewhere else
Yeah they just don't get it
In order to make his argument
Engages in
Exactly the same sort of behaviors that
We saw Alex
Do a Name Game
He fabricates quotes
I'm pregnant out of context in order to make quotes
Something but in contacts
Exact opposite
He treats
Conjecture and hearsay
The same thing as
Makes up sources
He never brings up and about to listen to
Is it in 2006
But he was making anti-tax documentaries
And make it something sational claims has committed a crime of text
He has more than
$2000000 after filing exempt
She kind of has a vested in
Maybe Lopez
So I will get to this interview and then along the way will learn a little bit more about that
You know those sorts of facts up front
Little bit of a flavor of where this guy's coming
From maybe Scientology is really just a normal
Possibly could be a little
So here's the first
Past and tells a
Dubious story
The late 80s
I was pretty big silver
Trader
Schrader
I don't even tell the story on tape
Supreme accelerate lingerie
I took
What was illegal tax
Seduction on my Soldier
Seriously
The
Iris
Claim
That what I did
As well
Now that's against the law. That's not good so you always 600 or 800 thousand dollars
It was legal to make something
What's the time
It makes no sense
What we doing it
And so everybody
Retroactively
That there was something wrong America with the IRS in the system
Sure
Listening to that claim
Can clearly surmise that he is telling the truth so far he has become nothing but a
Biohazard
Highest rating about Estates
Now I'm sure that you have done research on this claiming you will absolutely back it up Tia Carrere
Well ex post facto laws
Something illegal that wasn't illegal before he
Have always been
Illegal
In terms of criminal
Sybil
Cases and stuff like that
Applause
Most of the
Adore people have broccoli
Offender registry
Where people
Have made the argument that when it be
Became required to register as a sex
Sex offender that's adding punitive
Consequences on that didn't exist
Before
Handkerchief
It's only been like
No
Yeah I'm going to go
I don't know anyways with tax stuff
You can
Do ex post facto
Laws
Typically speaking
That's just because of
Right to happen that way I have a tax loss
Ends up getting past
Generally speaking
What they will do
Backdated to the beginning of the fiscal year
So it's
Skip to the beginning of the year
Is the only pic
Grievous circumstances
20 years that would never fly
Never fly
This is from the Congressional research service
Any retroactive tax legislation
Found to be a criminal penalty
Will likely be struck down as violation
Ex post facto clause
Which of the Supreme Court has done on at least one occasion
Extremely rare
Circumstances
Legislation B
Seems to Target
Get certain taxpayers
Microwaves
Concerns under the equal protection
Guarantees of the fifth
Finally it might also be asked whether such legislation is
Beloved
When there do not appear to
Any instance
Occurring
It seems possible that a retroactive tax
Play some good depending on its
Pacific meet the criteria to be
Be a bill of attainder
Circumstances wherein
Yeah you'd have
Crime being done
Bye-bye
His story doesn't
Check out
All that well I don't necessarily believe
The line
He's spitting I think it's probably a thing where I was like it's backdated to
To the beginning of this fiscal year and you like
I got to pay a bunch more than I wanted to
The creative mythology
Codeworks
Trader
That's that Alex Jones
You already know that you didn't
Right preload
Tell you this long-winded fictional story let me start by saying
My taxes that's just
In 2006
Whether or not
He pays attack
The relevant issues
This next clip where he
Explains that she doesn't believe in taxes
But he's not going to tell people not to
To pay their taxes
Legal gray area right there
You don't advise
Not
Single
And I like the way you summed it up
It's really very simple I mean
Since making that movie
You know how many people come to me and ask me what I should pay the record taxes or not
You know and I never devised people not to pay
And the reason I said tell him I said look
I've done a lot of research
The Supreme Court has ruled
The IRS has no Authority
Nope
Supreme Court
That being the case
The fastest if the mafia come to you
And say
We want $2,000 a month so we're going to hurt you
I would not advise you not to pee
Doesn't matter
Okay
Literally the 16th
Alright
The Congress shall have power to lay and collect taxes on income from whatever Source derived without
Apportioned among the several States
Any sensatori numeration
I would argue that
Taxes on income from whatever Source derived
Does include your labor
Is over your income
I don't know
Call out
Does problems with
Commandments
Defecation
One of them is that Ohio weather
The state would it was ratified
States ratify it to pass as an amendment in ar41 really doesn't matter if Iowa
Bunk
That's very considerate
What is the most prominent
Petitioners
You operated on
18th Amendment concerns
Name of William JB
He wrote a book
Call the
Like the biggest law that never was
Something like that
He's another one of these guys kind of
Sure of like writing books that so you don't have to pay taxes
It's really dangerous
He sort of rhetoric
But his argument
The text of the Amendment ratified in different states
Insomuch as
The spelling words
Different capitalization and stuff like that
Real human being
Right he made the argument
Because of these capitalization and punctuation
Application of the six
Amendment was and now we learn
Children
Oxford,
Considered back during the ratification
Sometimes even
This doesn't matter
In terms of like that being
To think that income tax was not legal
All over the f***
Complacent
I don't know what these people were talking about
So based on this stupid ARG
He stopped paying his taxes
Naturally he eventually was
Convicted of tax evasion and failure
Willful failure
To file tax
Returns
4 /
A hundred thousand dollars of unreported in
Okay on December 17th 2017 States District Court
For the northern district of Illinois
Ratification argue
Give me a call
Fraud perpetrated by Benson
Cosmo
I like
He got sent
Thanks for being a douchebag because this argument is already been
Using that as your legal
Backing
For your I don't want to pay my taxes yet
You're doing that
In full awareness
That this question has been settled
This stuff like this
Legitimately
Did Aaron Russo is paddling on the show is
Demonstrable enochtrue
Has been dealt with in the courts over and over and over again
To the point where people who have these anti-tax argument
Good
Until you're looking to the actual details and then you realize that
People keep going to court for the stuff and they lose
Every time
Usually have
Yeah they lose every type of that kind of
What like the wealth preachers that go on TV where it's like
And he's selling his book under the same premise
But
If you
Do what he says whippin you buys book
You just wind up going to jail
Basically
It was actually even address
Perpetrating a scam
Dangerous to them
And he knows
He knows or has
Them to know that that's what he's doing
Who
It's reference Tesla
He Went A-Courtin
He made the argument
So he ended up
The court case
Vettex protesters reference
That's because
He ended up losing the civil case
That was attached to it and ended up still being liable to pay all the taxes
But he won a case
Wearing it was a quart
Was proved
But he wasn't
Willfully
Breaking the law
They didn't find him guilty of intentional
Basically yes long and short of it
Subsequent
Attempts to use that as president
I have been like
Good god no
All of this stuff is so crazy
Just like right
Yeah that's more or less the Holy Grail of
These attacks protesters nonsense Target
Next clip we already got a little bit of a
Russo in his one-man show
The idea that like majority
Rolex
Songs YouTube
Okay
I'm referring more to the majority rule aspec
Right
Before he does
He's got to do his best impression
Of
I don't know college
I'm smoking a joint
Politics are Dormer
The American people are living in The Matrix
They don't understand the truth of how things work in this country
You know
Let me give an example of what I'm talking about 100 people in the street
What kind of government
Is America supposed to be
99% of them will tell you a democracy
America supposed to be a democracy
But that's a lie
That's an illusion
Democracy
It's not in the Bill of Rights
Separation of Independence
The founding fathers
The idea of a democracy
Why they create the river.
Democracy
51% of the people
Control 49% of the people
Percent you're not free
America was founded as a constitutional republic
Constitutional republic that we have
Ninety-nine percent of the people
Cancel
You have your rights cuz she was born with them
Human rights
I got bad news about Republic
Really also
Really don't like this whole you have rights cuz God gave them to you
Using that metaphorically
It's fine
In a republic
You could still have the representatives 51% of
Publix
51 tons
Also Supreme Court decisions could go on 54 there's 32 the last
Right I mean
Or even like a little bit before but like
What year was exactly but
Certainly
In the mid
I2 later 1900s
Women couldn't work as bartender
In bars that were called by a male relative but that just makes sense
Take away a right on majority rule
Supreme Court decision give me the right-to-work
Because women have one less rib or something I don't know I don't know
God works like that
Are we
I don't know I don't understand because like I don't want to get a drink from anything that bleeds once
The month and doesn't die
It's about the majority rule aspect of a democracy
Is exactly the same as
Arguments that could be levied against
A majority rule in a
Any majority rule whatsoever
Government entirely by anything other than a fascist dictator
Libertarian folk end up
Accidentally added
Waiting for exactly that under the pretense of individual rights
Tell you what to do
Right
Bright
Beb
I don't even know how to
I don't know how to deal with
That's because like
You couldn't couldn't
Vote like let's say if you have a right
To employ my
Or whatever
Person who lives
United States
Yet God gave us that one.
51st
51% of the public came out to vote
And we're like alright
You can't
Look for work anymore
Right
I don't know
Stephen Gunn
Even gun stuff
You couldn't vote on
Know what there's no way that would fly
There's a massive majority abortion is not an issue that would be on a
There would be
Unrestricted
In the same way all of this
I was just
His words are empty
And when you consider not
Some kind of like
Judicial scholar he's not up
Professor
He's a guy who was
Bette Midler's manager
Directed and produced at
Cheech Marin movie Midler only hires the greatest legal Minds to assist her on anything
I could be the canoes
Has argued multiple courses in the Supreme
Okay
I did not know that
Good coffee
Actually democracy
What
What is intelligent people
What former Governor America supposed to be
That's what that's what they've been brainwashed
Believing that
Play believer in Iraq
Democracy
George Bush Senior microsiemens freedom
Real quick
I'll tell you didn't believe that
Liberal
In 2002-2003
This is Aaron Russo in 2006
This is already a tired line of rhetoric based on like
Protest
That I was involved in in Columbia Missouri
What's bigger another city
I experienced
These words
This democracy thing is a sham
The argument is it is nonsense is travel territory for people
Other side
From people like
No
Democracy equals New World Order
Democracy equals slavery
Word democracy is not synonymous with freedom
What's the opposite of freedom
If the United States what is it
If the United States is a republic
Perseus
We have some really f****** long time
The original founders of our Republic we're the ones who literally ruling the play
Democracy is the worst form of government you can have to switch re-roll
Exactly
What they want to tell you to do
The majority wants it wants
My life as I choose
If I don't commit violence
Uproar
It's nothing you and being
I can live my life as I wish
So you can't commit fraud news about the show you're off
Why is they always pick
The ones they're doing well to be fair that's a pretty consistent
Because it's that like
If I
Commit violence against
Encroaching on your right
Encroaching on your right to proper
If it's fraud against you I'm stealing
From you through
Whatever they hold the belief that
It was always out of self
It was mine to begin with
Give me the song YouTube
Push it when it comes down to their behavior is really all they do
Both sides of the coin
Do whatever I want
You're committing fraud
Yeah you just say
You just said that the
16th Amendment doesn't apply to the ability for the government to collect taxes the IRS
Now
Isn't as a government entity to
Do that
Peppa 16th Amendment is being violated
Ed Court Suki
Distantly ruled on this one of those
That's a fraud he's professional one of those things where a guy is trying to use the insanity defense
I before E actually goes to trial
He's trying to act
Set up as he's all crazy like he's doing the stupidity defense but he's just throwing it out there like
Like the lookout Jamaya
Stupid tried to do at the Michael in one of his last
Appeals he was trying to save it
That he believed that he was the only person who could interpret tax law correctly
Alright this got blown up cuz one of his co-defendants
Imitate
We hate to have to use this kind of a defense but
So
It was like a it was a Hail Mary kind of thing to try and get him out of prison mail the invalidation of your
You think it's only going to your supporters and they're the only ones we're going to see it but no
Hellboy
Wow stupid to be willfully line
Well then
This that this f****** Aaron Russo commits another fraud on air
What happens is
Now the government borrows money from them
The fund the government
It's all about the Federal Reserve
Let's impose a tax
Existed before
Ronald Reagan said not one red Cent
Your income tax
Commission report
That's said that one nickel goes to the
Infrastructure the country
So that's fun
What do you know about the grace report the grace
Commission report
Put through I don't know
I know it's almost certainly stupid
Associated with Ronald Reagan it would definitely not be prosecuted for willful
From Aaron Russo in Alex Jones
Perpetuating an idea of it's in the report
They found at Reagan
That none of your income tax money goes
To paying any programs or anything at all goes to paying off interest
To these bankers
These International Bankers in the Federal Reserve
Oh yeah the bottle
Quote
Do you from the report cuz I read way too much
I don't know how to do impressions
Nope
I like it the quote from the report that they're misusing
With two-thirds of everyone's personal income tax wasted or not collect
Did 100% of what is collected is absorbed solely by interest on the federal debt and by federal government contributions to transfer
For payment
In other words all individual income tax revenues are gone before one Nicholas spent on the services
The taxpayers expect
From their government
Important
That what is actually being
Said they're
Is more to the effect
Everything is getting face
Did you see that
Beginning there
Two-thirds of everyone's personal income tax wasted
It's important
Consider what Reagan
Considered wasting
Of tax money
Very important
So
Remembering
Anyting
This is everything except jelly beans
Everything except
What Russo's claimed
Your taxpayer money is illegally funding
The grace commission which itself
75 million dollars
Found that there was
424 billion dollars of waste in
Spending
That Rousseau extract doesn't take into account
Is
Is that that
Number is cited in the report
What's up
Recommendation
Did this Commission
Can come out
I read dcboe
Congressional budget office
Assessment
Commission report
Aaron Russo Alex Jones read that either
Cboc
The thing that the Great Commission
Considered waste
And what part of that 424 billion dollars negative
State Department clearly
So you're some of the suggestions
Reduce food stamp Child Nutrition overlap
Consolidate Student Loan program
Spell unneeded public land
Modify federal employees health benefit program
You trying to get the sense that
Get some of those are probably code
How are you going to save money modifying the federal employees health care benefits program get rid of a lot of
Is felony programs
Probably
Let's pinch these kids or modify
Reduce civil service retirement benefits
Repeal or modify davis-bacon Act
Which is a 1931 United States federal law that establishes the requirements
Preparing the local prevailing wages for public works progress
For Laborers and mechanics
Also repeat
Remke delauer modify Walsh
Keowee public contract Act
Which establishes minimum wage maximum hours and safety
Standards for workers on contract
Excess of $10,000
The manufacturing or Furnishing materials
Supplies articles or equipment to the US government
Circuit and it's another one of those let's cut Corners bypass
Reasonably assume
We're getting those larger contract
Could probably absorb
Some of that
You know potato
Three individual laborers
They're getting f*****
Course VA Healthcare facility
Construction
Daycare fight and die for our country would you find to be so important
They're done they're done right
Also restricts federal employee disability benefits
To get hurt just paid annual leave benefits for federal employees
From The New York Times the red knuckle front 1984 while this was going on
Possible at least at this stage to calculate actual or likely total savings from the commission's work
These were already under consideration
75 million dollars with fat to end up with
Conclusions that Reagan and his friends wanted
Just to get rationalization and things
You see in it are largely
Get rid of
Start helping program
Don't want to see their mother
Go to don't you understand this elaborate fraud against libertarian ideas
Russo is perpetuating with the help
Very complacent help of Alex Jones
Is this idea that
All of your income tax
It just goes to
Pay off the interest on
Federal debt
This report he's using it in your friends
Right exactly
Say that
F****** b*******
Anyway
I'm curious about that we all recognize Reagan was one of our
God bless
And the only way to get up on top of that Hill is to
You stand on top of the Dead Corpses
Everybody knows that the grace commission report is like
If it being used in this context
Infuriating if you care about the
And if you care about the true
All you care about is trying to
To push bogus
Anti-tax
Anti-Federalists
It's Manna From Heaven
Cuz really easy to misrepresent ain't nobody can read that 600 pages easy to misrepresent
Even if you follow up on it you're like these are great ideas
And I like that kind of
Of course
Of course you want to
Use the report
It says f*** over the Ford be like see
They're f****** over the poor
Evil it is the taxes are due
Just taken out of your check
Yeah you should have to write him a letter every time
Control
Exactly
Automatically
No s***
That's my response that no f******
Do you understand operate any sort of organization
Would you like
You guys will take care of it
Lakeview massive number of people
People who I like
Alex
Aaron Russo
Would destroy weather
Even when their people are filling out their tax returns are still on
That I have a child
The other thing is that like if you
System in place
You would end up
Creating a much larger tax system
Because investigators
Tons of people who go out in like
Hunt people down for not paying their taxes
If we didn't have to pay the minimum wage or take care of their benefits
It all makes sense
Collectors making $6 an hour
What is a gyro government is the diametric opposite
Of what you want
Smaller tax system
And that would create a
That would have been for almost everybody
I just I just don't want
I need
It's just
These stupid intellectualizing of it goes back to
To these
Visitor
Bogus
That are misrepresenting actual cases of the Christian response to evolution
Like whatever they would like the Creation Museum
It's not just like
Well we reject their sign
Their Sciences
Hahaha
Yeah we do science with their
Doing it
And weak
Right
Jordan you ready for this
To take a huge turn
Because
Really think that every time somebody with a Southern accent
Does the word slaves they should have
To pay a dollar
I think that's a reasonable thing reduce government
Colorado collect dollars
People in the South saying the words laser
Everything changed
You
We talked a lot about taxes up till this point
And now everything changes
Get back to the new I had a friend
Nick Rockefeller
I'll tell you who's on the Rockefeller family
When I was running for governor Nevada he can't answer me introduce himself to me to an attorney
We became friends
Turn off Alaska mr.
And one of the things that we say
To talk about
What's the Arsenal plan
Dancing in the Street what they want to accomplish
What do you think about that
Well
The Rockefeller was
Clearly recruiting him
For the globalist
Emphasis
This is while he's running
For governor correct
I see you now Alex
Correct
He's going to say no
You were recruited by the global
What do you have to say about Aaron
Aaron
You
Have tried to take over
Through globalist mean
Clearly you have learned something from this and now you are coming back to me
To rectify this makes mistakes you're going to tell us the secrets behind the globalist
And Howard
People who
Clearly have
Internet
Good ideas
Into something evil
What are the
Industries wanted to what did Rod what Global is
The secret
Your aunt has some interesting
Threads that will continue as we go along
What you should know is this guy Nick Rockefeller
May or may not exist as
As Aaron Russo describes
From what is from what is available research cuz there is a picture of him with a guy who is
Rockefeller
Who is the lawyer he's a lawyer
Remember or a permanent member
You might just be someone who join for business
Contact or something like that cuz if you look at the role of members
It's a ridiculously huge list of people
That doesn't prove s***
There's no evidence that I can
Can find that he was related to the Rockefellers
There's where we run
I also cannot find any
Rockefeller records
IQ
I'll stick to the facts
What everybody wants
Aaron Russo ran for the governorship of Nevada as a Republican
Republican primary
6% of the vote
You don't want
The Democratic
The candidate
And who would be Russo in the primary
He's all over
Is there in 2004
That guy beat me
F*** that
It's possible that was the motivation
If possible
2402 run for president
He won the first round of voting in the libertarian primary
To vote
Which was not a large enough margin
The name of the candidates
Coming out of the convention
They had another ballot
You're going to lose the final ballot by 89 votes for
3 to 3:44
So
In 2004 at that point
You'd already
Been diagnosed
The bladder cancer
And that's what I'm pn's of dying a year after
Interview with Alex
You'd already been suffering
Struggling with cancer
Right
Might inform
Some of the
Because the other two million-dollar tax
He has
I've been battling
I think that
Not to save
It sure seems like he would benefit from
More government spending on Healthcare
It would also
Being unable to afford both Healthcare anti
It would also appear
But he would stand to benefit
From creating a documentary
Called America freedom
Fascism
And I'm creating
Niche market for himself by going on Alex Jones Show
I'm saying that he knows all the secrets
It seems like that is a
Pretty good to make a lot of money from that I believe he may have
Now prove to me
Larry Nichols
Existed before 2000
I think I can I had Aaron Russo faked his own death and became Larry
No because of Larry Nichols involvement in the early Clinton scandal
Troopergate
Stuff like that
For governor Nevada
He was producing a Cheech Marin
Nichols Road
Larry Nichols
That's probably not
McKay's
Larry Nichols did Ghost write most of Bette Midler
So I missed next clip we get to learn a little bit of what this
Mysterious Nick Rockefeller told
Aaron Russo about the globalist
Notice
Not using the term global
The international bankers
So these people have in mind
Is the gold to
Credit One
Run by the bank
The street run by the bank
We're doing insects
The European currency euro
European Constitution
Is one part of it
Not trying to do in America with the North American Union
Right and I want to create a new currency called the Amero
Right but I've worked
Is to create a One World Government
Where everybody has
Gotta
Is Tubi
In those chips
Tips
And so so anytime you have money in your in your in your
Whatever they want to take out
I find us just
Slightly
You know why
Mainly because
Pretty sure we do
To some extent have an international One World Government that is run by the Bay
Insofar as being
Tire economics
The world is
Sure
Perfect
Very mindful way of organizing Society
Ghetto capitalism exist
That is an inevitable conclusion of it because eventually you need to get into other mark
NetSpend
I mean capitalism has a
Has a vested
Not even in
Because of that
You can't ever
Look at the highest levels of
You can't just limit yourself
Even if you did
Still need trade
Clear resources from other places
Capitalism is a
Almost a disease
Like
Spreads and it only has water
He's all over RS
Sprite
I mean
You do what you do
Purpose based on the technology
Having a f****** debit card
You know I mean pretty much exactly like lose my debit card
Fuct
I can't buy or sell without a debit card
And that's not something
Evil
Can see out of an ATM
Or whatever
First Convenience issues that it does address
Never I think no self-respecting world government
Would ever go for that
Just because of how hat
You know what I mean it's angry gun-toting
Let's give it to them in something they can hold
Well I think is how all of our debit cards have come
Computer chips inside of them that function in the exact same way as what it is
He's describing a passport
And what is your what is your business with
Have chips in them
World government is what
It is like I don't want a One World Government run by
Xi Jinping
I don't want to write one world government run by the entire got it either
The problem with one world government is that most governments around the world are s***
Well I mean even if you take the world government aspect out of it
Like I don't want our government
Big run this way I don't want
It's not an issue of scale it's either bad I don't think countries are anywhere near as
As their shity governments that are f****** everybody having a central one
Necessarily not the worst
Maverick
Very Bad Things
Look for now
Because of the unevolved fate of all the world
Yeah I with exception of something at some places in like Scandinavia
The only the only difference between a One World Government
Now
And what we have
Is that
Instead everybody in the world would just be
Reflect over in the same way that touches on what
The fear is
That the capital f
Fear
I'll do it one world government
Alex
And that is that is there is a unified One World Government there's nowhere you
You can go
So like
If fascism took over in America
Horrible authoritarian
You could still run away to Europe
Or something like that
Whereas if there was a unified One World Government
Then you would never be able to escape it without getting off the
The planet which is
This point
You couldn't do as a city
In Alex Jones World in 2018
Of course you can absolutely
Not really
But like so I get that
For similar reasons
You were espousing about
Most governments
But I don't
Support
Chippewa government
Butchers from very different reasons
And I don't think
It's going that way I don't think the fact that
Figaro exist
Going hard the opposite way current there has not been
Sincere efforts
To create
I'm at the Amero I know it's been discussed but it's always been around
Just based on the
I did
Complications that would come from the differences of opinion
Air Canada America Mexico to know there's no way to be able to come
Agreement about how it's
Laid out
Record wouldn't
Everytime it gets suggest
No that's not Lisa
Because countries
Themselves are not
Unified
Blocks
So you know
As much as your identity maybe I'm American or I'm
Canadian
The guys in Canada who are like
Government is it real are more in the same country as I
The guys in America who like government is it isn't real as opposed to
Country isn't the difference between those two people
And that's an argument
For globalism
Because
Our borders are abstract ideas with l-theanine
I disagree with your
We should put
Like Alex and 21
Translate
Let's get the Arizona look
If you don't think there should be government
You get Arizona there's no government there you guys figure your own s*** out and everybody else will be fine be ultimate irony
BF like there was a North American Union that ended up happening
Because text
This is so bullheaded they're like
They are
Things that link
You have one
Little in the middle
United States from Mexico California
One of those assholes living in Canada jubilo
Well I could just go to this non-government
Because I'm staying
I'm test
Basically admitting that government is a good thing
I don't know if we're
Going to come to a resolution to this but it is more fun than talking about Aaron Russo
Arizona
Dollightful
Enjoyed it many times
Times of my life
I love you
Okay
In this next week
Shocking
Revelation of Arab Roussos that comes
From
Mysterious
Nick Rockefeller
Specific about when you met Rockefeller
Rockefeller
Call me up Wednesday and said
When the Rockefellers like to meet you I made a video call medha cell
Amazing video
I know I was running for governor Nevada
Shut up to me
Is very very smart man
We should talk and share ideas and thoughts
He's the one until 11 months before
And there's going to be an event
Never time with you that was going to be
There's going to be an event
The Caspian Sea
We going to invade Iraq
Enough to take over the oil fields established a base in the Middle East
And make it all positive World Order
Chavez in Venezuela
Sure enough
Play the 9/11 happen
He was telling me how
Sea salt
Looking in caves
Some people is in Afghanistan and Pakistan in all these places
Another thing is a giant hoax
You know it's way for the government to take over
The American people
Oh yeah
9/11 happen
And then nothing's happened since then
Nothing
Here's the problem with this
But also nothing happened since is a ridiculous thing
Argue
And if you're just saying it over more planes
I don't know because
Insecurities got clampdown real f****** hard
Now the other thing is
All of the household became hack
All of the stuff
But he's saying in this interview
In 2006
A stuff that has happened
Since 9/11
He's just using
His awareness of what has happened since then
And pretending that he knew it 11 months before seriously didn't tell anybody before 9/11
Years
Didn't tell anybody
And then brought the story out mysteriously around this
The time that he released a movie called America freedom to Fascism
Weird
And he has two million dollars in tax lien
Has a vested interested really trying to sell this movie
How do you sell it
Know a secret Rockefeller guy
Therefore everything
Must be based on
Totally real stuff
New York Times review of the documentary from freedom to Fascism
Near the film's beginning Mr Russo says and others appear on in a serving
Did the IRS has refused every request
Restore any law making Americans liable for an income tax on their wages
Yet
Among those thanked in the credits for their help in making the film is Anthony Burke
And IRS spoken
Mr Burke said that when Mr Russo call them asking what law required the payment of income taxes on wages
He said Mr Russo at like 2.
Including title 26 of the United States code
Siding display
Pacific sex
Require income tax
We paid on wages
Title 26 says on its face
That it is a law enacted by Congress
But Mr Russo tonight
Just completely lying about you do also review also include that Bette Midler she could have best picture
The film also includes a brief interview with Sheldon
Who was an IRS commissioner in the Johnson
Administration
Cut mr. Cowan said the mr. Russo use
Twist My Views to create a Folsom
So you get the sense that there's multiple people who were involved with this
F****** stupid documentary that he put out who have come out publicly and said
It's very clearly
Answer the question he asked and in the documentary
Oh no one will respond to my request and give me documents right if someone else comes out and says
Hey this guy lied about me using editing
And now he's coming on Alex Jones Show where they
Credible
Reputation is a truth-teller
It's completely under of viable
About a guy named Nick Rockefeller who doesn't even appear to be a member of the Rockefeller family
Using him because
Before
The deaths of three people
Diddams gray what a crusade Bush for not stopping it based on prior intelligent
What the f*** did you do
Also why don't you tell Alex Jones
Back then
Why don't you do something
Scream about it
Anyway
Is a big old con man
So foundational
Alex Jones
This worldview that definitely deserves
Being talked about
Now there's a lot of other stuff in the interview that
For the sake of time we don't really have
Time to get into
But
Suffice it to say the rest
You say
Brave pronounce
About the warranty
Warren Tire is a fraud
It's a farce
It's very difficult to say it out loud
Cuz people are intimidated
Again sang
Do you say they want to make you a donut case
What's with the truth with the truth has to be the truth has to come out that's what I'm doing this interview
The fact the matter happens to be
The whole War answer is a fraud
It's a farce
That's a joke
Again
You could have gone to any protest
You said the war on terror was a fraud
The news media would be like
I disagree
Aaron Russo said
Is a very common
Very middle-of-the-road position
In most
Liberal
Communities
Free dating 2016
So the war on terror in the fridge
I'm just saying that as a larger
As a large
Concept during this time I remember clearly that so many people who are like
This is bulshit
I don't I don't think it makes it hard to say
Of course
Him on Alex's show but at the time if you'd there were plenty of people
By coming out and saying that this
Pay for my teammates a repeat
I don't know
Anyway
We get some more news from the Rockefeller guy
About women's lib
I'm pretty conventional thinking about
Just like they won the right to vote
Idiot
He said you won't let me see what that was about
Refunded women's lib
No
Newspapers and television
He says anyone who wants to do two primary reason
We couldn't accept the population
Probably legitimate
The second reason was
Get the kids to school tomorrow early age
We didn't talk to me the kids have a thing
Tickets at look at the state as a
The family
As a school as the official
As their family that is the parents teaching
And so don't
Was
So we all know the public school didn't exist
Before women's lib
So there's that
Yeah but
Tangischools
The kindergarten app
Kindergarten
Where they where they guard children
I would I would say
We funded women's
Well I think you look back on it like after I even just as another example like after Margaret
Singer it already been
We are putting her Crusade for Women's Health
For years and years with no help Rockefeller Foundation
Did come in and find her a little bit later so you can
You can probably find examples
Support
What causes
Board game
Endowment
Stuff like that to people like Margaret Sanger throughout history
But that doesn't mean that they funded women's liver was something fake thing
Right now you take the example of a fake thing
You have people like Edward Bernays with his
Campaign
Smoking
Is a fake co-opting of women's lib
Typo
Like the bigger picture of it wasn't that
Aptitude to
Much finer point
This is
Grossly patriarchal
Like this sort of idea that you selling
Because women's liberation
Was a noble thing
And then he just
That
Men should rule the world
I guess
But like even if I call
Want to go along with the idea of
To have kids
I should have a career
Rob
Those people
Prospective
I think
Rockefeller funded it was all these
Elites that I'm imagining
Push this through
It takes away a lot of the agents
Actually did fight for change
Entirely
Global jobs
Again
He's not calling them globalist
Just interesting
These next two clips
We get to hear Aaron Russo Stacy
Stop
Familiar
Okay
I'm going to I'm just going to tell you this up
Front
I hope it doesn't color the way you
You hear this clip
But I got
When I was listening
Because I believe
What he's about
To say
Alex has stolen his bed
I I think that three men and a hot tub
Yeah that would be amazing
3 minutes
Globalist
Alex Verdugo
Aaron Russo died
Shortly after that
And he just took it on his own back
Because it's very familiar to us nowadays
But I mean I don't know
Extra life 2004 2000
I don't know
His
But I imagine it wasn't
Just comes from
I never really
Did that because
That was when I was coming from
As much as I like you Nick
You know
You always in my ways with the other where the opposite side of the fence
You know I don't believe in sleeping people
Will be more like you know
What's more like you know
It was like
What do you care about
What are you sure about this
What did he say to you
To give your own life
Do the best you can for you and your family
What is the recipe of Nancy Dominicans you
Richest service
The people
You know it was just a lack of
Caring
You know and that's just not who I was
It was just sort of like
Cold you know I was just like
Cold
You know and
I said what
The point
You have all the money in the world
Disappoint
So you here
That's silly
I hear they're him talking about how Nicholas Rockefeller was trying to recruit him in
So many
They're trying to recruit him
Because I don't want to disrespect the humanity of other people next clip where I talk about even more
This is even more familiar
Maybe
Say this in the ballpark
Successful business
And I sold the truth what was happening
I tried to express it to the people
Express the people they want me to join us
Already
Already we could have been Glenn Beck
Or
Million dollar movie theater he's already been offered tons of movies
That to me
The trying to get me in but I don't want to do it
So is it moving to shaker
I'd rather them
It was real simple and
He tried to recruit me into that situation and
Already I have to think that
First of all
Because his
Responsible
So anyway
My thing that I'm amazed that right
Alex
Asking leading questions he's not he's letting his guests
He's doing it be references interview
He references they had a conversation the night but
Before
Before he told him some of these
Bombshell
Jesus
Step on this
I'm going
To get a fake Rockefeller story
One time you said to me
New Jordans
And your triplesafe a on it
Simmons kiss my ass and anybody stops you
Can you show them your car dealership
Cuz one of us
You know and you know what why you fighting for the people for what was that about
The people just you know that they have to be ruled I have to have to be
The Constitution what you staring for
Is only for a few people
So if you want I can live that way
You know and we believe that
Asbestos iety
People who are
What's a syllable
This is so allocation
Yeah but then
Are you fully
Going to put kma on you
Alright
Getting an offer like
Yeah you'll be one of us
Why do you care about these Jeep these Lemmings that is obviously
Please do it like a f******
Put badass motherfuker on your wallet
The same
Bulshit that there's a badass motherfuker
How many people were selling the laminated
I have a postcard that I
What
What was that the phrase that you're out of there
The Phrase That Pays
Perfect example of something that I definitely
You watched
Like
10 years ago
Or something like that 78 years ago
This energy before
But knowing that what I know about Alex now
I saw through
Completely new eyes
Lake
Story
To me was
Horrifying
Because I know
From other looking into
Betty the liar
And then I know what Alex is sold about his life story since then
So I
I have
Really strong
That what happened was
This is Aaron Russo
Pretend
Bet
If you are, cuz his bed
You know he's not super mainstreaming ever got on
Comedy Central
Something like that
He dies a year later I'm going to
Do that bet rather good bet that's a great B Williams
The idea that the globalist have reached out to me and try to get me to join their team
Explicitly
That's a good fit
And he's just stolen that bit
It's a great bit
Absolutely
I'm not sure Alex had the money in 2006
People
Sort of bulshit things
Russo says
Before we wrap this
What's up
Even message me once
No problem trying to solve Israel
Palestinian problem
Any talk to me once about
I'll bring Israel to Arizona
You know until I got ideas ruined
The State of Arizona
Believable
That's pretty wild I like that
I like that Judaism just being like
Pagar Holy Land is actually Arizona
Are bad guys it's also
Kind of insulting that it's like
Bucket
That's almost anti-semetic and like that the
Not consider in 2006 the population of Israel was
7 million people
Italy 2 million dollars
Put them in Arizona as millionaires
And does that will somehow fix the israel-palestine
Does it
I mean
You know what they're a lot of ideas you don't know are bad until you
Cuz first of all Give Me a Reason.
The people who believe in Israel the most
Aggressively
Would never take that deal
Because it's not about like
Bob just being like a we can have Arizona great
It's not about that it is about the holy land that exist
Fair traffic Lee Bass
Even if you got rid of that say 2 million
Of the seven million people that are still going to have a lot of people
Still
Enforcing
Apartheid government
Yeah it's going to come into money
That even if you have
More than that
Much more than $1,000 per person
Number is called
Millions of million trillion is $100,000 per person
So I get there
It's not important
This is all bulshit
But
I got some stuff
Ikenberry issue would be then
What are you doing bringing 7 million Warp
People into Arizona
How is that going to affect the demographic
Certainly Arizona is famous for
Loving Jewish people not even saying from a demographic
I just mean adding 7 million more people into a state
Where to throw everything into
The chaos that are in Israel
That's including Palace
So I guess it would be all of them
Depopulation
Arizona weather
Do you double the population
Is it caca maybe nonsense
The idea that he's playing that Rockefeller
Makes me believe they Rockefeller Mike's big guy likes to talk s***
Is part of the elite faction because of his last name
I like
I really like that
I like that idea is fiction
Like that
Great alternate history fiction book is instead of
Instead of after the Holocaust we create Israel's estate we're just like
Arizona
Desert
Another investigation of a
Infowars
Sharply into Focus
At no point
During
Any of this interview
Aaron Russo
Or Alex Jones
Bring up George Soros
In any way
They don't reference him
That is a good point they don't talk about him at all
This is a time when Soros
Was not a thing that I was thought about or cared about
Interested in all Rockefeller
Ford Foundation perhaps maybe I'll get a plug-in there it's interesting to me that you have someone
Reporting is being on the inside
Knowing a
Arch globalist
Family member and having the invitation he's coming in and spilling the beans
And at no point
Does Soros
The open Society Foundation
Come up
At all
No wonder why
Interesting
I wonder why
Fascinating
Right
More on that 2 coming out
I don't actually know the answer to this question but it's right
You know it's based on Alex Jones his own reporting of his
Skeptical history
They should absolutely be like what you know about Soros
Collaborator
He didn't rank is b*******
Bulshit
Use
Involved in funding Foundation
July 10th 2006
Nonsense
I want to learn more about it but it's f***** up
This is if anywhere there should be a fingerprint of Soros
On Alex's fan
It's when he's interviewing this guy who told him he knew about 9/11 ahead of time
Probably
You would think that the
You would think that stores would have been like the main Boogeyman from the
You would think
Through 2015
And do that whole long-ass investigation
If Soros then comes up it seems like there would be a corroborating Infowars of Messi
During that time of like
Well we looked into the Rockefellers religion before foundation
And we found another guy we found behind some reason instead of a narrative
Emerging whole-cloth out of nowhere
Understand what they actually said
He just thinks like oh I'll
Take that sound bite
Of
No money all of it went to
The interest consider waste
Went to
Did something
Very debatable
Debatably
And you can see that even in 2006 I was hoping we'd go back and he'd have a much more strong grasp on
On information and stuff like that but no
He's playing the same fast and loose game who does with the
With stuff now
So he can
He doesn't have the
Not at all
Globalist
Imaginary
Right right
Exactly
If you like our show you can go to our website
Underscore that's correct also we're on Facebook
You can go to iTunes
Downloader
Send it to the internet and tell people about
Tell the internet people give yourself a return address
Rate internet
Absolutely
Baba baba baba
I'd like to say
You'd like to say that you'd like to say
I want not for Aaron Russo to be the first new self
To f*** himself
I got the feeling that Aaron Russo wasn't the guy
He's a conman for strep
He should f*** himself on some level but I do feel bad that he died
Immediately
No he's been diagnosed
For years I think
The stakes were lower
To come on Alex's showing
Say crazyshit
Woodside
Maybe
I mean Reagan's in the running
Alright
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work