Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alec
Text Joan
Day that may be unusual for the two of us
Today
Cuz you might know a lot about a certain event
And I don't know anything about us
WrestleMania
I do know a lot about WrestleMania you don't know anything about wrestling
I have a ton
Like their name
What's up
For joining up with the
I got nothing
I got nothing there aren't really any famous Jordan's what about Jordan Peele
Right Key & Peele
Jordan Peele
Go I think you're right
Horror movies about very much for dinner
Why is your name
I know is the prophecy brother of mine
Oh that's true
Colts
People are in a wrestling called
Yesterday for Wrestlemania
Done with rest
And it's not
It's not why was this one the back because it's not for the same reasons that a lot of people complain about it love
So
But predictable.
It was just like
I got to about an hour for as I
I don't know why I'm watching
I'm exhausted
I think you enjoy your non enjoyment of it to a certain extent I will say that I had a number of thoughts
In my boredom that we're traveling
The first is that they don't do a great job
Do not save it
The Jews could be
I really think that's a bad thoughts
Little bit
So within the first 10 minutes or so up the broadcast they played a teaser
Played like a teaser clip
For the upcoming
Smackdown Women's Championship match between Charlotte and Oscar
This is something they do they keep referring to Charlotte as being bred for Supremacy
I don't like
It makes me a bit uncomfortable during she's like a blond
Aryan goddess
Well
This one I'm going to go to the no
Claire
He used to be involved with a group called evolution
Genetic evolution
Related to them you're saying that there might be a defense
Good
Bucket super tall beautiful blond woman whose bread for soupremacy
That's not great the first couple minutes
Over something I don't know you're talking about
You don't know that Ricky Nelson
Yeah okay
I do have it real life
Comfortable and this is something that I understand is
Like a
Necessarily a real criticism
But they played this
Teaser that's kind of it has a little bit of a Nazi
In Subway's
And then they have the men's Battle Royal Andre the Giant Memorial Battle Royal
Battle Royale
Found out
They're all fighting with each other
Guardians of winning
Hardy has he does
He deletes people
Mr. fruit
Making it delete
-2X
And it's not a Nazi salute
But boy when it's 70,000 people doing it an arena
Like the first few minutes I'm watching
Anything together that kind of bums me out there
Dragged on
Against some of it was good but
The only high point for me and I know that I'm
I made it sound like the f****** stupidest wrestling fan of the world
He had a shot at
Be a tag team titles have a partner
I've heard this one because my my long-time buddy Matt elfring right about
Wrestling free games
Does great job over there
He was very
Very excited about the 10-year old child
I don't care I love the absurdity of it and I don't give a fuk
It's very fun
Yeah
And then deep the main event was Brock Lesnar and
Roman Reigns
Everyone complains
Games about all that s***
It's very repetitive
I just happen to bunch
Just kind of tired of it I don't really care about that aspect of it
Romans had ended up bleeding a lot
Gross
This is disgusting
I don't care
He cut himself like they do sometimes we have to actually from I learn t'ai learned that in the
The great movie the wrestler
I don't care really what the situation was it was grotesque
And like
I'm seeing a baby
Very sick
I'm just not really enjoying any member of the royal family does he have that that haemophilia
You know that's it okay
I don't know really enjoyed NXT takeover
Shorter
You're you've become the old movie critic a little bit
It was a great movie could have got 10 minutes out
Meanwhile hour and 40 long minute movie give me an hour and 39 hours
Episode
Reminder f****** talk anyway I thought it was fine but I don't know I don't know how much
Future but exactly as much
Disillusioned after every single pay-per-view and you keep
It's just boredom
Anyway
Today Jordan
That was what that was dedicated
We're going to be going over is
Because Alex has been out of Studio C
Thursday
He's going to Washington d.c. press conference
Long Trek via covered wagon
Troy hosting on Monday Mike Adams hosted on Sunday and then visit a best of on Friday
There's not a whole lot to work with here put it out on Tuesday
Instead of Wednesday this week
Because we might need to have an
MC recording
Prescott
Backloading
All right for this
Ridiculous press
On Tuesday
So I decided let's go back to the past
Yes we have been like that movie
The second one
Back to
The third one
Where they went backpacking frame
Jordan
We had been going back to 2008
Looking at stuff
I've come to the issue that
I keep listening to episodes
And they are like
Clips
Of interviews that he did have on a previous episode
Splice together and stuff it's just
Time-suck
In 2008 so I decided to jump forward a bit
Find ourselves in June 2000
Today we're going to be going over the first
Second and third of June 2009
Let's see what happens
Put your cards that are behind your vest I don't know what what's the saying
Hematite not good you're not good at it interesting stuff those going to be there going to be
Samara
Just like I was interesting to see the snapshot of Alex Jones from almost a decade back
A bit of these 2009 episodes
And it's much
More like it's a radio
Has boots women 2008 worth
Sometimes the radio show and then sometimes you just
Here's a mishmash of shows for
We will go back to 2008 event really cuz
We got to cover like the election
Right
Obama
I think
I don't know we all lost
Like a terminal Alien versus Predator situation
Whoever wins we lose we start here on June 1st
And the first thing that I noticed right away
Is the Alex has a very different way of like Scholars are very different.
His collars are all in it for themselves
Hey Alex
First off
Love your hair
Product or whatever it is
You know that kind of
At the beginning of the
I love
Or whatever business for themselves
Here's the first example of that
Birdman in Florida are on the air
Congratulations on the author
Program so much
If you give me a couple of relax minutes
I want to ask you
If I can tell people. My old punk band 1984
Okay go ahead and tell us about your pumpkin
So
We've got Birdman Telugu
Hey Alex
I just want to tell you about my mixtape
Already to Schofield very different
Exact Alex could I get the directions to the Walmart you already here like an exasperated
How's the weather like
Punk band whatever here that goes
Welt from 81-85
That's all we ever sung about with everything you guys talk
And I would like
You get someone to put overdub some of your voices on some blank track
Premier programs
The Scream
Same thing
It's myspace.com
No freeplug
It's amazing 81-85
Another call from another guy
Well when I want to call and tell you that two things going to say you been a great inspiration to us here at we are change North
Caroline I'm a member and co-organizer that
Anna
I've got me a radio show starting on Saturday morning
Coming up starting this Saturday
Quick plug on it real quick
Alright
Eternal vigilance for Dustin freon on Revolution broadcast
Anthem.com they're going to run it from 10 a.m. to 12 noon
Car shows this weekend
Stream travel opportunities get a chance to do this and I Alex Jones is my inspiration
Spoiler that show is no longer on
There's this sense
It like Alex
People think of Alex is like a way that I can
Can get my thing out
Which is the current temperature
Still operating on
Some sort of like local radio vibe
Like I almost Public Access show kind of
I was like ideas of somebody giving out their website
In a
10-second
Clips
Like because
If you've ever given anybody a website there they're like Okay spell that for me
End
People are
On their computer ready to type it in as I speak people are recording this and are willing to listen
Send back to it
To get it right there's no way
It's probably in the Coast to Coast AM
I just think it's fascinating with that sort of the vibe that's going on
With Alex
We get to local radio
He's like oh he's like one of the failed comedians from the 80s who
Became a regional
Radio station DJ abs
Promotional
League Baseball's first day of the year
Yeah yeah
What is the narratives that even worth going over there all kind of just
Nonsense
Screaming about
Everything is about to collapse
Would understand but 2009 surgically
That's sort of feeling
People have to feel whenever everything had already
A reason article about Society about to
Collapse from Pravda
Just fun
Do they sell those purses
The Devil Wears Prada
He also screams about how Congress is being blackmailed
He doesn't mention anything about
He said he also doesn't bring up the pedophile blackmail or anything like that it's just
Some service regular old black man
3D screens about how
Supreme Court Justice nominee Sotomayor is a racist
Goes on some of that
I remember her confirmation and reading up on her
The consensus at the time was very much like
Well she's she's more of a
Centrist liberal
Like center-left
If you read her decision she's been
Pretty hard
Pretty heart
I like her
Go to now
Is a guy by the name of Eric
Blackwater Blackwater
Great episode
Alex now calls him a great Patriot
Hero because he's involved with a lot of trump Shady dealings
Is deeply involved
Trump let's hear what he was saying about Blackwater back in 2009
Yep
That's the same thing that
Blackwater worldwide
What the f***
How do you still work for those very same people who go from there to
Abandoning
Simple
Conservative principles
Ever been ill
Has been
Demolished
Absolutely
That applies to
A SeaWorld just
As equally
Yeah you know the icing
Pretty accurate picture that
Blackwater AR
Murdering Thugs and death emergency
Pretty much
Conveniently forget that the same guy who ran that
All about it being a great Patriot
Probably left
Duda morality
Probably
If I know anything about Erik Prince
It's that morality is
Is high on his list right right
You see these
There's a ton of them
Haha that is
Pretty consistent throughout Alex Jones
Early career that were finding
Thing is
Weird commercials
Zoe we love of course anytime we get to hear a new country song from Diamond got absolutely I wanted
Nowhere to hide my gun
Pre 2015
This won't top those
Football
Summer's coming to learn self-sufficiency
If you're going to eat from Nature's Bounty
There's a learning curve experience is the best teacher but that means time
To speed it up you'll need to build on the wisdom of a teacher who has lifted
Hawaiian food knowledge package
The books gives you an in-depth reference with all of The Insider know how you'll ever need
Enter wild card
Parts are your portable summary and cheat sheet for your fieldwork
Wait for it
Not years
I can vouch that Linda's the real deal
She's my mom and I watch TV
Knowledge is power
Better take I think the storms coming
That's crazy
I want that book now
And there was like,
Thunderstorm sound
Need to fill this 30-second spot
Better have a thunderstorm sound effect
Yikes
Tell me more about a gourmet survival
Sand ramps
I got to get some of those great brooms
You can find the right one
But a lot of those are poisonous
Value need that book
The greatest teacher is experience
Which I feel like they should not be selling on their ad for
Don't
Exactly what time is short
Storm coming
So
We know we know that one of Alex Jones
Throughout his
Is that his life has been
Opposition
Can do abortion
Except for the tablet
The shooting of an abortion doctor
I remember this
This
F*****-up domestic terrorism
This is super weird this pain he takes on it.
Historical comparison
Ground in Kansas
This morning
9 slave owners kill them through
Salt
Abraham Lincoln was a misguided show
But
This is the war situation
Wildebeest
I'm going to go with no
It's a very easy question to ask
Don't
That's the only way they're going to be able to drive
Yikes
Yay
Weird outro music weird
Is
An insane
Consider how many statues are for slave owners
Subway on board with statues for sale
Slave owner murderer is not right
I got a boner
I think when you really take a
Look at what is going on here
What you see is that the guy who shot
Abortion doctor
Doing that because he's motivated by the plight of The Unborn
Really don't think so because they're threatened by the idea
To commit terrorist acts in order to skip people out of abortion doctors
What you're doing is when you kill an abortion doctors you are trying to reinforce
That is not equitable
In fact
I would
Suggest
That what you are
Is the equivalent of
Slave owner
Nvidia in the metaphor
So you
You're killing
An abolitionist
Is what you're doing
What I would say
Right in the same thing
If you kill Jesse
Jeff Bezos I will make
You can make a statue
If I if somebody killed their crafty
Disturbing
By and large
Is it back in
Go ahead
Like
To a certain extent
Kind of understand from
If you are
Taking his standpoint
Because unborn children are
People
Then that's a murder
Rite Aid
I can understand why somebody murdering
A murderer
State-sanctioned
Positive moral a
Button nose
No I'm not
The other problem that I have with that is the title abortion doctor is silly
Because
Suggesting that there are people who got killed in just like all day I abort that's all I do
Just abortion diseases you just have to learn about
Murdering
Maybe
In their words
Babies
I don't know I don't think so but
Listen Pleasant where we got to move on with a lot of road to Calvary
This next
Is super Wild
Alex Jones is callers where
Or calling him out for things
And in 2009 Alex Jones
Can handle credit
Okay listen to this guy called
I mean it's not good
He doesn't get mad
So I find YouTube
Extremely difficult to believe
Most of what you say at this point this sucks
Completely
You said you were losing touch with your
Ability to think a couple of weeks ago
I think you should admit you're a right-winger for one and quit saying you're trying to break the left-right paradigm
Hello
Okay and I had this guy called in Friday
Regular Show
Jason Lewis
Jason is real prank with the guy the guy was going to disagree and he was going to say that you guys are picking on Obama
A whole lot more than Bush which I totally agree with that
Good golf and I want a backpack guy up but Jason wouldn't
Really wouldn't listen to the guy just got really tried
Bellissimo
And the guy ended up just kind of hanging up during the break and never got any points out but I would say that we're being bombarded with Obama
Miami being the tip of the spear
I mean Bush within the tip of the spear he was kind of like a good old boy who you kind of like the underneath you know you're kind of like
You killed him you get a statue mining Mercury mining gold
Causes mercury poisoning the are you familiar with you
Yeah
Deepest mines in the world gold mines are in South Africa
I'm not sure what is happening
Wax fried in a gold mine in South Africa and the
So you just
Like I know I disagree get mad at him
He let them speak now I feel like I feel like there's trouble
Like we haven't seen it yet but I'm guessing there be a musical Hamilton
That's right
That is an unheard-of amount of time for criticism
Did let someone save that pretty critical negative
Accurate
He would come back from it and start
F******
Screaming
Like that commercial even plays Reese screams at that Frank guy
But he always makes jokes about
In response to this now
Is like
I understand your criticism I'm not saying that that I'm treating them differently cuz he's black
He didn't point that out change it to straw man version of it
Are you playing with you
He's not a
His soul lives on the right
Super
At the end of this episode we get a delightful appearance from one Jesse Ventura
Time having to chat
Smart
He's making independent-minded opinions and
People keep bringing up points
You talking about like
Dom policy ideas
I love Jesse Ventura every time he shows up
Publisher
Exceptional Dental
Chris Kyle Saga everything everyone point
Admit
The opening up of Cuba
Right
Spectra 2000
A bunch of Mancow had recently allowed himself to be waterboarded
Picture
No you didn't really say that
Remember this
He got waterboarded as a
The publicity stunt
Of course it is
I don't do that to do that
It's it's
Pretty the tentacle
The lot of it's not really even worth list
But I think elevated to the level of greatness
Where we learn something very important
Okay
Very difficult and people don't realize
That is a life dedication and I love to say this
If people got dedicated to a religion where they call them religious bombs
Hahaha
That's the top 10 top 10 Pro to break has brown
Owners of coconut from the beach
We were talking AC Slater and that is an AC Slater movie
Oh yeah
I love that that's very fun
And that brings us to the end of
Stop
Navigate to June 2nd
Hot garbage
There's not a lot Alex Alex
88 starts to show off with an interview with Mancow about this publicity stunt
Nvidia Dawn
And Alex is like
I think I should do
I should get water board
You're too much of a
Weakling
10-second
Probably not
Also no bait because he seemed
Albright
He has to realize I'm probably going to fail to
Superfast
And Alex has dated position at this point is already that it's torture
Nothing to really
Prove about it other than
Yeah
But you could just say based on that gas video
Do it all except for this
How are you Alex
I was about to say something really horrible
What was he going to say
He doesn't say that we never said
Eric man, I wish I would have heard this before I was on Mancow
God dammit you suck
But
I'm talking about
Two pairs
I'm a little bit later Mike Rivero
Does the show called what happened
I believe is the name of another song title
It's another show on the gcn radio network
Communication
He got kicked off
The
The radio network
He got kicked off let me find I got to advance for a second cuz I got to find the exact quote
Deptford
Zagat
Bay I will be
We've not what I meant by that
Terrible
For you
He was a host on the
The communications Network the show is called what really
Until about 2010 when you left
According to him because he and Alex Jones
Did not see eye-to-eye on Israel
So what really happened Mike is staunchly anti-israel and felt it was becoming more and more pro-israel
Was time light on
His statement about moving to show off the Jensen
Included the following
The reflection of Alex and more and more are points of view regarding Israel art
Diverging I guess the breaking point was
She said that anyone who is a Critic of Israel is a weak-minded
Deadpool
So he's a guy who in his future at this point when he's on the show
I just want they're still buddy
What have you
They have a Breaking Point over
Relative levels of
Support for Israel
Which
Where where are we at now with Alex
Supportive
He's Pro
He's
More
He couches look like in a vague way right
He couches it more is like they're one of the only nationalist
The countries left
Esports Russia big
Because if you use them as one of the only National
Okay
Governments that murder people
For no good
Mysteriously that seems to be all the Auntie globalist countries
It's like that
Billboards
Mike rivero's on and it's boring interview but he does say one thing
Worth noting
Alex would never allows
Something like this on the show now
Every major war was Altima
By the country that started it
Soldiers are committing suicide
Numbers
Lowe's
Wow is that intense
I don't think Alex would allow someone to say something but something like that about soldiers
I think he's so pro-military infocop
Now that he wouldn't allow that sort of
At this point 2009
Because it's wrong
No no you can say
If you looked at every single War ever been fought and try to figure out if the aggressor win or lose
Well you have to cuz
He said major war which means he's classifying
The wars that he thinks
Are major and all other Wars
World War 1
Right now I guess he's he's talking about what
Three Wars
Maybe
I don't know
Izzy classifying the Korean War and the Vietnam police action
Soldiers killed themselves
They know there's a bad guys
Even from my position
Position
Before before
Position AIDS
Because they know they're the bad
I think
There's a different way to phrase
PTSD in Greece
You're made to do or make part of your friend feel like you should have been there
Position
Good
Yeah
That's that's ugly
This is kinda ugly too
This next clip I think Alex's
Expressing an opinion that
Pretty cool
Kill cops
Generation
If you going to have to
Korean War Vietnam
Baltimore
And about that all day and have the media said the old man was bad
By the end of the day
There's a lot of blood
And
And get control
That's very weird
Wow
Yeah
Too far from
That's justifying murdering cops
DUI checkpoints
Ordering cops in Alex's world
Right ahead to the third the second the third where we're going to focus
The third is where we're going to focus most of our attention know this is a refutation of what you're saying
Alex says something about
The cops
Negatively to start out the 3rd
I don't like the way you keep saying black
In this clip not good spirit of this clip
Think about what you were just saying
Black
Homeless black
Retarded
Watch
You can stop
And in the squad car videos always malfunction we always find out
What did malfunction there is a surveillance camera
Article
Just just two step
Look at that
Look at that position
What are the position that I was told kneeling for the national anthem this whole f****** time I mean in 2009 he has up his
Position of the cops are trying to cover up murdering black people
Pretending that they have done
An accurate depiction of
There was just a guy in Brooklyn with a
I don't know how to deal with that it's very very weird right now
Don't like not even like
A number some of the language
Appreciate
He's not even like he's even like we normally agree with him he's right in the wrong way
Like he's dead on
This is 100% accurate
Cops are murdering black people and they are covering it up
Stop the problem 2009 it's still a problem but Alex is a problem
Alex has changed his tune aggressively
Since then
And now has
His
Aggressively pro-military in
Prokop
Positions
Because he's been
Cold perhaps
But that's his big guy
Audience
Or whatever but is it is it that or is it
Does it really just come down to
Sports
Like what's it wasn't possible for the right-wing to also at this time be like
Hey
Cop shouldn't be killing people
And then it became a thing where
A black person
And talked about
And they can't
Abide by that I mean it's possible I want one
2009 I have I have a subtle
Reason for what
Not subtle I have a bigger reason for why I'm doing this
So one of the other reasons I want to figure out like
His trajectory as a relates
At this point being very anti-military and
Psycop
Think it's because of Obama
I think it's just because Obama's president
Anything slip
Nations in WhatsApp
So if I understand correctly
Point of view
Is on this one
Is that maybe
The reason that he's against
The military and the cops right now
Because ultimately
He believes it's headed by a black
Maybe and when it becomes
Is headed by white person
Fine I don't think it's that
Simple but I don't know what I don't know is that plays in
To answer that question
Right I don't know if we can
I don't I don't know if
He could even answer
Christie Brinkley
I know that like one of the things that
Fascinates me the most is like
Things that
Are different
Blackwater he was against it
2009 loves Erik Prince
Yeah that's easy to explain its
It's Trump related that's that's giving up
In this case I'm I'm very fascinated and where
Did the pivot go of like
Cops are evil their sporting a terrible system
Sometimes you got a bad one but it's very rare
I don't know and we'll see
But he goes on to talk about another caller which
I thought that
Just popped in my mind
As far as
Alex talk
Talking about right now
How many abortion
Do you think Trump has babe
No idea
Hold on
A lot
This next court first
Perhaps a barrel
I'm in this excerpt he goes on
Where it does
About these
African-American soup
Chop by the police he talks about a caller
And I think that she's just a racer
But he has a different name of the different positions
Strange
These good old boys
What
Well listen here
Know-it-all control freak
Kill yourself
Okay
Don't sit there in the minority neighborhoods until 17 year old pregnant girls
And that's what those on Coast to Coast
Platinum track I don't understand
Where's the Starpoint where's endpoint how do they get there
No idea I don't know what to talk about
What he's describing is
Just erase a scholar on a talk show Broadway
Part of his imagine system that I'm afraid of
Shortly
That is still in place
Listen to thousand
Cosmology
Existed route
Entirety
Same way that I'm interested in things that are different
I'm also very
Things that are the same
And this idea that the
Eugenicist playing by the elites
Yeah stop that's
But this is almost
A cover
Story
I think now
Because the concept that he's putting forth here
Is that
The globalists are trying to divide us
Through race right right
That's that's his idea
I think if I understand correctly
There's a
He says the same
I'm saying but he's
Dividing Us by race
Consistent lie going on
But
Stopped
Talking about it or or like
Explaining it in the
Whenever he's describing her as being a
Globalist
Doesn't matter
He sees his imagined enemies every
He talks about like
The grocery store in someone's face turns into a demon
Like what was he
Yeah exactly
Mariana's is better go
Yeah
Yeah I don't know man
It's very weird
Listen to that clip that like
Oh you want other people to die why don't you kill yourself first
That that's fun that sounds like the open-mic version
But he did on air like
The other day in 2018
Read screaming about like
Kill yourself
And s*** like that
Tibet's fleshed-out the right version
We get to see the Raw on for a bit it's it's
So you asked me second to go how many abortions do you think Trump
Is paid for
And I don't know I can't answer that but I do know that Alex
In 2020
You paid for it
It's we do know that
Interesting
Is this in 2000
Control control
Their own future their own treasure
Because they're too lazy to get the baby
Okay
I mean what you going to do
This is every Catholic priest
Other people morality whilst you
Do as I say
Not as I do it's just interesting that this point new career he's not ready to open up
In the same way that he is now
Weather
Probably feels a lot well
That's true and I think if you were to in the middle of that rant where he's judging people for being too lazy
Directions
I'm if you were to say
I'm guilty
Abortion
Then I think that would have really hurt him
People just laugh at it
What's 6
How to take a m v in dogs
He's paid for at least
Four more married to Kelly
They have three kids together
No no I understand that but I don't think I think at that point Didn't you settle down
All of them
The abortion
That he has had whether or not that number is exaggerator
Atmos
I will give you a list
Intuit
Before 08
Woodward
Also in the brain
Price of a prize winner Alex
Before being married
Have
An elaborate book
A gambling book on this
About Alex Jones
Concepcion record
You can bet on that
In the same way that Alex
Probably would have been hurt by that information
In 2009 where is he
He's not hurt by it now
Yes
Another difference
Very interesting
Could not have
Was he good
No there's no videos
B was a little bit
Backstabber
One of his sponsors
Is So-Cal benzo
I really was helping you adjust.
Soap2soap Industries
Or
How been so
VyStar soaps
Alright
Eventually he went on to leave the soap industry and
Go to ice cream
Best friend
Call Jerry
Just to the chat room they're asking why I think he hasn't had abortions
Since he got married
There is a little bit of
I don't even know what you'd call it Purity by us on my part and maybe I'm wrong
Maybe I'm Wrong
But I think that given that they had three kids still believe in love
Hey maybe that's kind of what you believe in
That's a very cute and no it no point in my saying this in any judgemental
I'll admit my my flight
Four more than the answer to the question of what is life the universe and everything back to self
So
Alex has a soap sponsor
And in order to have him be a sponsor of the show
Alex makes
Clear that part of the deal
Is that the owner of the Soap Company
It's to be a guest on his show once a month
Alright
I wouldn't know the owner of this Oak
Brown here's that yours Alex introduced
Trying to get into
Guest appearance
This is the only soap to defend against 911
Genex War
Okay
I want to get into the soap
I want to get into this up with this is all related let me talk to you about Hitler
How do you get
To the bottom of the story
You follow this
Absolutely number one rule of Journalism
Omad
Brazy
So he tries to get in
To some of his narratives with the soap guy and I
Doesn't work out has work that well
Have you ever looked into Margaret
No
Hardcore
Walk on record
This is sad no
Alright we'll talk about what's wrong with detergent
We'll talk about detergent and millions more of that this guy is like
Talk about.
Sodium chloride
Being insult
Everybody's like oh what is this chemical it
Call salt is just a filler weed
Question you're out
It gets to this
Satisfaction guaranteed
Hair care products
How do I wash my hair after this morning
Good on-air read that is
Beautiful silky smooth
Strongman
English
I'm so I want this alley
This is this is Alex if you're listening God
Come back to this
This is a sad Alex because what you're seeing is
A guy who has to allow this
In order to
To be sponsored
I want
Sponsors
Badly
In terms of allowing us to
Continue doing this without
Me needing to
I'll give him a call
Never
I would never
Vince
Talk about your time working for the Alex Jones Show
No
I would I would
Never accept that as a stipulation of sponsorship
And it's clear Alex does make clear that part of the sponsorship is
He's on once a month
Yeah doesn't do anything about it. This is how the interview man
For five-star soap.com
Who is the young lady
What is bent
She went
Marty Schechter
Who's bad there's so much fun there because you've got the long pause
Alright
Great stuff
That's a
Limerick that's a
Fascinating glimpse into 1009 Alex
Ejected to this give me
Quick Limerick is my favorite sentence
Alex has ever said
It's clear I mean you can pick up
Context clues
Deliberate
Because that's what this guy is known for improvising limericks off the top of
And everybody's like you a******
To do he wants to go on air and do a limerick
Talk lyrics
Love it
Happened Larry Nichols you'd be back on the show
If you just figured out a way to talk about how you're not a duck
So something happen
About Alex
People making claims about him
First of all
Address public criticism
This one
Government operative info agents
Bring me to the point I'm at I love this rock
But I do have the answers
Absolutely
You have
I want you seriously
To try and guess what he's talkin
You know I want to go with Israel or something like that but I feel like that's not good either way
Serious enough to
Address on air
It's criticism for months
People have been emailing
You know what
I am going to go with
That's not the best way to hide your guns
Interesting
If that's not it
And so I guess I might as well at least
Chime in on it
Ridiculous
This is why mainstream people laugh
Are you question the government
One more one more
Beef vs. tofu
Because
Smart-mouth
Absolutely
The rest of us who were questioning the official government story that's almost always a liar
Fluoride
Look
But
People actually believe it
It's almost crazy to come on Aaron
It is a little crazy
Cool
A little
2 point lighting
What
Yeah
So just be at before you respond to that about a minute later
Do you make some
Beneficial state
No I'm 35 years old and
That's a very mean thing to say
I mean I think it is a mean thing to say in terms of like Bill Hicks is on life
Right
Like if you have any respect for Bill Hicks it's
Insults
Slater's specials weren't that great
Are they true
Comic
Either
This is fascinating
To make is he wouldn't
Wouldn't
F******
Or he would have come up with a better spin on it than just I'm not Billick
Maybe you should go back to being like people from time to time
He has done that like you going back to the well as like
Pieces
Play with that.
Which which should be the easiest way to tell he's not
His satire
Garbage
Pretty bad
Has no grasp on what's that
Even at his worst Bill Hicks was better at that tire than
Alex Wildman in 2000
Isla Fisher
To make a big
Production out of
I'm saying like
This Is How They invalid
Questioning the government story on 9/11
They just keep calling me
Write everything
Beckett
I would say he was Bill Hicks
Make some more legitimate
Like I all right look I tried to play a little charade but
I just didn't want my
Password to be
Involved in my present work I created new identity for myself
Part of that
Not a big
Major Crimes
Text Brian
Plane hijack
D.b. cooper d.b. cooper
Isabel Hicks Cooper
So
Now at this point
We get to Alex Jones
Giving us
A lift
Globalist
Remember the story from a week or two ago
The carryout eugenics
The car of overpopulation
Through a world government
For your own good
Is Michael Bloomberg is Oprah Winfrey
And they met at Rockefeller University
President
Private home
Regardless there
Conspicuous
George Soros
Also
Write another conspicuous
Glow known globalist
How else do you have to move
You know
I mean
This is probably larger picture of what I'm most
Interested in it and looking back on
Episode is when did George Soros come into play
See here we already looked at that episode
With Sarah Russo
I talked about that all this s*** no mention
Documentary about the globalist agenda and their plan for enslavement
And now here we are in 2009
Global
And no mention of Soros
Right now I also want to be clear I do know a little bit that I should
Just tell everyone
I do know that in 2000
Glenn Beck
Does a
Fart
Tonight's special
About how George Soros
Anti-semitic nonsensical things that has ever been aired on television
Credible blowback
Yeah and by working Theory and we will see if this is
I'm not entirely sure
But
Suspicious
Alex Jones got on the Soros tip
Before that
And that's why
You think so Glenn Beck ripped that off
And that
Glenn Beck in those weird creepy Circle actually going to go with the opposite
I'm going to go with this is our qanon situation
All over again and he gets
Soros a little bit after Glenn
PCS Glenn Beck getting all this at
Right so then he jumps on Soros
And that's why he's pissed off at
The climb back is because he doesn't get to
Take credit for
Either these things are possible and we'll see
Free as it plays out
Cuz neither of us know
Agreed we have hunches and we'll see
So far mine of all been wrong and yours tend to be right
The fact that I have
Remind maldron
This dumbass hole
Mexico versus
About
Humanist
Eugenics future
King s*** up
So fun
It's so fun to know for sure
But even in 2009 he was just making
She things are well now there's thousands
Thousand
Wired Magazine
Why the future doesn't need us
Conference
With 200 top players
It was very upsetting
Subaru Outback
Killing everybody
This this professor doctor
Report CIA operative
Acquit
And starts
Baume & Key
Total grid
Merging with cybernetics
So real quick
Text Cynthia was crazy
So did Alex just come on Aaron be like
The Unabomber had some good ideas man that's all I'm saying and then later
He's the guy at the party
You do not want to be anywhere near Michael's B
He's Drew Michaels B
Forgot about that
My bad babe
Couple things that I want to point out is that article
Why the future doesn't need us
Ted Kaczynski is all Alex Jones red
Cuz all of the other stuff.
He's talking about about like people like
Elite making a decision whether or not
That's all from the Ted Kaczynski quote
He's taking that it.
Being Bill Joyce position
Whichever it is
Not
If you go to a website knowledge, I have an entire big write-up that I've done on Bill Joy why the
Future doesn't need us
And why Alex Jones
You're find a link to the actual article
Worth it it's enjoyable
But it explains
Are notated
Version of the Unabomber
Yeah absolutely did you do that on our website
VM saying that but I might do
This for my next block.
I'm just going to put up that good this week
Unabomber Manifesto
?
Shrugging emoticon
This next clip is weird I think it matches up
Put some of Alex's ideas
In the present but I don't I don't know where
Information from
Super f***** up
And also a
Little bit
He's not around to start Hunter on
Know Rodger Stone
Barebones Alex Jones making up s*** hole
We know in his world have been around for a long time
I don't know why those guys might be around I just have
I'm coming to an end
And white
Social workers that ask him questions
Because
We've got a nice foster home especially of your blonde hair
Girl she better be careful
Cimarron
A few weeks ago from Georgia
Where she was naming names
I don't believe this. Walmart is everybody watching
They can a smell
Walmart gets a few grand.
Walmart in pizza places in everybody
Grid
Walmart get the commission
On the
Kidnapped
Kids are on the kitchen
Kidnap
I'm more curious about
Does the employee or Walmart LLC
Now maybe the employee gets a little bit of
Cash kicked
Is like
It isn't just indicted million and they only get a few thousand dollars
Finder's fee
Solutely
That did this to me is like
The perfect encapsulation of the Alex Jones narratives you don't
I like to research
And not the kind of thing I like to research cuz I could just
I smell it in my
I want to research
I really want to find out is to find out
That Walmart
If
There was a senator
Who was making these plans
And the week before that you have a senator from Georgia
And not say the
You better remember that.
If a senator was
These sorts of allegations
It looked into
Need to figure out a paper trail of
Kidnapped
Kickback to walk
Walmart
Let's be even catch that f******
Clear that
Walmart is a billion-dollar company they don't give a f*** about $2,000 for helping
Kidnap children
So
Build your you build your Empire on the
I think what you really come down and that by that I mean
Alex Alex resent
Video child
Tube services
Which to me is like
I don't know
I don't know why you don't want
Abused children
To have resources department
I don't know I mean you put this phone on air
Spurious
Accusation not alright
Aggressive
Violent gun rights debate 28
Transphobic video
A one-point
Very
Very agree
I don't know if we can make those sorts
He's just doing the version of the guy who's like
Well they hit me when I was a kid and I turned out fine
Your answer to that should be like well
Some of you turn out to be Alex Jones so maybe if I can figure it out
B b b
But what I want to talk more about it
Is the idea that lie
Like this this child protective
Evil or weird because they're asking
Kids were
They come into their purview
Are you okay
Right
I don't think
That's an evil thing at all
I think that's what I'm doing there
Your job Mommy
Because Daddy hit you
Kids a chance
Tubi
Savefrom
Abuse
Falcons against the back cuz
The family or whatever
I got to say I
A hundred percent
Verbena
What would you say to GPS
Social worker that asked that question
Right
I would say no to it
Okay
Indifference
They know where I was
That's a good way of putting it there the rod spoil the child by friend
Nancy I've only realized
We're bad as an adult
I would have said I wouldn't of articulated it back then
But be that as it may
That's my way of getting away from this uncomfortable territory we have
On this side
Third
Episode
Missguided
Did you ever wonder how Alex
No
F*****'-a
You're right
I should have
Please consider that for some reason
Alex Jones knowing Jesse Ventura has made the most sense of anything that they show has ever
Is just like
Like I don't know how to find out how he met
We'll see what
Musician best-selling author
Jesse Ventura
Kinky Friedman
Stop
Separately
I ran into a movie
Contact
What do you know about Kinky Friedman
I used to know a lot more but that's one of those things
No matter how much you forget about somebody you're never going to forget the name kinky
Jeffrey Friedman
Kinky Friedman
Is
Really
Cool
Business being on Alex Jones this year
Both Texans
And kind of dude
That's all you need I'm going to tell you a little bit about Kinky Friedman before we get into the internet
In the 1970s Kinky Friedman was it a parody country band called Kinky Friedman and the Texas jewboys
He's already
They played such songs as get your biscuits in the oven and your buns in the bed
They Ain't Makin Jews Like Jesus Anymore
Celebrating his country Judaism
No I don't lie
Not to profile
I guess that Kinky Friedman was
Set alarm
He toured with Bob Dylan and 1976 on the road
Start of Saturday Night Live remember that he was a musical
Episode
Saturday Night Live in 1976
Will host with Steve Martin
How awesome is that that's so cool super
This course he started writing mystery novels
Super successful after his music
Music career ran its course
It's like well course
Can you play the Grand old Opry
I don't know if this is entirely true but he claims to be the first full-blooded Jewish person
Who's ever played the Grand old Opry
That's possibly true that's amazing
Play the off today have any books about my local library
Even more than his musical career he started writing mystery novels
This is great
Yeah who is finished up a musical career included
Atlanta Braves
No
Kinky Friedman was the character's name
And then move to New York start
Love it I would love this I love this so much
Then in 2006 for governor of Texas
Of course I hope it follow in the wake of Jesse Ventura becoming governor of Minnesota in 1999
Schwarzenegger California's governor 2003
I didn't see that coming
Ventura and kinky were good friend
I love it
Quote my platform is to remember that when they went out searching
A Sam
Listen to try and persuade him to be the governor
And he was the greatest Governor the state has ever had
Sleeping under a bridge with the Indian
Like it
I'm a big fan of that he sold shirts with his slogan kinky 2006 why the hell not
I love it
Absolute Showman
And on the campaign Trail he would say things like quote if I win the first thing I'll do is demand a recount
A promise
But if elected the first Jewish governor of Texas he would reduce the speed limit to 54.97 it
He's so funny
Great from everything I get I mean
There is every breed of the show
Truly I think I think there's a little bit of a
How much
Hey are you making out of your Judaism
At the expense of Judaism
And that's kind of like that's not a
Question I can answer
I think he's
Hilarious on the on the list of things I'm going to
Care about really hard
How much
Hey Kinky Friedman made out of his Judaism
Way down there I've tried to find like horrible things about him and I can't find all that much
If you accept the GI band called
Kinky Frank
Friedman and the Texas jewboys you're fine
And it was really fun
But he ended up getting 12.6
Percent of the vote
Coming in fourth out of six candidates
Texas governor race
That's a lot more than I kind of thought he would have
Of crazy awesome fun lunacy
So although kinky is a fun riddle text
Alex should not like
Absolutely
Because kinky is a very public
About being friends with both Bill Clinton
George
W bush
You wrote in an article in Texas monthly about Clinton
I was just minding my business one day 7 years ago promoting my latest mystery novel at a book signing
In Austin at Barnes & Noble
That's the greatest since I've ever
I just told the crowd that the reading and signing were free but there would be
Tattoo latte minimum
A guy came up to mom quotes
Find one for the present
I didn't think the book was really going to Bill Clinton so I signed one of my standard scripture
Yours in Christ or see you in hell
And forgot about it
Fun two weeks later the postmaster in Medina brought me an Express envelope and said Niger
Excited tone
Kinky you've got a letter from the White Horse Saloon
You know that place in Nashville where they do all the line dancing
I looked at the envelope it did not say White Horse it said White House
Inside the envelope with the letter from President Clinton
And at the bottom he had written I have now read all your books
More please
I really need to laugh
And that was the beginning of a three-year penpal relations
During which we discussed many things
Foreign affairs
Baltimore metaphysics
Hey my Bill Clinton tell me
Bill Clinton
Made foreign policy decisions
Baytown Kinky Friedman
Maybe I don't know
About bush
Quote I first met George W bush but four years ago at the text
Facebook festive
At the time he was just thinking about running for president
Then I was just thinking about having another Chavez Regal
Skyscraper
He's a good writer to
In a flash of misguided inspiration I taken Larry McMurtry
Unclaimed nametag
Slapped it on
In a matter of
Larry McMurtry
In a matter of moments people were coming up to me and telling me how much they admired my work
Not wanting to burst their bubble in Fairly hammered by then I played along
You've done so much for Texas mr. McMurtry one lady told me thank you kindly I replied
The governor having witnessed
This little Exchange
I don't know all his work whatever it is so George W bush
At that point
Right
Look Governor I said
McMurtry the shy little booger
He never do this for himself I'm just helping the old boy at with a little PR
George W bush and whispered something to several of his aides
But nothing happened
I asked one of the aides what he said he told me the governor is said I want that guy from my campaign manager
I
Lovelace
George W bush it isn't one of the few moments
Pure joy I've ever experienced
George W bush
Come to the White House which he does
Awkward
Discussing his friendship with George W bush and Bill Clinton
I just got sick the friendships that he has
2 presidents
Some might ask
Particularly particularly in these days
How to pray
Can afford to maintain such a light-hearted friendship
The answer is particularly these days
Everyone needs a laugh and everyone needs a friend
Also
As early as
Kinky was saying in interview
Use that he did not believe that rifle should be allowed with magazine
Higher than 5
So
He's friends with to globalist president
And believes in gun control
But because he's famous
Alex is totally cool.
Losses past all of that Alex is Principe
Also
Be clear his name is kinky
But it's not meant to be a dirty
That's not too bad like sexual kink
I didn't care one way or the other
Curly hair
Interesting Lee his nickname was given to him by a guy named that
Who who would mysteriously now also
Stop it
This person would also go on to be a parody country artist
They released an album called country p***
A1976
I want to listen to that which was distributed
A hundred percent
A hundred thousand copies
I think you can
The album
The album included such songs as one of the title
Come stains on the pillow
Yes
More
Rental cars
Where your sweet head used to be
One of the other titles
Sit on my face
To go down in his class
Recover later and still does
I performed by Merle Haggard
Yeah that's a winner
Man
So why do we even need to hear him talk I just want that biography forever
I don't think you really does anything to invalidate himself on this episode he just shows up as I can't
Run for governor
And then just acts kind of like an a****** but
We learned that he sells cigars
Okay
He actually has that
Cigars and I your website and Williams.
Cigars cigarettes bad cigar
That's my message to young people
And help you live longer
All right.
So this you know what
I'm still fly
I'm still fine with that
This
I'm still fine with this sets the tone and leads up to this
Really be arrested
Friedman lights of a Cuban cigar on air
Not giving a s***
It's pretty great a lot of nonsense about and running
I forgot her again cuz
Say discuss police
Corruption a little bit
I put your mic down put your mic
I'm weighing
This is so wild
Buckwild
Cops in Austin or plant drugs
Here's one solution
Get a guy like Kinky Friedman in as governor who doesn't know anybody that doesn't know anybody okay and I appoint
I got like a racehorse Haynes
Head up
Antabuse Commission
And this is a legacy for a guy like racehorses in other words he doesn't need to do it he's got plenty of money
He believes in Justice
Case by case
All through death row all through Texas youth Commission
Through all of it
Empower these people I don't want to commission a report
He wants to put a guy named to racehorse in charge of police corruption
Agree with him
Resource has been on the wrong end of police corruption
I'll take
For sure
I love it
Look racehorses is a legacy position
Thousands of cops
Holyshit
Cell phone
Sofa
Alex has no glitches probably be great actually
I think it would be awesome
Yankees appearance cuz most of it is really just Aiko
He doesn't have any of his like
Standard Market
On the show it mostly Alex just trying to impress him and it's kind
It's a little sad
And he has to make time cuz he has another guy
This day
Is a guy who does one of his
Bumper songs
The song
Do the Renegade
I don't know this song You Don't Know It
No
Can play it it's fine
Under the radar
Country
New wischkaemper it's like it's alright if not old rebel country
And I
This clip
Facebook in trouble
I live in Southern California most of the time
And
Illegal streaming across the border and that was the year the riots in Los Angeles
All that kind of stuff
I got the point where I could
Play anymore
Wrote a song
From my heart called we must take America back
And
It just to it live Firestorm when people hurt it
Out there on its own
Out there wanted to put it out on a record
Make it available nationally
I was right
Zooming up the charts guts numbered print
2 on the billboard country charts
No
Powerful
Influential
Free radio stations in the big city
Always with your stomach
And that was the end of my RCA career
Oh
Ma'am
Alex ends up playing his song we're not going to listen to it but it made me
Delivery
As it should be
I've been living
SoCal furlough
Frustrated
So I wrote a song about it
Negotiable
Absolutely you noticed I got pissed off with these illegals coming over also
That was the year of the riots
Illegal said so now I have to make a song called
We have to take our country back from where you inspire to the Mexicans and black people
Not sucked up at all
While they're talking about
Nero we must take our country back
Song reached number 6
68.
Made it clear that
Police are framing and murdering black
People
Out of
Bulshit racist reasons still having a guy on strong
Should be allowed to take that back
The song reached number
68 on the hot country charts which leads me to believe it
Was never the most requested song
67 songs ahead of it
People like you
Didn't play
Make a regular chart at all but it's actually really enjoy
Sing the sky Steve valves
It's vaus
He does have four Grammy
To his name
Wild Ghostriders he's a songwriter
Four Grammy nominations
Under a stage name
Buck howdy
His stage name is Buck howdy
Actually want a Grammy in 2010
In the category best Spoken Word album
For children
Alright yeah I'm in it so far
So he's still a country musician today if you go to his Squarespace site
Chivas.com refers to himself as he probably sitting on it
Your first himself as Grammy award-winner hoping that people will just think it's because of his
Country music
Who was the
How much do we have
The show we got to listen to the entire King
Thank you for even catalog
And this has become on the pillow absolutely
You got to listen to come on my pillow
Parentheses
Where your head used to be this brings us to the end of the show
And what we see here is Alex having
Racist musician on
Yep one of the greatest people ever to come out of Texas Kinky Friedman odds to smoke on air for now
What we see here is very clearly in 2000
90s
Concerned with globulin
Right has no interest in George Soros
He's very anti-military
Anti-cop
Auburn same time does recognized
Getting a f****** Raw Deal
And all
At some point weird
Except for his strfkr
No that's consistent
And the dumb
Relying on him not understanding
Primary sources
Has been better is if he
Did a like
I wrote a little song about this
Appearance or just told Alex
Alright we are at this up I got to be
Ferret.com
You are you're also capable of finding us on iTunes you have to search for the words
Knowledge
And then fight that's true if you search
Knowle we are the
The eighth thing that pops up on Saturday
Oh okay
I think it's you you got
Falcon go f*** himself I wrote a f****** racist country song
Alex
Same color with huge fan I love your work