Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Go to the round drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Is there a hook to the b*******
Automatic classic Vines
I don't know
Front of the show
People seem to enjoy its
I don't know what's fun about that
I know it's fun for me but
Look out for a couple of portmanteau is coming later we'll see if that happens
Theater near you
So I would like to give a shout out to a new donor what's going on out there Rebecca
Thank you so much
Rose Rushmore for anybody who likes the thrilling adventure hour
If you like to be a much like Rebecca you can do so by
Accordingly
It does support the show we really appreciate it
Cuz you know
This is why we're Where We Are
Appreciate because Dan couldn't survive without it let Ruth
Hayward probably a honey
Maybe a hundred
$150 a month away for like
Legitimate comfort
Or like
Survival level
I'd like to get there without having to sell out
Any further down this stock
Cancel Jordan wants to kill white people
Search Jordan today we are
I imagine being as we are insects
Client
Yeah the only reason we would be spotted like
We would accept spaces a sponsor but only if they just gave us free
It's got to be a piece of it you got to get a little bit of taste like
Is that all you get
Whichever one probably gases that we would
Baby going over at Matty's
Tuesday
Alex Jones
Did he
Press conference
From Washington d.c. to the swap to confront these
Got to do it
Spoiler alert
Disaster
Good disaster like not a fun
Entertaining disaster it was just
The press conference was the equivalent of a comic
You can't get on Comedy Central
Can't get book
So they booked out a small theater make their own special
It's basically like no one wants you
No one wants you
But make it look like they do
So he rents a room in the National Press Club and then just does his normal bit
She doesn't like
Let me
Say on it
A couple clips of that
Something that is way more important
The cross here
Clips of the actual press conference
Coverage of the rest of the press conference
Or go look at rightwingwatch
They covered the
Standard stop
You wouldn't pick up on necessarily unless you knew
Too much which I do
Here's the first thing in this is the sort of an out-of-context drive but I can visit the most offensive thing
That
Resizing the entire Prescott
F*** you telling us to bring it
Brinks market share this almost
Do they have like two guys working on it
No like
We're never going to compete on that front
Office gets exploded by a meteor in case
Let's stay around on the off-chance
Story that you see on that the headlines about his press conference
He went over and growth of the American
Can flag
That is because someone asked him about his connection
Americana
And he goes over and starts kissing
It was okay but it was just lectionary according to the uniform code
I believe a violation
Like a prosecutable
Touch the ground
Kneeling during the national anthem is of course the worst thing that
And they should never be given a job sir
Essentially f****** a flag that's all whatsoever except
The guy was trying to
A very legitimate question that is like Alex you have been appearing on Russian television you have your
You keep reposting without permission stories for Marty all of your narrative seem to be Putin
Apologetic narrative Rogers down your story doesn't really
Really make sense
Lee Stranahan this other guy who's there you literally work for Sputnik
You like you have to understand why people are asking question
Start screaming
Tiny flag
And I over at that song
Dry cleaners
I have a theory
I think that the press conference that he did was mostly
Desperation move cuz
He doesn't say anything he doesn't say normally
He was wanted to make a big splash out of it but I wasn't
Suing him
I think that's I think that might have been one of the lead objectives of him going
Do this press conference
And in this clip
He's just head
Lee Ann McAdoo come up
For a little while
And she does this like
I'm afraid of public reopening was the opening comics
Murderers Row of losers
What's going on
Press conference
Was Jack Purcell
It was Lee Ann McAdoo Millie Weaver
Jerome corsi
You had Jerome corsi Hadley at least ranahan
You had that
Do the Cardinals announcer
Everyone was drunk
Spoiler alert
Pictures of movie star right
You have
Do you have the end McAdoo up there I don't know if she's actually afraid of public speaking or anything like that none of her behavior
Run the show order
Live reports where she goes out and talks people on the street
Indicate that she has a fear of public
I don't know I'm afraid of addressing crowds but I'm here
And I think there's a little bit of it that's trying to make a feeble victim out of her and Alex
And then if anybody attacks her that it turns into like
Which is exactly where the eclipse start
How do I do that
This is Lily.
Also really really sorry about this deep sound is terrible and it's because none of them
Have Mike technique
We're going to be some stuff that's a little bit lower than you wanted
Tubi
Daffodil
Alright
The camera
Blink twice
Sentiment
That's a lie versus actual
Make it all up
We got it
Brake table
Call Jessie George Soros
Sarcastic
I'm telling you he's a superhero
Voice
Quantum
Soros
You are a hero that killed Hitler
Anderson Cooper
Turn into werewolves
How about off Hitler
Great movie
Like there's no part of this that is like
You would expect professionalism
And to be fair he does have his lawyer speak for a little while
It's sort of profession
Alex Jones lawyer none of this is admissible
I do not want anyone to know what it happen
Don't snitch advise my client not doing this adventure
I will advise him
Not to have switch is not possible Lord knows the media is not covering this
I think I can cover this
They're not going to because it's clearly stupid
The horribly offensive bulshit that you say
I'm even better not really because most of the articles are about him groping the flag
Like that
Which is to get reasonably inocuas compared to what we're going to be talking about
After we discuss
The
The Prescott
Is that we have
Cuz it's way more important and no one
Has been talkin about that
We just really whatever one
I'm should be talkin about
Before we get to that
Hi we are getting
Appearance of Rodger Stone
Alex
Rodger Stone should have left the country by now
He's there
He's standing up and fighting
He's going to be there he's going to
You f****** a deal already
Ric Flair of Infowars
Like he's a political dirty so like of course he's like
I know what I did
I know what they can find out I did
I'm going to go ahead and get a little bit
Detection and that's why he's acting like he hasn't gotten that deal
I don't know at least some of the interviews where is like
Alt-right credibility
Also I think it's what we talked about all the time
Cuz he also wants to f*** with people
Perfectly with what we know because otherwise
He's in Washington DC for the
Suppress
Hey what think I think is really awesome is it Alex's so distracted that he doesn't realize that he brings up Rodger Stone twice
He's brain breaks
Bring them back up well after like two other speakers or so
About this guy
He gets up there and he does a bit
Tattoo on my
Which is a daily reminder
Things don't go your way
The only person you know
Couple laps
One of them
Alex really loud and the friend who's there along at the show
Hey you got
You got it without you still got it
And that f****** joke
He has the same joke like a million times
And also
Like we were talking about Andrew Breitbart episode about Larry Sinclair
The guy who claimed to have blown Obama in the back of the limo after doing crack cocaine with right
The Press Club press conference
The accusations or whatever his lawyer if you'll recall
Was wearing a kilt
And you know his lawyer
We're fine for some people who don't
Large dick
In the Press Club during a proud
I'm kind of a fan of that
It's
Rogers moment
Like that that's your press conference sucks
It's almost it's almost like a comedy magician
We're going to throw all these sleight-of-hand techniques at
Adicto good every now and again you're going to forget that I'm shity at both right you'll be surprised
So this next clip is a question from someone in the army
In the audience asking question
And I don't think you'll understand what he's talking about
Most people dead
But I do
Cuz I'm crazy
An expert
If you're down my show
Crowdsourcing
On YouTube
Any presented
He presented a document that was given to him
Contact
Department of Homeland
Security
The indicator
Was applied for
For the March for our lives
Prior
To the shooting
And he said
The indicator
Something
The difference
We've been talk
Video received an anonymous strike
People who think they've got First Amendment right
As Anonymous avatars on the internet we don't even know if that's a person
Dexter being artificial
Intelligent
Maybe someone operating out of a country
It is not protected
Institution of the United States United States
The face my accuser
And know what I mean
So that's powerful information
Alex knows that name
It's a plug relay
Mcgard
Because he holds the acts of Damascus
He's a frequent guest on Project Camelot
Love it
Kerry Cassidy false flag guy I love it we haven't listened
Episodes that have him
Crazy Richard's episode
Depressing
Dumb just not fun and more like oh you're making up all this s*** you have sources who tell you all this nonsense
It's crazy
To me that this is a really interesting illustration
Just how close
Camelot world
And Alex Jones world really are
They are not that far apart you have a guy who is
Interviewing
On his YouTube show
Mom is from Europe somewhere
Denmark
I'm not entirely sure
He goes on all kinds
Sounds like YouTube conspiracy shows
That are just like weird people with the webcam
Essentially us
Not
But
A better tomorrow
Simcam that's not a good idea
I don't know man
I don't
I don't know what further point I have
On this other than
It's fascinating
Tumi
Just be that name come up
I feel like
Discovering this should
Be like oh my God
Look at this look at the connection
But knowing
Water when I was
Watching this
Really
Press would be like
Oh well Olay dammegard of course is the
Because
What
What does Alex the only reason I'm interested
Because Alex called it
Powerful in
Also Hoosick
Crowdsource the truth is what this guy is from
Is that YouTube show
Alex
And a lot of
Because
There is a guy for right walk there
Super excited they are people like
Mothers for Trump
A trump
Talk
I went to the mothers for Trump website and they have like a issues
Button
Compressed and it links to Donald Trump donaldjtrump.com
Dot-com his position as interesting that if you click that link it says 404 page not found
Inspiring
Mothers for Trump obviously don't really know how to use
Let's be honest
Automatically
This is the end of what I want to talk about in terms of Prescott
It's just
It's just nothing
Do they redo it
Wait what
So Alex
And he's sort of just it's not a variant
Interesting show but immediately after the show
He did a free-for-all question-and-answer thing at the Marriott Mayweather Hotel
The ballroom to save the Marriott nose like that sounds right
They basically just redid the press conference where they just had
Minus Lee Ann McAdoo come up and give slightly different speeches
And it's important to notice
What the differences are
They know that it's a place
How many watchful eyes
Fair in front of a friendly audience
And so it turns into a
A white nationalist Nazi rally
I totally saw that coming
No one's talking about
Alex Jones had this big to channel
Did you go and listen to it there is
Distance
Really troubling things that are being said by people
A couple of them even
Earlier we were in front of the press but now I know we're all friends
Which is
Not great you want to hear any white person say ever know
There's never been a situation where I've heard at like after a show if some dude is like
Hey let me tell you some
That automatically means you're about to hear erased
Okay bro you're cool
We're on the same team
You want to hear me say the n-word a few times no
I'm getting I'm making a little bit of a
Declaration of
Listen to
I stand by what I'm saying
But before we get to that
Here's three minutes of before the press conference
Eyewear Alex Jones
I think
Fink's
Jordan klepper is trying to get into the question-and-answer
Session
It hasn't started yet
And Alex is clearly drunk
Wait so he thinks
The outside
Jordan klepper
Fighting to get in them doors
He's talking to a guy
That is not on camera
Might be Jordan klepper
But I don't know that it is
She wants everyone to think that it is
Haha
I can't say one way or another
But this is Alex
Very clearly drunk
Talking to someone
Who he does not want
On this question
Chuck-E-Cheese
Chuck-E-Cheese rap
That's not a good thing
Call Tess Cantrell
This goes on for like another form
Chuck-E-Cheese the rat over and over again
Great that's a solid move
Has his traditional drunk thing
Possibly
Positive reinforcement is like
This going to last forever
Time to work
The first time but that it does not work the second
So you might be asking why the f***
Screaming Chuck-E-Cheese the rat
Kind of weird thing to yell
A lot of that
Chucky
Chi-Chi's the earlier
I heard him say brains
Yeah that take your brain Force
Alright
Just going to plug Hotel Ballroom
A couple of these people do plugs
It's interesting
Teleprompter reader
Yes
And then later on
What is ostensibly Jordan klepper
Says
Allowed to
Accuse anybody of anything I want
Free speech
Sure does sound like Jordan
That's a very bad things
Bad
Isn't he supposed to be
Supposed to come up with better
He would have sent Tim baltz
Or something like that you would have sent other people
Who was Alex doesn't know who they are
Chuck-E-Cheese the red
Cuz I don't understand what that means
Radioactive
I'm so out finally about 5 or 6 minutes in
Into this video that he posted finally
Robbed it was like
This way
Alex if you want to Mike
That's illegal
Yeah that's that's copyright Michael Buffer is going to sue you
Comedy Central
Comedy Central roast
Sad
I want to just before we get to this the premise to be clear
This as
Feel like to our question-and-answer session
Not that
Anyway
There's no call
There's no no calls
Ballroom
It's respectable but
Based on his pretenses about his audience you would think
The room would be over swelling it's not
You would hope it's very it's very
Modest
And in turn out
And
Like I said
He just redoes the
The press conference
He just had all the same people come and give speeches
I meant at the end gets
2 some questions
And it's unfortunate does
Cuz one of these questions
Gets asked
Is one of the most crazy things I've ever heard
On Infowars
What is a big
Big pronounce
It will blow your mind
Okay it will absolutely
But we have to go through a little bit of bulshit to get there
Here's Chuck-E-Cheese rat
Chuck-E-Cheese the rat bastard
Chuck-E-Cheese the rat which will be his new meme
What is known as
50 years from now
When he goes on to Valhalla
What is that was not a big
What is a globalist rat book
Like
Jews
Chuck-E-Cheese the rap
Robots when you're home
Anyways I'm sorry
Solid
Inside that is
If
Globalism is what you're against
And it's a philosophy
Safid of trying to
Undermine nationalism and National sovereignty in order to sell out to multinational corporations and what have you
If that's what you're really mad about that doesn't have a physical component to it
If you're talkin about why these people
Look like globalist
Generally speaking that means that you are talking about something
That is
Something about their appearance
What is easy really busy
Think that the global is look like hipster is that what
I mean it could be
It could be anybody who looks
Not as white as a
If it's next to skip over it I think
It's not that great
Cambridge analytica about how like
Information
So what
Remember when you railed against the Patriot Act
Scraping account
Spore data it's not
Like
A little bit isn't mining just scraping the ground for s*** and he's not taking into account
How would the actual thing they did
Where they
Encroached on other people.
Accounts through accounts that they had
That's another wing of their operations
Can stop a lot of it was
Gaining access to personnel
Account and then by accessing sad that they were able to get information for
From a bunch of
All of their friends
Two billion accounts information were stolen when only when they only had
At the beginning is like 400 million
He also tries to bring in like an idea that people think that it was identity theft and all it is is
Taking it
Texas
That was never reclaim
The people are making
Right so anyway he runs us
The whole thing
Pointed out is that
Metadata
Can be used
To influence a ton of s*** like
It's disgusting how much data
We we actually put out there
You can learn from things that you don't think actually says all that much
Right
But I mean
You get just a very amount of information from somebody and you know how terrible people are at remembering
Passwords or like those
I forgot my password
What's a what's your mother's maiden name
It's easier to do than anybody wants to imagine
Runs out of steam really quick on this brings up Rodger
My mother's maiden name
That's a shame
Tough to spell
Inspired a little bit
Because of a bad diabetic
Doesn't reduce dick on the front and the back
Alyssa
But
Then he gets off he's he's a he's generous with his time does it take five or so
Alex
Come back up
Who's this
Super f****** weird
Truck
Crushing
Nicole swap example
Sellout
Your resources
Quite frankly
That
The claims over
You'll notice first of all no applause after that
Staring at him like
Boy
Is Galaga
Stand up
Yeah whatever
I hope do it anyways like
To do a trump
Style rally
There's a couple people every now and again little applaud certain things in my head
It's not a raucous
They probably are like
It's not 1000%
He's like four
The more the more important thing to do is there in that clip you saying that
He's now concerned
The Trump is going
Too far in the other direction
Sure
What is that Alex
What is that
Too far with nationalism
What happens when people go there with nationalism
18 different examples of TT going too far with nationalism things International
Believe it of ever happen
So he even said that
Really expire
Again I think he's drunk
But anyway
On record
They haven't
Motels
No it's not
Got it Brandon Gilmore
That's good he's getting help from the Georgetown
Civil rights
Feels like he has to specifically point out Inner City
Always really saying is
Black
Surprises me that he didn't have diamond and silk
Hazel
Why not you're going all out for this
You got a ride other
Trump weirdo why not why are all of your people still White
Like why is it like you're trying to do this Optics involved why don't you at least get some of
The creeps
Right
Diverse Creek
They're all creeps on his team
But at least there are a couple who like
You would add
Diversity youth Shield yourself from the attack of like
Millie Weaver Rob do Alex Jones Rodger Stone Jerome corsi
Lee Stranahan
Lucian wintrich
Lucian wintrich is the whitest name I've ever heard before.
We've gotten Jakari Jackson to run down the aisle head with a chair
I bought Jakari Jackson
Comic book
It's fine
It's not about Alex at all I would have loved
To discover that he
Tremendous Talent
It's very cute
It's about a
Like a young child who doesn't
Applied himself well
Because he's too busy daydreaming
The description that you busy daydreaming of a segregated Society description that we read as it led us to believe
Leave the possibly this was about like to put a
Projection about Alex
I'll give you a call at your earliest
Watch
American Way
That's a federal filing
Real quick break
Let's take a step back and
Consider all of the people that he has on the show
Who have connection
Koch brothers related to think tanks or
He still talks
Lord monckton on mobile
This is all nonsense
Soros
You say Soros overthrew countries
All former communist authoritarian rule
Fake left
Audience
Stop
No we're talkin about
George Soros
Funding you
He doesn't he also says that like Chuck-E-Cheese the rat
Who ostensibly is Jordan klepper
Can come on
He doesn't allow that
That man right there
George
Nazi collaborator in the world
Call there's more
Financing
Georgetown law
Overtime
First Amendment
First of all there is literally zero chance that a civil lawsuit could overturn a Amendment to the
The Constitution
Completely absurd cockamamie.
Rulings
Even
If you allow for what Alex believes about George Soros
To be true
If you allow that which it's not
But if you believe that he helped Roundup Jews as a fifteen-year-old
That's still not a
Top-level
Not
Oculus in Hitler's
There was.
When he was 12
That's ridiculous nonsense
How much
Absolutely
Despises left it there
Liberal
Libra
And then at the same time is super mad at fake left
How that could possibly work earlier he just said
Leftist
I just call them
Regular if you hate left
So much why are you concerned with the
Purity of their last album
Music music Michael calls himself a classical liberal which makes
Now and then
Regular liberal
Which makes no sense either and then he also hates
What is
He was he's just angry
What other than white nationalism
Sucks it up
Cupid step up the other thing that I think is really sucked up in
My clip is
I mean I know it's a small crowd
But at the same time you still have a guy
Who's yelling at the podium
This guy works for a Nazi collaborator
Furthermore
Year-old Oskar Groening
Simon wiesenthal
Escaped
Escape
Nazi Collaborators
All of these are older than George Soros and the murders
Collaborate
I know that I already said that
Repeating
He's
Pointing out someone in the crowd
Who is a journalist
This guy works for a Nazi
This guy works for George Soros
I like a much larger audience
With a more charismatic person at the helm then Alex Trump did the exact same thing
You could turn that into
Do something very dangerous
This guy
That's very close to like this guy is part of the Union
I feel very
Ratably uncomfortable about that
Just because George Soros has donated
Do a sound ation
Is it May
Donate
To rightwingwatch
Or one of these organizations
You don't understand level I do still despise
That you just described you know like
Oh well he can't be mad at George Soros
For donating to all of these things
Whenever
He is
The Holden to Koch brothers and all of those things
No I'd like batter frustrated infuriates me as well
The topic has come up and maybe there are new people listening who don't know are staying
Plugging super into Soros like the reality that he is not a Nazi collaborator
It's like a beneficent
King like
Get the first part is
Technically good
Really bother
Billionaire is still a billionaire
Stopping around how much money Bill Gates
His money should all be seized and he should be beheading
What is a right
Just agreed to be heading
Cuz you advocated for murder
I'm so also one of the big things you were saying but that last clip is all the people on the left
You're stupid
All your stupid you don't know about
Right you don't know about all this stuff
I know stuff
Alex Jones talks about
John Hancock
And we'll see just how smart Alex
Confront
Better
My wife
Who decided
Real quick I'll start it every time he lies
John Hancock did not sign the Declaration of the
July 4th
I was signed on August 2nd 70
On July 4th
Congressman
And voted on the Declaration
So Alex is already wrong
It was either
Victory against
I believe it was Benjamin Franklin
So John Hancock sign
Swamp Fox
First because he was the president
Continental Congress
He signed first
Also super annoying for everybody else too
Showboating
Dirty Trickster
I'm also the Declaration of Independence
Not sent
That was not part of it at all
No sent to other nations in colonies as an attempt to be like
The British
Bulshit the goal was to explain to other colonies
Why was a good idea for them
Declare independence
And sent other nations
As adjusted
Vacation so they wouldn't be on the side of
Absolutely no point
To be like
Hey King George
Suck it
The strangest thing about this is I
I kind of disagree with America declaring independence
Because really what was what it was about was like
Tiny little tax
Stuff
Because the King was like
We are giving you a s*** ton of Mike this is essentially the trade deficit argument if you are if you are so
Supporting Trump
Levi you f****** tariffs against China you're a
The Declaration of
Interesting
Nazi collaborator
Denny's
Not true at all
Haha don't answer questions
Pakenham
Fairplay
Cooper
He was disinherited
Forget about that no money when he
What are you
No I don't know
Never
Never got money
When he was a child his parents told him he was not going to any of his narrative
Because it's probably that one
There wasn't
Rated over
And because the family is diffuse
And they've done a few studies on that we're within three generations
Things most wealth is is gone
There's not the same like consolidation of we marry within 3 or 4 times
You is
The of the only way to consolidate your money is due at the way that the old my did then didn't
Exactly
Interviews about
It's very clear on record he has no money
They came from his grandma right
You did
What up piece of Filth bracket.
What
Otherwise
Soros alone I will not
About you
Crostic that's where they put the code
Message in there
If you look at the first word of every set
That's the moment where I'm most felt like
Weird
Basically in the middle of a Nazi rally
Because Alex is lying about George Soros
Nazi pass
He's screaming about go to hell
Where you came from he's drunk
He's up there he's rambling nonsense
He's repeating The Lure about John Hancock and having some kind of
Truth
He's lying about everything in such a way that it's just
A boy
Manifesting is
Maybe throwing that is he throwing the hand up
Izzy Izzy throw the hand up or is it down
Which Hitler are we getting
Slams on the podium are we getting the Hitler that salutes
We're getting the sweaty Hitler was holding on to
The podium
Chubby sweaty Hitler
Play some hip hop
In the middle of this rally
Market freedom
Classical liberalism
The song
Bill Clinton
Oceans are strong like this is the kind of Hosting I've seen it
Terrible shows
That's what I want to be I don't want to scream it b****** to get out of the way
I'm not saying that he's yelling at women
Make it sound like that's a criticism
I just think it's stupid
Maybe a little bit
No I don't think so
I think that's why he did move move
The second time around cuz he even was in his head being like
You were just a b**** last
B****
I think he's probably just drunk
Also
He said in the previous clip he was going to write books right
You can't do that
He can't do that nor can you make documentaries anymore you made a documentary in like 12 years
Not to be fair to him either
I think I'd be a whole lot of work
Hayward makeup
You just need an editor who you're paying
And then just tell him
You know what are we could get a grants from somebody to make a documentary about Alex Jones I will steal the
I will steal that ribs
Score of the entire f****** thing
I don't know if we can afford it
I don't think that this is what was being referenced in the
In the chat room salon
Broken Arrow
And it was in the middle of me doing the right thing
Poirot
Anime
Donna Donna
On the Orient Express
Disappointed I love David suchet I love
Borrow I love mystery that show I love it all
I do not think
Get the murder on the Orient Express as a good story
It's really not everybody does it that's not good
What's his face
Murder on the Orient Express
The one without
Brenna Brenna
He is maybe the most insufferable actor I've ever seen
It's fair how much prefer things like the ABC murders that was a good one
Three little Indians ugly that was another good one for a lot of obvious reasons
Weaver AKA rainbow snake
Gets up to the mic
Let's hear some of this
She has an interesting perspective on Charlotte's
That's cuz he was there and that's all she has to go on it
That's sort of Infowars claim to fame
Is that she was at Charlottesville
Weeping auntie
By George
That's based on those fake documents of a sound unfortunate Alex Napoli's
He's now claiming that they've been verified
Know what happened
No one
His arguments about it for a while
No one told me to stop so they are real
Boo boo
Shity love
If it was if it was wrong somebody would have said something by now right
That's why he has to go to
Okay bye
Corporation
Groups like move on.org
IPhone
I was there on the ground
Anime
Immediately
Singers of violence
One-sided
Violence
Coming from
Right
Oh we have a
It want to try it
Removing
Boreal
I mean anyone who
7-Eleven
Group
In horse
Element
Hold on
You did have them
Radical right
Stretch out their box fort
So that you can see by the entire right
Demonize Trump
Trump movement
So you're keeping score
Literally a narrative that is built
To just
Defy white supremacy
Okay hey
People who were out there
They're also funded by George Soros but there also are being funded by George Soros
In order to come out and scream
Blood and soil catchphrases
That
Really. It's memorializing history was put up a years and years after
30 or 2
We got to have the image of the Confederacy the time that they were like
All of those like spikes
Confederate statues that were put up over
Apparently are at times like when the Civil Rights Movement was going
Remembering we used to own you
Her point of that their radical left
Does terrorists and they're only demonizing they're all right and it's like the alt-right is fine except
For those people
Who has the FBI recently classified as a terrorist organization
Antifa
Minimize
That's not a threat he also said the Juggalos
Yep nonsense
Absolute nut
Is it one of the larger
Just cultural mouthpiece
Pieces of this
Permissive
Of white violence
Terrorism
Directions to Sonic
Now we're seeing these things of like taking questions about lgbtq identity out of
DeSantis
It's not a big deal
There's reasons that those sort of your citizenship test in there as well
But those things are very important because
Without
Those
Sort of metrics
You
Lose track of
Statistics about
Hate crime
What's up you say what is and isn't a hate crime
The groups that are having him I mean maybe
Do you know a bunch of dudes or
Affiliated with
Groups like identity
Europa answer to white supremacist groups
Beat the s*** out of the black guy while screaming
Slurs at him
Charlottsville
Find me feels like a hate crime
Hood
You could class
Fire dispatch but feels like it
I don't know
Probably be.
Deep State actors
It's a frustrating experience to have
Like
Get
I get why they feel like it's necessary so many news organizations put that out as like
Alleged hate crime
You have a video of somebody screaming racial slurs
And beating up a black person
That is not an alleged hate crime
If you have a justice system
That is trying that very black person who beat up by white people making racial
Where is that him as though he is also guilty of assault
Justice system
Is perpetrating its own hate crime both sides
No it's not it's not
Mueller's investigation because the FBI
Has been a white supremacist
Bright white supremacy
Organization
The very f****** begin
The Democrats are running on
Let's get rid of f******
Because if we actually do take the house
They're not going to do it they don't have to
Women should make up the entirety
Trick Daddy take it to the house
I get it I agree
I'm just angry
Restart your rant
Huh
Quick break I got
Alright
That sorry about that bro
First-time caller
My my right calf
Can ain't doing it
Perfect
Millie Weaver
Supremacist white nationalist rally
Made the feel real strong Alex is drunk
Straight drop
Any further sorry to interrupt you for like the millionth time
Billy Weaver
Seems like she's
Like those people who almost
Like when she starts talking about how corporations are funding all of these people
Seems completely unaware that all of the billionaires
Behind
Populist movement
The Tea Party
Directly behind all of this s***
Confuses me
Withheld from her or is she aware of it
Can't believe she is
She seems
Now this may read this baby Leighton sexism on my part
Are you not aware that we're covering a propaganda Outlet
Good faith
Can imagine her in like a backroom conversation
Being like
Man I'm telling you I know these right-wing billionaires are running the country but that's where my bread is buttered
You know
Like she seems like
Like she seems like why
Original I mean there's so many
There's so many like profiles of what some young white nationalist a****** who's got who's
Believe
Always wind up being something at the base level
If you just start with
Billionaires are controlling everything you're like yeah
You are right on board
Because the left
No
I think it's the
Just willful team sports
I think it's just that probably just like any kind of
Groupthink kind of cult thing they inoculate themselves against any information that denies their narrow
The other side
Which billionaire
Beings ever to exist
Generally
Sometimes they can have
Benevolent
Intentions and sometimes I can
But
Shouldn't have that much money.
Yes
Refuge
Alex is drunk
Millie gets off stage there
It's crazy Magic
Probably
Could
What's up
Theosophy
Just about it
Do you want
I think that it's one of those things where he
He knows that he explained Chuck-E-Cheese the rat
But you going to have a couple more drinks
And I was like
I don't know if I really explained it so he gets back on stage
Everybody knows explained
Absolutely
Jordan klepper
Justin Foster concert comedy show
In Florida
I did say that
Slander definition
That's what he does
Citizens School of Journalism
Texas
Misrepresented
Chuck-E-Cheese
Or some other men that makes them look bad
Pcloud evaders
Continuous
And I can't even have a conversation
No no no
Sony later out there waiting
You know you got ass kicked today
Just that you're a fraud you're a scam Chuck-E-Cheese a rat
You see one of these guys George soros-funded
He's back here
Like they're journalist
A paycheck
They're going to lose
Solis
You're not going to protect yourself from a comedian by saying Chuck-E-Cheese the rat over and over again
He will just make a bit about that
So that's probably what's going to end up happening
And then the second Jordan klepper which
I'm guessing it's not
No.
And then I don't remember the idea of like
All conservatives are always mad at
It really must be mainly because they don't understand why they
Can't be comedian
Furiated
Just have like
No
Ability to laugh
I know but also what
Shroyer
Owen Shroyer did not make the cut for the road
Hitman David Knight had to stay at home and the host Alex Jones a show for it
Of course he is there is cuz he was already there
That'd be great if it turns out course he does a wonderful Jordan
That'd be great
Citizens School of Journalism
In Texas and I don't know what that is
I don't care
Probably something we should look into but I assume it's at least
He's he's gotten
I need to look more into it
But I'm not entirely sure what that.
Interest too much
Dumbshit's thought I'd ask a question since it's your job to do all the research and I don't have a bunch of stuff
Everything
I did research this next question is why our donors are not giving up the big bucks I researched
Stranahan talks about people that Alex
It's been really interesting
Here's one reason they hate Alex Jones
Right
In fact agreement
Hanging out with my friends
What home is gone Andrew Breitbart
He was on coke all the time probably was fun all the time
And I missed
I'm hanging around somebody
My other friend is Dog the Bounty Hunter
When is a little bit of
Remind me of dog
Is a picture
Hahaha
I'd like to read you a quote from Dog the Bounty Hunter
This is
It came out from the conversation he had with his son
Inspired by the fact that his son
Was dating a black girl
Quotes
I'm not taking a chance
Not because she's black but because we use the word and sometimes here
I'm not going to take any chance ever in life of losing everything I've worked for 30 years
Because some drunken and hurt us a n and turn us into The Enquirer magazine
I'm not taking a chance
At all
Never in life
Never
The the thing that reminder
Meaning of Alex in that state
Is
A complete understanding about the
Right
I'm not taking a chance that some
Call
Hear the
You don't understand what just happened
Also if anybody
Puts me in the sentence with
You know
The same thing about
Jordan and dog is I take a lot of pictures
I want to be out of that too
I want out of that sentence so fast
I wanted the Dog Bounty Hunter is
Dog the Bounty Hunter
Good luck is a private conversation that he had that got leaked
It shows a certain amount of guard up
And in that conversation is like
I don't want to present around cuz we use the n-word sometimes
And I don't give a s***
We just use it
Because we don't give a s***
And I know that it offends black people
And I don't give a f*** about that now that
You're coming to dinner movie right there
I'm sure it was not a comedy
I think they would get the rocks
Play back bro
And then also Dog Bounty Hunter got in trouble because he went out of his jurisdiction
And I got somebody
The Bounty Hunter
Ukebuddy went to Mexico and got this
You got in trouble for that
Court case took so long
Extraordinary rendition isn't under their purview especially if you're a reality star
He ended up not getting in trouble. The case got thrown out
Because of a statue
The dirty business
Yeah you can't go to foreign countries
Expedite
Before that
So now here Lee Stranahan he really vocalizes what
The feeling of this after press conference
I was expressing earlier than people
Make
The littoral states
We're among friends
So I can speak
Edward among friends
Knowing
It might as well be that but I mean they still broadcasted this
This morning I was trying to
Remedia you want to be conciliatory
Christian
I want to be open and inviting
But now I'm a month
Friends
I'm not trying to make you feel badly for the left
But Alex said something very interesting
Recently he was talking about he did it
Who is yd
Three days ago Sunday or something like that
Where you was talking about I used to live in Austin so I know there's a lot of hippie
Hippie Hollow
Used to be in favor of free speech
Used to like
Remember when they were
In Skokie
Remember that
Jessica
What
We're talking about this
George Soros
Oh boy
Do George Soros destroyed the Lac
By funding a bunch of organization
You can go to the ACL use website
You can find out about what they're actually involved in right now it's people just don't actually pay attention
Mansion 2
It's hard
Look at the website you got to go
March 29th 2018 that Alex Jones probably would be super into that the ACLU
Police fighting in court instead of screaming about impotent Lianna internet show
ACLU report urges City sometimes to provide internet service as a utility
That's something that Alex Jones
Super into
They're protecting about
They are
They're working with students in Louisiana about the door order to take down a mural
On the grounds that it's a violation of their free speech
Let me just goes on and on and on
The ACLU
Has done
Everything
Possible to
Not
Support
Causes
But support
The actual defense and rule of law
Absolute like even when you disagree with them as in the
Aforementioned
It's still the rule of law
You know is if you don't apply the law.
You don't actually have a legal system like real talk if Alex Jones had illegitimate
First Amendment breathing
Will be the first people who would support him
They do
I mean here's a press release that they put out from March
7th
This year
Supposed to measure with
Restrict public comment
Exit meeting
The Proposal
Prohibit political intellect
In common
Disruptive inflammatory self-promoting threatening
Or interfering with board
Feel like they're doing all this s***
On a local level on a national level
That are
Making a difference
Consider trying to help
People
All he does is
Why are they are they called a leftist organization
By the right
Because they want to apply the law Tico
And that is
Anathema
To write philosophy
Especially far-right philosophy
The fee which is essentially authoritarian
When you do that when you apply the law equally
The
Hard right will
Always fight again
Yep. No but I just I find this disgusting because
ACLU
Is still living there mission
The only rationale you could possibly have
Fort Knox
Dingbat
Is willfully
You have don't let you don't care about what they're doing
You know like that's really
Appointment
Damn independent noxious recently a number back when they did that in Skokie
Has a
Nazi candidate running for congress overwhelmingly
CB all good luck
The right to do that
They still do that you'll still hear stories
Even in the last few years of ACLU defending their rights
To have
A demonstration
Ratchet life
It's f****** b******* Lee Stranahan is just
Lying
To perpetuate a narrative
That the left
Principal
In service of demonizing George Soros
Also
Actually just talking about the Blues
Remember the Nazi rally in The Blues Brothers I think that's what he's actually reference
My mind
Glitch
Because I started thinking about Chubby Checker
It's not Chubby Checker
Who is it
Chuck-E-Cheese the rat
Now I'm thinking of checking
The wrap
As as like Chuck-E-Cheese brother in a in a Hamburglar situation
I'm enjoying that whole life
Never
I don't want to try and get into this weird fantasy that my brain
No Doubt
Is he did the twist
Now all my brain can do is think about the time the Chubby Checker did that song with the Fat Boys
So did the other version of The Twist
What's the mic down clip for you
Lee Stranahan
And now we bring up that old
Puffy b****
I really hate calling people a b**** or anything like that for some reason everytime I see Jerome corsi
It's swollen a b****
I don't know why she's the person who get that like you folks
In a like
Ark
Clear that you're a propaganda
Abundantly clear in Riley ever on the show
Your entire life has been about propaganda
You were brought up by Edward Bernays
In the propaganda game
You are clearly a person who has written books
About Obama's birth certificate
Are John Kerry in the Swift boat situation
Your entire career has been about lying
And now I look at
You and you make me sad
You look like you got f****** left out in the water too long
You look like a bloated corpse
You piece of s***
I hate him so much
I hate what he's done to the world
Baby just makes me
Do waterlogged b****
Anyway
Motion for me I've been I've been holding up holding back a lot of Jerome corsi
Now
He's doing all this qanon
It's over like it's even better
This is a delightful
So he comes up in this press conference
It starts talk
Qanon she turns out
She knew about it
Citgo which is counter counter-coup
But
Because we've done our research we know that this doesn't match up with Jerome corsi
She's timeline
At all
I want
3 years ago
Water
About three years
Barack Obama
Also sorry Jerome corsi is terrible like sex
This is amazing this is no one should allow Jerome corsi
Any kind of
Rally
Closer to the mic
Heather a few weeks later
Call
That was Alex
Screaming from the back of the room
Six Flag
Trump agreed
Wood rot
And they agree
Run
There
Coup d'etat
Rudy
Tradersway
That's not a concern.
As we've been
Alex
Military
Intelligence
Nope
And
What's the truck
And the intelligence
Forgetting
That we've explained
Really
Inside screen
Course he just gave up the game
You just admitted that a lot of these excited formation that they pretend comes from sources comes home
Yeah you just basically gave it up
Like he's like a lot of this inside information
From this internet hoax
This is
Wow
Like we haven't done sad we haven't really sad we haven't talked a lot about qanon
Because why would I probably
Narrative
Then we realize our always begun talking about now is that
Alex is trying to catch up
The conspiracy world is too fast
888 he's just not able to put out enough content
It's just a bunch of random dudes having a great Ole Time
Exactly what they want
Open cryptic.
And probably will make a
Shitload of money
Once they give it up and write a book about
Wannabe Macklemore Killam
Pages that are just hand tie
So the end result of this
According to Drum Corps
Amman
I would say that this
Describes what they are
Traders
Crater
Is a capital crime
And I want to
Predicament
Even Hillary Clinton
And Barack Obama
Request
Unlock garage
And Donald Trump
Heat
Play a role
Did you hear her troubling what he's saying is
All I know is that
In historically military tribunals have been the best part of every functioning democracy
Especially when they're brought up to punish your political right
Really aren't even political rivals
Trying to consolidate power and punish your perceived enemies
Also Jerome corsi at the end there saying that Trump has a vision
Of the world with
Him staying involved and he has for decades
It doesn't sound like
With the timeline
Green overlooking the 2015 that around
The time
3 years ago which would have been in April
Jerome corsi wasn't at all
He was even in about
September
When he would come on Alex Jones
The show and talk about it he said the Trump was just f****** around he wasn't really serious once he was even running
So the idea that
And even more specifically back then if he had that in for
Formation
No he wasn't for you would have told Alex
No I mean just on General Bible
This is this is
Before the whole team got behind Trump
So this is still that read well
3 years ago
That still when they would have joined like Jordan
You're stupid
Bus 14
If in Jerome corsi timeline that he's pitching now present day
The three years ago
For Donald Trump decided to run for president and get Obama out of off
Ron
Have either been like
Hey I know that there's a secret coup d'etat going on in truck we got to get behind him
The bastard has been like
Alex I think you really should support Trump
His first couple of appearances after Trump announced that he was running
And was on the trail or like he's not this guy is you got to still love
Love Rand Paul of course make any f****** goddamn sense at all
Corpse on the beach
That f****** hate him
Stupid dick hole
I love it
We're just going to open up every show now with you
And esoteric in Zelda
To describe Jerome, Jerome corsi with your laying down in the sand I poked you with a stick in it
What sucks about it is like the only ever own swamp
Bloated balls just exploding all over everywhere
Like mushrooms in a fairy ring you are. This is the problem
My head is legitimately a waterlogged corpse
That's all I'm going to do
Of course you suck
You can go with a river I think
I think the reason that I'm so mad at him is his history
He's so f****** pretty
Like it's like
Specifically three years ago there's a lot of people who make me mad and Alex Jones's world and what have you
He doesn't make me mad I hate
You know I like there's other people who unlike
I'm more interested in explaining
Do you why this person is a problem
Want to do a dance on his face
I love it when it gets personal with you
I don't know how much you hate this
I don't know why you
Me so boring
I think it's a combination of bordova and murder
Hamamoto Steve
And I generally don't listen to as much as
I think I only get I only get trickster God
I'm I'm I have
Such
I mean I want to call it a fetish
Metaphorical kind of a fetish because in the way that I listen to Infowars
I can really only get it up for people who are creative
I can really only enjoy it when I
Coming around, Modo Larry Nichols
These types of interesting crazy
Interesting
He's a boot-licking assholes it's like a
Your you're
Tasting imported like eventually to escalate to the point where it gets more and more shirt
Of course you need something you need
In order to make things
Alex's
That sort of white bread
Mainline mom and popcorn
Send run-of-the-mill that's already in a weird place right there
Especially these days get off this topic
My point is the
Knowledge
Feel like I got railroaded
Picture of course I do I love it
Anyway up in this next clip we get someone who I'm not really as a
Excited about
Don't care about
But
U disc
Cast me as a human being
Like every part of his life
Bums me out might as well be mini Rodger Stone
Like you sort of
Shittier more boring
F****** a monstrous Rodger Stone
See him is kind of like a satellite
Dirty trickster in training like the
All of the beginning with all that pizza
Not going today not going to the pizza place in creating a hoax out of it
No not at all
We see this
He's very easy to see through any
It's not that interests
But you'll enjoy this first clip
For he tries to get a USA chant going and it
It does not work
Coronavirus
What's in the news
What else what else
Join me
How's Logan
Chico's
You
You asked
Wolf
I've heard more sustained USA chance
Empty open mics
I've heard the same USA chance
At
Hitler's rally
Hey here's a slogan you might know it
Listen I am going to play a little song for you
So you know it's not my first date is USA
Mike down clip
I think the Jack was so big
Accidentally reveals
In this clip
The realize he is
Fiza
He's revealing
He is and that is
Videos white Nash
They want the US dollar
10 US dollars
Chinese dollar
The one thing and
Say that
Is it always talk
He said
Jack one day
American
Baby
Baby adopted
And that's the way it's going to
He said that's why
Really shocked me
USA a verb
Impoverished country
Where I
Where you can
Alright
And I don't want my child to grow up in
That's going on
Recline and that is why
I fed all the 2016
Working my butt off
For Donald J
Strong and that's why I spent all 2017 I'm going to spend all the 2018
And as long as it takes
As long as it takes
Thank you so much
So he closes out his his set as it were
I really don't like
That he said
No I had a Chinese
Visit partner
That's not good
I don't know if that's how you phrase it but if it is it somehow I missed my ears
The thing that's important is that
White nationalism
White supremacy
Based on the 11:00
Onwards
Most of it is about
Securing attic
Sims 4 white chili
That is very spiritually similar to what
He's talking about
Offensive
Babies would be sent over
Coded up bits of language
Personalized
Play I don't give a s*** about me or not so I don't take care to get the
A big fan of it
You have no idea right I don't want my kid growing up in a country that's in Decline
Send them elsewhere
No no that's not even
Concerned about
I'm like well what's the what's a f****** infant mortality rate hear you f****** idiot that's what it what are you
Talking about
In the same way the people who like
Attack abortion clinic
Because they're concerned with
Bored
It doesn't match the belief
And the belief
Then he's espousing is
More or less
Very clearly to express that's why I supported Trump
And that's why I'm going to
Continue working so hard for him
And all this mess
There's so many like
Every time every time these guys get
Eclipse
Take a note
Where it's like well obviously you're talkin
Think about how you're a white suit
Their likes
I just
What have we have we have
Years-long
F****** rap sheet
Supremacist
There's no taking this out of
Contacts
You are
Literally
Prove
A white
National
You pretend otherwise
Is f****** ridiculous and it's insane that they realize it's like
Among friends
Why don't the Bounty Hunter. He's free to say the n word
That that's her to think that's because they're free to say things
That clip of Pacific talking about
I don't want American kids being adopted by Chinese people
That's I mean that's dog with leave for sure
Yeah but it's
There's a name to it to Rio lights up
How come African Americans
Wiggle wine
American baby
F****** p
Absolutely
Why
So
What do you mean
Are you f****** me
Like what is it take
To not be a white
Is it like is it just
Can't
Just be that you were raised
The part of it like it was a traumatic experience that.
People who go to church really just kind of hang out
The benign version of it but yeah
I think there's a
Interesting articles
Recently about
Conspiracy of being a shortcut to Phoenix
Smart because you have like this idea of like
Our believe
This I know the truth
But I could do know what's a smart smart
Because I have this alternative now I haven't researched papers about
Truth
That I saw on YouTube 7% of scientists
Can be wrong
When they talk about
Yeah it's only the 3%
We know that
Spira see behind
I'd like a shortcut to feeling smart
And I think there's a disenfranchisement
The people's feel pause
Possibly
Supremacy gives them a shortcut to
Being
Awesome
I mean
How to make
I'm a piece of it probably justification for it so much as a
Psychology behind it
Excuse me
Because you were asking like what do you get out of there automatic boost
Perfect sense
It's not a coincidence that everyone on that stage
Write a note
It's right
Anyway
Finally
You like with with both of our insecurities and mental illnesses
You think we'd be better off if we were white supremacist Dan
Not too much baggage
Comes along with it
Going to hang out with weirdos
That's a good smell good you got to be a proud boy that's the worst part of it alone
Is disqualified if you ever watched any documentaries about like neo-Nazi
Two groups and stuff like that it's really fast out the Green Room that sound about right
You can't go wrong that's the movie I'm starting Doc's baby
If you watch documentaries about white supremacist groups a lot of the times you'll find
If you were in the place of the person
The documentaries about like who do like
Why do I have to hang
Yeah these people are assholes
What am I doing
Garage
Hang out in garages garage like
I'm talking about a garage
Finally an hour plus
Speeches that get to the actual q-and-a session
Wisconsin
I enter Alex is too drunk to do it
Star Trek Q
Alright we're going to open the floor to questions Billy Weaver up here and I'll come if you want
And then he kind of just disappears for a long time after
After this
He's
He's doing something probably yelling at Chuck-E-Cheese
I think we all agree that Trump
Historical anomaly
It wasn't really meant
And
There's discussion that
That Alex
And
And mr. Stone Rodger Stone had about
Basically
Street fighting pack
Versus
Long-term strategy
Token
I want to save this guy is a very valid question
And so my question
Rodger Stone and for Alex Jones
Or outside of street fighting
Outside outside of short-term
Street fighting
Gorilla attack
What's the long game
And who has the long game and I'm
Talking 20 30 40 50 years
And I like to throw in one
Caveat
Question for both of you
Please
Can you all them in that
How do you work with institutional Christian
Organization
And your long game
Now I'm going to give you a call
Yes
Do you think
Alex has a decent answer to the question
Leopard to boil this question.
The question is essentially
Can you actually governor
What is your idea
How do you get it so you guys have taken over
You threw a couple uppercuts
Right
How do you govern and what's your plan
Christ
So I assume
Alex is responsible.
No we can't
Huh
The second part of the question is based on Alex Jones
Is rampant distrust
Any Christian organization
That's not Patriots first and a very few reasonable position that he still made
Your your prediction
It's pretty accurate
Chirp
Thank you
American
Not an answer
Just doing a bit
You help
Right
That's all I'm doing
White nationalism is not a given that
I think it is
Telling the truth
Exposing WhatsApp
Not being
Group
Individually
Checking out
That's not an answer
That's nothing
If your answer is
There is no way to govern
So
Nah
That's a badass
It's just
I mean he just is rattling off his catcher
Phrases you might as well if y'all 1776 2.0 and stir
They would have been
It wouldn't have been out of place in that
String of bulshit But ultimately what he said at the end there was there's no organization that is going to help
Well I mean if you want to if you consider the government and organization then you are
Essentially advocating for
Complete and utter chaos
Anarchy there baby
I mean I think what he's just saying is
The streets I don't know
That's great I'm going to not answer it because that is a hard question to answer
It's a dawn answer because he has no grasp on policy
Well here's what we would like to
University initiatives that we would like to push for
It doesn't address the ideas like are we going to evolve Christian organization
At all and that answer questions
Humanity which means nothing
I believe that I can just do what I'm doing and you do your thing
I'll go Diamond keep telling the truth
I'm going to keep exposing code for
I'm going to be a white supremacist on Aaron repeat Russian talking point
I don't I don't it's just not answer
Great question though
Steve
Either
I can't see really any group
Answering
Crabs have a 30-year plan
I think if you don't grasp on
Nobody to talk to
Mainstream
Actually
You could talk to the conservatives or liberals.
Even even middle-of-the-road would have a much
I disagree I think their answers would be stupid
They wouldn't be nothing
Maybe if you try any one of these
They're not going to give a solid consistent answer to
Like here's how we survive the next 30 Years and what's more important is that Alex
Terrible
Rodger Stone
Or a video
Or break
Or anywhere
Dory
Freedom
And post it
Your social
Because you see that
Don't disturb your plans Facebook shares
A warrior
A nympho
Warrior
Nice
Pace
Hurt
So I control control wax what are we doing
Extreme truck from the back of the room
8:30
I mean Rodger Stones answer to the question is help us spread propaganda
Functional in like a
Hey Sarah Link on Twitter shared on Facebook
Unplugging the Twitter
You can follow us on at Infowars you can follow the real Alex Jones
Smash those like button retweet your plan is a 1,000
Millie Weaver comes back
And
If you thought you was lying about Charlottesville get a load of this vaccine bulshit
You know I had the Opera
Communities
Ohio
When you believe it
Almost no incidences of autism
Back
Statistically
Are almost non-existent
Jackson children
What's one more question
So I grew up Mennonite which is not honest but it's
Sota clothing
Should Jason
I have a lot of how that works
Flights really shity of the WWE is going over there doing you f****** Royal Rumble
Perform
I'm so there's no women's matches
Hi there WWE
The great idea
Good paycheck
Absolutely what Millie we were talking about other horseshit
What she's doing is she's operating off a 2000
Story
That was a non-scientific survey of an Amish community in pencil
Very large one in Lancaster
Cineworld
He claimed that he could only find three autistic
The kid
Three of them have been vaccinated
An implied that
Very uncommon thing
In the Amish community
It was not a study
Is apocryphal
These are just stories that he's relating
And the ex
Clung to it
Like it's the Holy Grail
The proof that vaccines cause autism
Unfortunately
A 2011 study in the magazine Journal Pediatrics
Showed that 68% of Amish people had their children vaccinated which is lower than the national average but it's still
A majority
I also
In a 2010 presentation to the international
Society of autism research
Researchers from the University of Miami and the University of Vanderbilt
Discuss the research into autism in the Amish community based on interviews with
899 individuals in multiple community
They found a rate of approximately
Shekinah
They found a rate of approximately 1 and 271 children's playing autistic
Also there's a clinic called
Clinic for special children in Lancaster
Transylvania is specifically for the developmental disorders in Amish children which would not exist if those didn't
The main reason that
Suggested for why rates are lower
For a diagnosis of Amish
Communities
Is that they don't have they don't have the stigma
Diagnosis
Sabaya
Also Advanced like how people say that the
Diagnosis of
Doesn't has
Explode and nobody understands why well if you go back they put peep
People in f******
Institution
Further
Because the populations are so insulated an Amish community
There's a much lower genetic diversity in play which reduces the risk
Certain diseases in elevator
Another
It's not entirely clear why autism would be one of them
But it turns out that the one that has a much lower inside
Unless
Genetically diverse population
Who's that at the door that rainbow snatch
Is that your burning
That was for the chat
Alright
We were just going based on an apocryphal story 2005 but got Traction in a T-Rex make
But also there is always get traction
And the debunking
Never.
Studies
Rob gets on the mic everyone forgotten you still exist
He shows up on the mic
He said some really weird stuff one of the things I like to hear is that the bar is
Does an open bar that's a good
It's really weird
We should do that and just hang out
Mango
If somebody asked
It's cuz I was too drunk to get back on stage
Networking
Respect
Super Shore
We have a DJs can play Electric Slide
Babe jungle juice at the back
I don't know what's in that punch
Radu baby
Lemonade mix
Is terrible terrible in my past
He stole the margarita mix for my parents
We're gonna have a good time
Yeah
They should have stopped at 6
They take a question
I don't know why
But at some point right
Before this guy asked
2 question
The audio starts going f***
Terrible
This is going to sound like s***
And I apologize in advance
But
I will say I tried to hunt down alternate versions of the audio
There is nothing that doesn't have this glitch in it
Paper worth it
For what ends up happening
I tried to fix it
I could not fix it would have taken me like
6 hours to
Go through and fix all the Audio I apologize for subjecting
But I wouldn't do it
Is it work one of these
Craziest thing
When we get to spoil it all
You cannot imagine the look on Millie Weaver
Why the f*** is Alex you're helping me with
This is not cool
So I hear is the guy his name is
True Dave
Inside stew
But no
Utah
He's a genius
He knows how to start at
You knows how to start out a question
With a plug
Strangely enough he's a fake leftist
Good afternoon everyone.
Having the courage to come forward
Rogers
So far so far
People are making it out what do you say let's give ourselves a round of applause for being courageous
Come out and
What's his name
He's doing a bit
Cyberpatriot
I love you
Purge YouTube
Bible store
Text
Stop
He gets it
He gets it don't pay your health insurance product
Nobody knows
I mean they should be it should be a national Alex Jones is Healthcare
I love it
Who is this f****** rude
No
So to recap what you said so far is that the longest-running government in the world is a Christian government at the Centre of it
Is a man
Jesus
What
Jesus gets his
But I'm going to go a little deeper
That's wild
That's nuts
Channel
Gettington
Dragons
So he is asserting
Very clearly
Say we are in the end times
What should we be looking for Christ is the focus I have is
Preferences that with
As though everyone
Already knows what we should be looking
Looking for
Critz is the folks
Yeah
I don't know what we should be looking for
Steven
Revelation Scholars
Really don't know what we should be looking for have no idea where this guy already happened and it was a mess
Weather for Pahrump
You have no idea where this is going
I'm also to the chat room I appreciate everyone suggesting how this audio could be fix
Trust me
And maybe there is some really really long wait
To do it this manually but
Such a mess
After you fix that audio
Right
I think this is
Bring up
I took this audio straight from Alex Jones YouTube
He put this outlaw
Oh yeah.
It was like working on this and every time I make it
Motion rate cut out the little black sand audio in
Either way it's going to hurt the ears
If we do not understand
Millie Weaver
Sonya, wait hold on
Yep
So this guy
I was like
Now's my time
To let everybody know
I already know who crisis and and
He did it perfectly
He got everyone behind him by doing the plug products are going to love it
First war in the end times
You do plug
Talk about Alex Jones for a long time a infowarrior from way back I love
Call this look
Christian Christian
I believe in Jesus
And then you f****** Trojan horses
Part where he's like
No
He's not mad
Do you know I know but it's like just like
No I am
I have First Amendment rights
This whole thing is about how his first amendment rights are being encroached on
And now we started the episode with him trying to kick out what might have been Jordan klepper
From his event
And now we end
With a moon
Looks like it's just Shadows cuz
To him like
Dude
Stop
Like
Hold on one second
We
Are crazy this is getting
No no it's f******
It's because it's getting too real
Like
Not because
Sundial movies Christ
Sun Myung Moon
Mega wash
Washington Times
Hand washing
X
Is a load of s*** Journal
Publication
Stop the same narratives that Alex does
And he does use them
Mosasaurus a lot
Sundown moon is related to a lot of funding
No
Are you sure he's not really sure of the unification Church
Christ
Sun
Becoming
Sunya sunya moon is related to a lot of funding
Conservative
Organization
Right
There's a lot of
Connection between the narratives that Alex Jones puts out into the world
And Sun young Moon funding
Until this guy
Is crazy
But at the same time he's not crazy and thinking that Alex should be on the same page
Listen to Alex for a really long time
Like your focal point was Sunday on the moon
The Washington Times
It would make perfect
Sense to you that like
How to get to
Alex
Alex's
Gino's
When was the super behind Nixon and Reagan Alex
Seems to like those guys
Love it it's very it's very not he's coming to Rodger
Just Stone as being like he was behind
Bringing Rogers
Love it introduces the question of does Rodger Stone have any relation with Sonia
Two of them have had
Parallel tracks
Have they ever been in the same room
I don't know
Is Korean
Yeah but was he white dude
The Christ surgery you know that's Christ was Jewish and then he became White that's why all the Italian
No weed one more Clampett's
2 minutes long of him it's worth it
Cuz he just Rambles more about Christ
It's really funny to me the rest of it and you can go look at you
He keeps being like
There are moments like that that are really funny prize is great
So there's that but
Alex had his story bombed by a Mooney
Love it which is going to be my punk band
StoryBots
It's been a really interesting thing cuz I I
You know everyone but I wasn't expecting everyone wanted us
To talk about
The Press
This is much more interesting drunk them
Staubach goes out in public drunk Millie is doing her best
She is dreaming of better things issue does as heavy lifting to do
Maybe course
She's drunk I can't tell with his
Second
I can't do it anymore. No more. No more metaphors for a
Soggy
Jeff
Dapper cadaver in a bog
Just a f****** Lake full of with blue lips
His f******
Tiny little
Knockout whiskey
That's what Coursey f****** looks like
Falcon dick
Guy suck
I love
Doing his best
Just started
Just bananas
Ain't no man
You look at when you look at the totality
As you see
I think the major points I want to take away is
This
Has all of the flavor of a white nationalist Nazi rally
That is a failure because the audience is not very
They're very energy audience
All that be crazy they were all behind him
That be crazy
Better better chance than pasovic could get going
So that's one point then the other point is I really think that Alex is
Trying to get
Soros
Som
It's really funny to me
That's never going to happen
It's never going to happen
There's no there's no no
Just keep slandering him and eat it doesn't matter
Cuz why would it matter
What I find interesting about the
Is that
The only thing that will get us to sue him is if
One of Alex
Texas fans killed his.
Which I think is a remote possibility
As things deteriorate
Might do it
Possible
About
The coverage
The press conference
And the lack of coverage about this
Yeah
Is that
Every time
Every time we see this type of coverage
From
Rightwingwatch
Media Matters go f*** yourself Adam Schiff
So do you
But we had to me is that they
Always cover Alex
At his
Wrong
Do you know what I'm saying
Like they always cover Alex
The most hour
Colorado Alex at his weakest
Gives up the game it's the strong embarrassing
Conversion cuz kissing the flag and stuff like that is embarrassing
Embarrassment
Used his strength
Like his inability his complete lack of
Ability to feel shame just like Trump
It's the lack of
Complete misunderstanding
Of what it's like to be another rational human being
Blinds were Alex Jones
Promotes
2-hour q-and-a session
Too drunk to follow through so his buddies have a nationalist rally nationalist rap
Cuz that's the reality of what we saw.
Came up on stage
You know piggyback some Auntie Soros hate Express I don't want
Adopted to Chinese people
Or just
Jerome colored corsi allowed to speak
Headlight
God
Man
Anyways
Be f******
The Rock KC
He was in the queue to be an on-air like the line with it in England they call it a cue
You all right
Directions to the end of episode I wished I was supposed to do a better job of covering this
You're right
Much more potent
Very obvious
What's going to happen at the end of this but first
If you would like to
Follow us on Twitter
Join a specific group
With Allah
But you're going to have to stop
Pause
Listen to the next words I throw home and tell your father you're brilliant
Go home and tell your mother you're barely on Facebook
Frightworld or just on Facebook
Mostly about the group these days
The page is kind of
You know what I realize we like
Positive reinforcement way too much
It's
Like
Facebook works
More people see stuff
In the group
Then if I posted it on the page
What's a good time so I realized
What's the f****** point of the page
I want to just post something on the page like join the group
I don't post anything over here anymore
We're just over 200 people in the group now
Hundred people listen
Well video
More than that
Anyway
Find us an iTunes
Someone must
Be told
Their business episodes
Something to give him a break
Say
Lucian wintrich
No I'm kidding Lee Stranahan
Alexandra Thurston color