Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
We are a couple of dudes who likes
To sit around and drink wine
I know a lot about
It's very lies the fun we're on how many episodes
Still don't know anything about
Infowars I think you know more about it than a lot of people who listen regularly
I think because of your
B******* detector your awareness of History
I've been building up today's episode
I can't I can't begin to describe your face
Is lighting up like
Christmas f***
Independence
This is insane there is a reason and I am thrilled
There's a reason for this
Today we are going to be
Be covering
M24
In the Life of Alex Jones
The coverage of the Alex Jones Show
Homeagain for Wars Network
And this is a show that I would like
Like the call
I would like to start trying to give our episodes
Is what it is
Doobie
A roller coaster ride
Alright it's
It's fun
Idaho
Instead of deeply at the end if you want to follow us on Twitter at knowledge underscore fight
If you want to reach out to please describe on I would appreciate it we are both
I have a feeling
That are showing
Are going to become
Way more relevant
Inexplicably
And also it is both
And
That we are suddenly relevant
Yeah we might
You sound really smart with your friend
I asked Alex Jones becomes more and more mainstream eyes
Like it's like
Being a hipster but for the apocalypse like dude I was in the Apocalypse
Tipster
I was a podcast before the Nazi thing
Do you like the shows
Tell your friends about it Word of Mouth
Ludacris album
Word of mouth so I'm going to I'm going to break
Traditional me to put my
My personal handle out it's all my God I was driving earlier
Today
First thing I thought was
Borgata
Deathreats like to see how that goes
I bet you won't I can run and I made sure that it only got put on P
People's Twitter walls who have a college
Georgia diploma
Eventually we're going to have to
David the Infowars
Possibly we might have to confront our fears and actually tweet at them at
At some point sooner but for now let's enjoy
Looks around
Let's get to the fun
So Monday
The 20th
Classic Alex
In the studio
I like
Alex
You are
People
Might do a pirouette at any moment while it is why it'll make sense
Time
We'll get to my
Encompass
I hate that I slipped off the broadcast on Monday
Complaining about the new season of Homeland
Call here at the office a few months ago that the
Popular TV show
Was going to be coming out
And is based around me
And I'm this evil talk show host that puts out this information and causes disasters
Just a pause for a second
Bullshiting
No he's not know there is a character that
Very clearly based
That's a classic Alex Jones embellished
Later in the show he plays a clip of the guy
And he's like
You know taking umbrage
At this guy
You know playing hit
Version of him on television
Let me play a clip and his guys just talking about the club list
Everyone needs
Share links to Infowars
It's literally do they even sound the same
The guy is doing a bad impression I think I could do better
Quite frankly
It's like
The guy just says that there's globalist
And that people should share link
And that the spirit of the Republic is coming back
You like that
Yeah I like I also hope that that actor just
It's Alex
I'm doing research for a row it's just for
Like a Gerard Butler did with Adam Carolla
The one f****** movie clip about Homeland
And I think it highlights one really enjoyed
We've documented
Doesn't really know the difference between reality and
Fanfiction
And it turns out I don't think he knows that other people can tell the difference
Which might explain a lot
Seems to think that everybody thinks
But it's actually him on the show
Really
So look
Eerily similar to have a picture of it I just heard the audio but anyway here's that
Also that is the article that he was talking about the photographer on our life
Episodes
One part of that is confirmed there were pictures of pictures of him
Detox
So much more about this article later
And we'll get to it because it's a glowing positive review
I'm good
People believe I'm on the show
And they believe that I am now working with Showtime
To put out this information freckles playlist
No
When did others
Muslim
And covering up basically Terror attacks that that that that that other group carryout
Is he on The Big Bang Theory now
For the parody character to be
Framing NFL
Muslim
Kind of metaphorically what
And then covering up terrorist attack
False flag
When he does say everything is a false flag
Legitimately I would not be surprised if this is just
Transcript
From one of his shows
Is all of this guy's lines are just reading down
The play is
Really
Aperitivo
But also did
Today
When the New York Times articles
Came out the sister of one of the kids killed it
Sandy Hook
Yeah and was like
Disgusting
This is a man
Who denies the murder of my brother
That's the that's the kind of thing he says of the false flag
Go fly a kite
But the thing that I can
Seeing was
Referring to
To that as being a
A seminal moment and that is terrible
I hate that
He's so much more crazy than that
You guys don't know
Yeah you don't know the nuances and little stuff
It is but also I want to make this argument
And I think it's going to
Overarching
This entire episode
Part of the reason why I brought up
When you said those things
He did not have his free-speech taken away
One of the worst things you can probably
Do or insinuate is
That all of these murdered children are fake
Write someone was
Was all the family members
Of these kids got her ass
Yep and they got
They got death threats
But you're part of a mask
To cover up all this stuff
How could you imagine a worse tragedy than your child dying
Sing I can think of being shot
Having your child
Murdered
And then
After while you're trying to grieve
People are giving
Death row
What is wrong with Humanity couple of dumb people who don't get it
Character in The X-Files
The new series
Ankle was based on it turns out there's a lot of people who are inspired by his version of craziness
Covering up false Flags
And the boys sounds enough like me in the trailer
Sellout for a show
Play the part of me
Upon fake
It's
Fake
It's Fiction it's just a TV show
Creative
S*** yeah
Well within the parity law
Who is who is
King him
Like why did you sell out
Maybe his lawyer
Remember his lawyer didn't know if
People kicked out of the lawyer
Documents
Are you home
They don't have to
For that dude
They're basically using
Trademark
Work yelling about global
Good good
I also also we just looked at a picture of the actor
Nothing like
I recognize that dude.
Stuff
Can't for the life of me place where they
Monday goes on
Alex Jones
Argumentation
Bisquick
Okay
Is spectacular
Because he accuses other people of misusing sources
Which is his bread-and-butter it's all he does
Then
He argues about people making a straw man fallacy
And then without missing a Beat
Makes a straw man fallacy
The visit
This clip is arrive some kind of superhero
Being a
Complete and utter moron
Yeah
I can wait till we get to Tuesday
Mr Show verifiably
Easy to disprove
Is that a bunch before saying like
Oh you said you don't know Russian agents
That must mean that you don't know Rodger Stone
Good Rogers
Deep ties to Russia
So the idea is
Style of argumentation
You know it's just a classic
Syllogism
If Aven
You know Rodger Stone
Rodger Stone has deep ties to Russia
Therefore you know someone who has deep ties to Russia
Alex doesn't understand this at all
Ethological
You don't understand the point
Or you do and you're just trying to murky
Do the water
Basic
Your basic trick is just
Then maybe
I mean his followers are just going to believe whatever it is
Double and quadruple
And triple down and just don't
Rodger Stone and Russia
Yeah first he never says Rodger Stone
In the tree there's not even the nest
Computer
Like no it's not
I know a better metaphor
If you want to come over there for someone
Claiming a source says something but it doesn't
Go to any of our episode listen to us explain every time
Avetta
The Perfect Analogy
I saw a bluebird
Nest in the tree
Resume
Wait
Are you
Are you looking in the right place is that the real issue
Are you looking still in your stupid
Alrighty so
Pictures of psychological
Warfare tactic but
By his own admission right there
He engages in psychological
Yeah but he really just be praising the tactic being like
Hey everything they're trying to do is what they're saying
This is a psychological warfare
As evidenced look at this giant screen behind me
Look at the fact that I've called all of you with bone pillow
I guess it premiered last night
And
Because I guess they start out the first episode where you don't see me I haven't seen it yet it just sounds like my voice
He's totally
But again
Doesn't say you don't see
The character
Simi
He doesn't understand the veil between
Fiction and reality
Entirely upon him and so far
It kind of
Yeah it sounds
It's crazy
Sorry I actually give him a pass
But I'm still going to keep
Perfectly described what the guy looked like but he was just looking into a mirror and described
Looks like a chubby pug
Haven't slept in months
And it's just like I have to defend myself against its that this isn't me
The whole bunch of newspapers variety and
Egypt
Entertainment Weekly
Again he has no idea what numbers are
But the other things in there if it's important for what's about to come up is this idea that he's like
I have to defend myself against
This
Defend yourself against vet
Insecurities
Or something like that is Illustrated something about himself that he's uncomfortable
His entire existence
Possibly
His defense like
He has to come to terms with the fact that
This guy
Is a propaganda
Who's falcon
Conspiracy theory
Yeah so he's looking at himself
And going
Wait
If I were watching
This I would think this guy is crazy
Yep
I think people think I'm crazy
At least enough people to make a TV show
There's a lot
Kind of a funhouse mirror
If you if you at once we have corn
Right if you are walking behind your clone it's like looking at your own ass being like
I got to work out
Yeah but
But I think also says
Defend myself against
And then immediately his next thought is
People are saying
Alex you're crazy
No one saying that we all are very clear that there are
The character on the show
He's the most
Character on the
In The X-Files was not the most
Important care
It was not Fox
Smolder
5th or 6th
Season of it and I'm sure that it's just
Part of the Ark
For the season
Becomes
Or maybe Dies who knows about it
He's got to get back to his Galaxy
Letter dice
Pictures ideas about hubs
His character is a straw man
How it's stupid
To do straw man argument
Then he's going to misrepresent what a strawman argument is
And then he's going to commit
I was so fascinated because I was like knows what a strawman argument
The next thing you said was
And he gets
The strawman argument
Call Chris Carter
But nobody listened
I got the Press reading cuz it's all like liberals
They just make up these
Bob the kickboxing done
We got one here in the office
Object
The pinata I'm saying Michael Moore and I'll beat it up I didn't really beat up Michael Moore
They realized it
So
That's what he thinks astro-man is
I don't understand what he was talking about
I'm just excited
Good to know that they have a punching dummy in her office of Michael Moore he could
Beat up Michael Moore
Strawman
That's not
I want a very very metaphorical bases it kind of is
If you create a fake version
Michael Morton rhetorically attack
Then yes but it might as well have
Beat-up avhs
Copy of the Wicker
Destroyed a straw man
If you save that Chuck Schumer is a vampire and then you attack him for his vampirism
That's kind of a strawberry
All Liberals are
Of the globalist
Who are trying
Destroy the country
From within
And they've openly said that
Instead of
You do engaging with liberal ideas
You're just creating some
Some sort of
Imaginary but hey dude
If Bob
The punching dummy
He lives in
Is the point
And here's a new one
Safespace
Just basically don't even talk to me
We're coming into jobs and you can't never criticize me or I'll have to
And this is what they're pushing this is what they're doing what they're doing
Anybody who knows what those
Safety pins are about its
Trying to signal to people that I will be an ally for you
If somebody
You can count on me to defend
That is the idea of the safety pin
His argument is
I'm a cuckoo bananas person
It's clearly that people
Every liberal
Think Steve Jobs still alive
The same way the globalist
Frozen
You can't you can't criticize
Who
If you criticize me
I will see
I'm glad you picked up on that
Important to remember
Okay
Just remember that you complaining to be snowflakes
And
You will be right
Now we are going to take a little tour through the rest of the time on the episode where Alex
Precedes
To be every negative thing that people think about
This first clip
Shows off a little bit of his islamophobia chops
To New York City
You showing video of a protest of March there where people took the
Sometime too
Appreciate and enjoy
Muslim prayer
Take a moment of silence
To recognize
One of the world's largest religion
Respectfully
Yes and Alex
Really is not happy about
Show solidarity
Celebrating other people's cultures is a delightful thing
To do it's like wearing a
Safety pin that looks like a
The boy
I think I left this in cuz it's really nice
It is it is kind of weird
Any religion whatsoever
I like that
Throat sound
There is a
Reason that religion kind of resin
I do have some ideas that kind of drift
Sexual in a weird way
She probably cut today up
This is a FedEx this is a cockle
This is really anti-christian anti-freedom anti-west Society
Enter the group
The women then put on 1011 they put it on the news
Look how beautiful this is
Does he get to the clip of a woman
Allahu Akbar
Prayer
March
Yeah
Doesn't mean that the
The phrase itself is
Go with you
Are you
Yep you are all phrases
Is there bad okay
I couldn't tell if you're being sarcastic
But it's the same thing with like
You know it's
It's it's a harder argument but
In some unknown hateful contacts
A swastika isn't defensive
You know in like Hindu traditions and things
Okay now I'm back on physical shape of it is not what defensive
If the connotation
And do you suck
Yeah the phrase Allah Akbar is not offensive
Someone is shooting you yelling
If you were yelling
Pretty much anything while you're shooting
I'm going to take that in
Breakpoint that's a good
He always goes on this long
Think it's cool to have Jihadi boyfriend
Talking about
I did not know that
Cuckolding their f****** nationality
Leading the race
Yeah
Will because
What don't you get
All things
White genocide narrative
Okay still there
Cuckold p*** online is all essentially black and white
It's good stuff
I'm not against
But that's the depths of his understanding
It's always white men being humiliated by white women dating
Absolve
Is that what is he saying that all white men should be
Humiliated
When a white woman dates
Anyone not
I think that's
Implied underneath what he
But I don't think he even knows that he believes that enough
That's pretty much
White National
He is advocating
Full on segregation
No miscegenation
I don't know if he was just not being careful with his words
Is always
I mean everything I say
Even when I'm
He gets into a little bit of a combo platter
In this next clip
We get to
Enjoy a nice ride through
Three of the greatest hits
It's like the taste of Chicago
Homophobia
And
Haribol exploit
Native pedophile fear-mongering
To avoid
I think he does
Play Upside Down
Premacy
Everything is anti-white anti-west
Even though almost everyone of them
This is mass mental illness
If you are against
Dismantling whites
Supremacy
Fat fat
Really bad
And if that means
And if your argument is
Isn't it crazy that they're against white supremacy and they're all white
You really might be missing the mark
You should be
Not against whites
Yeah yeah
The very least
Nutrilon
Or else you might end up
This is what you pay for it the colleges
This is what goes on
I need to see the type of women
Only somebody else
Come up
In front of you
And they can't believe you're like a backup
Royal
I want to go to women's bathroom can vice versa
The backyard of your five-year-old says they want to go
Star Wars
Your child allowed to love
California
The Voice
Let us have sex with him we won't have to kill him and throw him in a shallow grave
It's your fault we got to kill kids
It sounds unbelievable
But it is
This is who were facing
It's your fault
We have to
To Kil-Kare
We should probably isolate that for an out-of-context.
What's the next
A policy wonk
Tequila kid
We would love we don't want to
We just
Really have to
We file the law with the UN every time Alex Jones speak
We have we have to
It hurts us more than it hurts
But you understand the logic that he's using their right
Repeat the logic he's using is
That look all these pedophiles really want to do is have sex
For kids
Because they're not allowed to
They got to put them in a dungeon and kill him
He thinks that liberals want to allow people to have sex with kids
In orders that they don't
I have to kill them
That's crazy
Especially considering that he defends Milo
Who now has been outed as someone who was literally defense I was I was just listening to that car
Clip gun
This is before the viola
Information about us
I won't lie that plays into What A Difference A Day Makes
Talk about Bi-Lo
It is
If you guys didn't hear
Number of Clips came out that
Have been in the public
Sphere
Like a lot of it was from his appearances on a boiler alert
Snow
Talk about
Five-year-old
Kids he's not
Milo's talking about his owner
Experience of having sex with adults
Not recognizing
His victimization
Right
He's not recognizing that the other person had an adult brain
At all
And because
He makes it so fine in the waist
He is constantly saying
Is it okay
Absolutely
It doesn't say it's okay
It says you have to
If you have to you have to go
That's where it starts because I promised him candidate always starts with Star Wars
Absolutely the globalist put a lot of pedophilia imagery
Kill the Younglings
With broccoli
Yeah so that's the best
Crazy f****** b*******
3 clips
We've heard rampant misogyny homophobia
Transphobia
Islamophobia
Again
I don't know how many times I'm going to say this
It is not allowing men
That's not what
And if you are in a woman's bathroom
If you're in a men's bathroom as a transfer
There is a
You are the one who will be sexually assaulted
Yes I mean
There is zero chance that goes the other direction
Documented
Nothing is 0 but
For the alike
This or trans for the incident
Some bad people
Some bad Hombres doesn't automatically make you a good person
Definitely doesn't make you a bad person
Very much
Is a
It makes you a person
Train people
I still
Hundred percent
Want to make this clear
Okay our show is not about trying to get Alex Jones
Kicked off the air
I hate the things he says
Yes but much like a vote Voltaire would say
I defend to the death his right to say them
Yes he is a crazy a*******
Another crazy a******
But I'm not interested
Despite all of this hates
Interesting Lee enough
If he was Spencer
We wouldn't be allowed to play his clips
Yep right
And if he was legitimately censored
There would be a part of the show where Our obligation would be
To defend
That's true
And I would stand behind that obligation
Now
All of that hates me
Yes
Transitions into
Of course
What I would call
Some of the worst
Sketch comedy I've ever seen in my life
So he's got a new reporter named Billy Weaver
Who is making
YouTube videos Annie discovered her
And brought her in
So she's as newest reporter
I don't know what the fuc
Convinced him that this was a good idea
But she comes on the show as a character
On Alex Jones Show
The character as a character called rainbow snatch
Called rainbow
Who is a social justice Warrior
Okay
One from My Little Pony
I feel like there's a character on my little pony named Rainbow snatch
One way or another has run afoul of copyright law
Rainbow snake
There's no other way to take
So rainbow p**** is
Number one
Seems awesome
If Ever I found one I would be like there's a birthday of my life
Horribly out of line with his brother
Has anything like this ever happened on
Experience
Time that Alex Jones
Did some skin
Play How It starts
Broadcast
Rainbow snake
I'm sorry but
As we all know rainbow snakes
Snitches get stitches
This is terrible
F****** long
It's so long but please
Enjoy how bad both of them are at character-based Improv
Literally
Minutes before this
He was talking about how legally you are
Have to let your kids be taken by pedophile
Dura level 1 Second City
It's all about Pettyfer
So serious
They're going to snatch up your kids
They're going to rain.
I appreciate you joining us
You're racist
Okay well we finally got one of you to come on the Joe
Riverbank
Seriously
We do what
I just want to say that all you Trump supporters are bunch of racist
I never heard that before
Really
Pessimist
Do you need address me by my proper pronoun okay because you can
Call me
I want to be called
V
What happened
Nope
Excuse me but that is extremely racist
I identify as a multisexual transdimensional
He brought back the cupcake
That seems to be his go-to
So there was no last
Yes and
Was
Thrown away
Athan
Response
Respond to something else
Starting to
Just a totally unrelated set
Right
Or like you ask me a question
Call me I'll be rainbow snitch
Rainbow snitch
How do you feel about liberals
Good point
I can't believe
I have to think that
When they were doing it they were like
F****** nailing this
Because you watch Alex Jones
He looks like a
The cat-that-ate-the-canary
He is
So thrilled selling it well
No
If he actually heard that he was
V
Long rant
Astonishing
I also
But anyway
Did you about this when I was watching
And I want to reiterate this Theory just in case something comes out down with line
I think he's f****** this girl
I can't think of any other reason he would let this on his show it's so bad
Maybe just once
That could be it to American Beauty thing as opposed to the end of American Idol
So we're saying that he's masturbating the shower a lot
Yeah
I think that's probably
Yeah it's so totally different than anything he does
Enough to be a reason for it
That's the only thing I can take a hot young girl
Comes in
She said transdimensional witch
If I were him in this scene
He would be like
Well that's a
You said that makes a god
Yeah
Yeah it's so bad it goes on forever
How many talks to Jerome corsi about a bunch of bulshit
But he has an interview later with the Motor City Madman
It's just
Eclipse
Assume what he says
I love God
I also love God
I like how your voice down
I like to read a couple of Ted Nugent quotes
Just remind everybody
Should not be in the Senate even though he choked it'll be fine
Established my position
80s rock stars in the
What's a feminist
A fat pig doesn't get it often enough
8 Ball
Boy boy
Yeah when he was interviewed in 1990
I said to this
About South Africa
Me being there isn't going to affect any political structure
Besides apartheid
All men are not created equal
Whoa
Well
You know what here's what I will say
All men are not
Created
Here's another one that's a little bit harder
Defend
I use the word
Edward
About that you said
The Edward
The real word
I use the word use the word and this is where this is where we cut out the part where we
Play 20 minutes
Is it okay to
YouTube MTV and I'm not going to walk that line right now I use the word n a lot because I hang out with a
And they use the word an
Communicate
That's just a poor leak
He also said that Barack Obama is a piece of s***
Anyway
Metal rockers
Wango Tango
Man.
Name the song Agenda 21
Okay anyway
Let's not talk more about news
Now it's time to get into
February twenty first
The Milo news
Has broken noses broken
The New York Times story has come out
And boy is the world looking differ
Just going to play this clip
And see what the
Consequences of life
Doing
I don't know
Five six times in big
Article just last two weeks
Dr. Rogers reporting out of this gym
And Britain calling for shutting down
Realize that I
But still
I knew it would be in the paper physical X
Woken up
So
He is so delusional
When we believed when they said they want to
Down fake news
He meant everybody but
Or everybody but him and Breitbart in the light
I don't understand this phrase
So what was going on there is
Did the interview is because
They were talking
And they said we have a goal of shutting down
Fake news
So he
The interview because he's like
Without any self-awareness that he himself
Is the
Piratey of fake news
I have a little theory that I have no basis I don't have no
Rodger Stone told him that he could work out okay
Yeah I think that Rodger Stone might have
Set a trap
God dammit
I don't think Rodger Stone was trying to hurt
He was doing was trying to create negative
Press
For Alex
So Alex
Play the victim
Okay
That is what we are
2 levels deep
Or
Let's go through I'm going to go I'm going to go
Alex
Now I'm going to finish this
This clip Up
Microwave from your face
Because this might Alyssa to scream
We got contacted
This morning
By our big third-party advertising group
That brings in a large portion of our funding selling our products
You are fake news your political
You are kicked off of
Our system
We're good
Nazi Germany
Telling your ghetto you can't have businesses anymore
And he said I was
Free speech
They're coming after it
In 2016
We're in 2017 and I have congressman
On television
And that they want a law passed
They play that clip it's not what they saying at all
Trump should have
His Free Speech May
Yeah
That's
Play clip from senator
I don't think so
I'm going to go with
Let's go with you
Why not
But they're going to go after
Drudge's free speech
And they gave him a heart
Something I don't know if the Supreme Court
Has ever done
So-so Scalia is
Yeah that's why I got killed
Forgot
OSHA
That's the narrative Alex Hotel
Now we're going
Sponsored
It's Google app
I was thinking it was like it was some kind of alcoholic
See I was thinking it was our secret hacker
Know who is finally decided
Nowhere secret back
Immediately
But it's not
It's Admiral Admiral
But
It's a very serious deal
How much
How much money do
You don't get into that a little bit later to eat so that's benefits
I apologize
You can't talk at all because I had to
But I don't know why this clip is playing real low
Compensate
Alright
Also
Tennis Twitter
He can't read those and interact with the public
Twitter is being gamed again
President
The president is also on the 9th
60 switchboard
I also forgot that I was explaining
About about the guy wanting to send
Free speech is it talking about how the tradition
The phrase enemy of the people
Peasant
Sync Lineage 2
Yeah I'm Trump needs to be careful when he uses terms
Have
Traditions that go back to Stalin
Especially when you're talkin about
The Press
At the very least
What the senator was saying
Is
Don't
Say things
Dictators have set
Yeah
If you're going to act like a fascist dictator
Not much we can do
Good idea
Say it
It really if you distill it down
The message is morphe cool
If it's not stopping its pace
You know what I would vote for any senator who goes on TV
Like dude
Chill into the interview and chill
He loves it
Somebody always did
Erasmus family
Donald Trump
Criticized
They're the fake news they're the collapsing news
Answer is
Trump
Warther heating up against
Total War and spread the links and the Articles from the more
Buy the products directly from us
Is there
The whole episode
Becomes Annex
I'm going to sue everybody
Somebody criticize him
Right and
Is going to sue them
I actually took a screenshot
Correct
Cupcake
Yeah
I took it I took a screenshot of
The
They supposed letter
But he got from the Admiral if you want to take a look at this this doesn't look like any letter you get in an official capacity
I mean look at that header
There's no way that header for support of Donald
Play Trump from major advertising
The fakest s*** I've ever seen
Adan terrible MS.
Here I'll just read the entire thing
I apologize for the lack of communication here prior to pause and campaign
Infowars has been flagged by the Admiral policy
Result campaigns
Suspended
Remember to protect
The privacy of our site vendors
Are Parker ad networks as well as the national advertising
Have
Our partner ad networks as well as the national advertising initiative have strict policies
Retargeting user segments
Stop potentially sensitive information
All content on your website should be relevant accurate informative and up-to-date
Any claims should be easily verifiable
We're not able to
To promote websites that intentionally misrepresent their business
Peruse
Supposedly enhance reputation
Or misdirect
Actual offer
Furthermore
All political content should focus on the special interest
Special interest or group
Or imply affiliation
That last part
Is what he does not understand
Here is here's the other thing
Look up the national advertising
It is a sin
Regulatory Prince
Couples
Which Nai members must agree to uphold
Maybe members
Yep
Selfridge
Is the self-regulation at all
Why I don't know about any of that I don't know if he's lying about stuff or what
That letter is
Just like a copy and paste job so they can add that header on which I think is possible
Cuz there's no way they got a letter that said we're Banning you because you support Donald J Trump
Instead of what we
What we know that
Bi Nai uses
I would love to
Cease and desist
Comic Sans
Wingdings
Stop vdi park there the
Any political content
You know...
Cannot apply affiliation
Yeah that's important
Because he is essentially a wing of the Trump campaign
Yes
And especially now that Trump is doing campaign rallies again
Which is bananas
And Alex Jones
Constantly about how he talks to Trump
Right and that article in the New York Times
Explicitly
Laid out
Him bragging about talking to Trump
It correct
She can no longer imply that he is not affiliated with Trump
Arrow
According to
The document that he showed
Has every right
Not to allow their service
Supposed to be used
Real
I don't know but we're just we have to
You know you have to dance with the one that brought you
And if we got it we got to talk about the actual instead of the actual
Enough about the advertising contract their sign
We can only go on what do you provided
And based on what you provided
He doesn't understand
The letter that he puts on screen
Do they have
AJ
Contract with Admiral
Cookies in your computer and they
And so if you go to Empire Court
If you go to
If you go to infowars.com
You'll see a bunch of their weird super male Vitality caveman ads on the site
Then you start going to other websites
You'll start seeing Infowars ads on those other side
That's how
Adware work
Essentially
This visit the service
Yes they have a bunch of
Spaces on Tom's website
That they have a
It's this really weird system
But because you go to their site
Infowars you'll now start this is what's been taken away for
Nothing else
No one is answering him
No one's taking away his free-speech now they're just saying
You are now a wing of
Administration
And you can't use our server
It is
I do not stand up for him
On the ground
Also I think he's
Pretty much fun
I don't think they can even really do that
New York
I mean with citizens united as long as he doesn't actually
I'm not I'm not even going to pretend I know what I'm talking about.
They probably didn't do it because of the fake letter and he gets to play the victim
But maybe they did do it and I don't know why but
You're playing fast and loose
What you need to realize is
Is this real cops
For Alex what you spelled out in disc
I would hate to Molly's Echoes of Alex Jones conspiracy theories
The message wasn't
This is all the New York time
Coming out
In the article
New York Times comes out and says that
Alex Jones
A funding
That's a pretty
Shear
More
Exposed
Nancy Pelosi W bush still the president
Nevermind
He still talked about that clip
But you get that three points
$3000000 number
Route and that sounds
Like that's a real number
3.3 million dollars this morning
That's a good day for all of us
Excited I wasn't worth
I hate reality
He's one of the worst people in the world not encroaching on his free speech
This is a business
You're no longer within the terms of our service
You're gone
Targeted me because of my affiliations and I'm a libertarian
Brooke knows that I mean unless one of the implied
Essential pieces of you being a libertarian
Is
Do you violate their service
You know what he needs to do
What's that in Mexico
Carlos Slim money
What you got to do
So It Goes On
The rest of this episode
Legitimately
It's him screaming about needing money
Cons of interviews
Because he can't handle filling time talking about news
Jerome corsi in in Washington
Broke
He's f****** broke he might not have an angel investor
Actually I think there's two possibilities
Which we'll get to I also got some theories as we go along
But I want to be clear
Jerome corsi
Is out in Washington DC
And it really feels like he's pulling whoever is in the hall and to do an interview
Begets Informer
The guy who is in the Senate
To come in there and talk about how he's going to
Spell dirt on the check
He's amazed
You keep know he keeps saying he was the vice chair of the sub
Committee
It doesn't really spicy
Activia Senator Senator Senator okay what's his name
It again but then he gets like the guy who published Rodger Stones book
7 interview
And it's all just
Search
Aston Township
They're all just like
Your
They're f******
They're all pan
Yeah they just lost
Million dollars
Wow
Great
Next
Is it
Sales pitch
That money
You know one of the things that I
What are the things that I think is
Implied and Alex
Cuz he's just pitching
The entire show
Right is it I think he knows that a lot of is traffic that he gets to his website
And a lot of the traffic to gets
Like I think he knows that he knows that there's a very limited
But he has to work for
Okay
Kind of a feeling that I get
End it
Desperation mode
Here's my theory
You going to be fine
Probably
There's going to be an investor
Alexander
This might be the best news ever for Russia
Did you just have the same thought I did hear yours first Rodger Stone to set up
New York Times article
The New York Times article ended up putting
Alex Jones in the hopper
He needs funding
Invest in him he is over a f****** Barrel
Wow
God dammit
War games
Not what happened
Russia Siberia
Two things that we need to do right now
We need to be on MSNBC as Alex Jones
Expert on.
We need to do
Some serious Consulting for Russia
On how they need
Proceed with this this all out show situation
Scenario I just
Slide-out is one possibility give you a second one
Alex the f******
She's a horrible bigot
And the people who work at accents
Is there anyway we can
. talk with this guy anymore
Breach of contract
Faucet
Roll
Need to get letter
If they're sending that if there's that letter the way it's
Get a letter b a business
Sad roll
Here's this this life
F****** in tent sales
Not normally what we see is him talk about something very serious
Hibbetts into a commercial
In this case
He's doing an ad
Denison to Aiken
Theory about what happened to Milo
The night before
Calendar
Hillary for prison 2017
Rape shirt
Yeah but I am shocked that more meat
Let's go through all the ways that that could be
Sure is it a shirt
Bill Clinton breaks
Reply
It says you should read
Is a shirt
Bill Clinton
,
Rape
It's assert with Bill Clinton raping a shirt on it
Bill Clinton raping a shirt
Wizard of Bill Clinton
What it is is that Shepard Fairey Obama hope
Do you not know that
Nodded
Network really really hateful
Cargo van
His whole campaign where he would tell he was telling people that if you got on the news
Right photobomb the news
And yelled Bill Clinton is a rapist
And said infowars.com he would give you $5,000
Sophie
Well I hope he's already paid
Those people out
Looking up the Admiral situation
None of
What he is
Is on Admiral
We talked about all of the stuff that they emailed him
It is completely mentioned that terms of service
Yeah none of that is on a draw
So
It is
Is this
Is this all a secret game
Game plan
To sell more s***
It could be
It could be you could be having a fire sale
Biggby thing is
Go to you or if you're going to have a gun
Sale
And you're Alex Jones
Make a call
Wow
Right so he's not ordering another shipment
Not a big salad
You know how those there are those compact your bones
Companies where you get your supposed to order the product and sell it to your friend
Multi-level marketing
Pyramid marketing
Ho Lee fuk
I can't be
Begin to tell you how great my come now that I'm eating other bugs
BB
But just to poke holes
A tiny bit near theory that maybe
This is all like a
Facade or fake
Listen to listen to
City of his
Sales pitch
Shopping cart
Would make America free again
I come and take it
They're the ones on every major platform
I will made it
And
All of these amazing
Now we're good
Organizations that are actually defending
No Mel
Conspiracy theories
With Alex
What's your theory on this way
I have no theory on this I'm talking about how the last weekend or the last like 3 clips we end
Immediately
The invitation
Yes
That's what I
Dammit I love this
About to be fair
Alex Jones is not a man who would
Defense ePacket
Any other
Right
Establishment
Thesaurus Republicans
Or something like that
Alright
They're the enemy as well
Republican
He's making them out to be villains
Ray Milo just to uninvite him
Discredit him as
The opening Salvo in the takedown
View right wing
Wacky news
Which he claimed is the takedown of civilization
That's insane
Yeah
That's a long day is they were like
Hottest s*** right now
Milo's a pedophile right now are we blew it
I can't imagine how she Bill Maher must
30 maybe not at all he's
Better ratings
Who gives a
He doesn't give a f***
Probably disappointed
He didn't have him on ask
I know
I nearly missed out on the best Cooper
Can light and my ratings
Everybody watch the ship
I would have been a lie would have been unable to avoid clips of that show today
Bill Maher
Opportunist
It's like we all f****** knew he was from the very
Beginning
He Rambles a bit
Actually sort of
Admits that it's
Cool if Russia infiltrates our government is
Is long
Just weird
And then he gets into another impassion
Sales pitch
Involves
Of the committee
Let's Be Santa
Curt welder
Head of the kid and he was not
Is vice chair of something but again Alex doesn't
He plays fast and loose with the detail
But he knows all about China
Superman
The only ways
Get through this
Of Homeland Security
About the clintons and the Chinese
Whoa whoa whoa
Beautiful
Here's the bottom line
Did he just say it was fine if Russia infiltrated our government
I think he just said it was fine of Russia infiltrated cuz we had Obama in there
What's up basically
He's cool with it isn't that bad
But it's fine now because they respect Trump at the very least
Supposed to pretend
3.3 given up all the secrets
NetSpend
Is he going to give up all of those I think he's trying to entice
The Russian investors that we were talking to
We were speculating about earlier
Of course they infiltrated the government totally fine
He can say that it's cool that
You can say it but I think
Sing it will only make the case against much stronger
Whenever people are alike
Trump song
We talked to him on the phone
I think that basically means it
Trump has told him
Russians
Or at the very least Trump has told him like
Hey man I got all these Russian contracts
What's the only ones left
Also
If we take
Blue lighter that he got
From Admiral series
Him saying that Trump is the most
Beautiful pigheaded man he's ever seen
This might be why you're in trouble
The ballpark
Kind of understand that but again
He's a beautiful pigheaded man pigheaded man
On the cops not a good
If you said I was a beautiful pigheaded man
I would not make me feel better
In your character
So I would never describe you that way
You're an ugly pig headed back
Target
She's on fire
He also was the guy who is behind the Swift boat Veterans for truth
So
F***
New York Times best sellers
Everything that's been a bestseller bestseller
It doesn't matter if you get a disc
Credited
You just shown publicly definitively to be a liar and a propagandist
I don't care about your accomplishments anymore
But also like
Yeah we got to start lying seller on Houk
Works
Oh he's like why is he at his age
Play me so hard
Another day shows that
Screen Jerome corsi
Please fat bloated f****** head
But you want to talk talk
What were the talk
Why do you think it is
The reasons because every other organization get work anywhere else
Listen
No one would touch him
They complain about not getting White House credentials
Another part of this
Been up this
Episode
First of all that really talk a big game before they really they really were
You know they just
They won't give me these credentials there's no reason
To give them those potential reasons not to give you those credentials
Anyway
Some I would love to
To see some Alex Jones questions
In the Press Corps
Just laugh
Excuse Me Miss
Trump
What are you doing
That's way too tight
Have you considered trying wearing a
Bill
Would you also missed suv-like
Direct I missed out
I also think he never lets Jerome talk about Quest
Because he realizes folks
Not anymore
Cuz your life depends on it
The money
Started
We're going
Pledge before God
That I am going to turn
Completely over this
Discernment
Bill about the bills
Money
Pathetic
Really
There are no more conspiracy theories about that
He wrote the letter because the actual email was like
Dude f*** off
Know the actual email probably had details he couldn't
Refute
Good point
He wrote that email
Also
Already but I believe that email
The sign-off is just a first name
Adroll
Caroline
Love and
There's no way that song by Caroline Amy business
Anybody who's in customer relations or anything like that
Has
Email signature they have like a very least they would have a
Phone number boilerplate magazine
You're right
This is not fake he is locked up
Him being f*****
Fox yeah
Hilarious now
Stop doing the show
But we are going to
To see a skeleton crew of a man with an iPhone
Filming him
Dial
Excited get there
Play one Theory
And that is
A bunch of Rubes
So I think he's going to make a ton of money off those
The people who refuse to Baker
Cake of a quart
Yeah or Chick-fil-A to work that way
I think he realizes he has enough bucking idiots
It is called
Maybe it's time
Nicole I can get a lot of money
These ding dong
When is Wednesday
Was going to do a Reddit Ama
But he's decided to expand
Into a 13-hour
Live broadcast oh my f****** god telephone for free speech
It's very much not a freak
Speeches here this is
Stood on his own propaganda pay card
This isn't playing
This is insane so anyway he's not
Seemed to know that he
He's making an extra
23.3 million dollars
You can continue to operate at all
After losing 3.5 billion dollar
How do you speak
Take three billy
Dollars away from the three billion dollars as we projected to make this year
You better fucken have a nice day
I'm so happy now
We're about to enter a weird. For Alex
This is going to be
Fighting for his life
The last hour from here on out
To do the full four hours a Rapaport
People is
Okay
Rapport
Nobody pays rap
For now
And don't put them on the court
Except for him as long as
Dark core of a clip of this either
Young woman's bedroom
Alex was yelling about how
I was going to add 25 more people around here
I lost three billion people I'm going to I'm going to hire four times
You just music I believe in God and Providence
That argument makes me think that there is a sea
Okay like view confident
Hire more people in a downturn
No it is probably just bravado
0 more people now
Ozonics
Affiliate
Mafia racketeering
You better believe you got 10K
Roblox
It says right here
Email this morning
Expenses on your website should be relevant decide
They just planes
I'm worthless
Their businesses are you
Besides
We're just loved everywhere the president
President called president the thing that's the problem
If that letter
No I think
That was the problem
Is that they wanted
Easily verifiable claims
And he has
0 verifiable
Listen to the episodes that we've done already we have verifiable
Evidence
But he's a liar
And consistently lies
Everything is a lie even if you even if he was
Trump campaign
Arm
Referencing
I think they would have been fine with
News is f****** Trump campaign October because of that sentence
Implies affiliation
Important
And he never reads that from that letter
Fox News as much as they are like a propaganda wing
They don't pretend that there
Friends with the
Army they have
They have
What's
What's the score
Yeah but he still doesn't
Talk all the time on his show about how he calls Trump
It like that
Alex Jones is cross the line
In terms of what he's presenting
Also like
Trump calls
No time
Seems like Trump calls him often enough
Yeah they probably talked a little bit but
Probably
Yeah
And he's like
Do you have any listeners who are willing to
Call me at 2 in the morning you got Nugent's phone number
Ivan wants to meet Nugent all the time interview that they kept talking about
Galaxy
Rebel rock and roll
Nobody more rebellious than 85 year old Ted
F****** Nugent weird f****** grey soul patch
It's always a good time
President
Journalist on
What awards New York Times bestseller Jerome corsi
Yes but he has a numerical response
Nobody's giving him up bathtub
Sean
Conspicuous
Guess that he's listening is
Notorious social justice Warrior rainbow snatch
Although
I would give her a comedy
Rice's it
I don't think they're unconnected
If I roll a troll song
That is God is real
The way that Alex Jones
This is punishment for that rainbow science just for how bad a comedy
What the hell are you talkin about we're changing the world we just put the
The other big news
Are contracted and viewership
I love them
They're all in trouble
Except for us
Switch worship
We just got hit by
We're going to
But I don't want to spend all my time crawling around just trying to raise capital
We need everybody to get products.com
Do you want to hear this
That's where this country is
Silver
He doesn't talk to Jerome corsi just talked about colloidal silver for like 5 minutes
By the way Breitbart has an
Yeah they do
Yasso doesn't forward
Nope it's all bulshit
You just go and find
You can't Google search
Yes you can
You can do that
Cuz you're lying
Are they merging with
I think it's probably
I can't be Breitbart
Because
That would have weird console
The
I think it has to be
Garage
You think so I think so
Okay so but Drudge
You just an aggregator right
Mostly
Summer Ridge
Metal content on there but it is largely posting link
To Infowars
Almost
The other so there's almost done
One other thing
Breitbart was taken off at
No no that was supposed
So he mentioned a couple names
He said Admiral was coming after us
One other
Audience
Contracted
And he knows that
Wrightwood which is
The opposite of the narrative that he likes
Suspend but it's also because there's so much fake
Check
Lakeview can have millions of hits to your website a day
But if you look at the actual analytics of it you look at unique
Viewers on a it's totally different
Really like if you go to his
Did you go to the Quan
Cast and you look at the numbers versus younique
Visitors
And it's true
1/3 was fake right most Twitter followers
Between 20% in the third
Yeah remember the exact number but it's in there
Between
Because I don't remember which was prisonplanet and which was
Alex Jones
Wow that's just Twitter
If you go to actual website
Set up
Artifact
Play traffic
No doubt in my mind
Wing sites are doing
Of course
But that's a whole nother
Dilemma for another day
Because
Because there is no there is no right way
There's Trump winning
And then there's
Reality
So there's Democrats who are
He has an interview on this show with a guy
Who claims
To be one of the most important
Intelligence operators in the world
His name is Robert Steele interview
Do
Rob's Mila's better
He's a weird dude and his interview is scary as hell but before we get to that I want to take a little opportunity
To introduce you to another gentleman who was a member of Alex Jones
Okay the name of Mark Dice
Pastel snow
Mark Dice
More less
Yeah I think it's time that we meet him
Is a clip this is a show right now
He
Is insane
Hey if you're adding
If you're if you're there now
With what we if you specifically single him out for being
Now I want
They take at least five minutes
To play a Mark Dice segment in the middle of this week
Yes but also I didn't look at
Intuit and marked iceworks rain for Wars a ways back
And Alex Jones had a falling-out own YouTube channel
He was mocking Alex Jones
Consistently starting are we watching
Special wrestling reconciliation this is Kevin Owens
Is Sami Zayn coming back together
Play Squash the beef
And now they're working together again
More or less
Does a couple of things you sometimes does really snarky report
Football a lot of what he does
Is jaywalk
He does a lot of like the man on the street
The lookout and the implied thing is that they're all liberal
Stupid Liberals are
I'm going to play I hate it whenever we are so f******
Little sample of
I'm out on the street
If you're watching the video
Get to are all trying to walk away
Born and which which means ours which means that not all Liberals are dumb
What country is Mount Rushmore located in
I'm going to have to revoke your citizenship
Located I don't know you don't know
I don't know where you live I have no idea
So
Could tell.
Something about your toy
That is
Dear God
B Barker
It's just asking people questions you were walking around them
But one of his big gotcha journalism
Homestyle
It's he'll pretend
Something really bad
You're so gullible you believe
I took this
Was in talking to a girl that that
Signed an executive order to get rid of tampons
Chestnut
Gullibility
No that's the world we live in
There are
0 things you can tell me about Trump be like entertain the possibility
But you told this girl that Trump is trying to outlaw
Now
Keep playing this in his
Sizzle reel
Stupid people
Response
What's being made fun of their response
Put that
Really
Grateful
Maybe Schnucks
Clippers
Because
He agrees with
Maybe he never wanted to
Maybe that you never stop wanting to take Alex Jones
Conspiracy theorist on this bucket
Jordan the worm has turned
And weird
This is all gone.
Yeah
Really great.
So how bad of like man-on-the-street
There's no punch
There's no like
You're an idiot
It was just keep introduced the idea that Trump was going to be
Preposterous I don't really believe but I will say that it's not luxurious to have your. I've had my
. for a really long time
Question of like where does Trump live it was asked
So far Trump seems to have
Many different living location
Seems like even though he's supposed to live in the White House
Rarely there
Also maybe he lives in New York
Was he born in New York
Probably but I don't know he spends a lot of time in marahlago
Exactly
Somebody
What country
Mount Rushmore in
America
What country is North Dakota
Boron
Highest ship
Camelbeach
Market coming up with your camera then
S*** blowing The Buzz
Trump kids are big Hunters they go on hunting trips just for fun in
Just getting people's reactions to Donald Trump's kids
Now killing the Triceratops toy in Africa
So you meet me in the corner
So again even though he's
He said Triceratops
She had the
Absolute correct
You kill a lot of wild game weirdly
Like if I was asked that question
I would immediately
We stop and go
Ceratops aren't real
To the bigger issue I would say that you are clearly make
Exaggeration and I'm going to give you a response
Instead of engaging with your dumbass
Cheese
Clearly
Like a wannabe actor
She's like grabbing the mic from him and stuff like that just dumb and going along with it for like
Being on camera
What is fine
It doesn't end up being funny at all
All it is is you don't know Triceratops
Fart real
What one I mean Triceratops are
Are real
Not today
Okay that's good
What's next
I don't think
It's true but to
Now this next clip is the beginning of this interview with Rob Steele
It isn't really short clip where Alex makes
Committed burglary Italy
Determinism
The right probably has robbed or stolen
Something
How did you not think of that that's the only thing I've been thinking about every time you said his name because his name
Ste
Ele
Steel
Rob steal to me is more like
Superhero alter-ego
Steel Man
Yeah
So this clip is really short and Alex makes
Wild exaggeration about the situation
And what current this is the most serious censorship
Since the Civil War in this country
Old
Okay
Alright
I'm going to try and argue with it
The most serious censorship
Civil War in this
This country
The most serious censorship
2 Live Crew
Milli Vanilli not being allowed to have a career
Girl you know it
Girl
You know it's true
Whatever FDR refuse to mention that it was
Typically the Jap
Bunnies that he's putting in
The order that he wrote
Never once
Mentioned
Japanese
Selective
Not censorship
That's a good point being forced upon somebody to Live Crew
Group
They got banned
That's great song
His balls to his leg
Although at the same time
Wasn't he already in trouble enough
PCP on video and selling it
My buddy
Me and my buddies actually bought that.
View from the
Like a late-night in
It's called PCP saved my life
It was
This is just
This Robert Steele talking
Clue dinner
Reviews on the show
Right but
This guy is not being allowed to see
Photos of a guy saying isn't
Incredibly scary
But I think it's actually really what this is all about
Hey you're my hero I think you're one of the best
Daniel Sheehan
Jaded
Alex their own whenever they have not yet authorized any
Actual
We still fought a lot of wars
No I agree
Problem
Jones
Losing a sponsor
Is not the biggest
Threat to democracy sent that
I would say
No
Question
Thrill
If you
Lawyers
Is the lawyer
I reviewed his book
To get to lawyer
The greatest lawyers on the planet but one of them
Defended the guy
Papers
Yeah
So you got that guy
Who defended
Let's go.
That's like
The guy who
And the guy who defended from it
Character
Whatever it was the Bob punching dummy
Okay we don't have time for it now but I just want you to know
This is not an Alex Jones take out
I came up with a segment
Next episode
Anyway just got goes on
But seriously those lawyers
The credits could not be further apart
Not good
Sailing company
So they Flash
Sunscreen an article
Finance
Mega sorry Fortune
Wendy's
To his claim that they laid off 500 people
Yeah I'd like to read to you from this
December 7th 2016 article from Fortune Magazine
Victory
Patient employees Fortune has learned
CEO Erin Bell provided
Decisions to focus on the growth areas that were most excited about
And there was no personal impact
We saw a record-breaking Revenue in 26
These changes will
Growth plans
Ambien
That 500 number come from
A little bit later in the article
Around 500 employees
Their entire business
He's one of the most important intelligence operatives in the world
Steven Reed
Paragraph article
F******
Liar
Whatever they're complaining this is why
This is why
You flash that article on the
How long did they leave the article did they leave it up long enough for you to read
Basically admitting that
My viewership
Do not think someone
I am
Isaac
Okay
Maybe we're the only people saying
McGinnis
No we've already speculated that it's just Bob
No one else
There is there are zero Alex Jones listeners and yet somehow we have
Song download
Call Alex
Like
No one was list
Cling to him using him as Source material
We just have a live video feed from a dude in a n insane
That is what Alex lives in his head
Anyway
Get to what I
I think this clip is really
We need to
Facebook Twitter and YouTube
A good start
I personally have never taken a pass on my website
Swore
Fairy
When you come home
F******
When you're complaining about censorship
Channel
I'm destroying the internet
Solid Ground Electric
Formed
Yeah because that
Scott
You know you know how much
Mugabe ran a dictator
97% of the votes
Dictators win 97
Great f****** great
I love it
The truth
Channel
Do you think
So the theory behind
Trump's Act
Was that what he was really going for
Was a
Trump news
That Jared Kushner with run
You think they're still trying
To put that together New York Post
He's a real
The paper
I believe I read that somewhere
I'm not claiming that
Which
If he was going
Merge with
Somebody
Wouldn't you want him
Find out whether or not
Is it
Is it actually this is actually
Ability right
Yeah it is a possibility
State-run media
And if we have
It's not what happens like that's Prevail Brazil has Crohn's the New York
Observer
Is that a like a
Like
I don't know it
It might be I don't know what the New York
Observers I don't know if it's
Paper of record
Incredible
S***
Just make up out of whole cloth video and sound
I apologize that I said
But it still happening
The idea that he's going to merge with some other propagandist arm and create
About earlier the episode is one of the serious possibility
For real
Wow
We are
That's it
That's Russia for all my goodies
Who
Who is going to back
The f****** Trump Channel
What would you ask
Free Rodger Stone
Jersey Theory from earlier
Full circle billion dollars lost
Who is going to finance
Nonexistent
Call Rodger page going to shoot it over
Other and abject Terror sofa
Well here's what's interesting that we're losing 3.3 million dollars
Mediacom
What's great
Did you break my heart now let me try and cheer you back up
So it is delightful Alex Jones
Being in panic mode
It's so fun and I don't think
He's going to get out of it for a while
We're we're here at the very least tomorrow is going to be
Bachatiger
13 hours episodes
You just you told me earlier earlier that you were going to do a full like
I got to take a day off I could have to watch this from
I'm going to come in here tomorrow afternoon
And you are just going to be naked
Writing your name in s*** on the wall
Friday though
So
The what I want to say to cheer you up
Is this
This state-run media s***
You still up
And we
Or on the ground
Floor
Against it
Weird hipsters against a run
The most out of it
You're naked self-interest
Is
Not naked self-interest
I don't need game monetarily or anything like that
What is now important
Yeah weird
Weird
Being important is the worst thing I can think about
It's a little scary this is so fun
So
Like it's. Severe released
Hundreds of people were listening
Like it did everyone loves
Appreciate
Do you listen very much
Debunking these lies are so easy
A hot knife through butter
We
God I wish just gave us
I think
That we are in for an
Uno's 6 months from now
Let's not go crazy
Maybe the only way to keep this going is to escape
We're going to go from being knowledge fight to Trump
News fight
Yeah
And also
Remember
I like episode
Three-year whatever I was speculating that
This could become dangerous
Yeah
This could become
I thought we were all having a nice little laugh
Not anymore
This could
Like
You know what happens to people that does sound very megalomaniacal
Now do what we're doing in Russia
Yeah oh my God if we
Look
Do you remember the journalist
Ate her home
In the face like
20 time on Putin's birthday
Birthday witch
Both
Like if it was
Real
TV show part of you realize that's wagon dick
Let's
Book The Wire
Like them
We might be in your f******
And shot today
The only way I want to die for sure
Just bring this back into reality
Yes
This hasn't happened yet
The state-run media thing
There's just
In this episode
We're not really in danger we're not we're not paranoid to the point where it's like
We think this is real no matter how many conspiracy theories we just made up in the past hour
We are not paranoid worst case scenario
Getting really dark
We will commence again
Best case scenario is that this
Get dark
For whom
Dark that's fine
Anyway this last clip I want to play is more from the Robert
Steel
Interview
Where Alex
Trying to get
Robert Steele to talk about how
Shity Alex's situation is
All you want to talk about
What's wrong man
Alex wants to do is talk about like I lost 3.3 million dollars everyone's trying to censor me
And Roberts
Steel is like
He will not
Stop
Cheating
You need to get lawyers
In-N-Out
Alex Jones is
Defense
If I just lost 3.3 million dollars
Holy s*** that's all I would be able to talk about
Taking the day off
That's a good point
F****** wasted right
This dude
He is sucking wasted right now
You should replace it about
10 in the morning
Still just keep telling him to lawyer up
Lawyer up
Dafuq intake
The fight
Google
I guess
If you're going to win a fight
Against
But that's that's another thing if he does
End up taking the skies advice
She's going to get why
Frankly if he fights against Google I wouldn't be surprised if
He died on Google
GE doesn't exactly what the
This f*****-up about this clip
But it's f***** up
You are our natural leader
Wolf
Lawyers
Washington Post list they admit was a fake list
You signed a contract worked with you for years and now we're not going to work with you
They said know you're fake you're a fraud
You are a propaganda
I wouldn't say it you
No nevermind
Speak out
Gloves off
That's not.
Oh my God
It's also not there is a trump News Network
Alex Jones will win all of the ports prices
Because you know
I listen to I listen to the Past episode does like
That's both just left
Just
Having a guy on
By the way
We all know how hard it is
To get voted out
To do that
Not great
Is Rob
Still currently
Sucking Alex Jones
Do you like Alex Jones
Bingo there are natural
The guy on Skype
Sitting with Jerome corsi in an office telling you that the Chinese are involved with Hillary Clinton which is something you said
100 x on your own show already
But given no evidence that actually happened
That's not surprised
Journalism
And I know
He's never going to get to the details
This guy came on my show and said his family was threatened
As that becomes
Enough for the story to be real
Was that guy's family threatened with polonium poisoning
Like Rogers
It's everywhere it's all around us polonium
I don't even know if I'm not poison with it right now I know you might just be sleepy or
Right where you're right where Wikileaks was
Which is not a thing they have to have
Freeport
Free Waze app
Symptom of steroid
And you make these purple people
O.j. Simpson
Let's stay right where we are
O.j. Simpson murdered two people
Lawyers to cover it up
So don't use that metaphor
When Legend Lee murdered
It was not
But anyway
I wish I was all the sudden everybody found out that I'm an OJ apologist or something
Your Holocaust denier
Cuz you're pigheaded
I am I'm a
Beautifully picnic
No don't like the dream team's you want to say that
Girl
Better Dream Team
I really hope he was on the Dream Team
I forgot tonight for lineup
Me in front of Donald Trump and Steve
Is that how we got the record
Because I've got to suggest this electoral format
Well if
I will I mean
Would total
Totally
Aruba
Little bit of a
Is playing Alec
Because
The whole thing where you were like
Because you trying to
How many dicks
Do you have to suck to get to Trump
My favorite
Stucker commercial degrees of Kevin Bacon
Trump
I think this guy does actually think that there should be a trump
Channel
But I also think
He has no
The Alex Jones
Which
Is a great idea if you're him
It's not a bad idea.
But he can't talk to Alex
We should use Alex to get to Banning
I do want to have a great future stroyan
Man that be bad
Yeah every so many articles about
Cox we are at Breitbart
Polonium poisoning every other day
That's true I've been trying to use the bike more and had to work
Not going well
Polonium
The next move
That's why you should not buy a bike made out of
To the end of our clips
What a difference
Restart
This episode
Happy fun time I'm pissed off about how I'm being portrayed in Homeland I don't know what's real
Racist bigot
Aveda
Alex Jones being panic
Have been at the height of
His powers this is Amanda
With fake panic
Vog share price
Panicked about
Others
Yes the first time
Hispanic about
If he's ever been in survival mode
What a beta cuck
He is
The moment
We have I still don't know what that
I don't either
Has something to do with Islam
Alex
While
Enjoy the weekend.
At gmail.com
I wouldn't mind
Beautiful God damn fool anybody can figure out our f****** Twitter handle
Jordans
So much fun
Always a delight
Tell you all about the 13 hour marathon
Question
Are we
Holding
Alex