Alexandra Thurston color
Is there a certain
There is nothing special going on
Absolutely
Using out of context
Text Rob
That's address to drop
But I believe a year ago I made the pronouncement
Turned on Donald Trump I would bring you a bottle of champagne
I'm a man of my word
Papa corecredit
Ever recording it was Friday
Guys that got on are about three hours of a Special Report with
Right before you do like to give a shout out to a couple of new walks couple new donors what's go
Thank you so much for joining up with the team
Dodge Demon
Hotel
Very exciting
Also exciting is someone who donated
Specifically in anticipation of the show
And therefore I must allow them to cut the line of other people who are waiting to get there
Butter Patrick thank you so much
And tell your brother
Someone someone sodomites a bucket
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Patrick you are now
A technocrat
Thank you very much Patrick I assume you inhabited the body of a Whoopi Goldberg
7:45
Perhaps but if you would like to support the show become policy wonk yourself you can do so by going to our website knowledge fight.com
We would appreciate it very much appreciate everybody literally since I was jumped
Got a got a couple of donations the game is about
Excited for us to cover it and point out all of the point where he's being
A complete dumbass
Validating his own narrative
Cheers my friend
Delicious block of Blanco
Blanc de blancs
Classic white on white
I believe is what it's called so Jordan
We have this 3-hour special report in front of us
There were a couple of false start
Alex Jones Twitter live stream
Did Rob do recording
I am so we will start by listening to a couple of days
Here's the first one
Kill the f****** feet
You clearly like
Morrisville
The passion behind it mostly because he realizes
It's a feeling of I'm sick of doing this thing I have now been pushed too far
I have a very clear
Beery
It's not a theory
I'm pretty certain I know what's going on
Alex.
Alex Jones is alliances
Allegiances lie with Russian I was Trump butts
What this strike accomplishes
Is not
Alex isn't afraid of the fact that
But he attacks Syria or something like that
Which
Super excited
He's doing
But yeah they're terrible but Brian Williams
The other thing
Without a massive
Conspiracy to
Nerve agent
YouTube back it up
Alex
Has to realize the Trump tax
Reveal to his audio
That he's been lying about Trump
For two years
Like there's no other way around the idea of like drops on our side
I mean just the other day
Trump came out as like I think we might want to get back into the TPP
Which is one of the boxes bigger Banner issues with everything he does
Which is a good thing
I think she's I think the tpp's going to be for us
I don't understand it fully enough
I've looked into 7
What are those
Letters larger trade deals
Themselves like that I don't fully understand
Because it's
Another Commerce difficult
Yeah yeah it's all good
Not for it
So
Start
Didn't work
He tries again
Right
The secret
Agreement
It should be
Everyone has already captured
Anytime he's like fun
Trump like that's what that's going to take the number one seed
I was listening to him start talking about Madison he's like
That's f****** Mattis Badcock
And I swear to God the next thought I had was Alison going to say he's got big full lips
Beautiful I mean
I'd like to apologize slightly for some of the audio Legos capturing this
On-the-fly last night
I was recording office
BuzzFeed that I don't think was very good
I tried to a
Lo-Fi stuff but it's got a
It's got a different flavor to it then a lot of
Yeah and I was pretty worried that
The situation we were going to have it was going to be
Delete all this stuff
You couldn't have deleted
Because those got those went viral as it were like those wherever one is reposting nose
Like
Little Twitter videos
And stuff like that
That much
Do most of the actual 3-hour report
But he does want to eat
Fixies deleted those speeds
And get back on air with Owen Shroyer sitting silently by his side
Which is what we will do
Disgust will start
And of what he thinks is going on in Syria
I will say that
Fairy
Okay
The first time of like maybe 6
DVD says I'm not a rusa file and then say something
Also I can't confirm or deny
The Tardis is an actual Port but it is a doctor who reference
They like the idea that Alex is icon are being like
They killed 10,000
Russian
Is absolutely
The whole reason that they were so very careful because if they killed
Evacuated the target
And stuff like that
The strikes are never all that well-targeted
There's this terrible
There's Terrible Things Precision strike means
We're going to try and kill less we mean
The ten thousand Russians
Workout
Bogus
And the only way he could actually believe 3,000 Russians
I believe the last report I saw something
Perhaps
So that's
Show me number dark lips wrong is one
Before this
Broadcast start
Ivan Alex
Expresses his feelings about
Go back on the rim
Call train
That's not good
No
That's not great none of that
Also
Is he talking into a shirt on this
Drinking or doing some blow or something but
Deviate
Things are completely underlie that there isn't
Arrangement
Between the military and the Russians and Assad that they're going to kick Isis and Al-Qaeda out of the country
Renaissance
Does Alex
Conspiracy Theory on
Ritsu would be that the British call the British released
Doing chemical attack
And that's the one everybody
You really have to take into account
How much is entire argument that
Making hinges on his idea that the gas attacks
Were fake
Didn't do it
The fair play to you
I guess
Make that sort of claim but
The facts on the ground
Indicate that that's not
Given his history
And the ideas
Involved in some sort of a deal that involves Assad stepping down doesn't make
Expense
Because of money
Drop them backing him up
There's a relationship there that doesn't is not just
Some sort of benign
Islamic terrorists and then
Have a great day everyone
Do
I don't know what it is but this
Nagging feeling on
Why
What Assad
Spit chemical weapon
Cuz he loves it
Like
Fetishizes
Mike Mike
First especially whenever I heard that chemical attack
It was more like
I'm guessing that
Soldiers or whatever
The pro-assad people
Just had them kind of lying around they ran out of other ships
That sounds more like what happened then Assad actually ordered anybody personally to do it there's two pieces of it
Possibly understand the mind of a dick
The motivation of like oh it looks like
He's winning
I don't know I don't know what that
That mind is like
Yeah that's a f*****-up mine let's true barely we're also like
We're assuming a coherent chain-of-command where there probably is not
Assad ordered
I don't know
I have no idea but
What you just
Explain to the very very likely possibility
And with Israel with those Israeli shoulder soldiers
Sniping
People just added
And laughing about it
That's not the Israeli government doing it that these guys
Way too much power and free reign to do whatever it is they f****** want
Because I don't know what really is f****** going on Defender
Goodbye
Murder whoever they want
So
This is all to say
Alex's Alex's
It's flimsy
But
There's no doubt about it
You mad at Ross
You are
Don't think he did that
I don't think so either
Did pretty much exactly what his family and his name has always
I got a I got a I got a full explanation for Alex
In terms of like why you like
Look up
You always good to his word on pppp and on the tax cut
And immigration
And now he's f****** it up here on 6th and I like
You got to understand that that all physical here in pattern immigration stuff is cuz you're the f****** racist history of
Minorities
Reverently spindle in the mouth
For City Treatment
The tax cuts are because he's super-rich
In terms of he's dating Texas
He hate immigrants and people who are non-whites
Exactly and then the TPP stuff
Are good
That Trump has done our very very well take
Can care of through just like
This is his personality
Dear Alex last year Trump bomb Syria
It's not a certain point you got to see like
Kind of fine with it
Also
He's a pathological lunatic liar
What Trump is
Dishonoring his family name with
Silly fool Alex Jones didn't go to high school he doesn't know math
Doing this makes Clipper Alex Compares himself to
I love that if you call me again I'm going to tell you
I'm ashamed
So mr. president
Have you no decency
I would
Absolutely
I defended you what you want to train people out of the military
Starting World War 3
Ellettsville
But sir you have gone too far
By pissing off Russian I guess I don't know
I don't know because like
It's pathetic to watch this
Display cuz there's a couple things that play
Are you going to see this play out over the course of the
This one of them is Alex trying to talk
Himself into skilled
Right
I love it
Sending Trump's phone calls directly to voicemail
Cubs score
If he's mid-coitus he's answering a call
Oh but the other thing is that's kind of
We talked about this a bit
It's kind of like you've negging Trump a little bit
Please call me
Please please I love you
The other thing that is in play your see this play out over the course of it is Alex
Trying to get a couple guests on
He's trying to get them to reassure him that he did a good job
Breaking My Heart
Can you play
Exact
Joel skousen on and that is the sort of feeling
Over the last
Two years he hasn't completely s*** the bed just like this whole
Alex
Real weird
This isn't like down clip
This is Mike.
This is one of the weirdest things I've ever heard Alex Jones
I don't know what to make of it
It's out of nowhere
Girlfriend
What
Oh man that is that is wild
Progressive
Minute-and-a-half clip
Lead me to a couple conclusions that I've never had before
I think
I think the most
Amazing thing that he said
Stonewall
Trump's beard
That is weird
No no cuz I think he I think he is
I think
Right
Truly
Straight but pretending to be gave in Rodger Stone could actors
But if I understand correctly
What's going on is Stone weird
Is
Chilli dating the women that Trump is going out with
No I think
Just bought I think what he's trying to imply is it because Rodger
Your stone is a libertine in a sweater
And then it would be an excuse for
For Trump to be seen with them or be around them
Alright
Then at the same time I don't know how that relates
To the allegation
Has not been made
Very weird
This is very very
I could be
Share it
That's weird that we don't even have time to
I don't know what he was trying to
How to say cuz he started with
Trump's not gay and neither am I
I'm not gay
But what was going on in the middle.
Top 7 or 8 Women
Then we thought you have babies
Exactly the other thing is like
Will contact in space command Sade from
He's trying to also present situation where like the idea that
Is the worst possible thing
You are possessed
No
No I'm not saying that I'm just saying that if he's like if I liked
I would tell everybody I
Which
Carnival
Possibly his ego
Into a man who is who is born gay
Yeah he be like
Rodger Stone
That's all I got info
Yeah I don't know either we don't have time to talk about is sex
Claims that's just the same
Go away
Send a text to rationalize the situation
And you just really
Daria furs
Got a call
Oh man
I'm trying to work this out but I'm out of
An idiot
Haggai
A guy
Welcome welcome to us
2 years ago
I'm doing the math
How true
Possibly sell it
I just can't
I can't see a situation where
Is entire past pattern of selling people out is now hit me
It kept going
You got played by a pro Alex and we've always known this this is been a constant
You know what I always believed you would never come back on
Very clear that like Alex couldn't get a hold of Rodger
Cuz otherwise Rodger would be on this broadcast
And I know for a fact
50 pechenick isn't answering his phone
Cuz Alex keeps telling
The crew
Call Steve pieczenik
I don't want to do
I'm going to be great he's you know he's going to do whatever Trump wants him to do now we have a week
Bombing a country
That's a shock
Do all of Alex Jones is like
Stalwart
Narrative guys
Arnot
Coming to the table
Rodger Stone not answering the phone
On the phone telligent store
For this past 24-hour W f****** a lot without
I'm going to Liberty meme
Or he's heading to
The Border
You might see the writing on the wall
This late-night drunk girl down podcast
Alex Jones blames
Expresses that Russia is awesome
Is it
Not like Trump did
Doesn't bring up any of the shooting of Hannah with ever
Do you make a rapid corruption that we
I was caught on tape
Oh boy
Kill all those
How do you spell shout out to all the people all the stupid assholes who are like Alex Jones works for Israel why doesn't he talk about his really
He's legitimately blaming Israel
How do you gas attacks
Oh I was joking about Israel
That that is a very very incomplete
This career
He's more willing to if he doesn't want to wait
Versions of the real world
In which is even more funny when you go back and look at the context of him saying
Never said he didn't payoff limit
Screaming on are about how this is all bulshit in a Witch Hunt and all that stuff for weeks
Very weird
He's very Wayfair nonsensical there's a there's a lot of
Mismatching s***
But pretty much
Politico
I know and just doesn't say much
Role in this
Call Sherrod is essentially just being like
Russia is going to attack somebody
And that's his that's his hold like a present a
Basically it's just being there.
Is Alex's going
He's not
Ready to make that kind of a sand
Or anything like that but it's going to be like
I don't see how Russia doesn't respond
They said they're going to
I think this moment we're like legitimately Owen Shroyer is kind of realizing I'm in over my head
This is about my grave this is this is a mess
Hours before the show
On the show
When you change the entire narrative
Exactly what you're screaming
Trump you drunk a*******
Alex
Amanda
What does come in and say want to be funny
If things I've ever heard
But
Something very not true about what the globalist
So done to him
When I turn on Trump like I'm doing right now
So
That leaves little room to interpret
This is what's going on
He's trying to do a face turn special report today
Saturday
Imagine we're going to get Rodger Stone
I'm pretty sure that
Car fender or whatever
Because
I mean even today like right before we started recording
Trumpet
Mission accomplished
There is a decent chance, we'll see is not more escalation and not an ongoing
And that will make Alex Jones how to be like
All right look
He just had to send a message
But in a sex club Alex Jones
Anybody who tells you that they re
Philosophy
Is a loop when did we get there
I know we're on TV off aqua.
Alex
You told everybody you read philosophy
What time
I don't really read much philosophy anymore I didn't College
But I started philosophy
Much like this Blanc de blancs
We didn't
Vouchers thing at the globalist
The kids from him cuz he supported Trump
Disgraceful but it gets even worse
Is back to
3 years ago
He's back to September 25th
Alex
How can you
Possibly run a casino without committing a crime
Yeah
Turning into just a pure airing of grievances
This is just all of his
Actual
Emotions
Finally coming out and we're getting my favorite Alex Jones
I don't understand the world and I have to admit it
Publicly
Get it I thought I knew what I was talking about it it turns out I do my God I was lied to me
Much support this guy
People are criticizing me because the guy decided to
Sports clips
Brooks
Abusive and violent
Idiot is going to punish me for that course
Oh yeah this is a giant Daddy
My God
Rough
I love it
I understand look I'm not one generally for schadenfreude I don't appreciate
Other people suffering
Pass on me.
Lighting in someone's Misfortune for a second
But you have to recognize two
That like
As much as we hate him and he is a
Complete liar and it is ruined so much
He is a human and I do think he's feeling a lot of pain right now.
Placed but I still like when he start like
Yours talking about fake tears and people in the chat room
The lilting the voice is like that is not fake
We weave listen to a billion hours of Alex Jones until when he's actually crying
I have no issue with the
The schadenfreude
I'm not defending it I'm I'm
Explaining this this
Experience
It is just like
When you watch a
Serial killer documentary from prison where the serial killer is just talking about
Oh I was victimized
Their history like yeah you know you're the one doing it though so go f***
You're an actual psychopath
No more human empathy which means you are no longer in the human race
I disagree I a little bit I think
Some piece of that is
Is
Is fair
I mean
You cross a certain level
Like you don't really deserve that
Used as an excuse
Like once you're doing such terrible things
You know all I had it bad isn't
Excuse the same time I don't think
Think it's right to celebrate
Humanity
That way like
Then Bill really terrible
I don't believe I'm celebrating in humanity
Like people who were abused or whatever
I have gone down the line
To like they abused other people
As if they are human
For the sake of giving up on some Humanity
I think
To ascertain
I don't know it's such a thin line to walk in
In terms of like
Yes there are monsters
In the world but those monsters are still human
And generally speaking in a vacuum this sort of behavior doesn't exist
Like just someone who lives their life and goes along naturally
Bit like an Alex Jones is Not
Created without
Some sort of terrible
Trauma
Something bad happen
The path that he is on
Making probably too fine of a point
In episode when we're trying to just laugh at him being an idiot
I love it but he is a human
And
I am not so out of touch
Humanity
Real Steel
Feel that pain
And it makes me sad
But I also still laughs a lot legitimate
And I respect that about you
Don't know how to
Turn that part off and really Delight in the monsters.
Are you kidding I do this drink
I know but you really got to turn it off I will try to something else
You better have a good sense of humor
For sure
In a moment
To Alex Jones
Appearance from his fake
Intelligence or Zack
Reset a bunch of really stupid s***
Before we do
Kind of hard little pan under the table I just did that
No you said we'll be back in about 2
2 minutes
They're back
Zach
Is about to show up
This clip
Show me
He's going to stop time
But
What are the things is really interesting is they're like
Galaxy
To reinforce
His flip
Is is Right turning on Trump
Going back to
Exactly do you need to create a situation where
We can go back on
You know like
Sprite
No you shouldn't get divorced you should work on your marriage
I understand exactly where you're coming from your spouse
The Lord wants you
To stay married so you need to go back
Go to write
Zac is going to create and bring in the narrative
I have a gun to his head
To do this all right and then as we go on
But we're going to see why Zach should not be trusted as a legitimate
It plays out pretty clearly that
He might belong on
Donald Trump
Directly work reward
We should have been a long way
Politically
Own it
Call Sophie
Are you talking about what's a lb
Are we talkin about any of the people who act
And was in his entire presidency
Looking for the war that would make his name as the president
Or the other what's the mythology
It's around the assassination and it's
Fun
Cuz it it creates a more robust worldview where in everything
Thing is fake
Oceans of the
The globalist
Right
Got a gun to his head politically and physically
He's got pictures of him getting picked on and then he's got a gun on the other side of the
They got to look back and forth between the tip
Look at his eyes and press conference he never hold
His head up like that
Every time he statement written by him for one of his idiot
Idiot doing one of his Planes lally's
Everybody
Wii support
Martin Luther King
Who what day is this
Whatever Pennywise I prefer senior
Absence exclave Alex explained
I wanted to make a Supercut of all the time because he's not a ruse file cuz I'm 25.
Mobile
When did you started laughing
So
They're perfect
What did Russia do
Russia
Joining the Syrian cause whenever Isis
And the non-existent al-Qaeda are there
Or did they join Assad whenever he decided that any Rebels who thought
Maybe living under this f****** autocratic monster who gasses his own people isn't a good idea
When did Russia join in
Did Russian join in on the side of the goddamn heroes or did Russia join in on the side of the guy who f****** gases
And murders
And murders and rapes and murders
They're not
His people he is not of these
He is a f****** moms
His people
His people are f******
Slobodan milosevic
The monsters of the of our history
I think it's a probably are most interested in their investment
The big made it have because they see
Chaos swayable
Government
It's Rhonda autocratic
Yep and it's a strategic position on what
Zbigniew Brzezinski
The great chessboard it's a hit point in the region and in the greater World in terms of
Influence
And approve time
Anytime. Kind of predatory vested interest
In keeping that outside of the sway of a democracy
Right outside of this way of liberal
I mean liberal in terms of
Free governor
You're the best
Everything that because
Create a very serious threat
To his ability to run
Oil
Through
The country that would cripple him as a as a
Probably more what
Then but I don't know
Ulta
Are there Heroes
I'm so at
Who is Zach his
He's pitched the narrative
The trop as apolitical
Biblical gun
Does a different take on what
Possibly could be going
Okay
MK Ultra
Could have either become a weird sociopathic monster
Orton Keyes
Mary prankster
I mean this is a mess
I mean even for like what
How far are you willing to go to excuse this thing you ate Trump for
You probably mind control
Probably
Ronald
Ridiculous
It's so weird
Tubes not that weird no no I mean
Type of almost
Textbook battered wife syndrome
Yeah like that's really kind of what it looks like your Alex constantly say
I feel like I just got broken up with I'm not a bruised woman near anything like
This is done wrong
Committed
I think I don't know we'll see what ends up happening I think you take
I think he probably
Future hold
In terms of this video existing
But I would say I hope they take it down
And further I think
That whoever allowed him
To do this
Gave us
A great boon
Did a very serious just serviced Alex
Whoever allowed him to be on air is like
They might be working at cross-purposes
They might be going into business for themselves
Cuz he's there in the background
Actress of question
Look at how much bucks
Compressor kit
Sure but it's not good it's not good
Goes back to work Sunday or whatever today
Start do you know what happened
Trump is doing something different this is what happened
This is what would happen if Trump was being serious
But I know he's not
Now but you know that my principles are intact
What
Would leave him
Well there's that but then there's also the existence of this thing as I got
Being a total baby on air
And it's just like if it was only deep-seated issues are arising because of
Trump there Larry there is a way Alex
Could have done this
Exact report
And it not be damaged
You know what I'm saying
Like there's a well
There's a way he could have got on air
For the last two
3 years
Already you're wrong because
Sounds
Very conciliatory in profession
That's what I'm saying he could have been professional about it
I have not Galaxy
You know the reasons why I have
I've gotten information from people that has led me to believe x y and z
This development
With bombing Syria
He's incredibly troubling
To meet because I trust my sources that have told me
Complete bulshit
Line about Russia and Assad and our military
Facts behind Obama's back
I believe that
And now what I'm coming to see is
Is that Trump is not a part
Of this world view that I have believed
And therefore I must
Say
I do
Even now
He is not
Really admitting he's
He's saying he was betrayed
Of course which is a very different thing you just described was a man admitting he was wrong
Get away from your wrong by saying I believe my sources that I had
And I was wrong my sources lied to me
Or my sources had
Something wrong
That they burn all the sources
If he flips on Trump he's got a bird a lot of people
None of them a real swell.
If he if he continues down this road and is anti-trump
Here's a lot of question
The desperately need to be asked about Rodger Stone on everyday and co-host
The War Room
Like he's a very massive piece of the operation that needs to be explained
Cuz Rodger
Turn on Trump
Rodger can turn on
But just for that
If you have to have a good time like legitimately if we're talking about real-world stuff and not entertainment if
He's got to go Beanie Sigel on this s***
Estates property
He's got to get in the witness protection program
Because he knows too much
Oh yeah
With what Rodger stones into Rodger stone is our situation
Just don't polonium poison
That I believe
What you mean the times you tried to fake polonium poisoning
So I can Poison by polonium Rob do data
I don't know
But I think it was him because
No
Rob do because he's got to save the ship
Do you know that Alex
Check his hands dirty
This Gathering robbed the fixer
Competency
Fixer in the history of the world
The more I think about it the more I think there's way more up with Rob do than we even
Acknowledged
Cuz he's so boring
He's our Kevin Spacey he's verbal Kint
Be there usual
Forever
Infowars trenches for
Probably
Almost a decade
That's crazy
I have to assume there's a
On the emails and he knows he's up
Nothing he's up-to-date bad works or whatever
I think we might be giving him a pass
I might need to look more into Rob do we overlooked him as was his
Goal all along
That's right anyway
They're guessing interior was Alex
You talk about it
Is like a round over Trump
He's going to bomb
Yeah
How do you breathe
Okay
I swore on air and
CiCi's paying attention Alex
But this is a theme to keep in track
You
So
I don't know about that
Releaf
Is
Alex
Only one who
F******
Get it
Careful
Alex's
The only one who is listening to what Trump is saying going
This is f***** up
He lied
He liked.
He doesn't mean
Because a liar
You doing all this s***
I don't think
Feared meaning
Lego
Not there
They're all so meaningless and
Nothing
Their own
Turn on trumpet they want
Singular idea and they're f****** head
Sir Alex like
Trump is Daddy and I can
Like Steve and Rodger Stoner Daddy
To all of his employees Alex
There is this
Placate him and calm him down
And then they're eventually going to have abusive relationships themselves in order to Tryon
And fix it
I like just say really quick
I'm not seeing the
The chat so people are pointing out anything that is very
Cool I don't see it
I apologize
What the deal is
But
One of the things one of the
Convictions that we have
Express tonight
Standby
Is that Alex's
Expressing
But his allegiances lie
Difficulty with Russia not with Donald Trump
Could not be made more clear that in this
So
He wants our government to be like
This is this is actually
Probably the best evidence
That
Trump colluded with Russia
What they're describing right now
Because what I'm hearing is
The Echoes of
Russia being like
God dammit
You f****** a******
Fascinating
I didn't even think about that
That's
He's a f****** lunatic so if we're to believe
Concerned about
The saddest
They were live
Nothing is going well
Technology
Oh no
What
I'm seeing the stream going out of my mind
On my phone
Now you're good
Is a foot
Anyway
Yeah
Brewery
You were in
Is entirely in line with Russia finding out that they have been
Yeah if you imagine if you imagine if you know Alex Jones assertive
Secondary station
Did these narratives
That does make sense
I never I didn't I not variable of it
Before
Expresses impotent rage
He is not used to it
In this next clip
Alex Jones
Zach
Fake
Source is Zack
They talked about what
That be great if this was actually
Call evaristo great
Secret Improv
This is
Is the moment that I'm making the argument that Zack belongs
Amazon Project
Hold on
Maybe we're not
This is a fight for Mars
Okay
Where you go through
He goes for Big Stone
All right yeah that's right they're trying to keep us back on planet
Dermografo coronavirus real
Okay cool
I'm glad
So Gone
So now you get to
Keep track of your dick
If anyone ignores you from now on it's Jordan not me
But I love that cuz
It's a way of making it like
Conspiracy really revolves around it's not what you
You think it is
Everything is a distraction with the real thing
You know when you take it
Would you take it from this is really terrible no one should
No one's into this
But it's actually about Mars
You can
This was all actually about Mars
Where did that way better world to live in for all of the all of the geopolitical
Conflicts that are currently going on
It look
You go to Miami
You go to f****** Burma you go to the rohingya
Philippine dealers are just quotes
For people who don't want to go to Mars it's all code
They have a base on Mars and don't want us to
They're working with the Raptors
Course Mark Richardson fight against them from inside Vacaville prison
Here's why and what area
Pavilion building
Well
Research Center
Call could be
That argument but unfortunately it turns
She's an Egypt right now leading a
Study group
What Stewart's
Egypt with a with a study group and so that's why she hasn't any videos out lately
Go to Egypt
Enjoy her being
No she's a
She's a tourist it's not like
Conference there anything
Jesus going to go to the pyramids and be like check out all these aliens
Church group therapy bring like that it's
Anyway that's why she hasn't done her Mark Richards update number 8
I'm excited
Anyway
I told you the exact should not be listened to
And that means there's 100
Use blowing mind pretend torpor
Presents himself as a
Someone who's in the most
High levels
Military Intel
And you would think
That is
Being in that position he would know who the Joint Chiefs of Staff
Frankly at this point
No one does
Half of them
Are there
Joseph Dunford
Alex starts talking about this guy
And I tried to get
Owen is no idea
Really should f****** know
Doesn't
On the phone
I don't know
If you want true comedy
Alex said Dunford at the beginning of the
The clip and is trying to come up with his name
Oh you already said you would do you know who you're talking about
So I have no idea
She's established
I probably should know
McMaster
And McMasters out which he is
Eager
Your Source still in play
The f*** are you listen to this guy for
Insights that he can bring that nobody else can
Battle For Mars
So this first guess not great
Not great
Alex
But it does sort of like Trump is being blackmailed or there's a gun
To his head
God damn phone
It's over 9000
Joel skousen is a survivalist weirdo
Do I also
Disney nephew of w Cleon skousen monster if
Who's responsible for a lot of terrible right wing
World that we will do a whole episode
It does not deserve to be talked about now
Joel skousen
For Eyes terrible as he is
He gave up on Trump
Before
He is
Clear about this
And that's why he hasn't been on the show
Quarterback
And they talked about that a little bit
But Alex asked
How did they do it
Skousen has a real
All right there we go
Jobs
Well first of all the stuff you said about Trump being smart not true he's a f****** idiot
First off
Trump
Is dumb and lazy and he's too busy
Trump let me tell you something
Is a
Boron Alex Trump is the dumbest
F****** president we've had since
George Jung
He is so f****** stupid
Get the chance to understand a word he f****** said
Skousen goes on to say like
Curative
You'll notice a certain shift
Prozac
Narrative
And Joel
Meredith and Alex agrees with both
Because he's just
Lisa malleable Lappy
Piece of s***
Because right now if if he brought low if he had a
Rajasthan Alex
Would be a Scientologist
At the end of this
Well I'm not sure about
Because there are things that are malleable there's things that are wobbly
In terms of the narrative
The one thing that is not malleable is
Is it Alex Jones
Russia
That sounds exactly like you founded in 2008 when he was on RT
Talking about how he is about America
Dick
I don't know
Where
Land
Achieva
What are your two paddocks
The point that Alex is making is that
Bombing Syria is a bad and stupid
And it is a betrayal of what he thought was an isolationist
Autocratic
Right right I know nothing
On one hand
I agree Alex
This was a bad idea
On the other hand
Not because
We can agree on
Like we can agree on the
Conclusion while disagreeing about Prem
That's very easy to do
This thing is bad but
I disagree
The reason
Right there.
Fine as long as as long as we can
We can both feel like
Man I just don't like
Like what he's
Extol
Suspiciously
It's almost 2
B like I do
Now I'm getting into conspiracy theories on my own
Silly saying that he's not a Rusev I about a Roosevelt
Super good writing you know the one who said
Methinks you Dost protest too much
He kind of knew what was up
Whatever you said that Alex is a
Existing in the listen I'm not the
I love this
Brett
Rapid fire
Like machine-gunning I'm not a racist but statement
All over the place
He's in a broken
How could I have gotten that communicates so fast from
Any kind of Russia
Handler unless it was Darian
Any
Have we looked into robbed
Americans is that where you came from
Didn't get any word from a sucker
Can Handler anything
Sing like that. Just been his mode of operation
I think much longer than we realized our investigation
15 about
One of the things that we noticed was even before he got on board
He was
In favor of Putin and Russia
I think we might have done a disservice to our listeners
And to ourselves
By not taking that more serious
And looking back
To wear that big
And I think that is going
Would be a much more important question
Ask ourselves
Because I don't think
I don't think it boils down
I don't think it boils down to
Anything like that
I think
He has been
Hayward
Ridiculously
Sweeper
Pro-russian
Influence for a very long time
After you
I don't want to give too much away
There's some stuff I've been looking
I don't know if we'll ever be able to fully prove
The just the very Occam's razor rethought of like
Maybe he's just
Of Russia
Lakemore of autocrat
It's something like that maybe it's just a fanatic movie is just like one of those guys who collects too much World War
Memorabilia like it that's just how he feels about it
Love so much let me relate this back to the episode we're going over now
Does Joel skousen comes in
Lesbian blackmail
And skousen is like
They're not blackmailing him
If it tried to threaten him
He would fight back against
That's in his psychology that is
Character
He would he would
Flattered
They think of the people who wanted him to behave in certain ways
And got him to do the thing
I think it's probably
Name of the game with Alex in Russia
Like he's already gone on Aaron talk about that Artie interview that wasn't an RT interview
That he was a genius and one of the best Americans
Compromised
Through flattery years and years ago and we realize
So
I think what I think
When the history
Free books are written
There's going to be a lot of
Complicated
Reasonings behind
Find a lot of stuff
I think ultimately the answer to
Daddy issues
Call across-the-board
Possibly
I don't know if it's a it's a it's a hot mess but
Skousen
Andweknow
But Alex Jones
Entire narrative
2 years
Has been
But there are good for
Within the military
And We Danced
Against
Against Obama in the morning Donald Trump
State everything is yours Wisconsin
Think about that
Ogp when we elected Eisenhower president
Boudoir you here drunky Alex they are
Leesburg
You shouldn't
As you say it's all
I don't need you
I don't like what you've done for the last
Finally admit that you're a f****** idiot
Do it for me
Joel f****** skousen
We live in
Such a bad world
What we cover that's like
Makes it very clear that like
He gave up on Trump
A while back cuz he realized
She wasn't
Competent he wasn't able to think wasn't able to be reliable and shouldn't
Right I don't so he is already on the he's off the reservation and Alex
Is talking to
Kind of way and it's dislike
Joel is trying to be like conciliatory in some ways of like
Hey look
You didn't even do anything wrong
You you thought
Did this was good
But
You got to get real with it
This guy is not
Trust him
Yeah I've been saying it for a bit
To where it's like you look at these people and you see them the same way that you do like followers of Charles
Manson we are like
How did you not
See this coming
How is this hitting you this
It's hard I think that's our feeling and that's the reasons why
Heads because like
Welcome. Like I think I seen a couple tweets
Better like
Welcome to the resistor
Since Alex Jones
No it is it is Ludacris
You've gotten this far without
Thank God the chats
It's Ludacris he's gotten the
This far without
Like
Having any moment
Anyway
Tell you what
We're about to enter
Amman
Alex Jones is about to make a claim that
He's never talked about on a
And I really don't think this is true
Here we go
Okay
Alright
So you don't kill Alex
Because he's too public
But you don't
Family members as a warning letter for record that phone call
Business has been his whole narrative forever is like in the public eye
Or what have you. Bulshit
The idea that
Videos of
Secure
First of all the Black Ops helicopter
Pilot in Vietnam
Who came back from Latin America and said that what they're doing to the children
In what
All of Latin America Larry Nichols with lyrics
Doing of the children
I mean what I did to the children
Little
For your family to die.
Pneumonia vaccines
Maybe
That's interesting
Is no protection against
There there's a secondary thing
To hear though that's like
I don't believe it
I feel bad not believing someone talking about their family.
But at the same time I don't
Because
He would have brought this up before
For way before
5 years
That would be in 2030
13 right
So
If I'm to understand what
Immediately
If I'm to believe
His storyline
They killed three members of his family and his response was
Start selling weird pills
Because that's right around when he started doing the dr. Wallach stuff at be started those weird pills could have saved
Maybe this whole weird
It's possible but they're actually
They're not bad for so many reasons are not dead
They are sitting right at the desk with him
Reno
Believes that unertl
I love Pharrell
His early work
Felt like happy
This is
Terrible
Hyperallergic
I can't
I can't imagine a world
Where in
A globalist
Who has weaponized pneumonia
I killed three of Alex's family members pneumonia a disease which can be
Buy multiple viruses
Straight bacterias
All kinds of different family members of pneumonia
And then they call him and
Hey b****
What's up
We kill we kill three members of your family
So shut up
Not like
Say what we want you to say
Comedy
What's considered
Black Ops helicopter
His uncle was killed on purpose
Pneumonia like legitimately
Kills old people way more frequently than young people
Who knows
Did you not know about that secret progress all the globalist
Immortality isn't real
It's just the government always killing old paper
River
I think the most important thing I touch on this already but I need to read
He said spider
No way
No way for his own
If you wanted to say 4 years ago
Maybe you can play that game
Cuz I bet around
Time
Ukraine
The Korea situation in 2014
I bet he changes to in a bit
Might of
So I bet he could say
Cuz of Russia
35 years ago does not work
13 doesn't work
Play narrative
That's possibly call Alex
We could write such good narrative for him he would
F****** loses mine
I forgot that we were supposed to make a huge now
Should we do it or should we wait
We have to now
Well let's make a hour and a half into the podcast announcement really huge announcement to make
What you guys in Texas doing on June 15th
Will be in Austin doing a live show at beerland
Beerland
Send text
Cool punk-ass Florida
Available tickets
All the available tickets
Anybody will way too early for us to really push selling tickets at 2 months from now
Whenever the show Dawson
Newer Alex
No
Also I think we could probably get
A number of people
Tagged
I think there are a couple of
Knowledge fight episode let's just do an Alex
This is your life without him there
Adobe amazing
We have to be there
Oh you're talk about the show this is your life not the Rock
Panda
4 / 6
Plastic
Anyway so we will be in Austin on June
15th
He'll be exciting
Kevin Kelly Hazard guess I can respond to think
Famous equipale explains why the globalists
Harbor Freight
Call Matt
It's not related to a diode
This is the other theme
I love this little talk easily blackmail
Maybe he's done all of the crime
Or whatever
Maybe they'll get somebody else who maybe has
And committed all those crimes that for the past two years
We have been interesting
And would never come
Absolutely
Exactly crimes that we're talking about
Who knows
Committed all the blackmail
Right
Yeah it's it's it's
Beetle
They don't have a thought
Like he can just
Toss that off
As though it's not
Piece of information that he has been denying
Horse
But with the same thing as being one of the shut up
Are we
Fetishize the truth
Such a nut then
Larry that's really important
Visit the other trends
It keeps coming up on this road
Played a bunch of
34 x
Weather
F****** Trump didn't make us
Trump
And I'd like to say
No
Trump memes
By coming on your show
Early adopter
That's definitely true they were early on the Trump
Bad before a lot of people dead but I think that's because they really resonated with that
Talking husky
People out of our
Countrywide
That sort of Vine
Their whole thing is like
You know what
Maybe he is black
Like malleable
Easily blackmail blackmail he said
Anyone with Google could blackmail
But what about the
The next time
What are the next
Guy who comes along
Who's that who's not blackmail bellizza paper
Like her like that
What happened to Rand Paul
What happened with Ron Paul
I kind of bet those guys are easily black malleable
Put my blackmail
You have supported people and it's been nothing
Even when the Paul Ryan became Speaker of the House
I was just like
Taking down Boehner we're going to get a patriot in there let's see what's up Paul Ryan.
Read the text, and congratulations on your retirement
You dumbass hole
Massively corrupt politicians are
It's about us
Not about Trump
F*** that
The Tea Party Movement is about
People standing up against Obama and tyranny definitely not racism and definitely not owned
And stoked by the Koch brothers
Not even tea party s*** anymore it's now morphed into like this
The other thing
Yeah
Video
Create
Good luck
There's always another redhead
But I look forward to whatever their next play is going to be down this road but course I know that it's
Not going to have
I get back on Trump
Is deck
Why we live in this moment
Before our
Obvious
Conclusions are you know what sucks is that like
Even as we're recording this on Saturday
Probably jump
Himself out
What would you do
Your son was at home lying on the floor of the bedroom
Francois
This is such a gift
For Alex though
SARS
Can't really dismount
Here is the redline
Play Jump
Write off
Become
The warrior that you are always meant to
Superman
The president you become an antihero you be the guy
Turn from a f****** a you're you're there
Clear the trailer that becomes a hero come on man
It would take
It would take like like I said earlier when we talked about this it would take burning Rodger Stone
It would take burning a couple other sources idiot
He has to disavow season for Sterling Cooper Draper Pryce
Disavowal
He has to get rid of
You have to change up
So much as possible
Who is irreplaceable
Other than Rodger Stone and not for the reasons that are beneficial to app
How many show existed before Rodger Stone if it's after
Will be lost
Stupid boat
3D wooden
We would have the strength
To f****** come up with some even more insane
That's possible
Right now
Stephen Curry
Closer to Project Camelot
What the word like what's up to
Berlusconi
When you're off the Trump train
Or just like
Own it
You know like whenever whenever your car is slipping on ice
You are
You're not supposed to turn against
You're supposed to lean into the axe
Why not just be like
We love Russia
What up
Publix completely out now
Like Alexander Dugan takes over for Rodger Stone
Why not
American art
You're already halfway there
There's no there's no reason why
He can't do that
He's halfway there already
No that's what I'm saying that's what I'm saying
The moment that you would
Created a break point where your audience is actually willing to go along with you like this.
If you're any info Warrior chances are
You are viral ugly pro-trump but at the same time
Anti
Going into the Middle East and f****** s*** up again
Really
Come
This beautiful new single here's the chance to get back
The credibility
Will it be fun if I show got to turn into something new as well like I would like to follow along.
Fucken Trump s***
4life
But you can recapture that like
False credibility that he had back when he was against
What's George
Or George W bush do that but
I don't think he's going
This episode
It's going to be like when Trump broke his heart
Piratu
Clips
Alex
30 Azle
Are there a apologize I would like 100
Now here's the next one
Man that clip makes the inevitable today
Hey I'm sorry
72 wayward
The reason why
Might get buried
We already saw that in the you like Twitter clip look like
Celine was viewing
In the background there a little bit
When I was recording this I don't know why I
I thought I'd muted the mic
The mics were on
And not so you here like I might Mouse click every now and again
Making her she wasn't thrilled of this either
But
Absolutely I'll talk to her about it
I'm so Alex
Cursing is like
Yeah these are
F*** you I'm going to get your ass
He is shoving
Isis
Up his dirty
Dirty
He needs a prophylactic
Because he's shoving his dirty asphalt
Right
Circumstance so creative
To say
First time I've heard Alex wearing
Hayward
We're on stations are there
She controls
Answer here is where Owen Shroyer says the only reasonable thing
Entire Brock
Okay
You've been swearing so much
We're out of delay
Can't
Delay the show anymore
To bleep you swearing
Maybe we should get off air
Obituaries legitimately that's his play wasting like
You're drunk
We should
Stop this
They do another 40 min
Golf courses
You maybe maybe like half an hour
Alex tries to stop swearing
In service of stopping swearing
This is a weird clip I don't really even know how to
I don't know how to
Set this up so I won't
What do it
It says that a lot
Get your ass
He loved
Either he loves to kick him
I can't remember the rest of the lyrics to Billy Gunn is being song Mr at from the WWE
Great song
Josiah pre-show
Batman
Littleton
That's always great
Picture of a pro wrestling intro sogs
I think this rash like that's way up there
With like
Hear the glass break if you do Stone Cold's,
Tops of the charts
So
People go to Russia because you can murder a Christian
Haitian never murdered
I don't I don't
Pissed off about the
Situation
The geopolitical situation
Killer Christian anymore
I would pause
If you are rich enough
But you can go on a vacation
It Russia
You can do it
You'd be able to do very similar things
UB about the law
Anyway
We're coming towards the end
This this hot pile of garbage
Ava Alex
I'm loving
I think that what you see if you watched the entire thing which I'm not entirely sure
It's 3 hours long and most of it's really boring in them just repeating the Syrian gas in
False flag
If you to watch it what you see is like Alex
S*** the beginning of it
Olympic wrestling in the middle
And it was dead certain in the middle of it as I was watching
Oh he's going to end this with a I like
We got to give
Or something like that
But
Here's what he says
That's where he's at
God for the Russian
Thank God for The Rush
That's all I mean I kind of sums up his mentality you probably would like to
Able to knock
Know that
I would assume
That's really Direct
Doctors that is really pro-russia
Propaganda right there's already said earlier government was more like Russia
But damn
So in this next clip
We have one more
Is the last clip
I did
Not record
The last
Part of the episode as it goes out
Because it's just
Shroyer trying to do
Weather like
Hey maybe the wife
Like I told
Yeah and it's terrible that goes on way too f****** long
But it's more important that
Before that
We get this clip
Alex
Conceding defeat
Being facetious
Subway
But keep your ears open for the hiccupping
Cuz he is drunk as f***
Explain to me
How you can get to this is the left
Just because they're there
Is there a is there cuz you have to Project online
These are my enemies if I feel bad they must have one
Meanwhile every legitimate left voice that I am aware of it
Very dense
This is not
And they're not like
Hahaha Alex
You're stupid
Haha look at you
Look at you look what Trump did it's more like
F****** a******
How did you not get this earlier
LED takes this for you to wake up
You stupid prick
It's more that when it don't know no way I
The AAA
Democratic
Establishments
Posturing
Bush do whatever the f*** he wanted
It was a delete the whole message
War Powers being tired
I know I don't wait for your left up an escape blame for this phone
Is impotent as f*** I'm not siding with that
But I like
Truly liberal movements voices
That you see
Very clearly expressing
Themselves
Press releases Through official Twitter accounts
Some stuff like that making their voices clear that like you're not allowed anywhere near Powers course
Allowed to go on
TV
Rory end up with
Region
We can look at this
And I guarantee
Where's a guarantee Iowa I-80 guarantee because who knows
But I strongly
Strongly believe
Chris back within the next
Text h yeah I think once he gets his marching orders
What time is it
3 Series probably woken up
He's hungover
I give them two hours some coffee if you energy drinks and then he's going to be like
I would like
I'm starting to suspect that most of his products are actually hangover cures
Because like the amount of
Like the level of drunk
Next day and he's not just like
40 something
No he Alka-Seltzer
His products are hangover cures and that's the
So we can drink as hard as
I might have to start getting those products
See if they help with hangovers
As a 33-year old man I got trouble
Fun to watch
Alex have an embarrassing crying
Drunk stupid meltdown
Ordered
Definitely worth remembering
Is this is a turning point
Hooray
Because this show will be a lot more interesting
Bananas in
Cuz he won't just be he'll turn into a
Secondary source
Supposed to just say
Propaganda wing
Donald Trump
We'll see what happens
But
If you want to follow us
You can find all are busy
Another try.
Absolutely you can follow us on Twitter that knowledge
Four fights final thoughts
I feel like I cut you off by doing that
Plug
My final thoughts on this
This is a wonderful last moment before we all die a nuclear fire
That's what's going to happen that we were all going to die in the wars immediately follow
Devastation
The climate change brings upon our water supply that'll happen but this is that
I don't think world is ending and I'm going to die within the next
Twenty years at least make it quick
I don't think that's going to happen at all I think
I think this is all fairly coordinated by
Russia's not go
They posture is well in the same way that
That we do and I think that everyone knows that
None of us are ready for World War 3
Or any kind of thermonuclear war
That's just my take on it I have no idea global warming is
Is coming and it's going to
Popular resume World Twitter
Knowledge underscore fight
Yeah I'm sorry even I can't remember the entire world
You are on Facebook normally
Also we are on iTunes
You can find it again
Unsubscribe
Do you like sport the show again go to knowledge buy.com and click the sport the show button we would really appreciate it
Alberta
Boy I tell you what
Latest
For sharing this
Beautiful beautiful moment
Realtor
To figure out who should tell
To be told to f*** off I'll be goddamned if it's
Not
Well
I mean let's face it
The number one person
You should go f*** himself right
Donald Trump
Holding
I love your work