Alexandra Thurston color
Looks around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Dan
Dance
Beard hair stuck in my mic
The disaster anyways
Shadow looking motherfuker
So I shared it off
Indeed I also know a lot about Alex Jones
Is today April 16th in the Life of Alex
But before we do that we got to give a shout out to a couple of our new donors what's going on out there
Congratulations that you've only one the few Oscar
Did you have mr.
Oh okay
Maybe one of those massive lifelong snubbed
Like a what is it
Career Oscar whatever whatever Al Pacino got
You guys are idiots
Oscars are other donor what's going on
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much I really you look amazing
Wonderful woman
With a nice little British
The number of people who donated since Alex Jones turned on Trump and we appreciate it so much
It's like their donations of the troops but man I appreciate it
Shockingly close to like
Making this work for me
Like living wise
We are getting ever closer and everyone I appreciate it so much
If you would like to donate we would appreciate it goes towards
Yeah
More or less
Cigarette
Sweets
Time we didn't emergency episode that came out on Saturday
Plans
Ahmed episode we experienced
It on his shoe
I have not as big a man is Alex Jones
I believe so the other choice quotes were fucktrump and fuckeverybody
That's a good one
She was in
He was in a real bad State on Friday night let's check in how he's doing on Monday
I still
Alright okay
You're so f******
This is so frustrating
Office dirty
Yeah
Somebody was Isis up their dirty a******
Man this we were talking before the show when I told you there was a reason why I've been down in the dumps
Right I didn't want explain it to you until we got on air
This is so lame we had this possibility laying in front of us look like
A complete narrative shift
After this year-and-a-half of watching him just be a boot-licking
Jerk could finally see I don't think
Outlook
I don't know I've heard some people on in our Facebook group who are speculating of like
A return to the Alex of the path to tell you there is no Redemption
Holding Out for something different
Mewtwo
At the end of the day
It's just not his nationalist
Yeah
I wanted something different I wanted a new flavor to it
Experience instead of this
This job has been feeding me for all this time
Idiots
Inopportune
It's so disappointing
Weird for me to say
Nationalist
Garbage
F******
Trump loving
Kyla of
Disappointed as much fun as we had with the
You like him freaking out drunk and Leon are
I still I still thought it was
Petrolatum stupid
At the same time you like
Hi
Right this moment
You would have been awesome
You know what though I don't know I can't figure out exactly what this
Situation is
Is Rodger Stones not on this episode
I don't know if you like
Got a call from Member something
Money is money backers were like
I think it's not I think
I think that he's still holding out some like
You saw what I could do there
Little bit of Jack
And I'm going to be
A lot of the coverage of it was like how stupid is Trump he's lost
Alex Jones
Took a little bit of a hit I think
Isaac
Know who Alex
There was a possum
I don't know you're right
Realized
No one else likes me anymore except for trumpf and what am I going to do
He's the best I've got
Rand Paul is not elect
Even if you went back to him cruise is a disaster you can't go back to him
Play nobody else on the global scene that Alex
Shift and B Bhai
All he could do is go solo again like he had four
For a long time exactly
Money's exactly
But I do think
He is back
More or less being like
You going to ride
I do think
Vet
Heave
He's cut himself out a little bit
Bye-bye going back
He's also a think everyone who doesn't actually listen to Alex Jones
Is missing out on the larger narrative
And that is I think Alex Jones is about to lose his goddamn mind
Turn this into an actual cult
Yeah like
He's gone
So close to Towing the line of Infowars being a cult
Listen to this first clip
I think it's the introduction of like
Things are things are not good
Most children out there
Society is collapsing
And it's going to get a lot worse
We need rehab from cell phones when he rehabs
Resorts
Do TV news papers
Call Ray Gun
Presby and swimming pools
Girls
Indiana
Jonathan post we are dying
Well I mean is he living with one of that guys like legitimately
How quick with that turn dark
Call
Alex Jones
Running a series to watch TV
The outside world
He's essentially talking about dr. Kellogg
Yeah
We're going to go swim
You get two enemas a day
You might as well
I think
This isn't the only time he brings up these sorts of weird fantasies episode
Listen to crying and talking about how we all belong
Ready
Because he's saying I don't even think
No matter what you do
You can make it
In this world
I think we got to go to the woods
Or whatever
They got the wrong guy
That's why Alex is the
Proud
Wrote that no there's no way
The Unabomber that was eloquently written
Illiterate
You know we've got this like we've got to go to the woods
Guide of narrative Beginning Witch
Is not great
We got to go
I feel that way sometimes I just don't want to be alone in the woods
Could you also get a good
Could you get a good massage
Add Alex Jones Resort probably let me tell you
Massaging my life
And I'll say I'm not Forum overrated
Throughout my back
And the time I was a member of
Jim Adams
Is there a massage
It was a comedy of errors
I was comforted like a 32-year old dude I've never gotten a massage before Zod
Like two years ago
Should I get naked
A little bit further how do I tip
Anyway
Speaking of weird things
These dudes I got to go back to
My bread and butter
I got to go back to what made made and that is
Classified
Call the closure
Believe they're called the penny
Case you are a
Okay
Alright
There is literally literally
Describe
He just read
Dune this is one of my like
Least favorite things about Alex Jones is be like
I'm out now I
I can't look into this
But I can tell you that everything that
Camaros near like growing organs inside pigs and stuff like that
Does not involve
Brainless animal tanks
That part that part
Slightly unreal is
Let me ask you a
Really just kind of
Insulting
Like women wasn't raised cow like a
Euphemism literally workout
Putting a brainless can you put them in there
That's it
Classify
Would like a a little agony
Scary Mary
Right behind growing organs in animals
Eunos flight human genes and them
For the purposes of growing
Organs that can be transplanted
Another
But it's not bad
It's about that
If nobody
I will say is that he's going on
Trouble trouble
If true I would like to see that classified information Alex cuz
I'm going to be honest
I would like to see
So Alex clearly also intro clip
Is waffling on Trump
But UE speaks a little more on it
Where are you
Support President Trump
Trump literally said IMA global
What also happened
Today
In regards to Trump
And quote on quote
Hating
The globalist
Is it
Situation
It is that he
Alien
We don't mess with Russia for any reason ever
About that and willing to believe it Nikki Haley
Something prematurely
I'm willing to believe that possibility but in the same time
Why wouldn't you do that
Good question I don't know
It's weird anyway Alex
Trumpet Santa
I am saying I'm a club
Finally done some basic things that are good for the economy in the country
Like a b**** but he starts going sideways in their agenda
It's the global Awakening
Elisabeth I am loyal to
EBay
Pressured
There's the old
That's not good
If your guy is at
That's stupid
Goddamnit Alex
You got it
Yeah
Haha
It makes perfect sense
That's exactly why
Busy thinking about these brainless
Cows
Brian Williams Stockton
And now you can get that that
You know you can go for a second ride
As it were
Government is
Always been pitching the account
Get some of that
Get the Rocks off with bombs and
Right
He's really tough Ontario at the same time
F*** off
What are you talkin about
He says my Lord my allegiances in my loyalty lies with
With the populist nationalist movements around the world
Putin
She's
Fantastic ever bring up
Is populist and nationalist
Well he's right
Nationalist
Never bring those up
No I mean except for the white ones in Southside
Staffordshire the sweet Flanders
Even know where South America
Does he know what populism is code for you know what nationalism is code for
He knows what nationalism
I don't think
You should ever use the word populist
It's so infuriating
Maybe cuz it's know that triggers you use to describe everything it seems like
People are angry about
So I don't disagree with you but it was Brian Williams pissed off at Bryant
The f******
Visit my allegiances
His nationalist movement
Proto-fascist
So it's
If that's what you're into worldwide
Boy
I tell you what
Proto
Welcome or aspiring cuz most of the Lost
Worcester election
You can be a fascist there's a civilian and it's fine
Listen Marine
You can be anything you want to be when you grow up
That's not what her dad would say
Susan a wonderful French private
That's cool where they were
Absolutely appalled
At her behavior
Right right
Something about it is falling again
Today
What we talkin about started earlier in the show talking about Alex
Wanting us to be like
More troubling than Alaska
Save yourself
A month
Nope
No 450
Super wrong
Modern world
Actually I am a Cancer
That is already got it
Blue
Elliptical
To get off Electronics we got to go to Alex Jones Resorts around the world it's
Isabel to make
Make it through life with these liberals all around you if you homeschool your kids there's no
Alex Jones
Which is
An accurate reading of the pilgrims history
Absolutely a religious supremacist
Make him go to somewhere else
But then you get the Israelites in Egypt
Are you enslaved bro bro bro
The metaphor might be liking the tiny bit
What were the
Anybody
Anybody who's done Annex
That's that is
Bestest
What record
What's your favorite exit
I don't know it was kind of boring
They just wondered
For 40 years
I like that though it's not about the destination
Truck Journey
He's probably pretty close
To like pitching himself as a modern-day Socrates I think we might be close to
To that can we make
Well to be fair
Yeah no no
It was more like they were like
Please leave please leave if you don't leave we have to make you drink poison we don't want you to
We're always glad he's coming be like we got a boat for you but you can view
You got you got found
He got found guilty and then
Choose your own punishment
Right eye is like I think you guys should
Feed me for the rest of my life but we're killing you
Jack
Yeah that's one of the things that I've always liked B fascinated by about soccer
This is like people
Thinking he was kind of too
Just a questioner that was like
I just like to provoke
The Socratic method is being like you asked
Bring people
To their own understanding it's more like the guys like
Yeah just
That tone hadn't
To develop sarcastic
So we covered it
It's nauseating.
Detail the Friday episode we turned on Trump
Here's his take on it on Monday
But
He's talking about the like Twitter clips that we heard of him like screaming and put like that key doesn't apologize for the
Trump has Isis up his dirty a******
Isis
I were screaming obscenity
To the point where Owen Shroyer had to remind him we're out of delay
Control myself a lot
It feels good to let yourself have an outburst occasionally
Because
If they can start to turn Trump
1 degree that can turn him 100 days of grace
That's also not great
To say about your guy
Compromises
You just said
If you turn Trump 1°
He is weak and pathetic and we'll go all the way
Easily
There's no there's no like Trump is going to meet you halfway there's either
You get a little bit of a
Armor and then you get all
No
There is no possible what are you saying
A great degree is
My boys
He can be a dictator
But your boy can't govern
Also he can be very weak
Screaming about sucking on a ding dong
Apologize
Stone with a beard
I mean Rodger Stone
Yeah
So
The International Community is largely of the Mind
That
The gassing took place in Syria was
Done by Assad or Subs forces
Absolutely
I think our position I like our position
In the best in terms of
Heather might have an oversight on it there might not have been who knows
Who's answers are impossible to know really
Kinds of stuff I I feel like a lot of people discount the fact
That
Everybody
A kind of s***** at their jobs
One day of the week
Expression the fog of War
Like Frankie
It's entirely possible that the people in the helicopter who were dropping those bombs
Are the plane or whatever we're just like
We labeled
I think that's
Too easy an hour
Are they in the planet
There's also put on the other
The first rule of Syrian Boy Scouts
Be prepared
Chemical weapons
There's also story this coming out today I believe
Amsterdam
About Russia blocking
Investigators
From looking at the
Besides
Confusing
Is it because they also helped cover up the the sites themselves look that way
Alex
In the middle of the show accidentally reason anti-russia
Headline about
God.
Situation
Does a rug with clothes
Okay
The road was blocked
If this two-lane road is blocked guess we're done
Different story
Really easy to
You know sauce out
Roblox
Very different
From
It's like on the it's like when I'm are on the red line
And they're like there's going to be delays because there was a chemical
Open the tacit
Chicago and State
I know it's
It's a real Chicago commute
12 minutes
Yeah
I'm sorry I mentioned
Up top that
Profound I don't know what he's doing he might be hiding out
Haha it's entirely possible
So Alex has got to get
The motherfuker
Fill out the show
Gerald Celente on
It's kind of boring
It's another it's a continuation of
The Joel skousen
An appearance from Friday
Tell me I'm a good boy
Gerald Celente
No no point bad it's not your fault I needed that.
Yay
And look
I like that you're supporting him
You know what you go back
250 on it
He just wants to talk about trans
And money markets
Some stuff like that
Vicky
Watch that video and then the next day was like
A man has to go into work on Monday
Video on Saturday
Also is being like
Backbone
So
So weak
Low energy
Still said
He has on here on Mondays show is a gentleman
And Paul Craig Roberts worked
In Reagan
Treasury
Undersecretary in the treasury
And we'll get into some other troubling pieces of his history but
Here is a clip so once again
On the info
Exactly
Clearly Young
Underoath
From the military security complex because of his original
Normalize relations with Russia
And all the other
False accusations
Trump into a militarist position
That's something
Really good
Thought
In the way that he's dumb
But it is it is
Trusting. Whenever you
Taken how many you hard right Russia Hawks
There are in there just like
The Cold War Radar National Security advisor
Find the Cold War
Turn right so let's just keep on doing that
This is another piece of the equation that we haven't really discussed
Nearly as much
And that is the Fulton is also a kind of anti-russia hawkguy
So is introduction into the fold
Probably has
Creeped out Alex a little bit now
It was worried before cuz he had an apparatchik
It right like that before but now I think he's got to be worried about that and a couple of things
By Bolton being like
F*** this guy he's been in for a week and now we're boss
Now
The other take on that is
Is Bolton is
Actually the janitor from the Looney
Kansas possible
I think that's one of his early goals
Still a little darker
So the other thing we need to take him to account I
Is important is
Paul Craig Roberts
His written for
And Russia Insider
At least 24
I also
Batman sets 2016 he's written
For Alexander Dugan
Think-tanks website
Container
So
I think he's got. I can use a regular gig got a full staff and they all mysteriously pop up on Alex Jones Show
Seriously
So here's some of the articles that he's written
For Sputnik
Will Putin realize that Russia holds all the cards
Washington is destroying the world
American government cannot be trusted to tell the truth
Washington is defaming Vladimir Putin
Putin calls out Washington
Is the Atlanta strategy to attack Russia
Justin that headline
We have
The Atlanta
Versus urania you have the Eurasian ISM narrative coming in
Or even just in that headline
These buying into that divide
Just on just based on the headlines I would give him a 500 batting average
Stuff that makes
Sawyer
Hey
American government to tell the
Write the truth it's different when you're saying that on a podcast for like apropos of nothing
Making a
Statement and when you're doing it on
When you're writing an article for a site
I do it right now this
Podcast will be over
Cuz I will be opposed to that
I'd be very opposed if you did that on
And MSNBC npri
Bri wood
Well one not be allowed on a I'm too loud
We get some rating
Cloud
Baby like
The difference between
Places that are legit state-run
Media and places that aren't
Yeah I was going to say
Like in America
Media is beyond listener funding has Grant and endowment
It's from the government stuff like that you know there is like a voice of America in
Change it like that
Clearly isn't using NPR
It seems it seems like there is a pretty solid Fox News control over the entire
When the president
Boxing
Friends and is like
Those are some good policy ideas we're not in a good place
So here's some more headlines
Braces written for Russian
America America have no unifying moral culture it will lose a war with Russia
Will Russia wake up
The West seeks its destruction
Okay so
Alright seems like he kind of has a Russian
Apocalyptic
He's really Apocalypto
Ciclavia
I can't imagine why
Also
Also interest you believe in the pre-trib Rapture I think Now's the Time to let it
Trivia is a
I think that 288 play timeshare one of Alex's Resort
Yeah
The great Investments
Deed I've heard that on timeshare commercial
I'm taking away from this
Is that
You've got call Craig Roberts
Coming in
Tell a Galaxy Note
More relaxed Russia is a good guy there's a good actors here which believes anyway
I only talk about
More less
That's the driving you look into his past
She's written for
Russian Publications
Incredibly anti-American things
For a very long time
Is weird
I mean it's not it's
It's
Definitely
Not a trend we have not seen
But it is it is
It is one of those things where somehow it is
Far more
Effective
To have a guest on
Echoes the s*** that you've already
Neco it back to
It's kind of it's kind of almost a pressure
Oh no
Call PCR we need we need we need some of that good old Russia didn't do it
Yeah you can do that or you can call Shaggy
Hayward
Thought I saw you with a cylinder
Biogas in Europe
In my country people guess you all right
Jack off speaker.
Are free
Nashville Springfield
Our friend Tyler Snodgrass
Like I used to write jokes for him back when he before he moved to Chicago
That's not your private information
Talk about it
But the show with the blue room in Springfield I believe
The place and jack off
Came out to the show because
And it was
Embarrassing
I just watching people want to come talk to you
Nothing against the legend of the game
He's a legend
I don't want to f***
Can go
Like getting the crowd to talk to Yakov Smirnoff
Just your being a fanboy for yakoff well
Are you okay boyfriend I respect him I don't think I don't like his comedy respect
I would like to see
In a picture
With his arm around your shoulder giving you the thumbs up if we could go back and do it all over again I would like that
To exist but I'm going to try my Principe
Where is he from I don't think it's
Yeah
I never thought to look into it
I never cared
Former Soviet Union but he wasn't actually from
Mainland Russia
The timeline matches up with entirely possible
The show you also brings in
The man
The mail
Doctor Steve
You just like
He just wants Alex
The shut up kind of I think right I like it
Why do you have to have your Outburst but like
I think at this point he was kind of sick about
Kind of I think he wants him back
Trump
Because that's the easiest status quo for him to defend
Is a good footing
Realized
Without Alex Jones credibility goes away too
Cuz he's not on anyone else
How old is
I'll put them in at 6
Be something
Yeah so this is healthy 60s really Steve's last
Like if at any point
Time if
Neuropathy
Media Forum
Know if he's if he's not involved with me
With Infowars
He can't roll with the
Steve is enrolling
With it
You could
Oh yeah I think you could
Yeah I think he could but he would be the one
He said that he's leading divorce
You had a man like he be able to manipulate our
Alex's next wrinkle will be
Probably see
Steve pieczenik
Okay I'm not disagreeing with you I'm just saying what if you like him so easily
I mean
The two of them kind of fight a little bit
Just heard of Beltline
Get up there neither of
No one's in a good place post Friday
Right you're alright
Just left everything because it's it's
Something to be associated with
Alex isn't a good place to go
Because he realizes
Can't get that off the internet
Nope and
Really need to go back into the Trump campaign
Talk about that
Interview
Incredibly
Is it
Has opened up a new
Finishing school
No that would be that would be
Every single resorts
Yep yep
Call their mothers
That is not
So what
Is appearing with
A painting behind him
The painting has
I watched him
A while back
I don't know
I was I was worrying
I've seen
People talking about the suffix
Afterwards
Now that's not cool
We'd been assholes but
Yeah
So Steve appears on behind him that is
Heavily breast it
There's titties
Okay
A slightly pornographic image
Of a guy coming down
Some sort of figure grabbing a woman with her breasts
Stout anyting credibly weird
And they don't bring it up
For the first segment
If Steve is on
I'm guessing Steve had to pose for a long time
Fortunate
Absolutely did this on purpose
Did this on purpose
He's broadcasting in front of a f******
Square behind him with huge titties on it
Purpose for sure
OK Google Play
Alright
Was he also broadcasting from an 80s car wash
No set up to save the Rex know this is his office know Alex finally brings it up and I think it's
Invalidating
Number 11
And then they're just always
Corruption
Friday's
I couldn't
This one out of the sky right now
Okay
Earth goddess Christ figure
The struggle
Even though
God
Alex the art critic
I want to go to a museum with Alex
I want to go to a museum with Alex Alex you are invited to the MoMA
Chicago
Oh that be great
Nothing but art
So we can invite him to our there
Home Depot
Steve correct them what the artist actually about
That this
I'll presentation from Alex cuz you can even hear him say that satanic deviantART
And then he explains what he sees there he says the end of it
It's the fruit of Satan
You know cuz women
He doesn't
Care
Steve pieczenik has weird art
But that's what he screams about all the time with John podesta
That is weird right that means some sort of sick in the head
Art all around
What is the
Weird
I know it when I see it
Exactly
Like this
Isky
I think Steve pieczenik
Broadcast it in front of that painting
Yeah or not to f*** with his head
But you like
That ruin
His argument about John podesta
That whole thing goes away does not care about
I think you subtly trying to undercut
A bunch of us and maybe this is fancy
Debugging on my part to Alex VR
But his behavior likes
Very clearly intentionally broadcast
In front of that picture
Cuz he broadcast
In front of a bunch of different
Something in front of
A flowchart of hip-hop artists
You know like you broadcast in front of things not like
It does tend to have a little bit of
But it's not like a riddle but he has a broadcast from here with this behind me
Me today
Enticing
Here's my theory and again
Nothing's back this up
I think the neck
Six months but we're going to see out of Steve pieczenik
He's one by one
Providing evidence everything Alex Jones has stood for his been b******* you have to pay attention
Everything
Exactly next episode he's going to be eating Greek yogurt
That's what I think is happening
It's probably not I'm just bored
The satellite of Love basically watching the ship but I like to believe
Believe
This woman has
Is large breasts
But no arms
For having breath
What if Steve
Like
Laura Jean demond
Behind him
Another world coming out
Or what if he has that skull covered in semen
Turned it into a chalice it was just
Flavor Flav and get the whole time
It's just behind him and he never mentioned it
Pretty amazing weird
Charlie Sheen
No I was talking about the light reflecting off
Evocative
So if it deals with
A little bit of difference
Like a
We're in this
No man's land of I love hate I love hate Trump
Well there's a Schrodinger's Trump
What's going on
In this clip Alex's sort of expressing
The Trump is good
Trump is good
Mermaid Inn
Game it's not a smoke-and-mirrors
Pino's
He said stabilizer
Happens all the time
It sounds like someone bragging about their dad telling a notch
True story
No
Incredible
It is a sabotage
Here's the thing
The Bottom's fallen out
I don't know exactly what's going on
You could have stopped their great
Debbie great sentence to end with a.
But now
Is the time for Larry Nichols
The Comeback he's not on the show but this narrative is weak
If you need
To get away from it all of this means to do what all of the right-wing media does
If
Things don't look good
Hey
What else did we not said about Hillary
They were like so it appears that Hannity was mentioned in the
What else is going on in the news
Better
Mr. blackmailing Congress himself
Boy
He has not been on since we did that episode
Really I didn't even realize that until the other day
Is fan
He has not been on Alex Jones Show to the best of my knowledge and I listen everyday mail Congress
Coincidence of some sort
Right cuz he's thinking
I will be God damned if that isn't hilarious
Feel like there might be a connection between that like
Ojeda
You did commit a felony on air
And no one
Listening
Was it our episode or was it his
What do you mean
Larry Nichols.
What are episode out like right after he had blackmail Congress
Play rhinoceros
That's fantastic
That would go on my resume
Look at the contact info for all of these
Oh yeah I do know what you're saying I didn't realize that you were asked
Larry Nichols
We brought up
Video
Those were about a week apart
Okay I apologize I did not
Understand what you mean
Yeah we do need to call
These fools destroy
More power than we've ever imagined
Yeah yeah
Pressure
He was at the height
Again not necessarily torpedoing
Get out of here with you comes back on
If
We're going to call
Right
Next time he's on it's got to be about how like
Map
Now I know that Linda bloodworth-thomason
Is a witch she is a witch
Alright
You know Trump is good
Glow blister bad
Assad wants to go to London
I mean
I think there's a really easy way for this to play out
So I could say
Anything like that
Could just go to London
He could know he
F****** c***
Appointment
Just like
Oh your password
No nobody's this s*** is true
There's a way to negotiate all of the stuff that like
Workout for him if he's just like
Look high
Been fighting bad guys this whole time
I don't want to be a dictator I'm in a bad situation I want to get out of it
Which is xylem and some other country
He could just leave
Look this is gotten out of control I don't want to be a part of it anymore
Stupid idea of the you like the Russians
Facade and our government
Military behind our governments back made this deal
Putin has no reason not to say that happened
She's already saying the United States is they don't follow through with her
You know their word and stuff like that you're already halfway there
Just come out and validate Alex's argument
Why not
I mean I wouldn't believe them but if you do
If just came out was like dude we negotiated the secret deal behind the government's backwood
With the American Military
To get rid of a sod and now they're back
Checking out that would be the best news
And if it's true you know he has evidence
Oh yeah officer he doesn't enter into a tripartite agreement
Behind the president of a country's back without some sort of corroborating evidence
Is the heroes in our military
Trump is just following
Everything everything
Ever said to
Anyone
Except of course the oligarchs with prefer
Recordings not exist
Yeah we learn about
One of the reasons
The globalist
Are really bad
Depopulation
You find a very small percentage.
One quick way to research
Just one small thing
Things like that which Witcher
Zombie
Washington
I don't need oxygen they don't need anything
A blowtorch
Spell
What is black light
Flash
The globalist
Watching football and basketball
Yep
Is that
Boy I'll tell you what
That's fun
They're zombie
Buddy
Referencing the one woman's genetic
Material that was
Henrietta Lacks
Mutation that made ourselves
Immortal
Nearby that does not
There's some sort of immortality that could
Be granted by them
When you talk about cellular immortality
What that means
Is that it will constantly split
Are always split more as opposed to a lot of cells they have this thing called
Senescence
Which is a termination
Point of they're splitting
Keep spreading to a point that's when they they
They can no longer
Go through meiosis
I believe it's also an Evanescence
Beyblade
That's cuz it's not a sexual
Whatever but
Alex is talking about a kind of real thing but at the same time
Really stupid about it
So they can't be killed
Except for with a blowtorch probably just from the living dead at Walking Dead
I don't think that's true
There's so many other things
Blowtorch
Well I don't I don't know I think that's just his fans
I'm through the thing is that these cells are like because they don't
Play Don't Stop dividing
Consistently
B / they're perfect
For research
Polio vaccine
You know there's things like that
That they took them and hit them without ever acknowledging that they were take
Taking from her or giving her any kind of
Over estate
Or anything like that
That is a bigot
No it is
It is but also
I don't really
I don't really understand
The rights issues enough
They took them after she was dead
It was like discarded
And so there is an argument that has been made by these researchers May believe it's held up in court
But you don't have
Necessarily possession rights after your death
Discarded material
It came from a tumor that would have been removed from her that sort of thing so it's
It's really
Murky territory that I don't know how to unpack
I don't like it but I also get it
Oh I understand from that
Is a
Weird
All the elements that are like
For Alex is stupid b******* about like they just want to create
Cures for themselves not for us
Do you have polio a******
He actually
Does the show The Iron law
He's been in a wheelchair for 6 years
People don't know that
People saw fpr stand up to.
That's a fair point
At the fair
Bear they got your point
That's why I said it three times
Like witches
Which
The reality of these like
Immortal cells in the Lazarus album
Stuff like that really interests
I think there are a couple of strains of them that they've been able to find
But there's literally nothing like whatever it is along those lines just another
Brainless cow tanks
Kind of like
He relies on the Taiwan train with couch now he's he relies on the fact that is audien
Not conversant in science at all and doesn't understand
We certainly stand I mean maybe weird
Conversant but not
We're the type of people who are conversant in science
Insofar as we know just enough to get ourselves to say something
Think stupid
All right you know
If you gave me a week I could explain this fully but I don't care
We could research it there would be no reason for us to
Alex Jones
This is mine and scream about to Isis
Trump's dirty ass hoe
We covered that but we failed to cover one thing I believe in
Yes
From Coast to Coast AM
A complete weirdo
Crazy dude
But also made one of those two interesting radio shows
I know you don't know much about coasttocoastam but is a big part of
Of my
Love of am talk radio growing up
Actors on FM
I'm in Columbia
I love the format of Talk Radio in one of the
Because of coasttocoastam
Now granted
Joe Frank
Cuz I mean
You don't know who Joe Frank is now
He did a weirdo monologues
I want
Coasttocoastam
Brilliant
Art Bell or George Noory would talk about something
Really crazy
And stupid laufenn aliens ghost that sort of Shay
Sometimes
Conspiracy stuff
And then they just take calls
And the callers would be
But they'd just be like
Yep you bet
You bet
Without the anti-semite
Yeah not over it
Anyway I'm not sure I'm not sure cuz
I mean I don't I hate George Noory Paula
He's good friends with Alex Jones
Aan is much as
The passing over like a radio Legend
When we did that episode about
Project Camelot episode about Courtney Brown remote
He allowed Courtney Brown to come on
And precipitate
The events
That would lead to the
The Heaven's Gate 911
I'm still like he had
F****** problem
The great broadcaster
Arrest
Peace are found
Brown precipitated the Heaven's Gate
We did a whole
Really don't understand that
I still Courtney Brown remote viewing an object was trailing the Hale-Bopp Comet and that's where that entire narrative
I forgot that was whenever what's-his-face
And then he got all
Weird about it
Marshall Applewhite
It wasn't his wife
That was his cool partner
Whatever
Derailing that
So Art Bell rest in peace also Harry Anderson died today we miss him
Glad we still got bull
Yeah I was really sorry that Harry and the Henderson
Was that it
I'm not making a joke here I did love haryana
I love Nightcore
Is a great show today
He wasn't that old though right
60 something
The article I read said no foul play was suspected probably are.
Man-Bat what was it was it Newsradio
No it's not news radio Newsradio
This is not the media
You know who tweeted about this
Alex's ex-wife Kelly
Kelly tweeted that Alex got his start or one of his early pushes was from Art Bell
Alex is literally responding to her tweet by pretending the cheese the media
No one in the media report that I'm not doing any articles about that
I've literally only see
Tweet about that
So Alex whatever he wants to lash out at things the Kelly saying publicly about him
Says
Look at the media saying I was on Art Bell
Weird I believe he actually probably wasn't on our Val cuz the timeline doesn't quite match up
Use on Coast to Coast all the
A bunch with George Noory
Call Kelly the media in open court
Nobody called it immediate the other day when you like the media is reporting that I was gagged
Kelly again and I mean we see it
Throughout the rest of the clip
But you know what I like art.
Art Bell mysterious narrator of the American Knights
The show bigger for us
You're just talking about like your
8 years
Your Feud with your wife
Ex-wife is making me very uncomfortable
That I know what he
He's talking about
I can see through this this is not the media
These are specifically things that she has tweeted
He's pretending it's the media
Barry
Very f*****-up would you doing on air
Like
He's too much of a coward to just say my wife my ex-wife is saying stuff and it's not true here's the truth
Because it does seem like it is the true that are Bell wouldn't have him on his show because he knows like
For whatever reason every time somebody doesn't like him
He's probably like
Whatever reason they think I'm a
Piece of s*** I can't imagine why he would let him have it
No that's my position on that
In this episode we've seen Alex have kind of a weird back and forth with Trump
Vanilla kefir
I'm still supporting him
He's probably corrupted or whatever
Famous mixed with Alex says something
M8 slightly familiar to us
Yes but at the same time it's like
If you think he's
Corrupted you sure
Want him to do this
If Trump doesn't move
With the military
Number one
Because we are overrun by Farhan level of power I appreciate it
You sound like you are
If he does
Do this
Calling for him to do this
But if he doesn't
It's like no big deal if he doesn't accept
I'm not calling
Walk
It's a very very top weird line
Trump orders
And then
Alex loses his f****** mom
Haha
Then he's like
Well I mean obviously he doesn't
Agree with what the military wants
To do
He wants he wants Trump to use the military to take out Obama
Clinton
Like you wants he wants him to use them
The military to take out his perceived enemies
Support
A trump
Just didn't
Utilize the military in the correct
Directions didn't use it for an internal coup and power grab
Piss off my good friends in Russia
And that's what pisses him off
Alright
That's not good
Do you know
Generally
When is an elected
Decide that it's
It's a good idea
To use the military to remove his
Usually
Only taking
Literally every example of this occurring in the entirety of human history as my
Reference point
But it doesn't go well
Forever
I would say that I can think of 0 examples of like
Hey everything
Well Julius Caesar did and everything worked out fine
Little Caesar
Is RC
Chavez did everything worked out fine Brazilian government a long time everything worked out fine
African countries
Let's just talk about where the word dynasty
Witches
When women
Glasses
The more important thing is
All of that is
Really
The idea that Trump is going to have military tribunals
They're sealed indictments on all of these people already
All this stuff it's all
I really saw this play out with all those other weirdos on on Twitter about like at the beginning of the Mueller in
We saw all those that bogus as accounts coming out and saying like
There is 170 sealed
It's the same game being played
Just buy the other side
Write the other side expensive
Believe it or not really on the side of cat
Russian Ordnance
It's trickster is
Interesting performance side of
It possibly
Really interesting performance art
But
It's doing a lot of damage
Sew-in from time-to-time wants the military to get involved
Get some tribunals
Who's going cuz he's heard people talk about that online is wrong course he keeps saying that's what's going to happen
Really works for us
I was thinking of Desmond
You too but that was a that was a commission
Yeah
For the Truth and Reconciliation
Impression
I don't know by the Tribunal
Is more effective
Of or or
Comes to better outcome
You're totally wrong
Yeah
The show Survivor
Is there a tribunal I thought that's what they called it whenever they go to Tribal Council
No no no that's
Tripartite
Negotiate
Somehow
That is a massive blind spot in my ability
Fire history
I think I've always just heard the prefix Tri was like
Well I can
There's a b after it
So one more clip left
Alex
Expresses that Trump is probably still good but he's been
Which doesn't work
From a logical standpoint
And then
So stuffy
I'll be honest
Are substantially.
And
Because they're not
They want to destroy a nationalist
I want to send a message
They want to send a message
President down and just like Hillary and all them said
Once I get him out
I mean
I'm not afraid
Response and I'm not saying that jacked up
So
It seems like
There's clothes
Open Rebellion
Boom
Now
2 years into this
How can you
Possibly believe
Has any beliefs
Whatsoever other than
Trophies Drake
I like
Right
Hey that guy said the same thing that I'm thinking which is that Trump is great
I love
What kind of f****** mental
Does it takes to imagine that that f****** guy has a bully
Why
Why would you believe that
How could you believe that
Higher because
Rodger is
Rogers
Rogers very smooth
He's got understand
I've been thinking about it
Think about it look at this look at this whole thing
Like you guys at the beginning of his presidency
CPP now already
Do you like
Alex is like rich friends happy in my rich friend I want to make I want them to think I'm cool
Alex is like
I'm a globalist
Animation
Keeps pretending that he's taking a pedophile network but there's no evidence of it in the stuff that we've gone over in
In the past is clearly
These sort of
Annual operation
Existed for years
Around
The month slavery and human trafficking awareness
Like it is
It's not it's
Is opportunistic
Weird
Contemplate
Solve human traffic
Working this month and then let it go for
It's weird weird
Weird
Weird thing
Does dismantled
Just buy
Time
Yeah it like you go on long enough
You Trump himself will invalid
And now we have the only thing he believes in
And now we have a situation
Cohen's
His lawyers
The office has been rated
Alex even himself is like
F*** they probably got a lot
He paid off seven or eight women
Casinos without being mobbed
Probably done a s*** ton of money you're missing the point
So when we did that September started in September of 2015 or August
2015 we did the investigation
We found it to be
Beginning of Alex Jones is narrative
With Trump the beginning of his ride with him
This guy owns casinos
He's mobbed-up
He is a
Frontman for a Consortium on the East Coast
If you get your name is Genovese you go to prison if it's
It's Trump you don't
Those sorts of things like all of that
He's never not believe that
This whole time
He knew that
He pretended that wasn't
True
It because it went counter to all of his other narratives
But the entire time
He's known
That was
True
And the fact that Cohen
Got his is office rated
And there's obviously
Reproof
It's going to come out of a lot of his stuff and Alex
Does piss scared about that
He knows like
Now I cannot
Pretend that I didn't know that
I have to be like it's no big deal
Is a very big deal
Well I mean sure
Paid 1.6 million December
But who cares
Who cares
George
Who cares that's what I mean that much money
There's a moment as it goes on Sundays
Clint because of these
It related
Because that was relevant
But now
Since he can't get it out
He can't get it out like he can't explain why this is somehow like
I just don't
Understand
The game
Like he had the opportunity
Because he
He clearly knows that some s*** is going to come out
And the writing is on the f****** wall coming out
It's already
Get it but the point is
If he came out
Now
Then he's out in
Front and Heat
They claim even more credibility
Because the other Fox News Fox are going to get f*****
Like they've been carrying water so hard for
Like they're all going to f******
Bb-but you know nothing's going to happen there going to be
Gear
Here
Here's what you don't
Aren't taking into account
Whether it's the
Forgetting about it or or negligence or whatever
Russia's not done with
And whatever whatever situation exists
Between those ants
Because I have no f****** idea
I think there were a lot of people probably making
Think about the bigger deal out of the
The Russia Trump
Connection that may or may not exist
We bring this up on the
We are very
Convince
We're very clear
Alex Jones weather
It's because of
You know some sort of compromising
Material whether it's money
Wreck
With one of those things
Flattery
He has some sort of allegiance to Russia that pre
It's more important to him than other things
We which we clearly discovered on our
2015 South
Discovery
From even further back
But
What
The reason that he can waffle
In all of this
Is the same reason the Trump
Conseil
I'm not going to answer
The sanctions on
Right
It's that that
Is what's important
Alex
And whether it's
Because he is dead
And intellectual purest that he actually believed
That there a nationalist country in
That there is a hope of globalism or whatever
Or if you knows that b*******
And he knows that he
I'm selling a line
That's what's going on
That's why you can go back on it be like
Drop baby
State but we got over got to set this out
They're still
There's still blood to be taken from this Stone as it were
You know
Are all the parties involved
I don't know
Some sort of writer
Walter's garbage
Look all of
The ship
It's come out
There's got to be some sort of
Awareness that
This is going to crash
I suppose the only the only thing that I would say if
If your
Russia
And you have this investment going on
Regardless of whether or not
Freeshop regardless of whether or not
Trump is aware of any
Collusion
RoboCop carita propaganda collusion or collusion
Wasn't it's not it like I'm not necessarily saying that they all got to a room together
Right
Perhaps
Coinciding interest
Happening
Simultaneously
It's like
The only result of
Is that
Trump goes down
And the only reason
That Russia would still be involved
Is because they think Trump is going to take America down
Sure the only thing that makes sense to me right now
Boy that's Campbell is look
Can good
Yeah
Why we should go to the woods but before we do check out our website
Autopart.com
What are handles knowledge underscore fight
What if you went to Facebook
You can find us there and also a
Go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
Absolutely
Camp
This is tough for me it was tough
Summon the energy to do this but I'm glad we did
I'm glad we made it through
Depression is
Mo Bamba
Yeah
I recognize and I hope
It'll be fine
Need a good night sleep
Imma go get a slice
Pizza after the shower
Maybe play a little Zelda in
Try to get my head right that's a good idea
All those things
Great ideas
I feel like I've named the last two people
Or so
I think it's your turn
Yeah I'm going to show the word Tribunal
Text Eddie that is existed in the blind spot for
Better
The word tribunal has escaped my knowledge
That's infuriating but I recognize that like weeks because
I have to honor your wishes but I do this
Under protest
Alexandra Thurston color