Alex
Text Jones
What up player
Are you doing when did this how you doing buddy buddy who lives with my slang and Dam
But who knows a lot about
Not talking right
It's going to be off
Going to be cool beans
I know actually I like
What's going on
Announce that we are going to be
Sewed on June
Do you know the time
Between 7 and 12
Somewhere Out There
I never asked
For now
Tbg
I will be there tickets I don't think are available yet but we will let you know as more details and.
All that stuff becomes available but
It's a bit early we're still in April but we look forward to meeting all of our Texas peeps
I living down there in occupied
Oh
Also
I can't think everybody enough who's donated to the show
So we have to do in prolong
Navigator Motors number of policy walk
To give a shout out to otherwise
Is it
Exactly
A longtime excited
I see them donating very
Thank you
Julia Stiles we have loved you ever since
The firstborn absolutely
That was great born
Later in the supremacy
Okay I don't remember which
What movies were with
I'm a policy wonk
Where do you live
Where you from Andy tell me right now
I also like to give a shout out to apologize about this
Either way no matter how you pronounce it we appreciate you
Policy walk
I'm a policy wonk thank you so much.
What's wrong with you I don't know you said
That was smooth.
Who donated
Another shout-out
I'm a policy wonk
Someone sodomites
Thank you so much
Thank you so much Sam Levine I loved you in the
Sam the man Levine Loganberry combat
We'll talk after the show
Michelle
And tell her you're brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket
So much Michelle Williams
I love every single movie that you've ever been
She's amazing
She's so good
At 1 with Julia Stiles
10 Things I Hate About You Feel like she's really good actress
Field where they are
No that's
Dystopian novels
Actually that's just our world being dystopian where Spider-Man
Rebooted every other week
Presence
Like
Oregon Farms
Sure do like a bunch of
Clones and shitgate
Entire lives
Is there to give away their organs
It's brutal okay it's kind of a bad mood but I loved
Relate to you on a human level
Well you know what I mean
Relates me on a human level is
You can do so by going to their website knowledge feit.com and couldn't support the show we really appreciate it so much at
No that's not that bad
It's done long-ass f****** name
Everybody
We're really making strides we're almost at the point where this is a viable life
For me in terms of a
And
I'm starting to realize that I hate
Do so much business up top for get to the actual show but I realized we just crossed our original goal
There we sat back when we started
Accepting donations
We would never reach
A breakdown of one of Alex's documentaries
We've already.
So we can't do that to reward people
No you could finish the f****** bracket
Oh boy I can do that I will work on that put the other thing is if we
We're close to reaching another goal or maybe 75% of the way to another goal
Other words that go with we would do a live show in Chicago which we've already done
We are really bad at rewarding people
Do the things that we say we're going to hold off on
Did not tell you that
If you have any ideas suggestions
See as rewards for us reaching milestones
Why would I be very open
Do you like to tweet those at us or reach out to us at our group
Go home and tell your mother
And now it's on Facebook
If we reach another what I would say another $2,000 in donations
Holy
We go to Sweden
That for that kind of money I go to Sweden or Finland listeners
But
Thursday April 19th
Amadeus
Nothing to do with that show
We're going to be going over Thursday April 8th
This is the day after the news breaks that Alex Jones
Course season 2 strain
Mood I don't want to talk too much about that come up at the end of the
Episode so don't think we're ignoring me
He's going to give a statement on it he's going to talk about it
He said he's going to give up that us the whole truth and nothing but the truth
Does not say so
Classic
Alex
Not does not anywhere help me God
Note that Willy doesn't need God's help to give the truth dance
Is it real hard and only gets booed at the end of the episode
When we get there
You'll do a little dance
About about
We will
Be discussing a number of
Shocking revelations were myth
People do not listen to the entire show. No one understands why you do
Thank God I don't even
Call me
No
Former director of the FBI
I keep trying to come up with a middle name I don't know what his middle name is
Pictures of him hanging out with Method Man Ghostface on
People in so many ways are you just wanted to find out it was backstage at a talk show
Did they just hang out
And cigarettes with Bill Murray just hundred percent
Very hurt
Boston built like the idea of like if you went back to like the early nineties and you were like
36 Chambers it just come out
You know what
About 25 27 years
You are going to be hanging out backstage at a talk show
With the former director of the Federal Bureau of Investigation
And it's going to be cool yeah they're going to word
No reason really we are in the
Alex talks about Jim Comey
You need to give me
I need the tracking
And that is the he's aware that like
Boy people keep suing me
I'm a pervert
Child molester
Okay
Here's the difference
Between those two things first of all I love the
Now I am watching every single thing I say for whether or not I will be soon but I'm going to pretend like I do
Care about very clear that I said
Think you look like
Maybe you didn't
Or whatever
Show me was being interviewed and talking about that like
Reason he said that is because
Navigation
They was inconclusive
And he was asked about it
Couldn't prove it
Night talk show hosts
George Stephanopoulos about it
He can't say
Of course he did
You can't say
No
He also probably can't do the like I can neither confirm or deny that sort of boilerplate language
Appointed in
Pissed off about that look
This is this is the worst
F*** the head of the FBI f*****
The former head of the FBI
Puppy FBI.
I'm sorry request station
Into whether or not this is real
And he's like I don't know
I don't know
He doesn't look like a pedophile
No one asked him
His thoughts on the matter it's just a complete
It's a very bad equipped
Little bit
Little kids
Martian from Pluto
What do you want
Victory or death no surrender
We all can remember back in April of last year and is being sued by Hamdi ulukaya of Chobani yogurt
Till my dying day
On this I will stand
I apologize by the way Slater public apology
100 percentage they wanted a lot of money and I totally forgot
Defamation
Also
I think you're pushing the envelope
Do it when you're in Alex Jones
In that last bit of it when he's like
Maybe you have sex with children
Defensible insofar as maybe everybody does or does not have
Also call me is like 66 he like he's super.
Too far for Alex Alex call me probably
No chance I bet Method Man
Basketball game
Huge
Basketball
I'm living back in the 90s
It's all about analytics
No my premises out the window
Victory or death
Haha
I get it
Rapping
Bring up a little bit
Skin in the game
I lost a lot of skin
Angelina's
Because
In the middle of Jones
Doesn't the future
You should ask your house
Gyros
Call Joan
Destruction
I think he's talking about Star Wars
No
You strike me down
Yeah you don't Alex
One everybody like us is like
Well I guess we got to move on
Or to Everett
I mean if he does like let's say someone kills him
Something like that
Terrible
You'd always be bad
And I'd be like
What kind of cute
The shame icer item not for it but I would look at it
These are kind of the consequences of this
Credibly bigoted violent
To end up getting
People so activated in a certain way
I see how that happened
The house of Jones getting taken down is not the Red Wedding the house of Jones getting taken down as the Lannisters getting murdered
Is it
Cool with that you bring that up cuz Alex Jones
Straight up steals the Game of Thrones theme song and uses it for a clip video
It is a new world order
Organization
So it goes on Friday
That goes on like to have three minutes at the entire game
I don't think that falls under fair use I think they probably is illegal
Opera
Looking to go with that
Secure the rights for the composer of Game of Thrones theme
And see if he's interested
Stop
He seems like a cool guy
Soundtracks
Set the Riza
Full circle
Coolio if you are listening
Just kind of Imagine our pre-show conversation
Always be
There's alot going on
Anyway
First of all
Thrifty dude
Integrity with money
All-time eyes traffic infowars.com
Ford.com
50 million-dollar
I mean I am a machine
You're committed to go all the way to the end
We're winning and they know it and their fifth
Nope really don't think so
Also wasn't the reign of terror almost over and at the same time
When you think of War Machine you think about that Ultimate Fighter who beat the
The s*** out of his girlfriend because he thought he was
He was cheating on her
Completely
I want to watch revenge
Warmachine is relevant
Is he paralyzed for like
Water
45 seconds and then immediately was saved by start
I don't watch Nerd movie
Anyway
How much of that money is coming from the operation how much
Could you save
Flies with those boats
Coach
Can you imagine
One of his boats
You don't even have the windows 10
Ridiculous
I'm so sitting right next to Alex Jones
United flight
Yeah I can
Number no
How do I talk with him
We see how susceptible years used
Alex
I got to tell you
Out
I was born in
One of the proto-celtic
You know what though I actually could f*** with him
Because I talked about this before on the air
Not like not like that
B interesting like parallel to Barack Obama
Throughout some of his
Education early life
No not that part call Larry Nichols
My dad was at Harvard
Same time
Was that the East-West Center which is a research organization
You got his doctorate
Episode
What do you mean
I mean are you going to eat are you Easter you with
It's about but merging
Terms of studying cultural studies
The conspiracy
I've been there many times
In my early life
My dad is deeply involved
Understandable I'd like
I could do something like that it would be fun it was really fun if I was stuck on a plane
I could really f*** with his head just a guy
F*** that
He would suck to be out
Right
Conspiracy that's that's the only way you play it on that plane
Anyway
Order conspiracy
People say that a lot of different
Evergreen
We deal with recent events
Positive made
Mad and rightfully so
USA
Almost
The further create white guilt
In restaurant
Your policy that you can't do that
What restaurant
So earlier in the show
Rooms are for customers only
There's a clip earlier in the show that I didn't cut
Because it was sort of
It got muddy and he started yelling about
And being on the right side
Civil rights
I don't want to deal with it
Two Gentlemen who got arrested
Starbucks
Vista
Aretha
Rashawn Nelson
Initially brushed it off with a Starbucks manager told him he couldn't use the restroom
Because it wasn't
He thought nothing of it when he and his childhood
Friend and business partner Dante Robinson were approached
If they needed
Twenty-three-year-old on spinners
The client explaining that they were just waiting for a business
A few minutes later they started noticing
Hardly notice to the coffee shop
Until
Sushi called
The police on us
Video of
April 12th
Trespassing arrest
Post office in the United States over racial profiling
Or shopping while black
Nelson Robbins
In the cities well-to-do
House Square neighborhood
An incident recorded on Waco
Customer cell phone
In the weeks since the 9th of May with a Starbucks apologetic
Lasting change
Is it coffee shop chain including new policies
Discrimination
Aiden
Quote
We do want to make sure it doesn't happen to anybody again Robin
Sunset
What is it was a kid but didn't know somebody that knew somebody
Do they make it to jail what happened
On Thursday they also got an apology from the Philadelphia police commissioner Richard Ross
A black man who defended his officers
I should have said that the officers acted within the scope of the law
And not that they didn't do anything wrong
Words are very important
At a press conference at snowbird
No
Miserably
In addressing the arrest
Shouldn't be
Shouldn't be the person bacon
Things worse
Shame on me
Is it anyway I've done
That you got to realize is
I don't know
I don't know man
Understand
These two dudes ended up
Spending all about 12 hours in prison
What didn't get out until midnight they were held in prison until midnight
And they only got out because
The district attorney
Klein to Prosser
Like this is
There's a really f***** up thing they make
B made them sit in his cell point where one of them was at
Specifically went on record
I don't think I'm going to make it out
I don't think I'm going to survive this
It's incredibly f***** up in the idea that Alex is just
Dismissing it as like
Hey how would I buy
Publicity stunt
What
Razee
If you are white they would have said
Hey
Go away
Even if the cops were called the cops would have been like okay
Now you have left Starbucks
So go home I can do something else I can't count the number of times
But I've gone into Starbucks use the bathroom
I can't count the number of time
I've been to my therapist office too early
There's a Starbucks down the street I sit there for like 15 minutes
No one bothers me I don't buy anything they said f****** matter
Used to manage a Starbucks
Rhino about their corporate policy
Threat so that comes into play
A little bit next clip
A card or something that allows you to
Be part of any
Like any Starbucks you ever want to go to you just
Unceremoniously
If anything they should be bothering me
Did you call the police when I show up based on me
You come in to manage the store tomorrow got a better job
Got to go
What are the reasons Alex is talking about Starbucks is in response
Uproar
About this
Legitimately f*****-up
In the public eye
The f******
What what
Word 2018
Imagine how long we've been going through this year
It's all
Ate all of the time
All the time in America
Two black men cannot
Anythink
Without
Being a taste
2% raise
Of having
Cops
Come down to
Forget that last quit
Is this trend that dumb people have
People with unexamined bigotry and bias
Otherwise known as
Well that I think we all have some sort of bigotry
We try and work again
The problem is my son examine
And when you just allow it to
Exist
And what it does
Is it criminalizes
Black behavior that you would forgive and look the other way when wiping
Recognized
But that is
Something they do
It's very threatening
Complete mess
It's
Disgraceful
Yeah well no other,
60% of 1
That's it
No I think it's actually I think it's closer to like 8
I think it was.
Evangelical Christian
I think it was like made 270
Support communities
The General Public
Real
Starbucks
Which is good
I don't know if it'll work
But
God bless
For trying something
Research Subway to give those guys
12 hours of their life back
Isaac
Very glad that
Murder
That's a totally legitimate fear
Totally legitimate
To Starbucks
Business
Then I will
Was murdered by the
The f****** cock
There was a f******
40 chance that was going to happen
It's about so it is good to address these issues
He's out Noah corporations are best
No answer answer is no
And stuff like that
No one
Serious workout
I don't know if it's going to be affected be that as it may
What happened
There was an uproar about it
And then some guy made a video
I think it's coming from you
Video of him going into Starbucks
Watch the rest of his videos he might be totaled
But it seems to me this guy
Watch the video in question
Hey Tim
I'm about to go into the Starbucks
Get my reparation
Coffee coffee
I heard y'all are racist
I want a free coffee
That story is really f***** up y'all give you a coffee
So that is all right now I just
Alex is going to set it up and then
Again as someone who has managed to Starbucks
I have some things to say on the other end of the
Call Mitch
There's a
Natural Ally about Starbucks
Starbucks
Association
I heard about that
Free coffee
Video
Coincide
He's mugging to the camera and likes having a great time
A person is working I have a really nice conversation
Before I end up going back
Everybody have a good day
Because
Stunt didn't quite work
Comedy video
And the person behind the counter was
Super nice I mean
The plan was actually to make a whole mess of things
Going to be like
It's unclear exactly
Starbucks
If
Starbucks headset okay
Change the game
We're not closing 8000 stores for race bias training
Every black person gets free coffee for a day
That's a whole weirder situation
It's like when Taco Bell gives you a free taco
Whatever Little Dipper
Idream interviews
They make her coffee
Avery about 2 hours you got to flip it
Tons of coffee that they don't end up selling
The company is
Keenly aware of that
To nurture
The image of being
The friendly establishment
So generally speaking
Managers are trained
22in
Courage costume
To give coffee to homeless people to come in
Because they know it's just going down the drain anyway
If you can create this place
People feel safe
Feel cared for that sort of thing
You get much more mileage out of that that the coffee you're going to
Cuz it's not fresh anymore
You'd always be given coffee to people who come in
That doesn't address
The other pieces
They know there's room way to coffee
And they know that these people are
Close to minimum wage
Locate employees
So if anyone comes in and is like
I demand
Wires
You just give it
Because that's how it works
In the service industry generally speaking when there's no loss for the company
And
Do you want your employee to get into a fight with this guy who's clearly videotaping whatever
It's it's
Absolutely protocol for you to be like
Employees are trained to be like
Let It Go
Not worth it to argue it's not worth it
To try and Chase down
Insured anyway or in the walk
Unless you're Orlando Jones in the replace
Sure
Don't remember that movie
At least
3 *
You think
Did I can take away from this
Really anti-union
Which is strange
Yeah
Yeah it's super and analyze what's going on inside that movie
Purely anti-union
Ownership
Banana
It's like every is every argument that you've ever heard somebody
Players are overpaid
If they didn't get the money it's going more towards billionaire
Yeah there's all that money
10 make it all the goods
Anyways
I'm sorry I'll be there in about replace the replacements
For so long I've been saying that will replace blade Trinity free show
So
Nothing
The little bit later Alex does say something to the effect
If black people are happy Africa
White people ugly
Territory
Eclipse about that and I've seen it posted in like
Hansa racist thing
I think that this one is I don't think we've ever documented any
I think this one is actually slightly unfair
Cuz I think people are taking him
Little bit out of context
Cuz he's not go back to Africa or anything like that
What do you think isn't
Okay
And what isn't being captured by people
Is what he's saying is
You should look at what's going on over there
And be like
It's still bad at H2 blockers
Too bad it's not worse
It's still bad
But it's not the same thing as like
I think that argument is
F****** insane because you can do that you can use that for literally anyting
You can get for any like you care about human trafficking
Human traffic
Looking elsewhere
Be happy with the status quo wherever you're at
Really offensive argument any human it is offensive and it only
Complacent
Play cats like whenever people are like you think there's no difference between the Democrats in the
Republican the Democrats say that we should
To be incrementally better in some respect
And then support the status quo
When every other
On every other thing you maybe maybe right
I don't know
It's interesting outright white nationalism of you don't like it
Could get out
Versus the
Elsewhere
Point
I don't know how to unpack that really they're both bad
So either of those things
Dumbass
Speaker not great
We got a new guest in the house
Great transition
Excited
Alright
I like the one word
Anything
You really have going on here is a guy who
Used to
And still does
Post a bunch of like a pro Trump
And I went to his website and I checked it out
Just weird Photoshop
Things of like Trump being awesome and giving the bird
Weird
Hillary Clinton with a bunch
The prison
Boob
Really
Feel like
More ironic
The only funnier when you realize that it's straight up
It's all just Trump propaganda
It's a complete
Trump if you saw street art with Trump giving you the finger you be like
Familiar
Did he
The thing that I think is really f******
Funny
Motto ethos
Is conservatism
Is the new Punk
And he's very clear
Conservatism is this Trump
No nothing a nativist
And I what is the 80s and it's
Right so
I would say
The conservatory
Conservatism
Punk
Would make sense
If
Back in the
The Sex Pistols
All of their songs were just about the Dupont family
We all remember
All of those great classics by The Ramones
About Howard Hughes know what was amazing about the Velvet
Love the world
Is is a mess
But you should. You should expect that Kieran this first clip
Are we find out
The Company You Keep
I'm with the proud boys
Officially they said
The left is going to do it
Yeah
Rihanna
Sure you don't want the proud boys in your bar
Authoritarian
Trapezoid
Corporate CEOs thing that he mentioned earlier
Like what he was talking about was the tax repatriation I assume
Fireleaf facilitated
Yeah
Gold
Imagine that
Some sort of global is plot
Isn't safe
It's ridiculous
Out-and-out
Trying to change
Reality
Into something
Thing that fits within your narrative
No I know this isn't unusual
For Alex Jones
I know this isn't unusual for what we're talking
About here
It's even more egregious
This is f******
Stupid
I think
The problem should be banned from every
F******
Business if there's ever been
There should be
Look up Starbucks closes 8000 stores
For racial bias training
They should also close 8000
About the problem
I had to throw them out.
Just keep yelling cereal name that them will get really excited to be impressed you can name cereals
Well everybody
Bear from the chat room at the California Uber Alles about to Jerry Brown
What's this
Being
Good work I was going to try and pivot that into
Something about
Your transition skills failed
Work that into another punk band riding song about
Gia Koka
Just because his name came to me randomly alright
Nope not saying be that as it may
Didn't write a song about how great Trump
Throughout this entire thing Alex is like
Street art
Love Street
He's like we got to get it in
Infowars art
You
Ben Garrison let's do this
Make a
It's not going to happen to go down that much like the Patriots
Music
Record label
I'm so
Answer want this weird line
Because
Vandalism is illegal
Doing these
Street art things
Installation
Technically illegal
Remind people about how much
Eyebright
Really weird
Encourage his audience
He knows that it's illegal it's very weird
So yesterday yesterday it's a sort of
Figure it out
And I do the best you can
In this next clip
Sabo talk about the difference
His school
Conservatives
Dumb dumb liberals
Republican
Everyone
To learn to do the same
Yeah
Looking to work
I think Alex thinks that is
Hail Marys Street Art
Because you talked
Chameleon susceptible to literally anything anyone says
Whatever you talk about
Might not
No that's ages
Old school information Warfare
Random pain
For a different reason
I think that
These Republican conservatives that he's talked about you just want to have a barbecue
And they want to ignore that the comfort that they're enjoying
Is built on the back of exploitation
That's usually races
Justin Texas to Nature
A nightmare
Which is what deliveries
But the Liberals they're particularly mad at
Are the people who have gotten to the point where they realize
Oh s***
What Comfort is based on basically a Whipping Boy
A metaphorical Whipping Boy in terms of
Underprivileged class
And for us to just sit back and enjoy your barbecue while we know that that's
The case is the moral equivalent of a
Actively supporting that system is very politically motivated
So I agree with you
I agree with policies that are essentially
Supremacist in
Action
Whether or not they are whites
Supremacist in
What expression
You are still a way
National
Like that is what you are doing it by your energy
Experiment are the ones who walk away from Amalia
I believe this apron outside would you rather fight a duck-sized horse or a lot of horses
Now that's a radical question it's a would you rather
Would you rather would you fight yourself or f*****
Yourself if there is a
I believe that
Text Pulaski
From the ethics class I took
Chicken College
Comfortable and utopian
And everybody when they get to a certain age
It's revealed to them
Utopian
Is that one kid
Is being beaten
Like a dog
Dog jackets
No just a h
Miserable
But because of that everyone else
Be super happy
Okay and the idea is that needs of the many outweigh the needs of the few
Walk away from that idyllic community and that's knowing
That is built on the back of brutal abuse
Of an innocent person
And
And conservatism right now absolutely was elucidation of what it's like to be
Black in this country
That might be what's up
Behind it
Experiment
Student ends up running
Right but I remember it so Vanessa
That's basically the would you save five people by
Purposefully killing one
Or would you through in Acts
Oceanwide up killing
It's not as it's not as dry as
Sabo
Accidentally
In this next
He talks
About a billboard
Wichita
Like I told you
Well so long as he doesn't deface Saba the Great Chicago Rapper put out wonderful
We need him to go against Obama
GoNoodle
What you've got here is
He's talking about this billboard
And what he did is there was a woman on
Figure skater
A picture
That picture of Al Franken
Who looks
He's groping that list
Remember that whole lot
Is Al Franken
Ramen
Blown up
And put on that billboard
Now
Here's where he f**** up
He says that someone contacted
I told him to make that billboard
Zeebo is admitting
Noticed but the story was too
Coming out
Which is incredibly
Listen to this
I have people to call me up and say hey I have some of the state department is going to go
Speaker
Thunder
Tim McGraw
I just know that
National
And
I told my crew
If you don't want
Tell me now
And they said nope let's do this over and over and over again until it became
Dance
And we got that thing up there like 15 minutes
He had very short notice like the love.
He had very short notice from
Somebody
Self-aggrandizing
Ready to get Steelers and didn't hire any
Bluffing
Things seem more important
Then it was
Quote
From the CBS News article
Hours before the allegations
Against Senator Al Franken became public Thursday Trump Ally Rodger Stone,
A Twitter account linked to the farmer trumpet
Stone in the early hours Thursday morning
The expected allegations involving the Minnesota democratic
Rodger Stone says it's Al Franken
Time in the barrel
Franken next in a long list of Democrats
To be accused of grabby Behavior
Later in the morning that story
Came out
Went on to
Except Frank
Apology and
Suspicious
I have
Very little doubt
That the person who
I told him hey overnight we need to get this billboard up
Was one
Rodger Stone
And because Sabo is so he's an asset casual
He's like a fifty-year-old dude her so like
Say what you want about Izzard I don't really I can't
Pretty art I'm not that I don't have that skill set can do is draw parallels
Not media-savvy
Accidentally saying on Alex Jones Show that someone contacted him
And paid him
To make this billboard on short notice
Clearly physically overnight
Rodger Stone hours before
Came out
It seems like there's
Probably
Maybe Rodger Stone everywhere they might be able
It's probably
Rodger Stone
So many
Bulshit
Probably going to
No I don't think so
You know what though
Might actually control everything
It made me think of Steve
Pieczenik
Collaborating
Okay I think it's Rodger
Throwing around State Department references or whatever
Massive
Slip
Hamer Park
Like the idea that street artist
Play bow
New about the Al Franken stuff before
Rodger Stone Infowars
Narrative
Specialist
I don't know
Trickster God executive producer and dirty trickster knew about it in the same time frame
Loki Stone
Rodger propagandists street artist to make propaganda
Is it going to come out it just seems
Likely
Crazy
Turn Rodger Stones Powers 4
For good
I feel like there's some sort of 40th Street
That we could pull Rodger Stone into right now
Tragically heroic way the redeeming of the anti-hero
Come on man
Now you're going Star Wars song
No
We have one more Clippers say about real quick
Before we got to take a break
Did everyone get industry
Everybody we are fighting for our lives
Onto the street
And then
From the Spanish
And you know what all you have to do is get your butt up on one billboard and you'll realize
What to do and what not to do
The first one's always scary the second one's kind of scary but you're right Jack Dorsey the CEO Twitter
Twitter
Real your listeners just get up on billboards the first one's going to be better
Who knows
Admission
What's up
Third dimension
Back in
Right
So we had to Quick break use the restroom
But let me tell you when we get back
We have
Lamest
Propagandhi Splash specials
From Millie Weaver
To discuss
Alright
We generally don't talk about her all that much on this show we need to discuss this
Cuz it's a next-level stupid
Just about 2 minutes
We will be right back
Larry Beck
Here we are
As I as I mentioned
Time
First take a look
Special Report
Familiar wafer
What happened
Would love to work on the road
Why was there great cameraman editor
Gavin
Chicagobears.com
Questions about the Clinton
History of sexual assault
Oh my
What a scoop
What is Coupe
So what do you think about that
I think
Protective
Powers that that is an issue that
Like the fact
It is a
Mensing it's a
A party
Not a
An
It's something that
Men should be
Parking
Regulator
So yeah
Deportment
It's not going to go well this is not go well.
What ends up happening
I don't remember exactly how these clips go
But
I think I think it was
First clip of Mount Millie's actual report
We get to hear the question
I'm not entirely sure
This might
I don't know
I need the label
Basically Tarana Burke got really upset when I asked about
The
Possibility of the hashtag me-too movement
Becoming too partisan and being used as a political weapon and if it was going to take away from
The mission which is to help
Which immediately then she turned nasty was like oh I wonder who you voted for
And just
Suck her mob audience on me with this
Mob like mentality that all started cheering her on and supporting her in
Trying to bully and intimidate me into silence
So
I would I would
A couple of important
And
What is accusing
#me too
Meeting of being
Is too partisan
Or that it's being
You're turning it into a partisan
Something
That is what Millie is in
Intending to do by going there and ask
Accusing them
It's it's
Banana impossible for her.
Philosophically it is mind-blowing
Cuz it's not inability to realize
I disagree I think they are
Legitimately
To dump to examine their own actions
This is a set-up
Like this isn't like we talk about good and bad face all the time
The definition of bad faith
Well no not even that cuz I think those words are too
Loaded
I've been good
Bad faith
Is much more relevant and important
With a video camera
Like if she doesn't live in f****** Akron
She flew the screen to go to this f****** complete
And she did so specifically
In order to
Hopefully antagonizer respond
That you can get on video that will feed into the narrative that she wants to push
All he wanted
To do is find out the
Truth wasn't about
Can you imagine a scenario where she goes to Akron
She's like
Here's my question
It's like
That's a very good point conversation that needs
We are having it and I think that you might just be missing some pieces of it
And it's actually just like
Not great video
She goes on Alex's show the next day
Hey it's really amazing actually I went there and they were real
They were willing to have a dialogue
There's no way that that works that doesn't fly for Alex that doesn't fly for what
She gets paid
To do
In order to ask
The question that was meant to antagonize
And meant to accuse
It was not meant to be like hey
I care about Juanita broaddrick I care about Kathleen Willey
I care about these people that Bill Clinton has allegedly sexually assaulted
I care about that it was
What the f*** is wrong with you
Care about Democrat
Assault
I think that's intellectually dishonest
Because I think
Isaac
What is it is just like
Alex whenever he pulls that b*******
Immediately after some sort of tragedy happen
He has no concept of like
I feel empathy for the victim
None
Batman it is purely
Worse
Yeah
Is 2
Give I could not give
Let's of a s*** about
Who he hurts
All I wanted is
Hip
It has nothing
To do with
And it's not even retribution
I want to I want to hurt him
In response to the damage that he's caused
It's just I am irrationally
Driven by Larry Nichols bulshit
A rookie Rabbitt of her actual presentation of the question in a little bit
And we'll we'll see what
I assume that it is very fair-minded
She's got a
If I know anything about Millie Weaver
It's that
She is about
Hugely and a great way to have a podcast on maximum fun she's so into the nuisance
Yep
She is all about.
Not at all
Complete bulshit version
Do things in order
So in the next
She talks more about what she
She had to endure
Mad at this place
In the name of Journalism
A mob of protesters came out I wasn't even sure what it was about because
Their Banner said
Take me
Real quick
I wasn't sure
Do able to go to the
Facebook
Group what she's describing here is going to come back and play out later but she's describing is
She's setting up a narrative cuz she's edited her video
She wants to make it seem like
She asked this question got kicked out
And she walked out and all of a sudden there was a protest going on
It wasn't before
It's a mystery protein ever where did it come from
So as I'm approaching it I start getting flipped off
And having women yelling at me and that's when I realized wait a second this
Is the hashtag me-too movement
And they were probably observing in a separate room cuz they were streaming the video to other room
And that's what I realized oh my gosh
They're very mad at me
Essentially
Tarana Burke gave them permission
Because they had all established rapport with her she did a really good job throughout the
Meeting the the speech
To make everyone establish rapport with her and seeming like she's just trying to help everyone and she's just the same plant
4ukey
Night
Self-help
So that's vectors like they built The Narrative of what
We should really be
Like
Not make bones about what this is about
This is what this is about
Denise Campbell that's why we need your financial support we got products
So uses uses all of this b******* that Millie is spinning out of this story
We couldn't afford to pay a bunch of you having
Bought a Nelly's weirdo husband could come along
Sign up
Auto
But because you did
We're going to
In a way that
Exactly what we are
Maybe
So I believe is the point of the actual question
With sexual allegations against
Decades ago
Someone whose power
They weren't
So very quick
Important
Her response was
Who said they were excluded
Which is
A fair question
Here's Millie's response
Included
I would say ask Time Magazine about that
That's an editorial issue
Not even like
Wasn't
Control of what
The time mag this directed question you're angry about nothing
You're Clear Lake it's
We're what you're doing
This isn't about
What's your question
Article
Worried at all the hashtag me-too movement
Partisan
Who did you vote for
This is where that like accusing
Your enemy of doing what you're doing
Is is happening in real time
It's because it's so murky
It's really easy to Bates
Someone interest
Situation like
It's very easy for this collection of people who are just having a
Meeting about sexual assault
To be painted
As
Liberal or prolapse
Someone who is there
Physically antagonizing
In order to push them in that direction
Are you worried that the partisan dance
What if the me-too movement doesn't vote for the guy who is relaxing protection
Do that women need even more
Why would you think that they aren't as valuable in the Moon
Is there any reason why the
The guy who
Making the
Poop
Clearly
Partisanship
It's not party
The very stated
F*****'-a
Group
To fight against
Assholes
Sexual assault but she works for Infowars and she's coming in to ask
Speak clearly partisan question
In order to
Partisan
Gunship on the group
I mean if I were to wargame this
I know the reason is
Because some of the most valid criticism
And very soon
Related
The sexual assault
That some of the most common all the sexually assault
Might have something to do with that
The fact that our president is a
F****** rapist
Is deflection
Service
They don't care about
This for any other reason
This is
In order to work
Towards that
Control
It's rampant liberalism run amok
Gorski even University
Interacting with Millie
If you want to talk about even earlier stuff we got to talk about Anita Hill
And the crowd claps
Alex Fierro is like
Like what
Because I asked her out
I didn't think if you want to talk about this. What about
You know
He was a patriot
Dial what about the governor of Missouri
Do is throw a Republican
That is what your B was
Pointing out examples where it was Democrats
When you came in
The accusation that you made
Was about people from us
Specific party
Why is it
F****** together
Nothing to do with part
And anytime you give a
He's going to f****** up music
What is what's going on
You know I don't even care if you give a dude power
Super cute
Direct
Towards women
I'm sure Lewis
CK was very liberal
To be pretty liberal politics Donald Rumsfeld
The lizard on the Opie and Anthony show
Non partisan issue
You know what I mean
It's just disgraceful
Winner
Propaganda
Updo treated
The chat room
Mark Dice was skulking in the bushes with a petition
Fresno that's super funny
Real bad
Streetman pieces
Dice dice we're going to have to let you go
Anybody turned
Really bad at this job everybody who has not listened to
Tons of episodes
I must
Tri-State
Go on YouTube
And just type in
Mark Dice bloopers
It is not to be believed
It's the least funny s*** in the world
So
At this point
Millie Briggs
She's doing her
We've heard her ask her question
And she gets
Thrown out if someone clear because the camera work is really bad
She's just not have a phone
Doing it
It's either someone grabbed the phone to look like
She's being pushed really hard
I don't know because I seen so many of those like
Second external views of Mike cernovich acting like Ryan
And it's just three people standing behind him
Who's going to the Rock taking a stunner
Flopping all over the place
I think that's
That is kind of a crystallization
My Philosophy on
How you should respond to
Is
Don't
Don't bother
Like there shouldn't have been a a response to that there should have been like well what about Roy Moore
There's to be a what about there needs to be a bye
In front of the live crowd
You know you know that is
Comedian in front of
Have a crowd
Your mind will go to just like this is a good point
Wendy's
You're talkin to the My Philosophy with Heckler like I don't want
Jordans
Comedian destroys heckler
Jordan is like a wonderful agreement with a Heckler about how life should be
That's my situation
Jordan helps heckler actualize
I would not get as many click
I've got a bit of stuff but there's
Because someone grabbed
The phone
Convenient way for her
Edit
About how
Oppressed
So here's what
Seems like
You can't really dis
Disagree with that
Here's what happened
After this
Speech
There was a mark
She has added its selectively to make it seem like she gets thrown out this
I guarantee there's like an hour of her sitting around waiting for it
He could create this for the parade
Exactly
And so when March comes but that
I bet that March
People start flipping or off which is
As the cost
You play the game
And that
Cuz they engaged
You came over
Telling her like
Why can't
We just have
Useful things
Rite Aid
NuWave
Play the with the video is
The girl who
Telling her why can
Nothing is about the March
Which would
Crazy
Because
The way she presented
This March just happened out of nowhere
And all of a sudden they come up to her
Hayward defensive about our March
Stopping Billy hasn't said anything
Clearly it's referring to
Earlier maybe an hour earlier
All those people who are Marching were inside at the speech
And they saw her antagonistically ask
The question that wasn't questioned while people were like
Why are you asking
2.2 display is delightful
Opaganda esta
It's so hot
People get tricked by mistake
I8
Cancun
Conclusion which is the
Does the whole point that I make is that
Millie Weaver
If you can't recognize
That these
People are
Trying to not make
Just their lives better
Your life better is what
Why did
57% of white women vote for
Like that kind of bull
Like if you're doing this
If you can't recognize if you were living in a right-to-work state and you're against
Union
They're at
Ghibli making your life
Better by Thursday Samantha
Boo
F*** off
Really exciting
That last episode this week got into something we cover
Oh yeah I think it's one of the first times we've beat them
Thule half a story Chinese Exclusion Act
I'm game, is the reason that I thought about that was
Because of the
Who cares anyway
Repeat
How do I Petty about that
There's a lot of reasons
Your patio
Alex
That that protest
That Millie Weaver walked into
Just because Millie was
Ladies and gentlemen is always the same
Videotape
Why can't we just
I like I like the idea that
People have
Protest
Just in case there's a counter
He was
Caulking
Was troubling because he's like
They got activated from a garage
Garage sale
Garage
And because Millie Weaver was there
Merely got a flight to Ohio
We have been preparing for Billy Weaver to come to Ohio
But we're ready for never saw it coming
But
Because there's
So scared
Every single time there is
Anywhere around the country
They're just waiting in that garage
Soros
Get on the
Hey get out the garage get out of garage we got to Millie Weaver siding
Cuz of course or he is cold like
Just
Next time to go right out of the fucken garage
Course that makes sense
This is like this is desperate
This is so sad because it's very cool
If you watch it the whole video you can
It's there it's very
You know what has
Here's what hear something that I keep struggling with
Like I'm just messing up the stuff cuz I did watch it and like
I know this
I don't want us to get into the same
Position
To italics
Hey you can check it out yourself
You know like
I don't want to discourage people from actually checking right you can
I respect that it's a weird
I will tell you it's boring
In the same way that like reading a lot of these books that he references
It's boring
I don't know
It's a tough position for me to be hard part
We are coming from a place of
Please
Please go read this stuff because
You should absolutely
Cross-check I like we're going to be wrong eventually casting rod
Because we want to know
When were wrong also thank you Mary Jailer we appreciate it very much
Give a little cheer
I don't know how this twitch chat works
The terms is like
It seems like a
It seems very nice and I appreciate it.
We are
What are you doing
Can you do
I don't have Snapchat
I really don't know what's going on there
As much as I love news
I should know about it
Anyway
That's a great
As much as I love nude
I should know about technology has left
Information with the Middle East
We have a situation where it's very clear that you have
Part of me
Actor like she's a crisis
Yeah she's Hamming it up I'm saying she is
Who is doing the
The acting in the
Chico's
And she has bad face
Cheesy antagon
Yeah she goes specifically in order to
To create some sort of
Response
In this meeting
Without her being there
Knows what you need to do
You need to get some footage Alex needs for the show
The Sandy Hooks is going on you need help
And so she does
Accusing
Me too
Being too political
Bye
Bring in Polish
And then staging this idea
Materializes out of nowhere because she's there
Tumi
That invention invalidation like in the movie
Inception whatever that whenever you start
Threaten the The-Dream all of the
Dream people
Start to attack
Twirkle invalidation of
The right to conquer
And the right to protest
Like the right
Protest if you disagree with conservatives
Position
That's f******
I'm looking over at the chatroom in sharks
You know our view on the gays
Big fan
Great
I'm so
If if we don't talk anymore
Liberal positions
Somehow
Marriage
How do you feel about homosexuals exist
What are the most liberal sounding Arabians there are
Elizabeth correct I think trans people should have
Absolute protection in moat
Bill Gates
For real you should be allowed to identify as whatever it is you want
Also skin colors about your character
Phrenology
Not do you know what we might have accidentally stumbled into a really good sketch kit that would never work
Like good characters Right Stuff
Battles of already been fought
No no I think racism is a real thing I think I think
I think that's just reality
But at the same time
I take care of trans rights
Conservatives going
The hatred of Jews that they wind up advocating for Progressive policy
I fear that we've gone too far based on this
Fair enough
Let's move on.
Comment
Millie Weaver sheets done
It's embarrassing
Aziz
This point Alex
Get the call from
Zach
It's make intelligent source
He very clearly has to take
Hate Mars
We heard from Zach
Was on the Friday show
Where Alex turned on Trump
And Zack was
Back it up on that and also say
War for Mars
They're trying to get us back onto the planet
They're not trying to let us go to the
Everyone's trying to fight for Mars and the Moon
Stance and he's bringing back another week later in order to make
Sure that Alex Jones held accountable is good and I appreciate that but you jumped the gun
Cuz I wanted to say other shity things about today
Also the last time we also the last time we saw him on that Friday he did not know who the Joint Chiefs of Staff
Not a good idea he thought that McMaster had not been fired
Possibly McMaster was a Joint Chiefs of Staff when he was the Nationals
Security advisor
All of those things
Should be something
High-level intelligence
Gym source
Kind of invalidate
Literal job to know
So here's the other reason I know that Zack is
Vegas bomb
Besides all of a sudden
Alex
MBA interview with Millie Weaver by saying
Like
He's in a rush
In the middle of Zacks interview he goes
Commercial
He blows hard for about 2 minutes about things he's mad about
Amen he does
He does a reed
Well Zack is waiting on hold intelligent source is coming in
And he's got information that you got to get you on a short time frame
3 things
Kill time while he's waiting on
It leads me to believe you don't take him all that seriously.
Playing to find out where he's got to go
Aldi
So f***** up because it's like
I don't I don't believe any of it
The end
Call was like I know you're on your lunch break
Replace spray
I don't go by federal law
You do have to give people a 30-minute lunch
But I feel like high-level intelligence
Since people probably work out a little bit more of a
Swinging schedules and people who like if you're not back at your desk in 30 minutes
I would I would
Maybe high-level intelligence
Put in late nights of urine high-level intelligence
So f******
Stupid
That like
Okay so what
I know I've tried
An early-season
Lock is pretending
Is about to do it
And now I'm going to
Lock role-plays of the general
The whole situation
Like a dungeon dragon
Anyway
And yet you still want to get it out here's a great idea
One of the new possible Rewards
Is we'll just do a podcast about lost for a week
I don't know for a week
We do the whole series
No there's already plenty of podcast
That doesn't make sense
I know a lot about lost want to know anything about laws
That's a good point chime in at our Facebook group go home and tell your mother your brilliant if you want us to do that horrible idea.
Anyway
I feel like what we have here
Is a situation where Zack works
Add a job of some sort
You didn't need to get back to
The time that he could make a call to Alex
Here we go
The only thing that you want to do is sort of
Reinforce Alex's narrative
He's already
From the
Trump is f******
Dover
Into like
Oh no
New narrative
It's mysterious how this high-level intelligence guy seems to
Blow in the wind the exact same way that Alex
Yeah
Probably just
Because Alex is so InTouch
Anyway here's what he wants
Anybody's looking into the death of the plant Nikki Haley's looking to run in 2020 with Mike Pence they're hoping
Toronto 2020 live
And all of them for months are acting like this
He's the guy
Always says Pence is perfect
Seriously pro-gay conversion conversion therapy Mike Pence
Alex
To your question
Of whether I've noticed the media saying that
Can do no wrong
Hard
No
Ulta
Well one
We've never had a vice president
Campaign
With a challenger 2 in the primary for that present would be weird
Because what is that
Yeah so but Nikki Haley
President
Become president
I think he
Kinda is implying that Haley is running for
President
With pants as her vice president is also saying they're going to get
Trump impeached
That would mean the president
There's no
New regardless of what you think about any of these people
F****** way
Did you end up with an impeached
President to the vice president becomes president
Then two years later
I like you better
I bet you would like it better
Look in the in the chaotic dark timeline that we live in
That's the only
Weird-ass world we live in
Currently the
And I'm campaigning for a lesser role
As
Nikki
As her Vice
She's going to serve two terms
I'm going to campaign with Paul Ryan
As he is
How
Okay
Here's a good question
How many terms
Yeah I don't know
I don't know
That's a really interesting that I've never considered that would come up
Forever ever one's kind of
Who cares that right
I'm super interested
I want I want that now
Outlook
Is President Grover Cleveland serving two non-consecutive terms
That's fantastic
But Mike Pence being vice president for life
I don't even know how to deal
Exactly
He's done with his lunch break
And so Alex
Finally is left
Without any more gas
Millie Weaver is gone
The great street artist anymore
He's finally got to get to
Sandy Hook
He's going to talk about it
You know I'm so truthful and Loveless respect me so much and I know
You are great
All the time
Sandy Hook secret is this
I'll go ahead and say it all on here
Because I backed off saying I didn't say call Sandy Hook
Wheel
We have
2015 I can pull up the entire list
If you give me just a second
Virus
Call Olga
She needs to have
Glimmer of light
My lawyers strongly advised me not to do this
Bright orange
Because they love the billable hours
On January 13th 2015 to go to knowledge fight.com we do have a link up to this you can find the in
Entire episode
On video
But again
Replace the Clipper number of time
What I'm curious about is
Do you think that there's a new
Level of sophistication with a lot of these false flag
Where
A couple of pieces of
Flimsy evidence that get everybody talking and Stearman the wrong direction
It's just that when you did that they were funded by Western Funding
Provocateurs
Becomes a red herring
Because
They have staged events before
But
Bowers and
Then I tear the building down
Email Bloomberg
Reselling is people get ready in the next 24 hours to capitalize on a shooting
Yeah show
Use a synthetic
Completely fake
In my view manufacture I couldn't believe it at first
That they clearly
Used
That is what you said
Is it was your position
Consistently
For a very long time
I'm sorry about the audio being much higher on that babe
Just refuses to say it
As Darrell
So I went when it first
Came out
He got
Sued
I thought
Because of the time
Frame of it
He did most of his
Brutal work
Long ago
You're too which is it within the statute of limitation
For definition
Is not it is much more insinuation base
And I've come to the position where I don't really understand
So I don't know I don't know
This could go either way but it is really sad the
Situation
Forever
It's real sad.
Are you spinning cuz it's all lies
Brackets
Congrats
You said it over and over again
In this next clip
From
The 18th
In present day
Are you saying a year after the shooting
Shooting happened in December of 2012
That would have been 20
Yeah least a year and a couple months
Before
The clipse
Did we just play
School shootings happen
From 2016
Did
My lawyers
Strongly advise
Sociopath
So he's saying that for years ago he went to his staff
And told them to
Stop
Looking into sand
Sandy Hook
Said that it was
2 weeks ago
Going to say it over and over again for like 4 years ago we're looking at April 28th
Now Debbie April
This was this to me was
Complete
Front
Because
We did a
Long investigation
And we saw a bunch of
. like there was a school shooting at college
In Oregon
Ain't on the October 20th 2015 show Alex
False flag like Newtown
These nuts
Specifically
Do you know what
Associate
To not look into
The new town and not look into
4 years ago
Which makes it
Very difficult to understand how this has
But now
Your uncle John do Navy SEAL
What's a successful security company
About yesterday
Therefore
The city council hearings about
He had sent a reporter to Newtown
In July of
In order to cover hearings about it in order to
Juice up
It being a false flag
If you told his staff not to cover it
In 2014 why is he sending someone in 2015
That
Uncle
Would we covered back in the 2015 investigation
And
Rob didn't say anything
That was suspicious you just said
I've never seen anything like this
This is
That sort of thing
But that doesn't stop Alex from trying to get robbed a manufacturer quote about it
It doesn't add up
Go back to the
I'll think about the exact words but
From what I'm getting from what I remember
Good cuz I was in the car driving laws talking to edit
Because I wanted to get something out of before we did that cuz we did the show that night on the 4th that day on the 4th
Talk about a short interview with you
And you're saying it's strange it doesn't add up he's like I've never been in a court proceeding like that ever wear
People don't know anything
That he's giving
Very easily be rationalized as being
I've never been in a court proceeding
That was about
20 murdered
Elementary
Visit I mean
Embarrassing
About what
You have done
In the past as a journalist
And quote
It indicates that your
Covering some
Something up you know what I know that would
Be admissible
Court based on the defamation laws
Dr.lee shirts
But
Like
When you lie to this level you're lying for a reason
You're covering something up and it's that you know you did
So anyway
We should be prepared for this
Emotionally
Already
But you know what this
This is how we close
Fashion Valley San Diego
Forget this is in present-day this is from 28
Call Lizzie
Call Alex races that doesn't work in calling Russian that Things Fall Apart
He is and they said that you saw him a few months ago about
Didn't work for the truth
To be fair you had Mike Adams on repeatedly guy who created a website
Specifically to Bowie of Vick's
Some of that shoot
Because you disagree with it
Is politics
Also you lied
Hoban
Timeline
Any comments he made about
Getting on his bike after school
In the evenings go back to
The score
Now We Cycling what I didn't really say from 5 years ago
Because they think you're stupid
Do you think they say
So blah blah blah
I'm going to go to this AP article right about now
This is an AP article Sandy Hook parents
Family file suit against Alex Jones
Jones responded to the allegations in the YouTube
Videos
And the news
Maybe I do believe Sandy Hook really happen
He said he believes the lawsuit
It will be thrown out
That's not them
Saying that you actually are right there just reporting what you
You said
Get it right
They're just
Forwarding
On your way
Cuz it's a news organization
Which isn't even what I did
Add
Liam.
So I'm going to we're going to be able to
And we just move on
Yep
Weather
Family. Thank you all
Alpha power
I even started up we should all be emotionally prepared
I was emotionally prepared for him to lie I was
Emotionally prepared
About baby
Yeah I know pretty impressive
Liar
Goddamn gofucker
Yourself covered on this
Which is not a glamorous or interesting
Is the Sabo it made it on air that he had advanced notice
Al Franken situation
What your matches up perfectly
Prickly with the timeline the Rodger Stone had
And they both have
Concentra worth
So
Anyway I got to pee again so we got to wrap this up we are at knowledge
Correct we are on Facebook
We are on Facebook follow us or find us or subscribe
Search
Next
We appreciate
Suggestions
Possible really appreciate it
According to you a very Petty
I suppose that means
Things that
Your turn to
Today
Holding
Alex