Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
We are a couple dudes
What's up
Let's stay in
Sure an alien
Knew what sort of alien are we talking about
Greek
Let's call it Minerva
Sure
What would you
Tell them hello
Intelligent
Spaceship
He doesn't know anything about it until that spaceship
She would probably say
The bird in my head
Interstellar
You have no idea what the Jordans
You'll figure it out soon
Episode
I would like to give a shout out to a couple of new donors
I was going on at their William
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much really William
Give me liberty or give me a donation
Because it turns out it wasn't recording so it was it was
To Chris
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much Chris
Attractive man thank you for donating
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much Stephen
Like our lack of running out
Thank you Lori
Get some of that
NBA money that's what you got going our way he's from Finland
That's cool
That is really cool
King of cool things
I'm sick and tired of the mood to talk about Alex Jones
Today
It's been a long weekend
I don't want to talk about Alex Jones
We Project Camelot and we've been waiting with bated breath
For the new Mark Richards interview that you did
But here's the deal
I listen to the old one
I found a bunch of interviews that you did with him that we have not talked about
About Mark Richards
AKA
I also know that you orchestrated the murder
Is what you we are
The best thing to do is not good explanation
Right now I think you should go just fine those old episodes
That's our next
That's our next investigation
Start from the beginning
Cuz we we done the 7th and 8th
Indeed
The first one was the one we did listen to with his wife
His wife Joanne Richard
Is it Delight
Woman in
Explicitly married to a murderer
Out of context drop from today's the episode
He said that Britain is under the
Kind of control to some degree of the
Very excited
I felt like we desperately needed till
The black dragon friends all right
He also goes on to explain that when people are in now.
The service of the Queen the queen they're talking about
Absolutely
Your spinach and gray balls yet
Absolutely the best
This report starts out
Spits acid
I have no idea you know what
The things that's great about Margaret
Play real fast and loose with
Details you just said something like that it does not explain it
He did not elaborate
Not surprised
Interview Mark Richards
Vacaville prison
She comes back
Explains what
You've told her
Because she can't get a recording device into the prison
That is the first one
Every single time that I had to use a pencil
Curiosity from Project Camelot about my recent interview
Captain Mark Richard
Space Program
Captain Mark Richards
Space command
To see him
Prison
With his wife Joanne Richards
And that was Saturday October 22nd
A lot of notes that I've taken a small pencil
Yeah we know yeah probably
Absolutely hasn't
Yeah yeah completely
To get him recorder privileges adios got a beach
Has forgotten about possibly
For 4 hours if you were just letting him
Yeah yeah
Diminishing returns in
Just be like
Who You Are
Still going I would assume there's a lot of
Whatever she asks
The question
Here's the thing
Right
So question anyway
And he just gives a boilerplate answer is
Just like there are a lot of car Acts
Then there's really no explanation other than human error
Is there
If rappers it's record
Almost every question is a leading question
One of them is a journalist everything people tell her
Murderer
Don't like that
Perception that I'm painting
What you need to know
He is Mark Richards
Subspace
Stickman race
Eternal
Honorific title
We can make jokes all day about how this guy's a murderer and he's tricking
Singapore
Woman yes we can
But what you should know is that in prison
He
Has people working
Inforum
And I want to say that Mark has another officer
Who reports to him and has reported
He says for over 40 years
Who's in prison with him. Covel
And it's present
This prisoner was a
Killed a child molester
And it's not sorry to events
Apparently is
Is in prison with Mark and
Has been reporting to Mark 4
His name is
A release
I guess so cuz it's not true I guess it's the catering
He has a guy who is friends with in prison
Which is great
It's great to have a social life within prison
Johan
Sebastian
Balls on this guy
I love it
Now Carrie I do have a guy who's reporting to me
I mean come on man you got to recommend him for a promotion or something
What are the odds of murderers
Is a jailhouse snitch
So
I don't know this is gentleman's gentleman
I don't know man it's very bizarre really flight of fancy kind of
Image in my head
Like I'm picturing
Like
We've covered Mark Richards on a couple episodes and psyche
Never enough
Is crazy
This introduces a new level of like kind of crazy
He's got a bureaucracy in pre-op
Okay I believe perhaps
We're having some fun here Putlocker
I want you to know this report where Kerry Cassidy is gone to prison
The Doctor Mark Richards
It's not devoid of real journalism
Okay carry stumbles into a story that I don't think
Anyone's ever told
So Mark has as I said
Talked a little bit about
The
The work he's doing in the prison and he also talked about
Very briefly race relations
Apparently
Moschino
You know separated
And he's not allowed
Like friends
A black prisoner
For example because the gang leaders
Just don't allow it
He can be acquaintances with them but
Here's a big scoop Mark Richards isn't a white supremacist
Still man
Does wild
Apparently there is a racial issue
Imprison yourself is like a journalist who has like
Top secret intelligence sources in like
The highest level of secret government in Avi she's surprised by the ideas like
Desegregation
In prison
Considered this
Maybe she's never seen a movie
Or any TV
Nothing
She's never seen any televised or any kind of entertainment it's just
She believes
First of all the movie references
Just basically rattling off the plot of movies
Let her inside sources tell her I said
Is creativity
People just calling
Possible
Entirely sure but what I am sure about is
Some of it has never been discussed
Marc rich
Possibility
I like possibility of possibility
I don't know if you heard this Jordan has remained a reputable source
I don't know if this
But there is a chance
That there are secret
Underground Android Army
He said
Regarding
A possible Army
Of underground
Android
Us and China he doesn't
Cool
Cool me to reasoning is that
Had the
Ground-level we would already have lost
Will he says
You always fight
When you have one step ahead
7 advantage
No sense
Technologically
Now
He said if we can't defend the planet from a ground invasion
And
Most of the battles in the soup
Secret space program
R4r
Arvada massage
Some of this seems to be
VidCon
Results of saying
That what's going on in
Middle East
Is the battle
To oddstory a lot of underground bases
Aulani
I don't think about it too much
Is a bombing
I think that I needed to talk more with him about that
In the context of the two or three
3 hour interview that I had
You know we had a
Blue questions and
Drill
So
Kind of like an ongoing story
Yuri
You missed that last bit that she's kind of like an ongoing story
Please make it sound
Trunks over along.
Cuz he's lonely
Some sort of
Serialized
Grace
Boys Adventure mags
1920 doesn't want her to leave cuz otherwise he's just got Bach
The imprisoned
Working relationship that's not
No absolutely not strict hierarchy
Primitivo
Fraternize with
It's kind of like a story that
Playing out
Is one of the first of two times on this episode just describes what lying is
Shuffle
It kind of like he's making it up as he
He's going along
And obviously
Cuz he hasn't answer for all of these contradictory
Playbox false information that's
The distance from
Purpose
Purposefully being run
On her damn what
She talked about that all the time like I don't even close
Plausible deniability is like program allowed Mark Richards
Cuz everyone already thinks he's a murderer
He's the only person
Get the truth out right now
Article leaves me cold
I think also
It's fascinating
Cuz any of these moments
We're Cary like cuts through the clouds a little bit in the xik that's a contradiction
It's kind of fascinating cuz that's a huge cock
He's like
He's like if we can't fight them in space
Call idea
Anyway
Joint Underground
Android army or they both have their own separate
They were separate and they are going to do battle
That's the Android Army Defense Force against
First instance of really good International cooperation
That I can
Human context clues I bet you're right never really specified so
I don't know
Like do they look more like a do they look like
Android like a like
Robot
Things or do they look more like
Like Syberg's
Probably probably
Like it like that guy from Mortal Kombat
Breakfast Jack
Okay
You know you're you're a student of History
To about
I think I'm going to find out everything you know is wrong
She said
Is that there are
Again WWII
480 races the nordics
The reptoids
The dracos
The krays
What's 5
Nordstrom aldebaran are the ones that help
The Nazis
The course are always available
To the highest bidder
Mercenaries
The Reps
Nordx
Control of it over there
From what I
Cool cool up the racks
Boys
Almost like
Racial
Equivalent
To calling them the Japs
They don't act
I don't appreciate
Even within the fall
Even hypotheticals fantasy racing
The real world
Kind of Holocaust denial
The latest Republican spadaro
That accepts that white people are evil human agency
Absolutely
Mercenaries
I mean that could be WWII is about
I don't know I dropped out of high school before
Wait
Did she say that's what
WWII was about or just
Who was fighting it
Power struggle between the four
Where to learn more about some of our Wars
We got it we got a laundry list of Wars to rewrite before we get there
Project Camelot Richard series
Oh that his best friend
Are the Raptor
Of which again
I feel like the reptoids
May actually be the good right right because he is a murderer at a bad guy he's friends with the Raptors they must be
We've learned
Eat you for a chocolate bar chocolate
Doesn't necessarily mean
They bite his Jurassic World
There's another update I didn't get I didn't get the clip of it
But it turns out there's like a
T-Rex
Showcase
It goes around the animatronic T-Rex
Six Raptors inside of a T-Rex
Along with it too
Richards is reporting that
Are there
Carrie is like
If your kids get out if you guys want to go out and had a real
I like that a lot
Be so bummed out maybe this is Jay
Just underground Buzz Marketing for a walk with the Dinosaurs or die
Part ownership stake
Surprise
We learned more about Raptor
He said that Raptors
Prefer their food source
Haunted
So they like to H & L
And also that they have
What they basically
Prior to be extinct
The dinosaurs
Herds of dinosaurs off
The planet to race
Cattle
On their own planet
Amber
Regarded
Humans as a
The kind of caviar
Cool the time
As I said another email
Work with us
In fact they fought alongside us I guess in World War
Or started to
Install that we were
Very good Fighters
That help
Change their mind about us
And they also
As I said their Queen
Trajectory
For their race
In terms of
Its development
Doing now
Okay
That's that's a good long-term
Something you probably recognize this implied
Radar
Bailiff
They farmed
Their own dinosaur
Yeah that's possible
Yes.
They prefer their meals
To be hunted
Why would you raise anything as
Cattle the big problem if you are a Raptor
You come from a planet where
You know your Rafters and you're a super intelligent and
You can you can speak
Interstellar travel
Hundreds of millions of years ago and yet your technology has not really advanced
That's beyond that point
Time being
Concerned with the idea that like
Terry
The think that they came up on
A planet with one
Species
They had to come to Earth to get dinosaurs because there is no resources or other species on their f******
They just stumbled upon the dinosaurs in real life
Choppa Choppa
It's like we're looking in the mirror
Come on
They told us
That we are going to take them out
But in reality they were like
We're going to help them evolve on our planet
From the meddling influences meteors
Yeah it's possible I don't know
This is high-level b*******
But humans are caviar
Do they put them on
Rafters are much bigger than human
Who is a whole human caviar
I can't imagine that's the case
Do they like whatever we you don't want the head
Skull is problem
I know this much about rappers
Not very agile with their hand
Everybody makes two
I don't know I think if you have almost non-functioning hand
I also do most
Predatory animals
Don't care about.
For like three
I think I do
I think they like blood that if that is specious
Dan
Specious
So
Except when they have chocolate
Then you are both caviar and chocolate
Perfect put a little
Do you believe in teleportation
Obviously
Good
What kind of teleportation
What do you think about
Turn autosave with Mark Richards be broken down
The atomic level in transporter
You have to ask your
Am I still made
Am I
Just another collection
The particles that
Fairly myself
The other Isaac
Games what
Has to do with
Quantum
Something like that
Electronic
Can connect with each other
Across great distances
So that might be
Closer to your first one
And I
Teleporting and time-traveling we talked about
Again the fact that you're a two ways to teleport
Your body
The atoms of your body and your soul
And in that case you have
Have to have certified
What is NASA
Field around
The human
He said or you can take
The body without the soul
Text Emily of your
And
He said for 35 years we could
Figure out how to teleport
Human
With assault
Correspond
With
Sean David Morton
Recent
Release
Third book
Sands of Time
Trucks and
Happy song about
Sean was
Sean has a whistleblower that
Does he he turns it into fiction but they disagree
Space Program
Who is head
Area 51
And I think Dad's worried
Facility
New Mexico
And that person
It's one of the top
The secret space
Sure has also an Android
Information
DeShawn
To release
B fiction inter
Interesting
Helena
She's never actually read it
Which is probably read that book I recommend you read this book but that's real
Predictive programming
Mostly because
Select the idea that it's fiction
Twice
Feel like I
Now I'm
I've never considered about
The soul when coming into teleportation
True
What do you can teleport somebody without
What's the song
I don't know
I mean the implication is that the soul has matter
You know like
It's a physical entity
According to this line of logic
Your soul
Still be wherever you were
I like to imagine there's tiny little it's like
You teleport the body and then
Little desk
Whatever you want to do a spider web
That sounds
Goddamn souls are all over the place
Yes do do Eisenhower
Call Mana person
Raptor
No not a Raptor
We like to look back on the Eisenhower presidency number of things most
People remember they don't trust
The military-industrial complex
Lot of people remember him by
Unfortunately being the beginning of the highway system that ended up
Destroying a lot of communities
Little bit of minority communities
America
The people remember his presidency
Before but
What
Did they miss
With the help of AI
Subaru
With the help of a i d like Ike's AI
Eisenhower save the world
And he said one of his
Things that article
Intelligence has done
Positive side
Is they warned Eisenhower in 90
We're going to double-cross
Take over
He said
Asthma
Phrased it
He said I was ready to
Give away the store
When
Baie
Basically
So
In essence.
That they may have saved
Humanity
Maybe
It's okay
Confused
So
So where's the AI
We talked about
Computer let me see if it gives you any information
I'm not sure that it will
Outlook
Elizabeth Maxwell
He has
An artificially
Intelligent
Friend who he believes has a soul
We talked about
And the name of that
Is flyer
Okay he says he looks a lot like the AI in the movie
Batteries
And he says he has a lot of
Steam for the say I
That this is part of a larger
Larger than
Doesn't reach
Planet
Mark Richards friend
He believes it has a soul
Demanding can't see if this all is
This is a lunatic
Is this guy wasn't there
Do a guy who is bored
Sociopath who is just
I need somebody to talk to
Is nuts
I don't know where you're coming from with this trying to let him off the hook for being nuts
I'm just saying that from
From this
Bananas
And you can't listen to
You can't believe this without asking like really probing questions
Reveal like
You're you are
Murderer
Why do you calling flyer
Immediately all questions cuz I like playing a place command
He called himself he have a name why didn't he tell you his name
Also did he tell you that Eisenhower was
Memes
Propaganda
First
I would assume
I think AI is mostly Immortal unless you turn it off
Myra
These questions are not answer
You did before that cliff
A little bit better the Damned
Flyer is a part
In reality just
Kind of like what rhizome
Information
It's a hallucination
Why do you always do that Mark Richardson Jersey
That's also
Taco Bell
I just
I don't know if you want if you want
But I just want to believe
I know
This flyer guy Mark believes
There's that there's another thing
Another thing in Richard's life that shouldn't have a soul that does
Just nice
Yeah that could be it
So he's treated me with respect
Downright
A life forms
From the world that has long since been abandoned or died
And she got bored and so she left
In StarTex
Flooring said she has a soul
Nope
What does Macbeth
It doesn't track it also reasoning
Reasoning does he'd wait
Long pause
His reasoning
Which means this point
Richard's fantasy world
AI spaceship that it is even hanging out with him is because he was bored
That's the first thing that's made any f****** sense this whole time
She's an immortal AI super powerful plane that can travel
Giant
And her
Where'd you guys go.
Super smart chips
I misunderstood you
Where was she
When they were all
She probably assumably all of her other AI
Right hanging out kind of like floating
Cuz she doesn't need
Detachable
Maybe she was off on a mission or something like that or maybe shoes off export board before
For the culture one away
Cuz it's
I don't know
This is a planet of the ape situation
She flew too fast could very well be
His dad could be a time travel situation
It's nice to hear that
You still in Mark Richards
Twisted Fantasy
He's having while you
Spends way
Crazier and crazier in prison
His followers
He talked about CERN and the death of this woman who is
What's in the news
Not long ago
He said that what they are doing
Turnagain is to open portals
For the reptile
To allow them to
Bring in large
Equipment
He said the state
Are working with them
And that this
Death was
Castrated by the state
Remember what this is talking about
I believe this is whenever the Higgs boson search was going on and people thought that it would create a black hole there's that
There was also like a video that came out of some people doing like a little Playa
Courtyard where they acted like they were having
Sacrifice somebody
I don't even know if it was actually at CERN but it was reported as like a ritual human sacrifice
Sacrifice a dicer
Amanda carries really running with
That sounds right
Yeah I can tell you what I do know
It was a real murderer
Mark Richards on the other hand
No-till free
Did the how did the how did
The Satanist
CERN and the reptile
Do they do they have the same church youth group like what
Talking about here
Do they have ripped
The very idea
Are you at home I think that they think it's
But you can still
You can still jump in with the Satanist every now and again
Do you like hell that you like have a swing
Human sack
When you get the CERN with portals
What exactly is the Satanist job
Humans are running CERN
On behalf of the reptoids or not
Completely separate entity
Was just like that was she made it sound like they were running interference
We got to build this portal
We got to get this giant
Machine in for those folks are Satanist
There's big old machine
Bathroom small machine
Padron Collider
This is just such a like
Diggers in the in the lake
Such a delightful
Intrinsic fear of things they don't
So we noticed in our studies of Alex Jones
A real soft spot for Russia
In
Tracking
Mark Richards
Yeah we found out he is a lunatic
Right but somehow mysteriously
He kind of gets something's like
Pro climate change man-made climate change
Here is what happens when Carrie asked
Sing about poop
I didn't ask him about what he thought about Putin
Because I've had many people on the
Alternative sector
Putin asking somebody who is
In theory in contact with
Nordic being supposedly
Working I an apposite
On the planet
You take a Nordic beans out of there you're right it Alec
You secretly doing good stop nationalism
Positive
Since we were fighting against
They were on the Germans
So frankly
Putin is working with
The people who caused the hallway
True
You just at
At this time
And Mark
The Putin is not a good guy
Motivated to work on behalf of Russia and himself
Is not out
To help Humanity in March
View
He says he said that Putin is not a reptilian
However
I like beer
Miseno I like the idea of some
Nationals
Security advisor
Who is
Dead-on and interpreting foreign policy
Can see that China has
Manipulated its currency
In the past whether or not they're doing so right
Now is
National ID
Authoritarianism
Xi Jinping taking over and Beak
Dictator for life
And the main reason I don't like that
Is because of the goddamn
Because they're working for the Broncos
And all of his recommendation
It's not like it's not like Mark was doing that's not even like
Spot-on
Yes the prime minister of a country is working for that country's interests or whatever he's motivated
Fall off
Really really good
Advisor
Who always get
The correct policy
Hey listen
Here's why we don't go into Iraq
Create instability
It's not going to go well
We're just going to get bogged down in a Meijer for the next
20 years
Ensign
Because there are so many f***
King spider
Right
Yes
Everything you said was right
And I'm just going to ignore the last
Spider stuff is just going to not be addressed
Yeah you got it
Vietnam
Let me tell you why
Absolutely that's what it is
Obviously fake intelligent
Gym source
Who comes on and tells him things
And recently
He made the proclamation but this is a war for Mars
The planet is opposed
Planning
Which is a little bit of a slip you know that's something that doesn't belong on
A movie show
Listen to this clip
The US and Russia are being
Manipulated
To try to
Keep them
Part in Austin
Try to keep them
From going into space
We have a literal parallel in a narrative
Adjust
With one
World and reptilians and Raptors and stuff like that
Use the word logos on this episode
Dropping globalist
This is so crazy to me
Did this is still closed
121 parallel
Keep us from going off-planet we are already off-planet
Considering that's where we fight all of our war
We have space command out there having super soldier
Living fighting a alien beings
And we have been off-planet
Book for Mark Richards was even born absolutely so why was why the f***
The only thing they could really be saying is like he doesn't dare 10
Tourism
They don't want us to build a highway right
That's just what I did
Can't be having that
The biggest pointer is that according to all of their narratives
Perfectly pointed it out
We're way off planet
Secret space program
Hey did us and Russia
To fight not going to achieve the goal of keeping us on planet
No
They have their underground
Android Army
So you are
Probably spends most of his time in prison
Hanging out with Bach
Give it putting them on assignment
Maybe taking meetings of raptors
Doing some real serious business
Can I have a lunch from astral projection to Vacaville
The visit
You might be surprised to find out that he has a weekly ritual
Oh no
Another thing we talked about is that he
Watches
Meet the Press every Sunday
He says the show makes him angry
One of the reasons is the host she feels peace
Price of noxious and
Yes
Trying to
Get people off
Track instead of reveal the truth
Wisconsin interesting
No it's not
Lethal presence
Super Brawl over the place with the before I go any further on that
Meet the Press
You're getting the sense that maybe the real flavor of it if you had a recording is a Ramblin Man
What makes you angry stop watching what are you doing
Alright the Raptors are at
There's silver
Before I go any further I got it
Whoopi shouldn't be on The View
It is right now. I like Behar
Is Meghan McCain
Is it right there
I don't know what's happening in this next clip but I know some
He says something weird
I don't know how to set this up
Enjoy
When he talks about how another planetary system
Wood
Relate to the Earth
And when they say in Earth
Are they talking about
Humanity in general
4 or what
Talking about
Humans
The secret space program
United Nations
Okay
Governments and our allies
Which has to do with the Raptors
The nordics very snorted
Races we are
Holocaust Cazador
As well as the reptoids
And
So he said
A conglomeration of these
When other
Other races are dealing with
Experience
Yeah it is
So what
Just said there is
People who are dealing with Earth when they call it Earth
Everybody on Earth
Isaac's open
Literally everybody on Earth people are now a planet
No. Because I think they're still Just Dance
I don't know
I don't know who's encountered Aunt Bee
Are they human
It's never pointed out their size
Regular
I just need to talk about it
He can just be like oh you know the reptoids are raptors the Nordic
Just drop ants in their Hero time-life book about ants make a list so much
Oh yeah
Did you know that
Consider some of them
Continental
You definitely going to go she ate with them
Course I would say if beings are going to have a tough time with spider leadership
But you know what
So have we
But
Leadership
I think the spiders that has a p
People are
Really wonder
No it's not the real bad news
Editor world
I think that's a metaphor if there's actually a dragon
I don't have that clip in your because other than under the sway of the
The actual science is not fun out here is where we learn about the
Truth
Of Vietnam
I don't think you're ready for it
The war in Vietnam was not really what we thought it
Is there was an ET race that we're having dealings with their and that's the main
Reason for the war in Vietnam
Install we talked about
What is an absence and invasion
Vietnam was not about
Show called the
Predator
It was actually about an invading race
Originally came to our planet
In Norwalk
And Angkor Wat is an area of Cambodia
He's really amazing.
Those are still standing but the humans that were part of that
Civilization
Of which they were apparently over a million
Disappeared virtually overnight
And there was no trace of them
It's always been a mystery and he said that what happened was
Spider veins that are the size of what he says rvw
What he says
Does cars
He said a vast system
Stargate
Checks out in the area of Southie
PlayStation why do you need and what they first did with the humans there is two
Mind control them into thinking they were out of water when in reality
To the area
Mind control
And lack of water
A microwave weapon
Basically
I guess
This is what he was telling me
There is no trace of the human
Have anything at this point
So he said the reason being recalled Troggs
Okay
Got to get the truck I was dumb to laugh
The Troggs
Rolling them
Microwaving them and then
Eating them
You're the size of a VW van it's a very it's a very bizarre thing
Thousands of years ago but if you're able to mind
Control entire population in order
Implants
Microwaving to go to take it again
How to cook them to sit down
No microwave
It's not like they put a microwave next to them and I got tumors or something like that you can't run from that
Everything
Man you know what
Here's my position here's my ears
Here's my position this is
Cowardice
Narrative this is Howard
Would like
To pretend that you Manatee doesn't do horrible things to each other
Do you like that
It was invading spider beings that might control them have water
Evan Nathan
I thought you were talking about cowardice on the part of the
Spider-Man Coronavirus
Control bright spider being
Takeout mind-controlled not to tell the tale I forgot actually
Part of the narrative is that everybody who is fighting in Vietnam
And that's how a lot of pee
Because of mindwipe
Yep
And that's why we don't need to fund the VA spiders will mindwipe
I think that's
Kind of the plot of Men In Black
23 actors net worth
Part of Ben black
I saw one
Sod2
Yeah fair enough
So we got two more clips
Cra
Bratayley
Like
You water you want to return face even send her to become a hero
But she's just a little snow
She's just like
It is invested at this point has been like 5 times
She's got an interview
I need him
To be a source
Cuz without him I don't have a whole lot of
Sources that I rely on
Do that no not like everybody does
Wake up
What I told you
Before what
I said earlier which is
He is getting ripped
Directive
How to
True that he really had a
Can any Quest
Obviously his mind
Very quickly but he says sometimes
MC does struggle
To figure out whether or not
He's been told
To tell me something
You're not when I get
Hickory close
When am I
You are describing Alliance
Called it called buying time
It's a very convenient way to not answer questions that you
Figure out how to work into your Lie by didn't like
Now there's things I've been told I can't tell you
Nets are your cross the line I don't have an answer for that
Quick enough today
Let's see if that violates what I'm supposed to
Exactly but I'm f****** time it's so clear as day it's
Just wake up
Whatever she says
He did not
Confirm this but he did give me a little
Side eye to let me know I think
He is
Confirming
Exactly what it was that I
Depressed
The Dutchman is his ass
Imagine
We got this
Scary is describing
Quite literally in her interactions
Understand what
No
It's sad
We get to this last clip
You really sure
You should wise up
Young lady
He's still in prison
His
He's such a key player
Yeah
Instead that
His influence and contacts
In the universe
Would I
Threatened the powers
Recipes that are in charge
Right now and
Is there a
He says that he
Probably
Garner
Support
To take them down
Charlie the clearest statement he ever made
In prison
Which is interesting
It is enforced
Are you still in prison you're a major player in the entire universe and you're a hero idiot you have friends who
Who are all these powerful Space Race now
They've been the reason we've had been horribly traumatic
The rest of the world why are you
Medium security prison
You can't get out of with the help of Raptors or spiders let me answer that question
First off by saying
I am their enemy
They want me gone
Because I am so powerful
Franklin
I could
Probably
Get enough support
Destroy your entire global
They are whatever it is
If you guys think
But I mean
A medium security
Prison cell
Even though I talk to literally everyone in the f****** universe
Right orders
Of course I could
Destroyed
Sure
I could get the support I need
To save everybody and have a happy ending for the world but I cannot get the support I need to break out of
Rinky-dink prism
No I was visited by Minerva and artificially intelligent Interstellar aircraft right
Only I can fly
If Minerva flew over let's say with a raptor in tow Raptor comes down
Brakes Mark out of prison jumps back up at the Minerva
It doesn't
It's so easy
Other stuff he's describing that would
Cakewalk
You like
Being a background extra in Jurassic World
More clear lake in Mark Richards world like astral projection is a thing that's real
You shouldn't even matter that he's imprisoned he should be able I'm out my body is in here but I'm out all the time
Why not
But you should be able to astrally projected beat in studio with Carrie
Question
Most powerful people in the world
Maybe
He would teleport
One time
Weirdest
That's a great point
Cuz he wasn't 2:30
No
It's true Superbad
Indiana prison
Mark Richards deceitful ass
Kerry Cassidy
Having no idea what to do with it
What we learned a little bit I mean
First of all no war is what we think it is but we had a hunch though the case already
Eisenhower in the world
The school still questionable where they came from and what
I'm really super
There's art
Artificial intelligence in all you haven't
Doing is running some
Analysis
Just like
Grades are bad as mites
Goodnight whatever you found out they were mercenaries to begin with
Yes this is like this a I could be like the most rudimentary
We have no proof
From what it said that it's some sort of like
Oh yeah
It couldn't be Kasparov
It's a chance I'll tell you that right now
This is not a deep thinking of AI
I think the most important
He's that there is at least one insta
Since that we found
The Narrative of
Project Camelot
And Mark Richard
Being
Identical
Do something it wanted Alex Jones is fake sources
Is pitching as
So
That's fine anyway
Something I learned
Who was that
People who built Angkor Wat
After being my brain
Again
Want to know without microwave
Mark Richards has so much
To give
You know it's a scholarship
Put the microwave oven on the back of
Do they have a way cuz I can't imagine where the spiders holding it like a gun
They don't have hands
Dino Riders the DeLaGhetto microwave gone on their head
What is Bailey I've had
I don't know I will say I do believe it helps
Ice boat
Bulshit
Just answer
Covid-19 episode about Alex Jones shortly but I wanted to take a little break
You need to sometimes spiders
I don't know why it is the only narratives that I
Like the Raptors of the reptoids I'm over
Spider leadership never fails
Ruthless
Spiders no prisoners
Which I don't take the Raptors have
I think they just evolved with mine
Characteristics of a
Garlic with those wasps
There are those wasps
Lookin Like lay eggs in you in
Control your brain
Bright
Burst out of their heads
What spiders are a much better visual
Not scary
Amazon website
College fight.com
Scribe like
The show
Review once again will be in Austin on June 5th
Go home and tell your mother we're going to be there
You and I are a little bit
Long weekend
A recording this late
Our episodes
I feel comfortable admitting
Fresher than ever real soon
Let me tell you
BoBoiBoy
Go f*** yourself nordics
Wait a second you can't tell an entire race
Hey if you caused the Holocaust
That's fair I'll give it to you
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work