Holding
Alex
Kristen color everybody
Music sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit
Yes sir
Say you had never seen the show before
You were just
Walking down the
Mistreat suddenly you will cost
You yourself
What about a lot about
Who's a very nice
He's cool with a good time together nose
Nothing about Alex is that a positive or negative
And therein we find
Fun
Exactly doing over the April 23rd
18 episode
And I'm frustrated without stressing the present
Not the show we get to this point over and over and over right now
Over and over and over again
Where it's like I just hate him in the present
And I can't deal with it anymore
And we are right about there
So I don't know what you're on about a three-month cycle I think I'm bipolar in terms of Alex bands is present
I still can enjoy him in the past
Pac-Man
It's not bad as a couple of new donors
Bilqis transition
I still got that game down 3 p.m.
Newtownards
Thank you so much George
To talk about style is wanting
Robert
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much Robert
From the jinx
One of the most common names
Give a shout out to
I'm a policy wonk
Someone someone sodomite sent me a bucket
Rebecca
Stamos anymore
Sirius Black
Doubt
Actually don't know if it's true but I assume it is the truth
Injured reserve
Is that is that a
Took their donation technocrat level
And we appreciate it very much
Don't get mad and tell your brother someone sodomites
Jesus Christ
Codeine
Nothing makes me happier than
What
Cody Cody Rhodes wrestler in brother of gold dust
Stardust
It was not very interesting
Of his brothers are
And son
Cody Rhodes as Stardust and his brother was gold.
Goldust for like 20 years and then
Cody's character Stardust
The American Dream Dusty Rhodes
I don't want to hear any stories about how he
Terrible man because it seems very very
In that era
Any news about Chris Benoit
Since 1997
I've good news to care about his dog
Maybe I don't know
I might be referencing something I don't even understand
Jordans
Episode
I'm sick of this s***
I got no time for him
Blowing hard
Forever about his
Oppression
You're doing your second tour and mam
Smithfield right now you're lost
Turned on Trump
I thought I was going to get back to my wife stateside
They said no circuit back on the road 130 country
I just
I'm just sick of it cuz now he's doing he's back to the exact same sycophantic
Trump is a great man
Already
It is
But then beyond
Issue is just the mat
Let down like I think we would have been a lot
It's it's like it's like we weren't we were at this level of just like it you nothing is
Going too far in either direction
You throw that
Movie that
Tremor in there and all the sudden
For the high we had whenever he was gone there must be an equal and opposite
I think part of it I have to wrestle with my
It's my fault it is because my brain wants a narrative
You know like
4 storyline
Reference like a
Heroes Redemption
I want there to at least be a third Act
You know a repeat of the second act
You know there is a crisis but not come through
There's a month there's a coming to Jesus moment
Where he's drunk on are telling us Donald Trump
Are we think there's going to be certainly No Redemption
When is available today
Drives me nuts
Oh and then the other thing is half the goddamn show with him just complaining about getting sued
I know that I complained about this and predicted it
Months ago where you just going to go with like
A boring angry Lenny Bruce mode
It is this like
Late-career Lenny Bruce angry
Talking nonsense
It's so much
I'm oppressed
These people are suing me are going to undo the First Amendment
It's like dude
You don't understand these are the consequences of your
Misguided or not
Of like you do probably deserve that
Some sort of a consequence
The Cal spiritual you deserve all the worst things that you could bring
Exactly
It's like
It's the stationary version of bang my head
Against the wall cuz I'm just sitting here watching this shiting like
I don't care
Yeah I don't care
Ain't even tell for me to get it up for new stuff
You know like
We're going to get into it here in a minute but like he talks about Kanye West
I can't get excited about it
Let's jump into some of these clips
This isn't to say that the show is going to suck or anything like that we have some fun
Talk about but like
Yuma
You might find me back in
For a bit
How do I get to take a little break mirroring
You're bitching about how boring
I'm sure he's feeling the same thing you got going off
On the same boring now.
This is a man who drives
Tomorrow's my birthday gift to myself a reminder
What is a sort of drying.
I apologize
Does Jeremy do not have enough
Text drop from today's episode
GameStop so
Just do this
Here is the first clip
Decides to start off the show
Is Renaissance
The Renaissance
So not
What
OSHA
Jordan klepper
The house the Senate
Yeah
What's a good point
They don't control the college's almost to a college
Are globalist and socialist
Really
Elon Musk
Amazon Fire
Masquerading as leftist and neoliberal
Incontrovertible
Neoliberal
Since becoming first lady
As if Michael Obama wasn't a polarizing
Do you like that
Just joking
He realize I did everybody have to
To be mean to me he kicked into one of his old B
Michelle being a man
Just joking
I wanted another lawsuit
I understand it's the season of the Lost
And I could probably
I don't know
I think that one
Might have more legs than a lot of these other one
That could at least be something
Again it's just like Jacqueline
This is like Tim Allen going to an underground shelter hours like
Reason why Melania isn't on a bunch of covers
Michelle Obama
And here's a couple of the Reese Michelle Obama ratings Joy
And is it amazing
Configure who is work
Hard to make the world a better place
A Milana is a
Trapped woman held inside of an ivory Tower waiting to be pushed over in the
Then she will fall and crumble before our very eyes that's an interesting Theory I can't prove that one way or the other
Spiritual truth
It turns out I know she used to be a model
Relationships
Remaining
With a lot of the people who are in the fashion industry
Gore involved in dressing people
Recovers
A magazine
Possible if there's some sort of
Inner workings of the fashion world but I have seen that
Speculated by
There's also the issue of
Right after the election she was into the cover of Vanity Fair
And the
Picture that they ended up using was of her with
The string of diamonds
In her treating it like it was
Some people to f*** off might have a little at that might be a bit of a let them eat cake
Might not be her pad
But whatever bad will that game
I certainly still lingers
Then beyond
Michelle Obama was
Incredibly active with a bunch of
Causes that she was in these magazines to help promote so she's on the cover of like women's health
And and stuff like that because
She is interested in talking about dietary issues
Melania Trump
His chosen
Cyberbully
Really doing anything though
Like I feel like our only goal right now is to not spend any time with Trump
At all that she has spoken of like this is an issue I want to I want to work.
Is it your doing nothing and your husband is a big old boy
If you want to start with
The big cos
Starting your own
That's all I'm saying if you want to stop cyberbullying
You're getting Cyber Bullied and Bully by your husband
I want it I want a divorce
August 8th in Fresno
Oops I would love it
I think a lot of the president loses half of his divorce
Love it because of that all those I can
Public
Wheeler had none of that headache
But like I could a lot of the Goodwill in
Magazine covers
Michelle Obama was on
It.
Trace back to advocate
In things that people wanted to talk about and I don't really know if Melania is involved in all that much
The people find that interesting very interesting person to talk to and be around Michelle is
She's a boy
Brilliant woman and that's not to say I don't know you don't know that you don't know her
You don't know that I don't know that
See the blue paint their own perception
That's what you picked on her with her blank canvas
Outside
Wheeler nights
Humanities training
Teaches me that she is
Married
What would you call it
Comfort
Sure perhaps
I'm guessing
Since you're a gentleman likes hip-hop
Yes you've been keeping up with the
Bears in the world of Kanye West
Good God.
Real life I want his
I wanted album
He's been tweeting a lot of sort of vague pseudo-spiritual self-help
A lot of it is very specifically to the vi
If you spend any time and sort of like
Theosophist circles are
Psychology
Human potential
Typa groups or anything like that you'll recognize a lot of these like these sentences that don't mean anything
What's a pound
Question everything was one of the
Go right right dancing is
Is only
The appeared that is the appearance of depth
Without doing any
To get there
Candace Owens
How she think
The border into the number of time
I don't ever
Who gives a f***
I've been saying this
Read a couple of
These articles that are like
Kanji
Who cares
Is what his brain does
Irrelevant
Don't
If you don't want to give you your just supporting him
Beyonce
Absolutely should have won that
Taylor Swift album all time
I'm so anyway here's Alexei
Not care about black
People so he's got two under
Agree with that
Sensor for forgotten about
About that tho
Newfound feeling
Coronado 23rd
Kanye West
I don't like him taking those words the Kardashians
Trumpet
Activist
Braces black
Lewiston
So you just now that I see him doing this
Specific clip you said
All I knew about was the Kardashians I didn't really know anything about him
Intelligent
To do with the Kardashians I'm out
Guilt
You're supposedly a guy who's like
Deep into truth
And you're admitting on Ayers
You engaged in a game of guilt-by-association
Without knowing anything about
Now what so I guarantee
Also a bit like I've lived with music it's free music
He said was blood on the leaves
I hear that song
It just comes across like 10 Rugrats or whatever
Zygarde
Go fuc yourself
What's your favorite
Favorite album
How many maybe heard Jesus walks
Maybe right
I don't know
I would guess probably have a
Alex only listen
Who's the music that's on brand
Probably just that
You could be worse
Yeah
Call Twitter of post
Like there's an article that Alec
The Illuminati
Consistently said I don't think that's very interesting as a receipt
Here's a clip of Alex talking about Kanye West
Austin June 20th
There's a special place in hell for these people
Kanye West
So before we get into what he's actually going to say about Kanye West
It's really funny
Cuz right before this he was in a big rant about you too but other album got put on everybody song
He was pretending that everyone got charged for the album
Goddamn is Robin a million
Not that it was a free
But they didn't charge everybody
Charge anybody
Special place in hell for these people
Send me 25 million
Pimping
Overland
You stupid
What
Look into Kanye I was just watching in State University
Didn't like him course I did think he was a slave master who is selling out fellow Africans to be
Just because
Such a f****** idiot
This is why it's so frustrating is his Dance all day
But it comes back to all the time is it
It doesn't matter
No one cares Alex wants to even address the fact that
He's you know
I think the most important piece of it is him I never looked into it and then you say
Extreme
Thing against him
That means that you need to work harder side looking before you talk about them
The part about it like you said negative
The past
Easily get around that by being like the Illuminati
Or something like that
Sign
Fun to see it's like
The thing about
This and then think about the way that everybody reacts to Kanye is b*******
In terms of celebrity culture
So many people
Blow In The Wind immediately
Just like
I'm like so he's an a****** now forever
Right
Yeah
I don't
It's like it's like
Another life
Pablo on me is like Alex
Complains about people
I like being involved in
Celebrity worship
Celebrity culture all the time
Because a guy said he likes
Trump or something
It behaved in such a way as to make it appear that he likes drops
Again I agree with you
Who get this
Well then on the other hand I don't necessarily want to
Supported artist
Two A's
A black white supremacist
You know if you're supporting Trump as a as I previously
Stated at this
Chances are
Percent wipers
Now we have to our sympathizers at least at least
I don't know man
I don't know
Later in the episode
Listen to the show
Because
Why doesn't take anywhere good
First
Saw him like sort of tiptoeing back to
To Trump like a little scared boy
What we were
I think my take on it
Just get back to shiting on Hillary
That's what you do all the time you need to talk about Trump
Just go back to that
He spent a large portion of the show going over speech
Did Hillary gave
That's going to be important later
But I'm talking about how Penn State
Is a hotbed of demon
Because of Jerry Sandusky
Sure there is a
For sure
But that does not mean that there is a hotbed of
They just mean
But there was a institutional problem
Where they did not address
Things
Appropriately at all
Because I care too much about the
Football program
Liberal Liberal
If they control the speed
People who are trying to point out that
You hired a job
If by liberal you mean protecting
Natural interest
In the form of the football team
Then I would say
But
Thesaurus has multiple sources
Devil worship
Penn State is heavy heavy heavy heavy heavy heavy heavy devil worship
All the ties
So you so much time
And linking them to Clanton
And Hillary Clinton
Cuz
Speech therapy
The punchline today
Comes about an hour later
I just noticed
This morning
Dot-com
Wasn't that wasn't
The final shot
Weather problems
Not associated with that
Journal for writers readers
Is an annual return on the features fiction poetry
Conversation criticism memoir
You stupid a******
You don't ever talk about it
I appreciate that at least
But that might be again a function of he knows he's getting sued all over the floor correct
Just like
Don't assume
LeQuint 15-20 minutes of your content
Is going to be linking Hillary
To the demon
That you see I paints date because she's giving a speech at Penn State
America find out what you're talkin about
It's so true
Iowa
It's just
I just always get lost
Did not hyperbole whatever
Whatever you say
There in 10
Okay
How much is that though
What's the lifespan of a white Christmas
Where you go to the coven once or twice a year for that
Facebook
But having heavy
What is that
Probably drink
Can blood adrenochrome
Daily Record
Conversate
Everything we're talking about is not real
You know today
Gets really frustrated
Yeah
Let's jump it I want to see what it would be like if this made any sense I want to get in your mind
You can put all these
Pieces together
Well the same time ignoring
Plot holes
Yeah
With this
I don't have to listen to it all day everyday
Melania Trump isn't on magazine covers and that is proof that the Patriots
Don't have any
That's not real
That works
Alex loves Kanye West now because you said something
That indicates support of trump
That's not that's not 10
In the past history
Vectren
Alex makers correct
GraceWorks Correctional
America
Real
Oh I just got the
The name wrong
Like what else is Panamera
Maybe in the future suing him
Light some incense
S8 note
Now that Alex is being sued about a lot of the stuff that he has been stupid about in the
I think it might be starting
You see a little bit like
I had to cover some of my base
Maybe I've got to at least bring up my narratives about what I did in
Certain
Yeah we know from covering it that he got a letter from James alefantis
Ping pong Pizza
Which was the center of
Pizzagate
Brouhaha
And Alex was threatened with a lawsuit
Apology
About it
On this episode
I want something I want to talk about that a little bit
Pakistan DC
Focus in on
Pizzeria
What was really going on
That sounds doesn't even make sense
That doesn't track is a like a
Grammar
But
We've already gone over that John bowne report that Alex did
We already gone over him check it out
No it's not
Even further
Two more times
Do you think he forgave his real number 2016
We're one of the first troops Bragg
I don't know
Did I just said what is this
Photos of kids
Images of people
It it's
Because in November of 20
He didn't have anything
Interfere really about being sued afraid of is the internet being like you.
Cover this
You missed the boat
Much like we're experiencing
So you didn't want that perception to be out there so he's bracket
First to cover
Now I said
I said is this drug stuff but even the way he's saying that he saying
It is about drinking blood
Next Quest from
At meetings about drugs
Nah dude
Turned out blood
Which is worse
It's be fair Alex thinks
Drinking but Alex is very specifically link
Hbic
Symbols
Pedophile stuff
To the logos
The pizza place
Which is one of the big Cornerstone
Of the online
Gerber about pizzagate
I'd like to comment
Pizza
In Washington
I'm just like
I don't see how you see anything else
Okay that sounds pretty bad when you look at the logos
Law enforcement
Now pedophiles
Traffic
Images
On businesses connect
Well
You know
I don't see how anyone could get
Symbols
Envy logos for these businesses arbitrarily connected
John podesta did have
My God
Yeah I mean this is very specifically talking about
Pizzagate at being a part of these
These restaurants now. Before you before you get to the guide one more clip
Where Alex
It's like you can't he
You can't undo this
But you can't walk
Canvasback
I can't just say something for myself
There's there's art
Weather shoving
Children in the women's
You were talking over
Like saying
Stop
Himself
I'm going to go to wash
Did you see to these pizza places in research at like it
Bohemian Grove
We already know Bohemian Grove is him
Just doing the f****** b******* the bus
Lying about everything
But like
There's a kind of revelatory looking at that phrase though is
If you say something
Try and see something
Like it's going the wrong way
Right
Right that's a good point.
It's Alex Jones School of non journalism
Can't handle
Fit he is doing a good job
He was just trying to lead us on
What you really said is weird
Easiest to lead on
In the
Remember who his version of what happened with Obama's birth certificate
But you remember what he was like
They put out the version
Kenya
Because they knew
That we couldn't resist
The idea of
Invalidating the American Miss of a black president putting reality
That Kenyan birth certificate was just
Cover up
Did his dad is Frank Marshall Davis a contract pornography
Where is weirdo
We get tretinoin are so easy to trick
Because we want things
Real so bad
I don't even know what to call this stupid people
If somebody says it's true we will believe it up media
Andover Andover Andover
Over again
Examples of
Just getting trick
Controlled and s***
You're not supposed to say we got tricked
Cuz then you review
Was Paul Joseph Watson
DM from a guy who told him
Bulshit
Tapes of trump
Come out
Call Joseph
To print
I told Alex and Alex
Did special report about how Donald Trump
He likes to have a good time
Like to see joke
Sometimes
It might save some dirty words
Respond
Do some stranger fake account and then later told the Press
I didn't realize
Is it they were actually going to
Screenshots and everything
Trick a lot
Easy to trick their stupid people
Severe is an article just came out the Daily Beast
About Paul Joseph Watson
Haha headline of it is Paul Joseph Watson
Sun is going to steal Alex Jones's crackpot crown
Pacifica Longos yr
Flout
Here's the thing
Alex's perspective on it is
I think on one level kind of right
Maybe
He's like they're trying to sow dissension in the ranks
Possibly giving away giving away your hand there Alex
The possibly like someone's motivation of like trying to build up home
Send to make Alex jealous
It's possible I don't know I don't think that the editorial position of The Daily Beast
Daily Beast
I read that article
And it's really interesting because
Daily Beast
Who is called the base
Aleister Crowley
Crowley was a beast on The Daily
There's no doubt
So
I read the article at one point
And most of it is very even-handed
Barry there's a there's a quotes from Alex's ex-wife
Talking about how Paul Joseph Watson
Paytakht on early on
What time do you think $5,000 a month is a ton
For writing
Yeah $60,000 a year
To get gas
He immediately was like
Out to put the rest of the article is like this person went to Sheffield
You want this this reporter went
Sheffield
I was trying to
Talk to people who knew him
And most of the actual interviews that they got from
People were like
Nice guy I don't know
Really boring
The only things they were able
To like really refute
Is that in an interview Paul Joseph Watson said that he grew up on a council
Allstate which is like share government housing
Absolutely
Now so that's the only thing that the rapper middle class
Like it's not a hit piece at all
Except for the fact that it's like
He works without
That's the only part of its negative
If he was a nice guy when they were growing up when he started
Cuz he does say
He knew that the story was going
Come out and that the reporter was asking people about him
And so he took to Twitter
And started revealing stuff that does not come out in the article Twitter
Tell Alex
But David Icke was the one who actually woke me up
As we started watching David videos
Reptilian worldview
Because he says that he watched
Some documentary
About alley
Okay if that's what made him want to get
In touch with Alex
And the interview Ronson about it and he's like
That because he's like
I don't understand how anybody could watch that documentary and then want to go talk to Alex
Very clearly that he lying
I think he's like I don't understand
How's the Motorola watch that in
Paul Joseph Watson
Together
Like if you watch that documentary in your life
I don't know I can't
I can't understand the motivation
He's probably not a reptile
Jon Ronson on together
You ready to talk
Reptilian
Oh no
Is it Paul Joseph Watson
Coming out
He got on Twitter in and out
Probably going to come out but I got kicked out of school cuz I was drunk and high all the time
Alright
It did not come out the article
Reportage
I like
I like it whenever the subject of it is clearly in the universe
Reviewed by
She's going to use there's just a weirdo
Because Alex
Is bad about this
Daily Beast
For one thing because
Bucheli talked
Does not like to meet
Yeah it's true
The idea that
She was talking about the inner working
Infowars
Back one
She was bald
He's kind of mad about that
Is she still a part-owner though
Not anymore
The way the shell companies work
It's hard to tell like where the money
Cuz she was
As I recalled last time I was looking into the corporate structure
Owner of
Free Speech test
But then there's
Branching off from that like
Infowars Infowars Health in
Infowars life
There's there's a bunch
Two different places
I don't know
I'm not a bit
Attorney I have no idea
Everything divorce for like 3 years
Is because
It seems to me if you are part owner
Forward part owner you didn't get hit with the same and EA
So who knows
Alex
Because he literally
Control what it is she
You saying
She doesn't have the
The same ndaa that so many of his former
Employees have been apart of
The divorce a word spitballing
Constructive for us to
Gas oven
It's possible that like a condition of alimony
Something like that
Cuz you don't
Reveal inside information
So I don't know
That's what I'm saying I don't know
I don't know I don't know any
That's what I'm saying
And I don't want to be like Alex talking about Kanye West
Open 2016 make stuff up
They'll be starting with the Kardashians
The Daily Beast article
Super pissed off
About it
Crowley but then there's another reason
I'm looking for men better than me
I'm looking for women looking for people
Lightbody Craigslist classified ad
No credit
Knuckledraggin
I called his government's listen intelligence agencies
Oratory
Just a fact
Joy
Manipulation
You just started
I
You ain't doing that
David after that but it was really boring
The article didn't compliment
This article about
Someone else right
Say great things about you if you are going to do an article about Paul Joseph Watson eventually taking over
Alex Jones
Spend the first I was a 3/4 of it
For discovering the man who was the plaintiff
Right here
Story
Man after God's Own Heart discovered
Probably
Tremendously Patty
Yeah like this is this is next
Level
Finding Owen
We know how we found Owen Shroyer
Hayden's not great
Right
The next
In Shroyer
Stupid
Stupid f******
Compatible
What's going on on this
How about that
You didn't talk about that
When car drives on the wrong side of the road
He's going to cry
Coco Baby
French
He smells too nice
But at least he is sort of understanding his own impulses
And that is that like
You rightly criticised
The Daily Beast
Alex Jones brain work
Trying to make that happen
In recognition of
That is what I would think
A+ about supporting
Is negative against me which is
Holyshit
It's not a terrible
Because clearly Alex only hires people who aren't
Shoot for the crown
I don't think he has a choice
So speaking of income
2B other lunatics
Alex
Speaking of another lunatic
We covered
Zach
Intelligence source
I picked him up and then he had to go to Morocco
Right
To the audience
Alex Morocco to get out of the states
Because it was too hot
Interviewed Zach from Morocco he's like
Very weird
A man's accent said about your crazy
Alexa dementia
Crazy b******* about how they were shooting from
Can helicopters in Las Vegas
This is a war for Mars between America
Ice Cube I believe when Alex was talking about him
He thought that HR McMaster ministration though he'd been fired at least a week or two previous right
The bunch of indication
This guy is not
Legit I believe he's actually running a hardware store
Probably not
So on this episode on the 23rd
They do it again
I don't know how else to put it they just do it again
Now play the audio side-by-side overlay the
Go to see if they break and come to much of a character that Alex
Who's playing it out in real time
Abu Dhabi
I am.
He already texted me and security
Cell phone
I will try and get them on the phone
Alex says he's based out of Florida
He's Baytown Florida that's doesn't make sense either
No none of it makes sense
Nothing nothing to make
Sense but I believe I believe video of command is in Florida
Colorado Colorado Springs
Get the fuel from Zach that he is in
Very
Very independent
Improv troupe
He's just trying to get by
For the last time he was on that we listen
He had to finish the the interviews like
I got to drop my lunch break
This is been good warm-up fabricate your audience
He's doing vocal exercises on the show
Might as well be
But red leather yellow leather that's red
Play any of him
It's not
If it's something like really really fun we play it but it's
I'm so much like I'm very very
Convince
30 tall
And I don't care messy release play boring not real
On the Shelf
So there's no actual clips of him
But the context
David all is really funny
Zach is allegedly being held
It's in Francisco Airport
Who want to look through
His phone
External hard drive
Still able to text Alex Jones
And tell him
Montague
You get one text to get wolf bow
The premise was that you supposed to be on in the third hour
He was going to have an interview and called in the third hours
Finality
Detained by
Insecurities
He might not be able to make that interview but then he gets out
From my homeland security impound
Or whatever
And it's somehow able to call Alex Jones
Coup
Apparently why they held him is because he keeps talking to Alex Jones
Which rice immediately afterwards though he is
Rights calling in the bird
He's now on the phone with Alex
Hey look I got to go I'm going to I got to get on this flight
You would have been on the flight
During the third hour interview if you hadn't gotten
What are you talkin about
No matter what happened
Whether he got stopped by Homeland Security or not
The plane during the third hour when Alex was supposed to be interview again
Understanding his timeline correctly
Flagged by Homeland Security picture of Most Wanted
Early 1800s Wild West
Bring in
We got to take a look at your funk but you sir
You are a government agent
You know the law
Your phone and we can't get in there
The FBI
The FBI is only 50 minutes away
Always always
Gmail
50 suits with the fur
They try and unlock the phone they can't hours
Surprisingly enough good thing.
Good thing
Got there 3 hours early the FBI
Recognizes that he is a flat and then says
And you know what we can't get it
Get on it back
I don't know how the inner work
Intelligence
We're concerned you were giving privileged information
Into a blowhard talk show host
Right
They probably wouldn't let you text
Play Homeland Security and the FBI
It seems like
That would only be
Something that occurs to
Look
We hate to do this we under
Need to bring in the back row
We got it we got to call the FBI
You're clearly a
You're above our pay grade
Any likes
Okay cool can I get my phone to text
Whomever I want with no oversight whatsoever
Yeah
I get the most
It is pretty incompetent
This just seems like a fantasy
Open Audible
Kerry Cassidy this is like a story being played out in real time
Huh
Have you ever seen the movie Red
There's one more thing I want to bring up before we get to it one more clip left
And that is it Alex's
Screaming about an hour
Mind control everybody
From
Black cell phone towers
I need like
PopularMMOs
And so I look for that I look that up I look that up
Groundbreaking articles
Popular Mechanics
For real article from the 19th
Curtis Bolton
Is the name of the journalist
About likewise
Supremacist groups
Federal law enforcement
Right
Either
Uncontrolled response
Accidentally contained
Zip file
That was called emfa
Song the human body
What
Attached
The same time what happened
I have no idea but
Images of this
Supposedly
Depicting
Psycho elect
Weapons
These are not can
In terms of
Viability
Viabill
Also just
It seems like these are either ideas or they are files
About someone else's ideas
Like as a write-up or something like that
And even this article
Federal government has absolutely experimented with mine
Control in a variety of method
But the documents here do not appear to be official
Even though
Even the PlayStation Alex's making is like
It's probably just something we got put on there accidentally
Could be
In order to
Limited Hangout
Seriously
And of course if you have Mike
Control you could just make them not take
Seriously
That also
I feel like the moment you have mine
Control over cell towers
It's already over
Since I can control your mind everybody
Cell phone
Oh okay we could go over
Coverage map
What are we talkin about if they had Mike
Control over cell towers
I mean we could go over we could go over some of this stuff that like what they this
The images claim that UK will do to you literally everything
What do you got
Forced orgasm
On your foot
This is Cal backpack
Reading and broadcasting thoughts
Controlled dreams
Rubber baby buggy
Artificial
Not organic
Artificial tinnitus
Is there just playing a high-pitched
Without cause I would
What do you mean without cause
I don't know what this means and there's a weird star next to microwave
There's also this one's and quotes
Maybe this one's in quotes
Paradise
Okay
Figure eyes are closed
Forced caffeine fetal
I don't know what that means
Whatever
I'm not super charm
I want all of those to be real
Microwave
Is the most terrifying power a government can have
We've all experienced
Difficult to reach
I believe the show
Throughout I've expressed that I'm sick of Alex
This is bulshit
And most of it does have to do with
You lack of story progression
And the hard-to-reach a
That you had for the
Holidays
Yeah for sure.
So probably stop
The middle here in there
But his last clip Alex
Is discussing his blow up
That Friday
Last Friday
He had
Look up a problem
Timeline doesn't work out
He seems to be calling booze food
It's just your standard Alex Jones
Cowering out
About something big
Because he knows like
Through with turning on
Maddie
Days ago. Last Friday before last because
Emotional
Email
That's not true
So I
6:30
Watch old movie or something
F*** you
F*** you so really what this is is a react
Listen to the death
No
F*** you
Not what you were watching
Seattle
What's the most wholesome thing I can come up with Old Yeller
Old Yeller
I'm a good dad
My daughters are sitting there in my lap everything
I don't know bathroom
And
Looking at the phone
Already
Family is
Marshall from
The 19th
It's not Alex Jones's family
April
Business
This is ludicrous the only simulator
Sorry I'm sorry that was a solid move that's
Jordan Bordeaux
Cedar Lake
There is not a lot of by the way
Pittsfield
No problem
I was in the bathroom taking a look at my phone
Your phone
Use one of these
Dirty socks
Clean the wine off my keyboard
Georgia
Repairs to my laptop
Paper towels
I'm sorry I'm sorry I lost it all
I see Trump
Go to my dad's house
That's his way of like trying to get around
He wasn't going to
Studio-x and all of the
People to go to this.
It was on the way
That's his way of trying to
To get around
Is ex-wife criticism that he was drunk driving with his son in the
Yeah I know he was doing
I got MI
IDrive
Before our lives
Thumbs up
Venting
So there's that
Dream where you not weird enough
Don't put this out there let's start again
Start again in play start it
Real bad that are bad this looks pretty.
Interested to know
Furious man right now
Fascinated by the idea of being on Rob Deuce basketball team
Thrice probably kids
Good 90s
I don't think I don't know man baby
Abdu is probably like
As a person
Speculative we have speculated that he is perhaps the Puppet Master behind
Lexus conspiratorial in
Like a version of Illuminati
Yeah that's not true
Brian just also happens to work 4 a.m.
Vicious white nationalist propaganda
I forgot to eat better
This is what we're really doing
Control most
The emotion got to me
Emotional
If you're talking about
Your presentation what you did
Al Green
Aubrey
Is not fake
Top-level analysis
That is
Is a moment of insight
So where you at
This
You know what
This satisfies off Mikey
Curiosity
You got you got the full spectrum everything make sense
I accept
This as
Let's meet up
2 hours before the show I was sitting around with
My wife and my loving family
Wanted
Syria was a false flag and I took a piss and looked at my phone
Trump is bombing
Emotional
How about Rob duvi
Then I got on here for three hours and then I just kept eating cuz I kept getting more emotional like I mean
Food just really hungry have you seen those commercials
Emil
That I was really full
The crying on Aaron saying the Trump show
Call Ben
You know you have a
Pizza all the sudden you want bread
Seattle
6 over 71 a salad you have a salad
All the sudden you want to tell people that Isis is the world supposed to end
Today wasn't that one of those
Good Times
And then dudes like doing thumbs up looking at me
And I'm like
Looking for men.
Oh no
The show
Has affected my
My laptop is no good
What happened
Is this not recording anymore
Doesn't work
No
So it's still recording but I don't know if I can stop it from recording
Or if I can say
Because now the iTunes I have control
Wow that was weird
Itself
If there's a layer of moisture on top of it sometimes
The signal won't go
All right so I'm going to jump back to this clip
Alright
And Sunday morning
Live feed cameras
Understory is Jose taking us
You know what you really want
Because that wasn't ready to go live
I just screwed up
Boardman
F*** your feelings
Correctly
Main issue
Trump
Striking Syria
With better
Feelings
Literally nothing about that in that entire four minutes
Nothing about the principle of nothing about like
I'm still super against this
A piss me off
You don't add
A million details that are not important to the
The story you know how that always works out when you're lying you're always like
The point in America
The story across
And ramble for 4 minutes creating a dollar
4 minutes
Is interior
To shut it off
Shut off the show
I'm so sick of this b*******
Just own it that you are mad at Trump about the
You still should be
Even if you support him on all of his other
Positions you should still have the balls to be like
Perfect
Things that I said because
Came from a place of me being
Very anti-war
I don't want to
To trigger things and make things even worse
You can spoil you have to stay still giving the good outweighs the bad
You could you could get around V embarrassing stuff
Crying on air
I gave up everything for Trump
You could get around that by doing the emotional I mean I still do by the
I ate a meal
Argument
Sure
Custody hearing was he had a big bowl
Chili that'll happen
I just I mean like you could get around the embarrassing
Stop with your stupid excuses
You could do that
But then you wouldn't have to like
That three-hour presentation
So stupid
I'm so embarrassed
But it does
Have to be now
For him
You could still
This is the third Act
Could exist
That we could
Still be like
Maybe engaged with
He brings nuance
To his
A situation where is like
I do still have those
Principles that I believe in
I don't
Truss Trump
Implicitly
I don't want to just scream buddies great man
Kanye West
Indicating that he's coming this direction or whatever
Doesn't
Not enough for me to
Go back on everything I've said about him over the years
Did there is a version of it that could like
It could be interesting and
This is not interesting
You say the word nuance
In Alex's
Presents he starts barking
YouTube
Unless he's
All of his dogs
But he's ever meant
I don't know if he's ever seen a healthy dogs
That's probably true
April 20
Third
Absolutely
We make it through
Yeah
I literally I enjoy ding
Full-back these like
Clips of him like we are Kanye's pretty cool I like his music
The song called
You shouldn't like that
Thought you said he was a
Slave master in 20
I like being able to point out this pizza
Stop by
It's just
It's not the
Kind of like that is that was all our show was I don't think that would be an echo.
Chamber
To be more and he's not giving us more in the present
We talked about this before we got on air
And this is
Mostly.
Mostly doing distraction
S*** right now
And it's just not
As much as it
Attention-grabbing
Headline-grabbing with
Send all the b*******
It doesn't doesn't get my dick hard
So
I wish I would have
Very much appreciated
Far more
Indep
About you
Is a variant
I love his version of it I don't have that conversation but I thought
I want him and Owen Shroyer to really get into Kanye's catalog
Delightful
Just put on that Ludacris Move b****.
I don't know man
Peace out
I will be
The past
I'll be I'll be looking into a 2000
Pictures holding the cell phone
Yeah yeah
If I'm eating
Step
My birthday yeah you know
I'm intern 34-in like
3 hours
What happy birthday
Back thanks
You're welcome
How do you feel about 30
You got you got a little bit of the Catholic Jesus in you
Jesus go to our website hotspot.com
We also Kanye base articles from the past
Mulatto
How to repost a man I was probably written at least
Tanner 11,000 words about
Webmaster of knowledge
I have a lot of important things to say Do not control
Your content
You know I'm not like I'm not an authority reading about this I let you say some horrible things to your blog
Kanye West review
I might
Underscore fight
Yeah
Where in Austin
We are going to if we do this every show it's going to be a lot
Between now and
Late May supposed to keep reminding until people until
Let's see if that works
I think it's on YouTube
Have you say Kanye West I will murder
I don't care
I mean
Here's what
This is what I'm talkin about
I can't get it up for any of it
You don't know what I mean but like
Who do we have
In our periphery from this
We got
Alex
That's goes
We got Zach
I don't give a fuk about
Seems like an alright guy seems like he's doing the best we can
It's a bad thing to lie to Alex
Appreciate it
Everybody in Sheffield who refused
To say negative things about Paul Joseph Watson
For that Daily Beast article can go f*** themselves
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color