Alex
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
To one of our
Useless Democratic senator the one you're on the warpath today
Murderously terrible
Possible f****** way
How would you explain the show to these incompetent
Veronica monsters that we have elected to lead
Well first I would say a podcast is like a radio show
The first step that describe describe
F*** you. f*** you right off the bat
It was
That's Show Business
I would say that I know a lot about Alex Jones
At your stupid f****** idiots
Spell politician sexual
Pelosi your garbage
Okay
Fuckingawesome
I understand man I understand
Soyuz
Today
Sure where we are going is
Great Dane
The present
BoRics
So for those people who have been following our escapades
Recent
The past
We're going to 2000
Before
Rarely sort of
Because
The episode I was listening in 2008
Not great
And they're on unusable but I realized
June might not be the best place to
Start buddy told me it reminded me that
In January of 2009
To be very interest
Get Alex Jones at takeoff
Specifically we're going to run into
I'm and we're going to
To be deal with it as we go through this episode
Episode of January 7th
Through 9th
You're going to be going on a very interesting roller coaster today
Discovered
2009 Alex
That you are ready for
But there are some familiar pieces and you have contacts dropped
That sort of familiar
Alright
Unforgotten
The business to do
The flavor of via the things to comment then
No I would like a glass
After that he starts laughing as I suggested food
Guilty of the sexual assault lawsuit
The area well harassment
If we give some shout out
Donors I want to say just big picture we recently crossed the hundred donor mark
No s*** hundred plus policy walks out there
Crazy is nuts
When we started the show
Ham
I didn't think they would be
Quite frankly
And now we're at a point where were over 100 people are we lost
Comedian Tommy McNamara's mom donated to myself
Dammit
It's just so great
The show is going
To be able to allow me
U2 live much more stable
Appreciate
It's so much
Everybody
It's life-changing
Support and I really really really appreciate it
Agreed I don't have to buy you cigarettes at 8
Becca about that
Beetle
The love and appreciation
Every time we play these drops
Cuz it's from the heart
Pure
Your beauty
Mark
What's going on out there mark
Thank you so much Mark
Mark
How do they let you donate from
Jail who you talkin about
That's very sweet
If you have
Do not feel like unlike you are still able to donate
This one is not this one is not
Publican jazz on know this
This dude's a great rapper
He's on the road right now with our friends far out
I think they're still on the road I'm really bad at remembering dates but they tore the the Northeast
How much for a spot in the show I-9
Really appreciate it music out there everyone should go check out
They're just no-name to playoffs
If your name is I-90
Thank you so much John
I'm a policy wonk
Amanat Ali Aprilia someone sodomites a poop
Yeah thanks, this is
If I recall correctly
Killed in any phone
I was going to say Jon Arbuckle
Alright
Donation up I thought this was the guy who earlier I references Being John with someone has an obvious Noms de plume
If they use a real cuz we did have a guy who donated as
Finally I give up finally one more shout out
It was
Very very fun
Technocrat
Don't get mine until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Jim
You so much
Your significant other were absolutely fantastic
Absolutely
Navigate to meet folks
It's a treat for us
I believe that spirits
It'll be most of the thrill I think
Secondaries
Well there's a part of me that's like
Real I kind of assumed this is more of an elaborate scam that you are perpetrating on me
Something that you're just trying to make my last days
Is exciting as
All your likes look
What is f l o r
I don't understand
I've got to be a dichotomy
It's great I'm emotionally overwhelmed and the only thing you can do in situations like that
Just keep on moving forward
So weird
Get to it alright
Start on January
2000 dime
And let me say something to you
This works clip is going to blow your goddamn mind
Alright
This is what Alex starts out the show talking about
Have you spend most of the show talking about this
You would never
Expect these kinds of things come out of Alex doing just now
In 2018
Anywhere that we've looked into
Oh no
Portugal
They took the black man off the train
And that they then we're putting them in handcuffs
The man was resisting
There was a altercation
Argument
The officers
Now he's talking about
Argument on the train between
They had the police respond
Psychological
There's
What the f***
It should
Alex Jones
Coming out against the shooting of life
Absolutely
Conversation
Like we should all be like murdering black people
Specifically
Do Alexandra like everything probably
Then that he's against it
Where did this
I almost fainted
Should be every dictator
Who decides which
Statute or Lord
Oscar Grant
Is out party because it was on New Year's Eve
2 a.m. on New Year's Day 2009
BART train
Francisco
Terms of the specifics of it but who cares the long and short of it I did cops try to arrest
Arrest this guy
Had him down on the ground with back
As I understand it looked
I've looked into this and from what I understand
They're trying to handcuff him but he was
Like they couldn't get his hands right so you wasn't to me
Station and there was bit of there was some
End up getting
He at least resigned
We got to have the details.
Somehow that was a better time
What do you mean
I mean at least he received at least he had some sort of
Forward I guess
I don't know
That's all
Was it today or yes
Today that Alabama put up a monument
Victims of Lynch
It's a good thing that that's over
Good thing we don't have to worry about
State-sponsored murder
A jury found the cop
Are Johannes marasli guilty of involuntary manslaughter
They're not guilty of charges
The second-degree murder of all
That's not great
Could have added
And yours too
Wait a minute legible for probation
85%
Great
Vitality
Is she at
That's not great but the end results receive Snowman
BrickTop's
At least
Alex's
Against the cops
And in favor of
Murder victim
Oscar Grant his name
It's kind of weird
Well
Humanizes in Witcher
To do
Is
The case was thrown out
I don't know if that's
Operating awnings it might be the case
Braiding on incomplete information about the the end turn out of this
So I don't know
What's up Jordan now
Still further
Kind of clearly assessing the situation
How much more real way I read the
Message in the chat room Rock nevermind
Sorry
That just change
My disappointment and sadness levels from from
About yay high
To evaluate
I'm going to stop responding
To iMessages I do
Don't fully understand
Alex is against it
The shooting is
Good boys
No that is a big issue
Excuses
It was
May have been
The police officials
Transit Authority
So first of all
That is
The point is good
I told you
Even understand
I don't understand how that
What what
I believe
You lied about it
Weird
I think is fairly philosophically consistent with what Alex pretends to be
You know what I mean
Like he's giving
Credit
Hurry leeway to some extent but still being like
Need to go to prison you lied about shooting a guy
Yeah
The issue there is that it almost seems like more his response
Had they just been like
That guy he would have been like
No I don't think so
No because
If they took responsibility for it then he would be mad if they didn't get
The
Direct consequences
David Mann
I think
Won't that all this is really to illustrate an eclipse not done
2009 is not like cop
But slightly Pro murder
Police officer
Dropped his hand with a gun starts cussing
What the hell what the hell
Because I hate cops
That could be we don't know
Every shot
Books
Doesn't matter you still
You killed somebody
This is crazy
This is crazy from my
Such a departure
This is not
We've been doing this show
For a long time
Almost a year-and-a-half now
Bat
Crazy
Very much so
That's the first time I've
Genuinely
Because there's no part of it where he's trying to blame to the globalist
There's no part of it where you saying he's fake it's fake or anything like that
Anything wild
He's even leaving it over
We don't know the facts
For sure
Is that this man was killed
You got to go to work
There's no there's no
I know he
Murdered
There's no
Globalist
Trick has ended
Actually murder
Bright
It just him
With a measured
No it is like maybe giving too far of a birth
To be like
But he this is where he's operating from
What I would describe as
Acceptable realm of conversation conversation
They lie more often they tell the truth
And bananas
Culture of lying and deceit
What
Hyperventilating
Cops are liars
It's a culture of lying right
What
Wild now
I am starting to believe in the global
Because now
It is very
That some shadowy organization
Murdered Alex Jones
Who at this time
Perhaps was
Okay and then replaced him with the monster that we see mouth as controlled opposition
It's to make sure that he used his insanity is it is ignore it's an interesting possibility
I'd say
Occam's razor
He just started taking
Supplemented my crazy maybe not I don't know it's very difficult for me to figure out like his business
Huge curveball
Yeah that's why is this evolve into the guy we know now
Like this and I just agree with
Agree with dentist even exist
Kaepernick
4 months
People on the field in protest of a thing that Alex in 2009 is super
Where is the problem
Forgiato
This bananas
You if you wanted a ton president if you want to become even more sympathetic to him
Alright this is all it is in the music of Lady intro music
Clayton Vinson packages Adams
Are those lyrics
Castroville
Holy s*** it's like unbelievable
Accidentally
You f****** loves good country
This allows The Highwayman
I don't know
I'm confused
Professional level
Singing along to work
Have a great time.
To do
Yeah
I feel like we started all over again
I have to rewire all of my hatred for Alex Jones
Knowing full well that in the past
He was less of a
Bedtime.
But
Is banana a lot of stuff that
That like
You can trace
Like
Literal
Parallel
From back then to now
Catch phrases that use using 11
I'd like 9 years ago and
I'm still using now like
Coming up in the mainstream media's ratings are down
He has like a philosophy of like if someone's being attacked that probably means they're right
Which is consistent all throughout this timeframe
There's a lot of visit lot of things that are really common but yet
I think with your mortgage
To wrestle with
He's like
You know the future
This is great look at this guy without knowing
I know you've read the stories are all over again
Whatever I want
January 7th
Weekend of January 8th
Nothing else
Not right now I mean what else
Show up on that little spot and that's all you have from January 7th
More about
Boring I just want like some kind of
How did this
Mystery all over again.
Alright
Texas Corridor that road that they're really matter
Stop
Not very nice
He has an interview with a guy named Eric Plumlee no relation to toss Plumlee
Mason Plumlee interview about like the government surveillance
Is it well no but Eric Plumlee is a surveillance lawyer but it turns out his specialty is like
You trying to bug your wifey
It doesn't go really far cuz everytime I try to talk about bigger-picture stuff
Are Plum is kind of like
That's outside my purview
Gotcha with Ray McGovern used to be involved in like a daily briefings for Reagan incest
It's not that it's not really all that substantial like
Kind of endgame stuff
I have never met before in my entire life
Is a lot of stuff and then
Very weird position on this shooting
Google Map
Give me my thoughts
You get right back into that road good half-hour at Lady of the show
Did you have fun
There's less empathy for the victim than you want it for a more anger at the cops
But at least
I'm happier with that it's a road in at least not like anything we
We've ever seen from Alex
And it gets even weirder an alternate universe right now
January 8th gets even weirder
Now I see more of this officer's body language looks like he's completely
He's resigning from the force
What does that mean
Capital murder
Manslaughter
Weather
I'm getting off on a
Because you watched you know
He cites
Black
Holds the shot for about 2 seconds and shoots the guy in the back
Closer video angle
I'm somebody cell phone camera
He looks like
His eyes are completely
You know what you remind me of the
He's not a human he's a literal demon bright again it's a little it's a little cowardly in terms
This is like not allow humans to take responsibility for their actions
The point is right that he watched another video
You can see him citing it
Point behind what he's trying to say
Ban
I don't
That's crazy
30 knots
Did the idea of Alex Jones revising his theories based on new information
Is that okay
Fat is super nuts
Well he got
Crazier with it
Become more
Concrete only
Got
And his beliefs changed
I can't process this in
Information
The only Alex I no understand
Is the Alex
To Double Down
Alex
Who waffles like a little bit
Shrek as the only
Yell cries
Drugs shirts
I'm so
This position that he's taking on the shooting is really wild obviously they're a bunch of
We're rightly mad about the
The situation
Now we get back to
Protests over Bart shooting turned violent San Francisco Chronicle I watched video of it
Permitted crowd
Play begin throwing
Police cars
The police began firing rubber bullets at the crowd
Excuses
You have to punish your officers when they murder people
What the f***
You thought the entire time he was ramping up to talk s*** about the protesters
He was
He was defending that we're justifying it
It's pretty nuts
Dan inosanto I had a whole bunch of anger in the in the holster for today and now it is
You're shocking
Before the show that I had something
I know I don't even I don't even
What is the show if I think
He's he's advocating
For violent but he's Justified a violent response
Stacked
That is again unlawful in itself
V
He's a very least like
Coherently explaining why
Let him know if my people
Rioting is the voice of the unheard
I don't know
Just
Credibly Bazaar
It's weird I'm confused
Neither
So
Time-travel is there
Is there like a
Like if we're if we're going to indulge
Which I think is probably
If we get into a timer
Is there anyway that we can talk to the Alex Jones
From the time
And then put him on a
Completely
Like like just just butterfly
We don't we don't
Just throw a Little Rock and then all the sudden grows into an activist like what's going on
Possible
But
Again I'm not eat his brains
Take a strength
I'm not doing this intentionally
To butter you up I'm playing you the
The clips that are relevant
In the order they come
This
Next clip
Made me smile
What are you doing
This next flip
This is one of the only you are f****** with my head about whenever he listens to Highwayman it's kind of
That's a happy Alex
You can hear a couple moments in this next
Clip where it's like this is
Thirdly happy hour
I was very clean
I like
Mother
That was it
We know you're a drug dealer
Don't forget the cops
Golf carts
Golf courses
Motorcycle
Sometimes
Golf
Astoria
The point is
Radiolab
Roll around in the leaves
That's about the extent of what are you working
That's human they're rolling around
Yeah you're drunk like idiots when you're 13 rolling around at the park and rolling around
No it's not it's a delightful
Adele figure
Mrs. number
Convertible
Easy Mart
Convenience stores on the main Highway by cigarette
Confession
Nemo
We decided we frame for a murder because it surely would have on our lives
I mean you talk about eminent domain
2 minutes or so of him getting wistful
Compelling
Adorable relatable human stories
You see some cigarettes in it's open Kearney
You scamper off and you smoke them
Like that's
So relatable in human and
Cute
Italy
In this world it could be in the movie
American Graffiti
But did you notice there at the end
Like
He keeps losing the point of why
He's telling these stories and he forgets to talk about
Like teachers trying to turn into a snitch or something like that
433 at this 45
If we don't actually know his age
I mean I'm fascinated by the losing yourself incense
Telling me stories
I meant needing to get back on track
View jumps back onto
The cops think we're all guilty
You know like that's where he's mine gets back on
To the narrative
And it's just
To me it's like
Vista brain work better
Alex Jones Show Now into a weird behind the music for me
Because this is turned into example
Like Eazy-E
You growing up
He's having a Carefree happy lifestyle
Getting into some scampi
Chris travels
Get the radio show get there and get the ignore his dad and you give him all the money
To build a little following forms around.
Really living his best life
Spirit Spirit
He pretends he called 911
Singing with The Highwaymen
He starts to get
Obsessed with money
It's all about money to have
Just going to make him happy
Doesn't
The money only
Problems do what's going on my problem Maybe
Current wife right now I don't know interesting and compelling
Used to love that show
Say that you're forgetting
You're going to learn more about 2
2009 it's worth
That's why we went back to
To this date
Specifically to
Relaunch r2000
From this point forward
Is that is because on January 7th
I will read to you from
The guardian article from that very day
Gazprom the state-owned Russian gas group today cut off all supplies to Europe traveling through the Ukrainian pipeline
Intensifying the political and economic crisis that has arisen out of
Payment payment dispute
Between the two country
Amid evidence that people in Eastern Europe are being deprived of heating as the Arctic
Cold Max
Continues
Russia and Ukraine cat
Continue to blame each other for the deadlock
Guess prom accuses
Ukraine or shutting down the fourth and last open pipeline
The country while efficient
Ukraine State energy firm SimpliSafe
Words fail
Russia supplies a quarter of Europe's gas and 80% of this Transit
It's through Ukraine
Has shortages hit Western Europe and intense
EU governments will meet on Friday to
Consider sharing supplies held in storage
So
After this clip
But
Suffice it to say
At this point because of some
Contractual
On January 7th
Russia cut off
Oil Vape
That was
Most
Of the supplies
418 conch
That all
Because of disagreements with
They're they're fine a
In terms of any argument
Public like this
Entertain in like a large-scale
I am immediately going to
To side with the
The person who has the least
Wordy response like
Ukraine's responses like
Dude I don't
Even know what that guy
I talkin about
I'm I'm immediately like yeah Ukraine's right
Words fail us is a strong response
You can't believe this guy
Escalating
A few days prior
Does Russia
Cut off most
Supply
And then on the 7th cut off all of it
What were they doing on the
Hanging out
Just put on the on the 7th
Didn't even bring it up
He says this
And now
Ukraine threatening to
Russia cut back on some of the
They just cut off
People could do either
That's a quick turnaround illustrate how quickly
Talk about it ever again
You're not allowed anymore.
Bring it back up and that's crazy
Ukraine is a Megan
Crane shutting it off
Call
Now we're back in Comfort
Triple territory Alex Alex Jordan with Russia on a literally anything
Is where I am where I am comfortable
Very very strange
Because it's so it's so dismissive
It's so
Like yours a 10-second blurb about this and then we're moving out to pay you can't resell crib
A report from the ox
Shepherd Institute of energy
Studies about the
The crisis because I wanted to get a good handle on what the
The situation was it was reasonable anyway
For Alex
That Ukraine was behind the actual shutting off
Killing Europe
Right
It's from Mystic Sea page report
That the Oxford energy
To put out
Dictionary by the way
Early hours
6th of January possibly the key moments
The crisis is far as deliveries to Europe work
Concerned
On the 5th televised rather obviously staged conversation between prime minister Putin
And gazprom CEO Miller rehearse
All the Russian
Grievances
Against Ukraine
Greenwood Miller's proposal
To reduce the gas flow
And instruct
Open him to inform gazprom's European partners
About the reasons for the ACT
At this point
On the 7th of January
The second more serious stage of
Gas was cut off
Completely two countries in Southeastern Europe where
Which are 100%
Imports to other countries
The Russian and Ukrainian size blamed each other neither
See about moving towards a green
It is important to underline the unprecedented nature of the situation
Supplies to Europe it never been halted
Spencer gastrin
The system was built in
Soviet time
The two sides finally negotiated two new contracts covering
Supply in transit
Which were signed on the 19th of January
Gas was to Europe restarted in the morning of
The 20th
And two days later returning to normal
So that's her
Description
Of what
Get to their conclusion
Russia Ukraine bilateral gastrulation
Does not in itself
Surprise
Many including ourselves of Tina coming
As long ago as December of 2000
The surprise indeed the shock was that both sides allowed to escalate
Disagreements about debts
Prices on Transit tariff
To the point where supplies to Europe work
We shut off
Allowed
The situation to continue for two weeks in the middle of winter
Mysterious adverse humanitarian cops
Before especially Southeast European
We do not believe the often cited desire of the Russian government to use energy as an economic or political weapon
Against European country
Played any part in this crisis
Russia's relationship with Europe
Pendergast beer is and will remain one of mutual dependence
Well you're heavily on Russian gas supplies
Russia which here means both gazprom and the Russian
Realized
Relies heavily on revenues generated from Europe
By contrast
The critical Russian
Decision to cut back deliveries on the 5th of January
Russia did it
Wasn't unnecessarily risky and commercially a rational action
At this stage of the
Dispute
That decision may have reflected
Did prime minister Putin
Anger and frustration
I've been aimed at punishing Ukrainian for its
Repeated threats to
Disrupt Transit
40 Years of Russia's reputation
Secure gas supplier
And Ukraine's reputation
Secure Transit
Country have been damaged
The Russian government almost certainly personalized prime minister Putin
Which took the decisions which eventually lead on the 7th of January
To the complete interruption
European supplies
3D right Ukrainian Transit Network
Should have recognized
Consequences
I had the off
Stepping back
Correct
Play Rosario de Lottery
Putin
Threw a tantrum
It seems like that's the most likely explanation that the people who have studied the case on it
Well that you look at
One of the one of the
I mean
What are the narratives that emerged with the Russian
Into
The American election
And all that stuff
Was really just a very personal
I hate Hillary
Kind of reaction
So
Now makes a lot more sense with that context of him just throwing a tantrum
And ruining relations with the rest of the world stop by a little bit
Into a
I would say an incompletely drawn psychological profiles that we may want to work off of
I think you look at more of the details about it and I don't want to read you guys at 6
DuPage report anything like that
Tutor do that either
I had fault
But the shutting off
Of the gas
Was 100-percent Rush
Yeah they do in response to failed negotiations
Between Ukraine
And Russia
And
Ukraine was feeling
It was coming through the pipeline
But it
Here's that most
They get a little hose and they siphon
Guy was breathing in real hard and put it in a gas can
A lot of it is really impossible to prove
Either way right
Ukraine's argument is
The gas that they're talking about
Is what's called
Sick
Operational
Which they were using
To power the pipeline
And create the ability to use
The transit flow
If the cost
Doing business eventually
In the transit of
It's incredibly complicated
From everything I can tell if you look at the reality
Ar100
When the stakes were so high
Four people in other
B
Also
Russia
The decision to shut off the gas
Which Alex
Is
Putting the other direction
He sings Ukraine shut it off
It matters not
No one would make that Arc
Even on the 8th of January 2009
No one would make that are
Except
Bitsy
I hate
I hate this
Because
Obviously
We don't f******
Obviously it still could just be someone who's hyper sympathetic
To the Russian narrative
Rush's
World of
Are you
Has a boner for Putin to some extent
To me is that we talked about going on art
The Russian intelligence
Debriefing
Had to happen
Before 2009
Because it would never come out of his mouth if you wasn't super sympathetic to Russia
Fascinating
Just on a pure like
Where would you
Kind of level
There's no way to
Reeks
It's through approved
State-sponsored Rush
I do hang out with Paul Craig Roberts
He's at the Aronoff
Clearly a a Russian narrative
Where does he get it
He is either
Absorbing and watching Russian television
Constantly which is
Suspicious. In another self
If he's got
Direct
Relationship with people whose interest
Are aligned in that
Still don't think we have any
Kind of firm evidence
That there is a direct relationship
Past
The exploitation of
Flattery that they have
Frere is Alex's story about that
Which I'm inclined to believe it is true
As we as we go further along I am leaning more towards
That's that the real narrative believe it's true because he's not that creative
No
We have millions of listeners
Concocting a setup
You fell for
Occurred
So I don't know man it's yes Next Level this is the reason going back to this
Specific Starpoint
And to see immediately that
Like
That narrative in the face of the reality
Is
Is troubling
And what's more troubling
Is to see it
Wheatley different man than we know in the present
Still Loving Rush
You don't like
The guy who is mad the cops
Kill the black guy who's innocent didn't deserve to die
And all this and he's mad about it
To go to jail
And he's still
Ukraine's f****** up here there
You know what I'm having I'm having the exact same revelation
That we did when we did the 22
Like
When we went back
And Alex was like
Some say Putin will save the world
Like before
He became on Pizza when I was surprised by that I'm super surprised
Yeah I'm super surprised to hear that
I'm not a surprise
About perhaps
A Russian
Are you sure
When did his dad move to this
There's a lot of
Really tough.
Figure out
This country don't know that either
So you won't be surprised to learn that
Really wanting money
Flavors so different
He hasn't started his pill company
Selling DVDs
He's selling books
Yes
Some sponsors and I like we've seen
Misshapen jeans
Yeah I received this episode on January 8th
He's got a f****** real interesting
Always trying to make money
Another issue
Heisman 56 years
Black rug
Got broken
And it's a favorite model
Finished
And he wants to
Infowars.com
Show me state
Your presence
Even that like
You should be getting the
Feel like he's a man who's listening
I'll tell you that right now
It's possible
Did the way he is
Asking for money
Working around money
That's how human does it I want that
Freedom Crusher Crusher one garage sale
I want that bullhorn so bad you're not going to like how much
Spoiler alert for the rest of the episodes
So his old boat Boulevard
She clearly had a scent
Damage
Find the loudest model
Within the best
Alright by that bullhorn
Then it gets damaged decide no
I am going to
To turn this Boulevard
Into my company's fee
Exactly
It seems to work cuz I don't want to I don't want to ruin thing but more
I want a blunt
Steal it I will steal it like a pack of Marlboro Red convertible
Bullhorn
That the government gets involved
Put that spoiler
The fastest spoiler for later
You can't sell that boy doing
Talkin about
The Heyday of eBay
A rhyme
Back in about 2
Nerve
Hey
This bullhorn is going to be
Player in the show the guest a little bit they have on
Google my notes out here and I just don't have any
Eclipse on the interviews are inconsequential
When you listen to 2009
Alex Jones
Design games
It is
It becomes very clear to me that endgame was specifically like a best of documentary that he made
Okay was just about the same thing
Kantime
Who's going to watch or endgame stuff you'll get most of it
The greatest hits
Listen to any of the Eagles regular album
Didn't listen to their greatest hits album
Investigation is going to be even greater album cut
Like him
Be mad at the cops for killing unarmed most people don't get to know
Going to listen to the song
Fleetwood Mac roads that were written by anybody who is any
Sure he is Steve Quayle on who he knows written multiple books about how Giants used to walk the earth
Crackpot
He is a ironic
He talks about how I
It's all just like the end is here kind of stuff like that we're in a martial law state
He has a good quote that they
It was already signed the globalist sacrificed
Live children
If they'll take your guns if they'll take your life
That's it
He also
The creator of Star Trek was the successor of Alice
Ahead of the Oto
The Ordo temple temple
He has Paul Craig Roberts founder of Reaganomics
Also gentleman
Like weave
Ghostwritten for
Sputnik for years and years
Also if you are the founder of Reaganomics urns
Mostly just talk about economic collapse
And that they were right on time
A little late
Any talk about how it's going to get worse
And then he has an hour-and-a-half unless there is some sort of massive stimulus package
Pastor
Hour-and-a-half interview with David Icke
Not good
Like it's just
Just boring
As much as I want to play clips of David Icke
For you I would love to but
Just nothing he should have been using a bowl
It's absolutely nothing
It's just it's just the two of them sort of he wants to talk about this
Saying the word
The only thing
I said that I thought was like
Lizards
Money's on Alex's show
Close to the vest
People like Barack Obama are white people in black bodies
And that made me a bit
I don't know what that means
I don't either but he says he was quoting somebody else but I couldn't
I couldn't make out who he was saying
Hazel I just I don't have the clip of it
I would have researched who he was quoting
But it's a
Is a battery
So he gets done with David Icke
I'm going to get back to the Bohol
What is the surprised well it's not
Alex Jones
A Scanner Darkly
Yep
Nope you got play equip just to prove that he was in the movie know you're in the movie Alex
It's not
Cares
I don't know I like it
Movie memorabilia
Obviously it's a fundraiser
Megaphone
Just as a megaphone is worth 3000
$500
So he's important things going on here
I caught it but
I'm still
Struggling
Wrap my head around that fat
Pretty good name for a boy
He has to keep talking about it
I was living in a world where you can just say it's a pretty good name for a bullhorn and everybody's like and then we move on
Same thing to say right you not concerned about what the surprise is
Surprise
This is that this is going to sell for a lot of money for my notes here's the note that I have from
This time
Alex's big surprise
Also still trying to sell that bull
Still trying to sell that board so it's going back through them like
He didn't have a surprise
I couldn't remember what does the price
And then I remembered
The surprise
Charlie Sheen gave him a jacket
This is big surprise
Really
Jacqueline Naomi not be true
So Alex is also
Wolverines
People did not understand the point of that movie
Allegory analysis super excited
To tell everyone that he has Charlie Sheen
In the context of I go over
I will not
Alright
Heroic
Zoe
To play some
Clips from Red Dawn
You know I used to listen to Alex a long time ago cuz I thought it was funny I'm like
I cuz I never do know I'm always like this
Is a f******
Saying racist monster
This is pretty funny keep in mind but keep in mind that this is like A4
Flower show in 20 minutes of it opens at 2
Listen to Thursday repetitive commercials
A bullhorn
Named
Not selling
Great radio
Eclipse from Red Dawn
Mad over them
Russia Today
Flowers
Smooth
It's like Silk
Election coverage that's so great
So happy
Very pretty good loving
This is a man
Who's getting paid to play clips from Red.
I think if anything
Alex Jones
We'll see what else we end up learning through this like 2,000
But I think you should live on in everyone's memory not as a racist propaganda
Because he is
But I think
More importantly to all of our hearts
You should serve as a cautionary Tale
Like Icarus
Take
Superman lights
What is that
But also like Icarus he flew too close to the Sun
You know like
Whatever it is it
Probably lost for money
For whatever
He got money and he wanted more more
Luxurious
When the happiest you could possibly ever be is right around here
He's making enough money to live as a fanbase
He's getting
Do whatever the f*** he wants
Free to see a bunch
No one's going to
Like for us
Getting to the point where it's just like
We have enough donations so you can pay your rent
Everything from here
Being rich doesn't Charming
I know it sucks not really
This is it this is great for us
If we ever do become successful
Immediately were both going to be like
Jordan
I'm selling broken
Megaphone
What's
I don't respond to name megaphones just bullhorn
What's a What's the difference between a megaphone
Just a tube
You put your mouth at the base of
And it amplifies your voice
Like a like a cone basically that you ride yellow
The bullhole
Anyway
You know what I do know
Is
A f******
Gold sales
In 2009
V level
The level to which
He is incorporating by 23
Resources without disclosing their relationship
Do you mean that they own him entirely yeah
It's crazy
Like
Almost every show with Ted Anderson coming in and telling him about what bullion he's bought like
Couple of Frank's buffalo coin
TV show on
On Fox News bringing in a lawyer that he has
Nevermind
It's just crazy no correlation
And I want to stress like
She had on a half-hour interview with Paul Craig Roberts
It's just about like the economy collapse
And stuff like that
Towards the end of the show
Can a word wear a good
Three and a half hours into the show now he brings in
Real quick he says it there a sponsor but that's not really a cure
That is not
I've looked there an ownership group
I've looked a little bit
Into the f
CC's guidelines
In terms of like
How you supposed to represent bonds
Their ships and stuff like that and spiritually
I think this is a crime
I don't like a legitimately I can't I can't say for sure if you take a little more research on my
Part
He's being syndicated by
The guys company
And not disclosing that
That is a an unfair representation of their
Jaz Sinclair
Who cares
Under the price of batteries
I did I was able to even be a little bit on the British side
Frank's right now
The French franc
204 the British sovereign
Yeah comparatively speaking I did a little check on it I was looking to see where
That's really boring stuff but the point that I wanted to keep it in the end there was that Alex
This is like talk
Can price-point
He's very aware of the business
Absolute football gold at
35% of what it is that it would be on the market
How can you get away with these prices.
We're going to have to put a clock on this
We're going to put a clock cuz we're going to sell out of gold we're going to sell out of French Francs
I don't know if those are gold
But that's fine
Where can I buy you got an hour call in now
We're going to sell out this is not like
Call Tom
Samurai swords
Which are
Made out of
Frank francophiles
Frank's butt
People who like
Isn't closed
Acceptable broadcast Behavior
It's
Slightly unaware of the business and just letting TED Talk
I haven't talked
That would be slightly different but he's doing it like a like I mean it's not funny but it's like
And that we jump into the night
If you have been confused up till now
Just going to get more students going to get so much worse
When I get to it
Still hasn't finished
All right but at the beginning of this show Alex Jones
Talks about
The president
Who's there
And Alex is a big fan of in present day
Policies for death camps and rounding up population
Non-aryan gription Russia and on all over Europe
American Indian program
Here in the United States
It was Andrew Jackson
Not a laughing
Google's not great but but the awareness there is that Andrew Jackson
That's weird
That's very weird still the problem
Does know something about history at this point
All of these sources
Willfully lies about the probably heard before after 2009
That's the thing like on the stupid flash evil Continuum that we often disagree upon
You know is his reading comprehension
You misunderstand all of these things
Now if you get
If you can read the history of Andrew Jackson
He is a f******
Monster
And then report that like a reasonable human being later on
You are willfully lie
About Andrew Jackson and all of this
Willfully lying about all of these
Primary sources that you say you understand
Because you can
It is you it is within your capabilities
America is
Genocide
I disagree I don't think it's that cut-and-dry because that's such a simple conclusion
You know like
You could read a children coloring book and find out that Andrew Jack
Text Melissa genocider
You know if we should publish a
A series of knowledge fight coloring books that talk about
Real American
History
Brujeria unmarketable
Doesn't that doesn't indicate too much
Children's book go the fuc to
To Sleep America's version to hell
Something along those lines grow the f***
Relationship
Soldier
Thrilled
To tell you
But I have answers
Question about that bowl
By the way
$50,000 red
Wow
Now
5 million
We just Googled their hand
As part of a government group
What
Never been affiliated
Cancel
Weather
Memory
Dollars Federal number
Four-wheelers
Have felonies
Criminal
Charges
And they put a bid in on the
Criminal activities
Of course for
What is
Central Command
Oh really is that it
He believes that a government agent
He was trying to f*** with him by putting in a troll
Gmail
I prefer a government that does that.
Control Alex Jones
In that
Infiltration exist
So I can get that don't get me wrong
I am dead is not lost on me
No yeah but never was like
Hey I'll buy your your notes on the I Have a Dream speech for 5 million
Also this is like
You know 2009 is where you're getting
Beginnings of people figuring out
Like really good ways
The f*** with people on the internet
And maybe Alex Jones
Alex's World kind of like
Coalesce
Was just f******
Absolute most likely government
Do not stop Alex
From spiraling
Vicious rain
About these people
Open internet
You got some shrimp, and FBI guys in there with you
Associated Press about
Put
And that's your problem
They Savaged
You're mine
So you couldn't connect
Your intellect with your soul
Wow
That's
Weird
Something like that I need to bring up that I have discovered Vermont
Alex
He's been against
The whole time
There was a part of me
Vet like I used to listen to the show when I was younger and
And I kind of fun and everything
But like
I didn't
Understand
Can you put in that bed
What I didn't do that I did not work for satcom
From the jump like I didn't realize that this is a decade-long battle against these again
He doesn't talk about it much but I thought that was a newer
Wrinkle in his world like a cosmology the
Oh there's devil
Literal Christian death
Behind all of this
I'm I I I assumed immediately bring up the devil
Set up crew
Yeah but he clearly wasn't born again this is s*** that he's grown up with
I bet in
He has a grandma talked about the devil
Non-Stop
Early 2000s
He wasn't
Overly talking about
Satan is behind all these people I don't like
Given our interview at the end of the show with the guy name
Not Alan Watts
Be Alan Watts know Alan Watts is the other guy
Inspirational speaker through find video
Leo's of giving flowing speeches about human potential
He's probably behind a lot of Alex's
Endgame
Honestly cuz everytime it comes on the show
It's just the plot of a
On this appearance here on the 9th
January 9th 2009
He is literally talking about the Christian
Being behind
Lucifer
The following the phone
AMC
Intellect not being connected to
To your soul.
There
It's about the intellect
Breastmilk baby
Suspicious
Yeah we are reviewed studies
What depends a base of 15 to 30%
Lotion depends on study
Complaining about these people launched
Into this tirade by the troll bid on his
No it's bad not breast
Do some groups of people behave
Got you all arrogant John smiley face
Devil
The Cowardly
Metrosexual
But at least we know he still home or something
Those women abortions
Can I get a new car every two years
Honey
So
Goodwill where can I order
Misogynistic
Women with their abortions I've only paid for like 15 of them
Something like that every two years
Every dude
Another abortion
What is right
Also remember when
People used to complain about metrosexual
Like they're not moving from the 50s
Jeans
Dan
Their jeans fit
You should get random GLG
Absolutely
Jordan
You're going to get in
I don't know what to
Alex Jones
First gas
No on the 9th
I'm out
The guy by the name
Russell
The name meaning
Means
He is a Native American Act
Activists
Who's been doing sit-ins in occupations of like
Potraz
Other location
Since the lights
So far am I bored
Hotel right
Original people
Use on a
Reasonable scientist remember
Batman
Being Adele was Italy still use a broadcast
Write to you as he was utterly bewildered by
What do you mean
He has
Support them
In terms of Native American issues
First Peoples Jewelers
It's the Rothschild
One who is entire life
About
Trying to get rights
For a minority
Which
Shwayze
What do you do somebody like a we have a
Massive speaker who is
Tirelessly tirelessly campaigning for equal pay for women
Will not f****** give it up and they do so much good in their life
You find out it's like
Is because
Everyone who doesn't
And you're like
Support what you're doing I'm just going to look over this one part where you think it's the devil
I'm not concerned about where Russell's motivation
Comes from
Or whatever dumb ideas
Become beholder
Too late in life
He was on that tape in the mid-late 60s
I don't
I will say that I did not have time
To do a massive deep.
But from what I could gather
Russell Means
Great name
Freedom
I like that that's clever
I don't
I don't judge
The Rothschilds
Narrative becoming a piece of his thing
I'm not
I don't give a s*** about
2009 Alex Jones had a
Native American activist on the show
And he was like
He was on but he wasn't talking about how it's a plan
Just separate us in bulk and Isaac divide-and-conquer
He's Native American
Global is just trying to make people feel guilty
It wasn't even like that
From Apple
Position of like
I agree with you
And that's nuts
Now this next clip
Is even more
Right now
All God's Children
So
Dark humor
That's just him that's just
Letting the past
I think
Alright
That's nuts
Spetsnaz
Who is this
There's so many other there's a couple other instances that were garbled and
Listen to much longer clips
Yeah in order to get the
The sound byte to make sense
But there are a number of other points where he's
Like
F****** critical of Israel
I want to take away for this clip
Is a very strong message
Do all of the people
Out there
Who claimed that Alex Jones refuses
To talk about Israel
Go fuc yourself
He does
At least in 2009
I don't know how how this changes over time or whatever but like
Him saying
They're killing the Gaza peep the people in Gaza
Like that
That's as far as you need to go for a at least a first step
That is that something that if he was
As his critics is
Never f******
Say something like that
Most
All people
No matter how liberal professor
We're still avoiding the topic of Israel's war crimes
As much as humanly possible
It doesn't matter who you are like
The fact that Alex is at
Yes
Is literally coming out
And saying that Israel is committing war crimes
At a time.
Where Obama would not even
Talk about that s***
If you brought up Israel
You know and then moved on its back
There are
On that tip
Around this time
I don't either I don't either and I
It almost feels like we need to do a spin off show about Alex
In 2009 that is not related to the knowledge fight show
Lele different person
Sure about the present
Like it's just like we said in the last episode it's all just
All this
Obfuscating a dump much rather figure out
Where does the breaking
Come
It wasn't true
No because 2015
He was a
He was he was a
The day after the Charleston shooting
He said well
Sky really wanted to be racist
Have you been summoned before
Everything went wrong
Xbox
Is like this guy
They were listening to in 2009
Does.
He sucks
Bureaucratic of mine you just weren't breast
Sad
Dick
And he's clearly a manipulative
Gold salesman / broken bullhorn salesman
Course
But
The nearest
Tough job to get it is
Really hard to become a broken bone
Double major
Narrative
You don't like that with
The cop shooting of Oscar Grant
With
Think about Israel bombing
People in Gaza
And it's murder
Do something
All things you
You could talk about
You know like nowadays
Nothing he talks about you can talk about
Nothing
So many times of like
If you if you are on the right it's not like I I hate
Conservatives are right-wing people
So much as it is like
They should just be ignored because if you can't have a conversation about what the best way to tackle
If you if you aren't willing to be like
Well
Here's a here's how we should tackle it versus how
You want to tackle
That's a conversation
If you just say it doesn't exist
Okay well how do we tackle this police brutality issue
F****** power of these people
Clearly built with clearly
Soupremacy that we're just not packed
This is Malik
You can actually have a conversation with
About how
To correct these
Issues
What the issues are
How old is this guy goes from
Is it is it really just
Team sports
I don't think that all it really is
I don't know is it just that people
From whatever
Knowledge I have of the other episodes
I don't know I don't know
It's fresh
Is this
Yeah so don't be scared
Do this.
The cell New York
I would argue that the people who are the people who offered
Look at these shity white dudes manipulating people
I don't know if Alex is getting the wrong lesson from very basic history
But it seems like he might be thinking that everyone's laughing
As opposed to
60 if you if you fall into
But you did hear Russell laugh
Spirit behind it
So little later
Alex Jones has a visit
Someone we know very well
A dear friend of ours
Such a weird that
Justin Bieber
Kia of a man who
He still says wobble
Yeah
Just that concept
And it's not like a half
Wampum is a totally legitimate thing to say
Using it for effect
You know.
No I think he
Uses it like conversationally
We don't have enough contact
I would argue that I sent
Tim saying
Hey at least it Wounded Knee that killed all the children
United States
But I think it's that same sort of
You know I'm saying
I would I would go
I'm giving it a lot of leeway because of the other stuff
Cure ignorance
Of like
Well
There's nothing wrong with saying that's a normal thing that happened in 1940s
So it clearly
We had a visit
Buddy
Body of Art
Jesus
Larry Stevie Larry Nicks
Still haven't
Sleeping around
Steve pieczenik is in play at some point
World
Paul Craig Roberts people like Gerald Celente
Are much more regular gas
This point
Haha
Have to show up at some point
Pretty soon
Eagerly awaited
I'm getting all these episodes
Nothing is label
Like in terms of the episodes
And stuff like that so nothing going in listening to this episode
Thankfully
When Alex Jones is broadcast career
He starts every show by Buena Vista
Until I can get a sense of plastic
A b
With modern episodes
You know up to about like
A 2013 or so you can find them on YouTube
Can I go see who the guests are
Hamamoto let's do this thing
Where is now I'm like I'm Flying Blind
Pink is not in play
I think he's came around in like 20-30
Universal
I think I'm not entirely sure but
Ratibor shows up randomly that be exciting as f*** weird like
Racism is like his blue. Like weird artists
Character Arc
Throughout this whole thing
Post-modernism this is when Alex was a pointillist like this is bananas
Because I think we have tapped into
To some extent
A villain origin story
This point you do see the remnant
They're only remnants because we know
The future
Do Steve the Colonel's rationality
Do the kernels of like
And then you see the kernels of delightful
What the riding along with the highway
The talking about stealing beer at a car
Like
Sure
Sure.
That's a great movie
It's wise as it goes along I think we're going to see
A man get worse and worse and worse
I don't know there's no other
There's no other Direct
Either that or for some reason like some
Let's say
We continue this investigation
Turns out in 2010
In this way
Weird like
Woke
In his words
Classical liberal
Concept
Crushin it
And then something bad has
Like he falls into a vat of acid
Something along those lines like something
Horrific him into the monster that
You don't know
Got hit by meteor
Murdered by the globalist
And replace
With an
And Alex Jones
Chimera
I have called it right now
That's
That we know today
Was grown
Innate
Cow uterus or whatever it is
Think about like a life event
Would have happened
Divorce
The big event that happened help
But I don't lose that like 2350
Was formalized falling apart
For a while before that
That would be that would actually be
The least appealing narrative
To me if we go back
It turns out that around when
The marriage fell apart
He lost his mind
Is that it's just like
Such a bummer
Happy story
You kind of want it to
To have more
Drama
We'll see
Who's our friend who's our friend
Jesus f****** Joe I'll give you 20 questions
I figure out who our friend is
Alright if you white
Yeah no s***
Recycle play Guess Who
Izzy idiot pseudoscience
No
Alright
A player
Is he a player in the game is he is he like a secret
He doesn't have any like inside of a
No
Okay
Izzy former law enforcement
Not that I'm aware of
Matters
Alright
Is he
No
His name yet
In the show that has accounts
Let me know tonight.
Keep going
Do I have any more questions
Come on you can do it
I believe in you all right
Happily
Member of a
Former Republican Administration
Not that I'm aware of
I got nothing
He's been on our show
Exactly one
Termites
The time
No
Alright
Is it
To tell me
Just tell me don't try this out
To draw this out don't make me feel stupid
Make a reference to that earlier in the show
The international forecaster Bob Chapman's
Ciara guy who runs a publication called the international forecast
Prediction
It's about time.
Hey guess what we didn't realize from the times we listen to him
He is just a f****** shill for gold sale
I think the only true place
Is gold and silver related assets
If you are
A wealthy person
And you want to have
20 of 30 of 40
Percent of your assets
In another state
Play server relatively safe place
I recommended Swiss franc Treasury
Other than that
I don't have any
Anything to offer
Okay so it's
Getting gold or silver ore
Swiss bank account
That those are the safe places to put your money
Thank you Bob
Thanks Bob
Sounds right
So you're coming
Joe who is
Silver sale operation
For the government to actually
You screw with rich people
The crimes for a long time
Only safe only safe place
Yeah
They can f*** with you I don't know
Corporation office setup and f***
You know you want to sell gold and silver
Bob's
Commendation for you
I pretty much is it even worth
Painting
I know it's pretty
Stupid
We pretty much children worth
Like
Most of these bills and credit card dancing
Aldi store the things that the American people are going to be having
To deal with I mean if
If the money
Nothing at all
Even understand that
The people that you are the money to are still going to
To be within the
System
There is going to be some kind of the system
Maybe it'll break down
From time to time
And
Just because
The value of the dollar goes down
It still means you have to pay those bills
The way you protect yourself
Is it called Midas
Enter just gold
Silver coin
Oh no
2 /
He was almost giving advice
Well he was really close to it because I wasn't
Just don't be an idiot
Disappear because of bad times
You sure
The world is going to last another ten years but I don't want to get f***** over before then
That's a reality check
Like two people who are too far gone
Did the other day
Call Mike
Yeah that's not
F****** over
That is too much
So
This interview goes on a little while
Speaker
F******
Confiscated like 16 burner phone from Michael Cohen
Type shyt right there like used in breaking
Bad whenever he opened the drawer with 16 burner phone
For the president
Find that hilarious
For me
Human
First human repo
Free phones
Why do you have sex
3 phones
Is it your house
One of them radio shows
You know that that sort of thing
Just fight Channel
That's all I'm saying
I'll accept that is 14
Alright personal cell wireless cell
You got three
That's it more than that you have
Mr. Arnaz
You got some splainin to do
I don't
Uncle 8404
With the fourth being a wild-card that I can't explain but someone has a good explanation point
Something like that
That's fun
4 make sense
You're crazy
It seems like more than enough circumstantial evidence for any jury to convict you of literally anything is like
This guy had 16 phone so like oh yeah he probably did some illegal ship it's one of those times
It's one of those times that I wish
Like this argument would hold up in court
Come on
You put your elbow down on the picture box
Come on come on
Guys
Your honor
Nothing
Come on
Text more calls
The Dixmoor calls
As much as we've enjoyed
Alex
Being bad cops
About how they killed an unarmed black man
We've enjoyed
Reasonability
Might have more to do with hating cops
In 2009
TPAC bulshit
No I don't know I think it's just that I'm not
I'm not entirely sure that
I can't explain
But I do know that it's not that he cares about black
Listen to this
Culture
But I'm in there
You were right about Obama
Betrayal
The people
They're just so arrogant and so trusting in the system
No no
It's perfect
Perfect
So
They're the reason that I
I think that that is racist
Austin character
Is because he says that he doesn't like
The culture of malls
And then immediately is like
Pocket bike
Did not get that
The fact that his mind went so quickly to apologetic black people coming up to him in the mall
After he said he didn't like the culture of them all
The culture of the mall thing
Did not bother me
Have nothing to do with Ray
I think I think the race issue comes up when he specifically
Three black people
International style of
This is a made-up thing
Specifically point out minorities
In order to
Bolster my credibility as though I have any but I also
From context
Clues
Even though we're so thrown by this man in 2009
I still think I understand his brain
Pretty well
I don't like the
Culture of the mall
I think he's responding
Two black people being at the mall
I think that's what he said
Because he's so quickly
Is he okay
If you listen to
He starts with
Here's the good
I don't like the culture of the mall
But I was at the mall because I had to get a haircut
And black people came up
Give me an apology
The track of that
Leave the person
A reasonable
Thinking person
To assume
That the culture he doesn't like in the mall
I've something to do with the black people go to college
I can generally he
He doesn't like it when black people don't apologize to him at the mall when he's there
That's fair and good news at the last time
That I understand that
I'm going to be honest though my own personal my own personal biases
My own personal biases came out and I was like oh he doesn't like the huge
Right
Mallrats in the 90s were all going to try and push it on my breakfast
Your haircut
There's Salon that down the
Come on
What are you talkin about
And also
Interview lady who cut Alex Jones hair
Probably took about
45-second
I have a whole lot of hair
Back then says the guy with
Hey hey
Don't talk about receding hairlines folks
Love like having the Terrible
I don't like how much it cost
So I
My bill is going down as my hairline received
To tell you that right
Wow that's
The good news
No black people to come up
Tomato tell me about how
AR AB
My hairline
Panda eats
Justice
Further
Bring home
I've said this to you couple times
What's up
The other friend
Listen your quiet mom
Not naming this show
0,
Because I think
More than talking about Alex Jones
Yeah
Is
All these other people who come up on his show all the people who are involved
Project Camelot
All these like Gavin McInnes
Mike cernovich jakpus obok
Steve
Hamamoto
Girl f****** condom
Everybody
They're all conmat Milo Milo
Wonky conman
But all of these people are
Running elaborate, right
I'm so
Not naming our shows something that is
Even harder to
To find that are free
Yeah
Bring this up is Bob Chapman
You said to a collar
You need to do is call my dad
Here's how this show
Cross-promotion right there
Chapman
Publication is distributed at least Park
Buy Midas resources
Tell people to call Midas
Doing a quid-pro-quo in some way
For help with distribution
And they're all doing it on the on this show in public
But Chad is doing
Ears
I guess $90 under what it is right now
Yellow Bass
That's code for I want you sandwich
I-88 probably going to say it's a good deal but I don't know what is
Going to say about it
I predict Bob Chapman's going to be suspicious
What would you give for Ted to go on and be like
Today's not a good
My grave
Wait until tomorrow
What I have right now Alex again today
Topeka date 6890 which means it is getting stronger
Came out weight loss
I mean
Way higher than what it was
What I did is I pick
Frank's
Short while ago
Referring to
And they're currently at
204 where the break everybody
The best
Are $8
$0.40 or $168
Roll a 20
Frank langella
Plus also helped boost for rising market prices
You know
You know if your whole thing I mean that gun issue that you're talking about earlier
So even Ted Anderson
Answer
Force on the show
Is saying like
In order to help sell my gold
Refer back to you were talking about
And spoiler alert that was Alex earlier in the show
About how everyone's going to get their guns
I don't remember the name of the Bell like copper it
WorldNetDaily
I got to know Bill
Didn't fucken happen
House of real fun
I mean 50 tripler
So overt
There's so
Lunatic there's only one clip that I wish I would have pulled in
You better bury your guns and ammunition if he's read the book
Might be even further Synergy The Runaway of it Bob Chapman owns where to hide your guns.com
Is that so
Is it still up
I don't remember
Anyway
We've gotten
Exploration
Free days in January 2009
Here's what I think of the important takeaway
Alex is already
Giving
Unacceptable
And tonic
Explainable pro-russian narratives 2009
Four major world of
He's at this time
He's sneaking omit
Somewhat
25 minutes out
He's just tossing in like eight everything Russia does
Metal
Selectively edit
Malaysian was resolved
Nicole
Maybe
I don't know
We might
See that in the next episode
You who knows who knows
Who knows
You do I don't actually know all that much
Actually Alex goes on vacation
Alright
Alakazam
Alexander vacation they are supposed to do that guy has
I know I do like
The character from
Use come out since
Secret inside the tower
I guess because most of
His old employees have
The other thing I think is important is that Alex
Is a racist
Yeah.
Which is interesting
Also
He's willing to talk negatively about his room if he's one of those reflexive race
At this point
Where it it normal
It's almost out and out
In which is what he is now
It's more like it's just
He's a he's a good old boy he was Raising
Underlying
You still going to throw in a Whopper
To have an interview with a guy who is there for First Peoples right you know witches
Pretty crazy
Compared to bananas
Also
I don't know if he's ever even
In the past 2 years
Aside from
Farrakhan
He's headed to Candace Owens
You know
I think I see
There's a lot of
Threads here and I hope it I hope that we're able to get to the bottom of a lot of them
This is a whole new
I'm so fascinated by this how much did you sell the bull horn for
California
Can't be real
Might be who knows
Wrap this up
URI in the past
You can first I'll follow us up
Knowledge
Underscore fight
You know where this bullhorn is
You better Goddamn tweet it
At knowledge on
4 fight for sure
All bullhorn related messages are welcome
Five star review on iTunes if you leave a review on iTunes and
Mentioned
Terror pressure 101
Wireless
To support the show and then
That's the best way to support the
If I get a broken Bullhorn in the mail and it's not Siri Crusher 1
Does Another Broken bullhorn
Just a regular
Spray painted on it
Tell it 450
Grand I'll tell you that right if you go anyway it's your turn
Do do you know exactly
Number of
Oh you think it's going to be rain
Related to this show that we just did this was
All the Democrats in the world
Go fuc yourself
Holding
Alexandra first in color with your trip and I love your work