Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Looks a bit about Alex to go
Sir if you were to describe
That lost episode brutally destroyed
F*** you.
Straight up
I put my creative soul
No I don't know the real you did was hours of hours of
I know that we both took it hard
If you knew the fun we had your you take it very hard to fight one of us
The other one
Ender Dragon
And recorded I also took a bath f*** you
I emotionally I slammed a bunch of beers and then recorded a half hours to make
Deal with tribulations that are on way
Trials tribulations
I'm pretty sure every Christian is like
Word trip.
Love it so you could say that we both know a lot about
A Raptor
There we go
I feel like we got a
Spiritually we've already
Thank you to new policy walk dog
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much.
Dakota
What's going on
I'm a policy wonk
Stop forcing Optik gospels in the Bible
Top four things that were taken from the Q source
I would like to give
Hi to our newest globalist what's going on out there Mike W
I'm a policy wonk Natalia brilliant someone sodomites Italy a bucket
Thank you so much
Got caught up in a little too long
Yourself and you haven't
If you feel inclined by going to our website knowledge.com quickness sport the show button
We would appreciate it
Now
Jordan
Today
Have you noticed
I don't
I don't because I'm about to blow your mind
See the only problem with that reveal to me before the show that today
I told you during the Lost episode
Possible
Wait for us to work our schedule. Monday live stream
Would be Project Camelot land
Because there's a lot going on over there
Must be covered
That's look for you so you knew coming in that we were going to be
Very
Kerry Cassidy has gone to prison and it is now time to
Floresville
8 interview
Captain America
Overspace by my ribs
Of all of those words
In the same sentence is a delight
Earth Defense Force
What could you
Possibly get in the eighth installment
You are so dumb there are so many New Ringgold this is
I told you just before we started that I almost f***** around and just play at the entire episode
All over again without nope
Record
Tobey Maguire is the Raptors of Project Camelot
It was really weird so here's a little out of context drop that I'm going to start off with and just it's something it's important to remember
And he does have access
Okay
You remember that
Basically synopsis of First 48 hours
She starts off the episode
Hi I'm carry
Gilyard
Space Program
How to delay because I went to Egypt with the group and so this is coming in
Interview
I took very good care
Introduction
So now
This
How do you get episode starts off
Blue my mind
I think
She might be talking about us
You have gotten a little bit
It doesn't seem to matter if it's not it's not anything less than
32 assholes are making fun of me now.
Basically when I first got there I we talked about the impact
On him
Some information that he was given
It had to do with
People had
Talk critically about him and myself
And also
Didn't do their research and and so on and he was given some information
Cruise on the internet
This is commonplace for us that are part of the internet world but for Mark
Culture so to speak
He doesn't know
People can hide their identity
And therefore
Very badly
And that's really what
Going on here so
That's true for World deals are negotiable in this world
Who the f*** else is making fun of them
I don't see anything posted around on the Internet it's like hey you got to get a lot of thing
This is crazy
Banana
I think it's just us consistently talking about how he's a murderer
Restrictive poor also
Anti-semitic lady
Baby when she watches
Which by the way
Thank you for joining us
Frozen
Speak up in the chat room
Maybe when she watches it she just sees like a Twitter egg over our faces all the time she's got like a
Browser
Possible interesting Theory
Mark's been in prison
For thirty years behind a murder
It turns out he's had some protection
Well even prison nationalist clearly runs with a dealer.
Command is
I think he was a silly move to another prison
Will another part of the prison apparently about how like
Kiesza hanging out with these old dudes
Old man in Portland
He's right
Early 60s like
How to use 29 when he got arrested
I believe so I'm not
Yes
Protection
Imprison the best around
Social Security or not allowing them
Get parole
Part of the problem
Prison system
It's very problems
Really barbaric
He believes he was put into this
These quarters
Silence him
And he only feels
Said he's alive
Because of the Hidden help
From his friends
The Raptors
Make sense okay
Okay they could
Guardian angel in him didn't help from a Raptor
Respectable
If people send him money
However chocolate from the commissary then that's how he pays them for their help
Accurate
You walk into the great room to meet your aunt
You better not be holding
We've wrestled with
The high level of bulshit that's blowing out of Mark Richards mouth about why he's not
Like gotten out of prison
Because
Theoretically he's got
Super high connected friends
Fireworks level display of b*******
The Raptors can create portals
Keep in mind that he hasn't
And a family
Including his wife Joann
That he loves and this is why he
Tolerates the situation in
Instead of leaving
Ingram portal
Sure
Actually could be
Facilitator
Nope
And so he used
Very dedicated
To his wife and family
Cool
Yeah
Boy
Anybody who has access to photos and does not overuse them Noble
Noble character
Very restrained
I could get out of prison with my rat report
Couldn't you get out of prison and then just get back into prison
Viaport how about like
Demonstrate like you don't have to get out of prison with a Puerto Ricans go to the other room piano
Really clear some stuff up
He's not making all this up cuz he's a board murderer
It never fails to Delight me
The reason that all of this is happening is because there is a board murderer in prison
Tricked
He might also be cute or not
He's not but listen to this
As far as
Arrest and
Tribunals offshore he agrees this is happening and not being
Reported in the main
Military
Appearing also
This week
Interview he was taught
Talking about
Pilot to Edisto
Appeared in
An S8
In Antarctica
Easy US ship to Priscilla
Due to the journalists who would
Reports
Journalist.
Who are attacked
And probably saw something
They were not supposed
See
And their minds were wiped
For the news
Porter Scott
Access to
All the time
Is awesome
Like
What was the F-18 event
The flight was it out of
Look
One of the best parts about these episodes is I have no responsibilities to look into this
Definition of describing
No one's going to report about it cuz of course you can
Here's why it's really exciting
But she brought up Antarctica
Because I
Know a little bit about this
Specific
Or just Antarctica in general
Looks Leighton exquisite
Or not
Play the next clip and then I will explain what I mean by this
Man Mark also has to have the internet
YouTube
Season watch
Hollow Earth and videos
This time and
He said regarding an R
And multiple
Problems
She said the Nazis in New Berlin
Are still there
Refers to them as fast
Easter
Distinction
And
The ruins of Atlantis are being revealed
And study by the US and Russia
This is the last
Human alien civilization
For humans an alien
We're living together
Openly
Hey guess what spoiler alert
If you're working together on a
Study Atlanta
She got a look
Trust the alien
But verify the secret alien knowledge that is leftover in Antarctica
But it never end never goes out of style
Underground in Antarctica
Wait what does Halo Wars ship
This is straight-up Halo Wars
Yes
Underground distinction
Cortaca March whatever
Regularly visit Antarctica
The hollow Earth theory the people put out there
Yes there's always knots
Applied to geography
So there's a hole at the bottom of the Earth
You can go inside it
Also have
Ambassadors over governments they have their own embassies on Floors
Within the already go to the 13th floor most places
F****** New Berlin Embassy
Is
Just literally
Just as reasonable as a superstition about the number 30
So that's the oldest closure I do have a bed about
John Quincy Adams believing that the Earth
The Admiral bird out their dick
That does come up
Carrie talking about how
Has diplomatic ties with
America
There is lots of contact
Between the Nazis in New Berlin and
Our government
There are several hundred thousand who are Mass
Simply rich
Pictures of minerals
Denture like
I'll be honest that would mind their
Real baby there are rare earth minerals
Where the f*** else do you think Alex gets his iodine clearly aligned with the fascist in Uber
Alex Jones believes in Hallowell
I like Hollow Earth stuff actually like
In terms of clearly
Wrong beliefs
Like this video
Truck like an hour
And not be mad
Hollow Earth
Hollow Earth frustrates me because I want
A
Mathematical certainty on
Halo Halo
Like how many miles
For some reason I can't get over like
How thick
Do you believe the crust is this is there and he wanted to pick you up you want
How much it's the Sun
For the hollow Earth
Inside the Earth
Forgot
I've had some issues
With the holiday stuff
I understand it there's like external gravity so it's like gravity pushing at work
We're walking on the crust of the earth and then like
The Outer Sunset
Exactly
We're not sinking into the Earth
Because the inner earth gravity is pushing
Bro
Find and it explains why you can't fly over the poles
Hold on there
My favorite part of the hollow Earth
It's not just
That the Earth is Hollow
There's a hole
Made
For us
What are you talkin about
Right it's always the whole
Why
Because that's how it is b****
Open doesn't make any sense
You make a golf ball with a hole in the top of the bottom it's a bad structural design
You should know that everything is awesome
Is Halo everything is all up
Chocolate
I can come back to Chocolate forever
Here is Mark Steyn
Who is also a Stargate
Are the most energized for Texas on the planet
Checks out
Regarding inner earth Mark thanks a lot of
People are at
Actually seen into
Earlier versions
Right
Stargate
Why is that a feature is that a bug
Reason
Is there a point
I will say
Gain or lose from
I will say that there are a number of times I believe one of them is right after that where she says
I should have asked for clarification
3 * 3
Yeah yeah you should have
So we always think of the best
Comebacks after
You know she was talking to him and then
And a day later today
Start a flight to Egypt
So I don't remember
Right
Cuz they're powerful vortex
Find checks out
The polls
Lubbock does that make sense
Satisfied
Hollow Earth
Where do they come
Poop
Target
Also why is it
But you can see into an earlier version of Earth
Through a Stargate
It's a date
Traveled
Between the Stars
Here's the thing
Alright in order to do that like there's a parallel Earth that you're seeing right
Parallel Earth where you also have to travel in time while you
Alright
It's complicated
I think
It marks his watch
The TV show
Actually
Parallel
I referred him to a
New series that.
Called
Ants called counterpart
Which is really
Love Deluxe Princeton
Stargate
You also have
Time travel
See
When creating a
Parallel
Strangely enough
The creation of
The parallel
In a time travel required
Actually
Just like
The storyline of stars
Right
So that's quite fascinating
Sounds like perhaps
Producers over at counter
Said information
In from the secret government
And I will just
Throw this out here as a possibility maybe
Describe to him the entire plot of the sticker show counterpart
That sounds right
She secretly has stores
I feel like stars doesn't come on
It probably cost more to not have stars
Also I completely
These days
Put my grandpa hat on
So I forgot to bring this up there's a new wrinkle to carries Mark Richards reports
Has she started putting a little like
Hirons kind of like a little single pop up like talking about New Berlin
There's two that I think are amazing Want You misspelled China
G+ chenia
Come on
Take a little time
What you talking about Antarctica
You spelled
Dash
Arctica
I should ask him about this
It probably could have saved after the entry
?
Just like
Antarctica
Wait
Ants
Right
Leads me to believe she didn't study Latin
90 point
You did study ass
It's true
Answer
They are
It being a
Oh yeah well we can
Stuff to say
Barbie
He's a big fan of Tom Skilling
He's not a fan
Of our present
President
Because
That's a positive development well it's because you can
Castration
Soompi
People in the Trump Administration
Administration are resigning
Because they can't handle it
What's coming
AR-10
Basically eluding
Disclosure
Ethereality
Entails
Here on planet Earth
Okay
If you took like a
You just took that inference at the end off the rest of the day
Trump officials are quitting
Because the repair light of what's coming
Bevricks why not aliens
But
Sure I heard
Ronnie jacks
When he was read the laundry list
But he was accused
And he specifically said
I didn't drive a car drunk
I did not deal with the rest
Clearly
That means the rest of them are all about it
Right on, how do you get
How do you purge
At Trump's rally that you had the other day
Directly and overtly blackmailing a senator
I don't remember any
Nearby
Yes I believe so
You said that
God we live in such an insane world the only imagine if Obama was just like
Mitch McConnell
You don't
The fuk up I'm going to take it down
What are you what are we talkin about that that's not the only story
Are you telling me
Add a goddamn dumbass
Front Page News
What Trump being like
Hey I am going to
You ruin your career if you don't do what I tell you to do also
The one that we elected is now openly
Unless
Anymore
Could have been like
All a trick
Goes to Michigan
And pretends he's drunk throwing a rally probably
Because he also said Trump said that if he's better
Careful with your second
I don't
I'm paraphrasing a little but
Regular citizen should kill it
Male stuff made me think like
One of his advisers is Larry Nichols
Nothing Nichols
I'll take all the
Republican
Amanda
Democrat
The Wharf
Does wonho
One hope
Portals
Portals are going to come back up
We have for Humanity to survive
Yes
No I think he's right
We believed our only chance for survival
For us
With the Raptors and
They're princesses step forward
Along with
The fact that they themselves
They also consider
Prefer to be their Homeworld
And are therefore in the game
Regardless
There are various
Spider being
How to get those spiders
There's a different AI
Expanding and there are
Interested in art
Dave tab Robert Salisbury
Said they are
Twisted in Jupiter and Saturn
Crazy
Hey we like our current home
But we are interested in diversifying and if there's something you know we do have some Equity built up
Better that we could get for a reasonable price
Go to figure this s*** out if your house hunting you're not going to look at one place don't be stupid. Stupid
That's why there for the Raptor princess
Cool
Nordic
Again on the side of the mountain
No that's the nordics were on the side of the dracos
No
I remember those
Does Nordic also include like the Pleiadians from lightbringer's
I apologize
The further that the Raptors are actually evil
Adelaide weather
However now that I know that the nordics are not all
Part of the New Berlin Ian movement
Also just address question in the chat room yes Jupiter is also Halo
Fiery definition
Bingo
Who amongst us is not Halo real just Electric
Easter Bunny
For the low rent to a dollar store
Chocolate keeps coming up
So Jordan
We learned that there's a i threat there's for AI group
You're going to learn
Billions of dollars
You know evil and what have you that we learned about
Put your f****** bike down
I just want to
Explain to me
Exactly how we could have four different
Let me tell you this
Can't do it I don't know what the group part means either I have no idea
No idea
The knowledge. Explain AI group
Absolutely
That's how
Got to trade with the new berliners there is a new character
Coming in
Never discussed this before
I didn't know what to think what I heard her say these words
If the AI want to take us out
They first have to
To deal with the gaseous
And Saturn
Gates there and are dedicated
They are friendly
Real life
Gaic anime
Gaseous creatures
Have the ability to take out a whole
Incoming ships
Instantly
And the way they defend us
Buy rechanneling
Local Star Energy
2D atomized
Destructive
For incoming ship
Makes sense
Really want that I really want that last fit
Written down one more
Bay
Control
Spaghetti
Glow cloud
Play all hail the glow cloud
They help
Suspiciously not artificial intelligence
Definition
Would eventually have to come
No because they wanted chompa chompa on Earth
They want to eat the Earth
What does the weather feel like coach
Gas giant creatures
Read Channel
Skyrim
2D atomized
Ships
AI group
I don't
I don't care are they like in Avengers
Situation
Do they have do they have a certain
Threshold of what a crisis is
Are they just
Are they just sleeping
What are we doing here
They're friendly.
They guard the gates
Benjamin Franklin Gates
Put capital letters on something it sounds gross absolutely especially when you gesticulated repeatedly
Kind of makes it more real to you
Little bit literal Gates
Like big hard the literal Gates of
Jupiter where you you are driving
And you may well
These gaseous creatures
He said most negative AI
Are based on
Annex
The planet
Because they're being stopped
However
Many are not based in
Mechanics
Any solid
Including
People
Everybody around you
Might be part of the AI group at any point
Good ones we might be
That might be what Carrie think
That could be Munoz
Could we know
I couldn't prove it
You know that's it
Intersection
I don't know
Because a gaseous beans which is a very very cool
Ceasefire tree
Entirely
Play eyes-only
Is to Chapa Chapa is your words
The Earth all the bucket list
It's in the bucket list
Right button until it gets to that item on the list the gaseous beans I think there's like a live-and-let-live
Still life
Destruction kind of way
They're not willing to go so far
Unless
Line across
The opposite of Barack
Redline with II
Jupiter and Saturn
Completely different sizes
Solar system
Are the computers laws
You know how old Wars in our history have been really did aliens
Spider being almost
Everything
Has been alien f****** around
Write often
This clip
Yeah they've been
Pools at the weird alien machination
In this clip Carrie talks about some boats
The guy had two battles
And
Let me tell you this
One of the reasons that you sure that it was aliens and it was a cover-up that they said there were sharks
Courses
Quote there aren't that many sharks
I brought up several
Famous
Battles
He talked about those
The sinking of Indianapolis
In 1945
There were men in the water they were
Attacked by sharks
It was actually
Cover
Are there not that many sharks he said
Alien race
Didn't say which one markers or shortening for Aryan race they were dealing with
The Liberty
Liberty which was an attack by Israel our ship
The Liberty was Archie control center
At the time we were a vacillating between helping Egypt and helping Israel
A Anunnaki on the ship
Attacked
Hold up
Came from
Egypt
And he said that the
He has a bad attitude
Towards the Anunnaki
Because he is
In the past and he doesn't like the way they View
Human
She doesn't trust them
And this tends to
Perception of what we're dealing with
So she's already
Buyer
Antonov is real 911
Israel
No no
Bubba story to check out
So ridiculous
Zecharia sitchin the Eric Von daniken all that nonsense
Translation
Sumerian text
Rap like that
Man
This next clip was like
Oh God does he even know what
She's smoking staying
What is all over space
Yeah where does he just get into
Martha probably neo-Nazi
Huge Palace in
Sure
Immediately was like
Going over all of the things that she is asking
And having answered
Why did she just come up with some
Random ass
Battles 2
Closest to the 8th visit
Jesus running out of material please just write and out she's just got to wait Borges
Boom what else do I want to know
Elizabeth we got to learn a little more about the Anunnaki and it also accidentally turned
Deeply racist
Anunnaki
Draco
And this
Makes their motive
Specious
However most Anunnaki are humanoid
And fairly
Play tall
The ones here on Earth
Can pass as human
Coloration in their skin
Call boy
Oh boy
I'm going to still go with Conan O'Brien
Anunnaki coloration of their skin
What do you mean bark-bark
Is the absinthe
You know damn well he's not what he said
So f***** up
They also have to be tall
Which as we all do tall people in Colorado
No
I think
LeBron James
Do you do you know how
Kerry talked to him for like 3 hours and then these reports are her to reading stuff for like 40 minutes
I'm just going to guess
Did some of the stuff she doesn't report back to Project Camelot is him saying some
Make some weird theories about Dodge
Right cuz that
For him
Kind of everybody knows that
That goes along with some of the worst stuff you can find
Worldview
Standby
Anyway
That's that's really f***** up
But it turns out that there's a hockey
Right
The bus
German government
There are many Anunnaki and reptoids in the trunk
Administration
Or another
Most of Congress
Some in the state department know about
The alien presence
And many more in the Pentagon
Are in the know
I asked him about John Kerry
Why
He said he is
Probably
Alien human
Pull up
Just making a note here that humans are hybrids
In this case
We would have
John Kerry Wood
Turn
Arista
So he's a John Kerry
I don't know I don't know why you're shocked and Confused
I told you there's a lot going on
How do you have any conversation in 2018
That eventually leads to John Kerry
What is he even doing right now
Hanging out
I don't know
I don't know if he's not interested anymore
Is that a news of the cabinet what do you want why were you even talking about
Alright so
So you're talking about Cary right now
What is that your next Quest
About a man who is utterly irrelevant 228
What is your next question
Say things I read
Well
Humans are already hybrids and then he goes
Hahaha you got me there mark well played
Wild played Mark so
About chocolate on the brain
Chocolate comes back up
Do the Raptors love chocolate so much
It's delicious
This
We talked about
Chocolate
Mark talked about the focus
Of other races on our chocolate
He said there's nothing like it on other planets
If you study chocolate
The cocoa plant
We still don't know how
Pollinate
What do you mean you don't know how it go.
We don't know how
I do
It's a little flies
Chocolate
They're pretty aware of how it works
Does she bring up the European vs American chocolate
There's a lot of raptors in Belgium
You should know that
And maybe
Semi
Invisible Knight
It's not it's not an ant or a v
Multiply
Take the cocoa plant
To another planet
To get it to grow
You know what
You got but I imagine that's true of all plants I'm right there with you
Aliens are not
A mineral
Or water he says
Plenty of gold
Asteroid
Fairy wings come here for
Things we make
Luxury items antiques
Things that beauty
My note
Obviously our
Sir
Antique
There's two things I know
How do you know the color that have you don't know tanaki
Color that's good
Antiques Roadshow
Favorite show is the Raptors
Armoire
Bulldog
Are you telling me this point is from 1910
Jack Briggs
The trip
That my friend
Stromae
Also
If you're looking at that list of things that you talking about gold fits like with they like things of beauty
Antiques
Oh man oh man
Alright
What happens when they go to Red
Probably didn't even know
They probably
Answer used to time traveling
Insulate a can just assume
You are used to
Doesn't the very concept of an antique become ridiculous that that's a problem
Season of itself
Nonexistent any further because it is always existing in the same present moment that's a problem for me
Logic
But you need
Before we judge too harshly
We're going to get a little bit of a backstory going for the rafters
The Raptors know more than we do not because they're smarter
Because they are a space
Bearing race
Cool seventh-rounder of
65 million years
And
A real quick
Where is that number from
Jurassic Park
Jurassic Park movie 65 million years in the making
Who is this
Have the Raptors
Is there actually
Match the Raptors
From 65 million years ago
So they were already
Herded cattle others up
To be soldiers isobe
65 million years ago
Earth and went on a journey in Tobermory
And they
Went into some sort of
Bandit animation
It's not clear
Returned
To the galaxies
Few million years ago establish
The home in the grit
Draco
Galaxy at that time
Technology
Power there
Chips
I can just slip into an event
Verizon
10-day return
Okay
So there was that
Time Gap
The planet they settled on in the Draco Galaxy
Belong to the Draco
And when they took it over became enemies of the Draco
And they are at War
Right
Like that
McConaughey and what vehicle
So you good actor
Impact
Now
Dragon movie it's about Dragonheart
Dragon
That actually does fill in some of the plow
It doesn't. Suspended animation
The plot holes
Funk do they get off of your 65 million years ago
It's not that they're smarter than us it's that they are a space-faring race
Exactly
Nelda
This is so what this is
Okay let's
Just think of it this
I'm getting a second Source telling me it's raining fire something
Confirmed
So dumb
No. Don't f****** that right don't do this
Are not smarter than
Ralph
Fire a spacefaring race
Propose a kind of
Polynesian Scituate
Where in
They can travel across great
Distance is relatively simple structures
Polynesian
They could travel from aperture stupid to make good boats
Who is relative
Same time
Sturdy enough for them to
Did you just watch Moana
I did not I watched it a few months
Fair
Also I've actually it's more I played civilization 5 whenever
Polynesia
Bonus where they can always travel
Ocean tiles even though they are even though you haven't developed the
The thing is whatever analogy you're trying to make is
Bumpus Bumpus
Getting off the planet is different than making a boat
Sounds like a compelling argument
Dinosaur
Do you think they ran into it
Dinosaurs don't breathe
Turn up
The Raptors are good
According to Mark drakos are generally bad
Right even though
From his own admission
Raptors
Colonized planets
Disregarding the fact that there were native peoples living there sure
Isaac Isaac
It suggests that he has
Is actually Eve
Mark Ritchie
Is gas-lighting us about
So the Raptors fully believe there are some good Draco
But the Raptors and humans are diametrically opposed
Which involves
Take over
I got bad news for you about humans
Erase
That is such a raptor concept of like
Is it the same thing as your grandma said oh well yeah but they're one of the good
Fresh
Okay so the dracos
They want to conquer things I've humans and Raptors aren't into that but
To differ
Every bit of human history would cost
Floors between the Raptors and the
Spider-Man
Every now and then so you know how
And the new prisoner
So you know how we just learned that their gaseous beans and play the last time we learned Aunt being served play
I knew about the spiders
In this next clip we learn about a whole new group of aliens but before we do we learn something
Dammit
About the first lady of the United States
I don't want
Give away too much
And he says he is
Controlled by aliens
He went from being a mediocre millionaire in
4 years
Tubing mega-rich
His wife
Is a biological
Call creation
That operates as his direct link to an alien race
She is his communication device
Alien race
Leilani's discussion
Talk about the bit about the cat beans
And so on
HopCat beer
Jobs
Cute cats
Could you be cats
Trump
Has a wife as a communication device
Don't know which one
Now let me tell you something right now
Is there a better explanation for why she will not always hold his hand
What is that
But a man calling
And then hanging up on
Perhaps
It's definitely not there in a Loveless marriage based on money and
Has nothing to do with
And I know that it doesn't nobody to do with it
That's still not ruled that out Ivan Mark Richards
Unreliable narrator in this situation
He's providing cover for the cap
I have it on good authority from my friend Carrie
Uno's
Numark
It's not there.
Where to learn about that here in a little bit
But first
Terry asked him about the wildfires in California
Well
Because the truth about it is pretty wild
Fires in northern and southern California the fires in Northern California War
Basically a group of
Juvenile alien races
Who decided to
Hardy
Psychology here and devouring human
This brings in the wrinkle
North-south Civil War
Now she goes on to say I don't know what happened with the self. No idea about the south fires but the North
Alien print
Explanation of the other is just
Atavistic
Mark was tired
Who knows why this other what's happened
It makes me eat
Clear that he's either telling the f****** truth
Organization
Super accomplished manipulator
Because if he was just sort of an amateur con man
Yeah
Allow yourself to
Appear vulnerable in order for the ability about you
I'll tell you what
I love it
Fireburn alien prank
Anycubic
We don't know that their people
There can't be
Pull up on your judgement
Terry was just in Egypt and you know there's a lot of people there
I'm so it could be to be on her brain
Where is it is viceland Vice President of the president
Longfellow first lady being controlled by cat beings
The cat being
Okay
But
Are pretty important
Mark does tell her about the Spanx
Their cat people
They were statues
I think that is correct
I don't remember.
There's another influence
Maybe maybe Marksman watching movies
This is this is crazy
The remaining Sphinx
A human head
From
Cathead and
Contact
On this is a
Black
Panther cat
Being called Contessa
Okay okay
Mark
I also asked her if she was on 10 yet
A lot
To take in
With a black panther
Cat beard
Course
I love it
Take it off
Can't Get Enough
Now calendar
Alright
+ 1.2
It is certain point it really feels like Mark Richards might be f****** with her
Or maybe this is just his way of trying to
Rationalize a rumble that he had with a black prison
And the Black Panther
I don't know I'm driving
I'm over exegesis thing this unnecessary
Why does cat people
Also
Michael B Jordan was great in that Egyptian fight
So
You know recently
Recently sir
The International Community
Decided
You know they
Good reason to believe that
Attacked a spy
In London I believe wasn't right
But
Get this
She wasn't Putin
Regarding the style Spirit attack
You said
Reptoids and Draco when a week in the u.s. Russian Britain
I'm so the aliens continue to pay
He says Putin is not miss
Messi
Pills lots of people that with
Precision
The collateral damage indicates
The Salsbury topless
Carried out by British
For the alien
Wide swath
Either the British
Orthopedia number of alien races
Brought up
She is the black dragon Queen
Could be under the sway of the black drag queen
Maaco in disguise
I don't know I don't think a lot of literal dragon
Portsmouth Portsmouth
Absolutely
Your own player f*** out of here Draco
Go on Planet Hunters
That would also being except
So
I believe it's
Skip this next clip cuz the really all that great
It's just mark
He's trying to stop North Korea and China from killing
Millions of
Himself
Yes
These leaking information is leaking information to carry
In order to stop a war that will kill millions of people
The people and you have
Both the information necessary to stop it and accessed
Right
You could probably do a little bit more than kind of leak it or just hang out with
Could help
Doesn't even have access to a pen
So now we learn more about this Contessa character the Black Panther game
She's got the
Some interesting quirks
We talked about the cat beans and
Tessa Leoni
Panther
Being that
I had mentioned earlier
He said he's written about her in his writing
Available
Defense headquarters site
Here's the problem there's nothing
Thomas.loc.gov which is a reference to
I went to the website
It's crazy
Like
His wife is made a straight-up
501 c 3 nonprofit organization
I have the original copy of the golden bough
Well I mean like the book
Not
Nothing mythical object
B of A
What's the other thing
That they've got together organization
At all
You know I am as much as we can make
I'll be goddamned try and follow through on their ship
So we wouldn't make a 501 c 3
I don't know what that means if you go to the website the earth eventually you'll find that the executive director is Joanne Richards his wife
Course not there's a board of directors with blue my mind
Wait what
You've been on Project Camelot
Do an interview about how much
Mark Richards
I was about to be like what we're doing that episode but I listen to like
Maybe 15 minutes of it and he is a boring ass dude I look further down the list
And one of the people on the board of directors is Lou Wagner
I was like what the guy from chips
Character X
I got to send them an email
I don't know very well
Years old
Very well
Did you swing the guy from chips
He's a good guy
There's there's absolutely no doubt about that
I'm trying to find the the exact
Page that I was on earlier
You could go into the website
Rambling blog
I'm stuff like that but it's all course
It's all for sale
Like it's just they're just selling all his like ratings
Stop
Look for like 40 bucks
You can learn about what happened at Hamilton Air Force Base in the summer of 1950 240 bucks
Play the page count here 40 bucks that one's 384 pages
I don't know I don't know
I don't know if it's
That
Probably written well know he would write it in
In Panama
Torture
302 pages of Bulge
I did ask your wife
Salad
Pipe it
It's the Earth Defense headquarters
Part and parcel of that is Dragon Hill Research Center
Alright you can apply to be a researcher at
Which I B do
Salmo California
And it's apparently in a castle
I'm sorry
A castle like setting
The moment you need to make that
Distinction
You buddy.
A lot of books
Spend a lot of research going on
Expensive expensive collection on Wicca
Mythical in quote
History modern military environmental issues
The research center is proud to own the parliament rolls of medieval England covering 1272
And several volumes of the golden bough
Crazy
I want to go there
Kind of thing
The saddest thing
Probably have
Have a better sign
I want to go there
Absolute
I don't know if my transcripts
This this club isn't done I still have to talk about the Black Panther lady
It's maintained by his wife Joanne rich
And I highly recommend.
That's a great place
She says
Cat things are not
It's time
Open late
Human
Cat races
Open contacts
And that
Detached from Human
Fairs
Marc's only contact
Being
She loves luxury items and has lots of
Kittens
Fast
Okay
Cool we have two legs
She likes luxury items and has lots of kittens
This Bixby
Really sad
Ficklin
But this one
It is this is lazy
I demand better
Different races
Alien races
Ocelot
Salata Lake
Negative
Rue21
I don't know how you can't just like
Be like Mark
Come on
This is ridiculous
Even Carry has to be liked
Give me a little bit more to work with him
Give me more than
Forecast
Species just
Not giving a f***
Just like cat
Sprite
Please who are essentially cats
You know
Look you go run the universe
Catholic
Cats have been around for at least 65 million
Well
If you wanted him to give
His next Club
Turns out we learn a little bit more about the Dutchman
And a very famous person
Had a bit of a disagreement
Thomas Jefferson
Carl Sagan
Stab the Dutchman
Had an argument over the
Voyager discs
Went out into
Say
Basically Marquette
Considered
It gambling with
Charlotte
Okay
Savers
Neighbors
Are already
And this matter
The Voyager didn't go far enough to deal with aliens
Coming from different galaxies
Impossible
There's no waiting for
Aliens were involved in World War II
Look up travel
Does it not the Raptors in the past 5 million years ago
Sagan was there
Mega Man
I love it
We're going
Confirm or deny the story about the Dutchman
Lizard Man species
For sahagun
Whichever it is
Amphibious humanoid sahagun
Now
Shortening
Right
F****** Reptoid he's a f****** Reptoid
Do it the whole time
He wanted to eat that.
So
This whole this whole exercise pushes the realm of credulity
Way too far
It goes bad
Going along with all of it is wild
We do reach one point
Geared towards the end
How do you wind up on a conversation
How do you wind up going from
Aliens
Right that's the biggest takeaway
You don't mind
He's probably like your grandpa and your grandpa
Stereotypical Grandpa's just like I tell you about the time I World War I punched a Nazi
He's talking about like doesn't I don't like soup
I'm sure Mark Richards is the same kind of dude just like
I love to hang out with people who like luxury items
Have different colored skin
Not because of that but you know you can't trust them cuz they work with Draco
Korean to conquering things that humans are against that and have her all the time
But that's just because
Lizard snap
You did not specifically say that the Anunnaki
Worries
Intrinsically
He does everything but he is staying
You can't trust them
Because they do
With those other people them in the past
Therapist
I don't know I just I just agree Terry reaches the point where she's even like a little step
He is a f****** captain in the literal secret space program that saved the world
Right right
Absolutely
But apparently we learn a little something about
Naming
Every insect that was in
Cancel that.
Interior slightly different information
Regarding mantids in Raptors
He said they are now a limo
Lions with humans
I and
That's very in
Interesting and we need to
To talk more about that
Especially with her
Regards the Mantis
Why though
Here's why
Are some recent
Information
From a remote
Viewing by threat
Stewart
And I'm going to be
In an interview
So some guy remote
Viewed something and learned about mantis beings in a ways he's learned contradict
Here's what I just found out about myself
It somehow it makes me way more depressed
When she has to deal with
Two sources disagree with each other
I guess baby video like
Now you're entering a whole being conned by one condom
That happen
If you're being conned by to con men at cross-purposes like a Michael Caine movie
She's calling everybody to cuz she's like
Well she was you know not posting up all these videos
Social media
Accounts and everything was going crazy saying like I'm being censored because we're talkin about this real
Saying that every tragedy in the world is fake and a laundry list of false proof
Of all of this s***
Because rightfully someone complain
It's so she wasn't allowed to stream anymore
Stop and she was saying that her livelihood was being taken away from her
And I'm here to tell you
There's a 40 minute long video there's like five commercials in it
Like throughout
Haverly monetize
In terms of the videos
I didn't take that away
She still making Bank office videos 190,000 followers
Something like that on YouTube how do you get that
Course
It is fun by myself
Lord of the ones that aren't Mark Richards
Boiler alert
Spoiler alert
Somehow remote
Viewing bump
We outboard than Mark Richards
Time travel portals
All of these
Why not
Remote viewing
Text you fart
I think it's because it's getting too specific
Like with Mark Richards
Never really established how are you talkin to these Raptors while you've been in prison for 30 years
Is it in your dream
I don't understand are they invisible Raptors
They come at night when nobody else is awake
Caesars
Plug one
Raptors
That's why I
Evident with the guy from chips
Flipazoo three blue Wagner
I do f****** hope it's the same guy
Really think we can put all this behind us and really dig into what the f*** is going on
With Lou Wagner
Wagner has a website you might have a contact ring on their Elders have any mail
Mark Richards explained
It's Loop
Is on Twitter
Are you on the board of directors
Cuz
From what your name is
Clip
Mark being like
I am never getting out of
Recticare
She keeps trying to have like what what about this what about you can help get you out
Go to prison
Controlled by aliens
Alright
But hold on
Now if Melania isn't alien
Control
Not a control box communication bot
Flexi 3 p.m.
What about the kid
No it's not
Exactly
Catplant
To make it look like it's
Interesting but they got to have their own diplomatic spy in their
How could Faron possibly fit into this Melania is a biologic
F*** alien phone
Can get pregnant
Before I met you
Alien phones can get pregnant with
Never have occurred to anybody in my life special
Chords
Too obvious
This is what it is you don't know that
It's really just Mark Richards door behind them
Weather
He thought Trump would
Release mark
He said
Nope
Trump is scared to death of what Mark and his
Trans the rap
Doctors are capable of
Market Mystic scaring those in power
His contacts
Make him a very real
Threat to their way of life
Right
Interview
You're the problem is
Drops got a lot of
Hello
That's been my problem with him
Holyshit
One of the ones that like there's so much going on
He realized that a little stale I've got to interject new characters you know it's like
Season 2 of Heroes got to have some new Blood characters
Contessa
In which they said the Black Panther was the highest grossing movie in the world
Raptors Jurassic Park
Very bizarre alternator run 88 mph and that get them off-planet
Also he's telling a story about parallel Earths that has mysteriously close to the plot of a show on Starz
Great from season 1 of Game of Thrones
Guy who gets his golden helmet
Here's what I want
Iowa
Make me sad
What I want to talk about
I want to talk about it right the beginning
She was talking about
Okay and what I would like to do I want to bring this back to a board nurses
No no cuz I want to do an experiment
I would like
To throw this out there mark Richards if you're listening
Don't tell Carrie about this
This will be able to visit you for a good
Vinmec
Time she comes to visit
We got to give him something to tell her
We got to see
If he's really this board
If you want to engage
It's got to be a new race of aliens
I would assume you like
Had to bring a cran today because all of the pencils in this prison were burned
And it could be an alien prank dial alien races
Drew
I mean one option is just head
One option is Mark could just yell like bababooey at her over and over again or something like that
We got to put our brand
Ooo
Nailed it
Nailed it failed it
Cat people
Cinema box
Come on
No perfect
No not good
Not good
What is treat people like the ants
Just three people
See I feel like the answer could be
All of the all of the bug species that are popular you got your man
Spider beetle
I like living in a world where were both like
Close enough
Cockroach
So did you got your you got your lizard species and he's not like it he's already got dragged
A gorilla
Cuz that's just an oboe people
Wales
We could do whales we don't have any we don't have any effect we don't have any Mark Mark
We got to bring the aquatics into this the people
They're nice
They're helpful but they will shoot you with some f****** ain't get in and out of everywhere.
Like have you seen not that smart
No other thing than crawling and then doing the thing and then it gets back in the face
Octopus and squid
Not a square
The Dolphins will be super smart
Dolphins are already
Silver dolphin people that's not fair
Squid
Possibility
Mark work with
Cuttlefish
Cuz they're within the same family
But they are perfect camouflage California
On the side of a house
Whale
Is cool
Too big
Squid
Twitter octopus
Twitter your call call
California Raisins
That could be a misconception about that
If you are hearing us and you want to stick it all to us from the outside that you have to what's going on
Good people
I'm around
Oh yeah I could use a portal we would never take money from Soros
But I'll be goddamned if I'm not going to take some money for
I want to eat all this chocolate only off Wednesday show up
Probably want to cut me open and take it out on me
Now that's not how that works
Forever
Frozen
Alex Jones business suit
This genuinely should not Delight me
Still
Never doesn't it's hard not to because you did so great but I'll say this
He's more creative than Alex
So he can't keep coming up with new f*****-up things
Forget these little other things like
Why is the chocolates
Special
Missouri keeps up the old stuff brings the old stuff back to mine wow introducing new stuff
In a way that's
Compelling
Do you know what I find fascinating about it and I think this might be my favor
Is unlike your your other
Where do you keep escalating things and it feels bloated
You don't like like Spider-Man 3 villains and none of them
Azalea you lose the real heart of the character
Kegels
Opposite direction
Instead of paying it back
Kind of focusing on the heart of the
He goes so
Far into the let's make it
The most bloated
Let's go from random messing to random at 6 we're just we're just jumping
From subject to subject
This is
F****** it.
Fury Road of alien conspiracy
Every Fast and Furious movie
Furious movie
With Ant-Man
They weren't in there
That's true proof of raptor wasn't in there.
Done
Crazy
Done.com
We lamented
Impossible to
Recreate
Improv
The Improv that you see if places
They're doing the same
Anywhere Twitter handle of that knowledge
Yes
Autograph
Yeah
That's wonderful
Start absolute
We're also on iTunes
Leave a review
Unprepared
To the end of this episode
There's only one person
From all the
All the stuff that we talked about today deserves
The owners of the end of the
Sonofabitch
Carl Sagan go f*** yourself
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work