Alexandra Thurston color
In this month of May where Jordan is doing a whole lot of stand-up at the
I'ma try and fill my favorite folks
One of the best
Mardi Gras
Good to be back welcome I'd like this we got on we got you on camera in this the sleeveless shirt
Oh s*** I've no idea for all their guns
I thought I actually was identified with Jordan
Two nights ago
And I told him at some point
You do know a little bit about that
We've gotten this criticism from listeners and everytime I come up
I think it's kind of fun
It just kind of the relative knowledge
Sure you know a little bit more probably than Jordan
Ivan keys
He knows more summer immersion
Also forgets a lot though
And even for me to a certain extent like it's kind of just like
We process this stuff we react to it in like
I've had listeners asked me like what episode
With my pocket
Anybody familiar with Alec
Congratulations you guys put out Episode 99
Important to celebrate 100
Libra
Give me five years to
To do
The proper amount of
Yeah that's that's what happens when you get down to business
Protector protect the businesses best
Is possible
I've noticed Alex I think
That you're probably on the same page with me
I think I'm the right
I was very
Before
You know Trump took office
Kind of just ruined
Yeah I know funneh the good name
Muskox
I think also that.
Conspiracy Theory videos
Have been
They're just not as fun anymore it's so important to Stephanie goof around with
Just like
Yeah
You know and then
Listen.
The stuff that my favorite was a couple episodes back on
Canary claims
Your goddamn job I would say because you're an expert in other fields
Such as the wrestling field
Wrestling
Torn maybe sure
I don't need to ask any questions about that. Okay
At all as we like the changing of
50 videos
With this latest event in Saudi Arabia the greatest Royal Rumble
See much how you're probably like
Completely
Unfazed by anything Alex does
Or can I can't be shot a shotgun
Yeah I can't be shot
Are there such a carrot
They talk out of both sides of their mouth
The Bell Pat themselves on the back
Belmont
Yeah wasn't I mean wasn't even Stephanie McMahon's quote they're like philanthropy is the new marketing
Yeah is two-sided
You know there's just a whole lot of stuff
Like that word
Women aren't allowed
Vape that the Saudis
Whoever's in charge
The Saudi royal family or whoever was
Had to put on an apology
Because an ad for back
Play the chode women
We are when I I saw something on like that Reddit squared-circle
It was like
Apology made
Greatest
Thinking maybe next time we will bring women here and
You know they wrestled in the have an interesting conversation.
Yeah and then
No they were like a sorry that there was a video that you saw woman arms
Stomach and super nice butt
Besari
But yeah and it's just you know
It's just
And they got
I'm hearing
Hundreds of
Millions undoubtedly
The staff thrown around of like 25 million or 60 million about the single of
But considering it's part of a 10-year deals imagine it's not in the hunt
But I mean I don't know
I see I see two sides of It kind of with the like
Hey
Maybe this will work
To help make things better in the future
But I also don't
Trust that when did the company run by crazy Vince McMahon right and his going to his wife is in the Trump Administration
So much time doing Faithfully Saudi propaganda on the actual show
David Meltzer who is
You nobody will call the Dan Friesen of
But the in in in the
The newest wrestler
Observer newsletter
He says three years ago Sammy's in russellton
And now he's not allowed back in
So it's like how is that price
That's not
Certainly he bought some for the severity of this situation
I don't know man it's kind of foolish to think of
They being I got a tool for Progress considering the EMT Progressive people behind
Those pictures of like the Undertaker and Curtis
Durango and Brock and Vince
What the f*** those things like I imagined like the Undertaker like Kurt Angle taking a piss
Get ourselves
Brother
Style
I think it's weird
Some people comment on it cuz there's a
There's some wrestling
People have said that like
It's pretty wild the idea that
They allowed
Iranian flag to be flown
Personally
The Brother show
He was
With cv1 play the terrorist years ago Muhammad assigns manager
That introduces a whole nother layer
Sure so he
He have been auntie
Pushing buttons for a long
Long time
Yeah they went there and then re-add to put out a
A tweet like hey I play a role
Yeah
So I mean
San Mateo vet they're still probably part of every wrestler who's
Yeah I still think there's that part of Russia
I felt that way when I was
But no no
In India rank
It's Pakistani
I mean I'm sure they
But that same
You don't like the bad guys in America
We're famous for it weren't Chicago okay with coming on Brett Favre jerseys back in the day they're also going to call
Call Evert cheesehead
Going back and watching
Awesome old stuff and I'll be to watch like the
The rise of stone cold or this crazy match they had or whatever
Bowser watching everyone else will be like oh my God
The worst I'd ever
Worthy
Yeah but using a method of getting heat on somebody or whatever
The one-off
Super Show
And second country yeah
Killing each other I think that's what it's like they've gotten a little too far there
Also not like it's not like there's a
Literal Turf War sports teams in America
Is
You know cuz they were there was that sumo
Well they wanted you
Book test
Now
Oh okay so a couple friends who are just like no no no no
Like a 22 cuz like I was
I was talking to you
My buddy Mike
Comedy
Wrestling fan
Sure but he was like
I think there's like some like
Like little Sally Prince
Geto Boys it's just like
And I want this match and I want this match and I want 50 men in the Royal Rumble engine
He's booking it on his own sound like
Remember the names
The kids from Willy Wonka
Surprised there wasn't no regard
Nevermind
With those guys
Victorville
Come out then
Do you think you can cut it here
You hear from Saudi Arabia you're not going
Cut it here
They could have gotten like the anti or the bad guy
Villain from America if it got in the exact same effect
Being a set-piece now where it's
Kind of a roni
As a as a set-piece as a skit
Weird territory to walk especially
The company is owned by someone who's married to a member of trump
The cabinet
I still give
Like
Linda a pass cuz I still think she's a nice lady
Linda she's the most harmless one she's not like
This is
Is the Linda leftover sympathy from that time when
I will say though it is kind of funny that she
Secretary of Smallville
Yeah they make all the wrestlers
Contractors
Small businesses in the form of breast
He's out of business
When they roll into town.
Get up tell the city
Okay don't let other places
Is Havanese
Irina is no commitment that milk
Stop
Small business east
You know
We still watched
Yeah
I still watch a little bit still
Valex in modern-day
Cuz I just came through moment where I was like everything is a distraction
Everything is b******* this is all nonsense
I'm posting on our group on Facebook about like
Oh my God he's getting in a fight with Ben Shapiro coming on the show
And I keep trying to express the people enjoy whatever they want that's fine but like
This is nothing
This is all a distraction Sheriff was going on and there's no content on
On his show anymore far as I can tell
What's just open up the couple web pages what's going on talk about it
Hibiscus before we can judge
I think he thinks he's an idiot
Okay
Does Alex make it seem like they're boys
Drudge came on the show in 2015 little experience from the Shadows
Camera but you had a Mike he was off camera somewhere
And he was telling Alex
Summer Freddy 2020
He's very secretive
Pictures of em on the internet
You telling how it's all this unbelievable b******* like 1T actually told Alex was
Litwin
The powers-that-be the globalist created Vince Russo
No the other one wrestling in the globalist New World
The right to censor is certainly relevant
Their violation
I'll beat you was telling Alex they when they
Created Isis
They make them
Because they were trying to demonize Daryl Aisa
Who's in Congress
Name of the enemy of the regime
That's fun
He couldn't even keep a straight face while he wasn't joking
He was trying to get Alex to take the bait on the narrative
And it's pretty clear that he looks at Alex's like someone who
He's got a patronize a little bit with like throwing blanks and stuff like that
Yeah I think that's the relation
Did they have
After watching
That Rodger Stone
That really bummed
I just like
Like there's times where I felt like we talked about
The Forum
Man these show should have
Have you on
To be in someone's ear
Ewing Alex like
Megyn Kelly was like interviewing of you could have been
And just like like hey
That's not true and ask him
That was the case
Why do you say this
And you think
Wow
It's like that Megyn Kelly interview
It's a right question
And then it lied to nothing and then when they added it they have to make it look
Somewhat presentable
Media training
And if you do I don't know
Maybe there's
Just like study
That Rodger Stone
Feel like this
Why
Bacon
Trick you guys so much
Enjoy watching
There's no good faith
Who's the guy
His other Michael Brooks
That guy
Knows how to handle those
Smart lift Barbie enough
I like this guy
I like this guy details of policy imitator both are really good at
Really end up getting people trapped like especially particularly libertarian
Whenever they have conversations
They always get stuck
In some
Big problem with libertarian ideology
Where we're going
If you watch that entire libertarian debate
I recommend everybody watch it it's one of the funniest things I've ever seen in my life
Hilarious
It's it's
If they do a patreon exclusive
Each other
Are you at the rent too damn High guy
About this
John McAfee trying to sound
Real
Relevant
Yeah
Who's who
Gary Johnson
Geese teams
So reasonable
Combination
Funny you should bring that up
We've been talking about libertarian libertarian wrestling Alex Jones
And the intersection of those three things
Is an episode of Alex Jones Show
But see what you think about that
Wrestling Entertainment
He is well-known around the world
Underhill
Criminal
Who discovered and we are as well
A free-market educational organization
Pop culture to spread the message of Liberty
As well as appearing on various television
Josh
And he is with us today I love the speech and I saw you the other day
Meeting on C-Span
Obamacare and the attacks
Now rolling on the streets of America
Did that years ago like to have fun very fun things
We're do some comedy from time to time
I would also love it if you did the interview in case or he would have to know
Bad news Caden appears on Alex to incorporate
Yeah okay
I do not have time to look into exactly the storyline he would have been involved in
Well
Probably deppe
No
That that was like
Okay
I don't know
Be wrong
That was like
I guessing that was like
Might be anger anger management years
Ryder John Cena little quadrangle
I mean who knows whatever it was something stupid
I'm going to predict sure storylines from years past I'm going to guess
Real.
Did you took it you know that Cain had appeared on Alex Jones Show
Did not but I am not
Surprised I know he'd been on other shows
Hi
Before that's crazy
Talking about
Yeah
Whenever I heard him talking about a wrestler and take you to Peter down a bunch
Shows
You could give that credit to like John Bradshaw Layfield
Yeah he had his own black syndicated radio show we talked about economics and stuff like that
More credible but
We got the we got the demon
The devil's favorite demon
Is so f****** weird
While
So In that clip you would have heard Alex McCain
I'm not going to Colin Quinn
Kane
Awakening
Due to the Austrian School of economics
MD Von mises Institute
Alex doesn't have the name right
But you wouldn't know what that is
And I'm going to be a real
Public American
It's about
So much people as it is I think stupid okay
And maybe some of the effects of it are end up being evil but I'ma give you a quick rundown of the Austrian
O'Hare
Here's the too long didn't read version of it up top these guys are a bunch of f****** dick okay
The roots of the Austrian School seems mostly based in a strong hatred of f.d.r.
His social programs
Collective larger than the state
Which is
Libertarian
I always have real trouble trying to understand like why do you hate the federal government
The state
When what is the federal government budget
Just stay in the mall Ganesha
Of State
Shouldn't you hate
The city or the state in like the city
And then what about the district and the city or household
That's what you really come down to us
They want everyone to have their own laws
Austrian School of Economics they subscribe to the Austrian business cycle Theory
Which states the central bank's control the business cycle through intentional booms and busts
By manipulating interest
When they make the interest rates low to give out a lot of credit to people with creative bubble destined to birth
First and that leads to a recession
Central banks are the evil one
But
They failed to mention that there were tons of Cycles before the Federal Reserve or central banks were ever introduced
The solution that they generally offer for gold
Peter Schiff who is a frequent guest on Alex Jones Show is appropriate a prominent Austrian style like
Not surprisingly he has his own operation
I also you know Piazza frequent guest on Alex's show witch's indicated by a man who owns a gold and silver
Company
For twenty years
Another famous gold sales
Tell him that close he's broken guitars in the wrestling business
Are you talking about GG
Slapnuts gold Double J was starting Global Force wrestling
Going to be
Jarrett's the king of
Get s*** done
He can key is the guy to get shot
His wrestling career has just been
Tubelight
Outside of derbies bobblehead
Everywhere he's gone
Even back in the day
But even within a you telling me that story while back cuz I was watching back through I don't know
Extorted the WWE
Was ending
If you do China they were this good
Embarrassing very embarrassing everyone
If I'm going to lose
To China
You can hit me with a mop I'm getting
A lot of my
Abasing made him
Years worth of
Music I need
Tell the wife
It's in the bank
Alright let's do it
Bethel got a car in a gyro covered in
Is big
And
And then it was a big enough
Okay
Buy gold
From Global Force vaguely remember that
But I remember like people that work there
Guys what
Weeden
Now what
Yeah it is
Takeoff it's crazy but you start to notice this real trend of what they call gold-bug
We're just selling gold and confused with skulduggery
Nefarious
Action
The
Conspiracy in libertarian worlds you'll just fine
People who are telling you to buy gold it's the only safe thing to do
And you scratch beneath the surface a little bit you find a financial interest in gold,
Huh
And it's weird but we're going to talk a little bit more about that little bit later okay because I did some looking into it and I found the roots
Will Alex slippers
Tough guy
Weather
Became like
Alex bingo card
He's going to mention that
You know you want to make a bingo
Vype
Dimension Devon Erickson Texas
I think he's going to
Mention
Rocks Don't color
Apocalypse
Where the hulkster is
You know what you would not get Bingo I'll tell you that right now but I want
I don't know I don't want to give him a ride. Alright alright
So back to school real quick and other people other like
Schools of economics
Chicago score
Anyways other
Schools of thought
Guys that they believe that individual choices and actions of the only relevant factors in economics
Statistics of economic modeling
Statistics exactly crazy because they believed that Society can't act
Society of the person only person
Boy okay
Find whatever
Empirical evidence
Willfully obtuse
Because they
I think that
Statistics empirical evidence
Are biased because people make decisions
They cannot be captured
Vixen models
In reality they do this by
Because it is not a school of economics
It's a front to push severe in ridiculous libertarian politics out
As an economic theory
When you look into it a little bit most of the players such as well and Murray rothbard
Those are two major players in the Austrian School of economics
They are having organizations like the Cato Institute
A deeply troubling ties to the John Birch Society
Emirichu a quote
About rothbard here
Ross Barra faction since 90
Rothbart
Describes himself as a member of the old right faction since 1946
Was it Jewish New Yorkers supported Strom Thurmond states rights party in 1948
Conservative success in establishing themselves as the only alternative
Rothbard called for a Resurgence of the old right to quote
Fuel the 20th century
Alator Alliance
Limited to what he considered good libertarian
As described in the 1990 issue of the John Birch Society is New American Magazine
This would mean purging undesirable elements from the libertarian party including quote
Hippies druggies
Antinomian zand militantly anti-christian atheist
If you don't know what else
If you don't know what antinomian czar
They're people who believe in the New Testament of the Bible
Specifically the Jesus is Grayson sacrifice were fulfillment of the law and freed people from Moses's Old Testament law
He wants to purge people from the party who don't subscribe to Old Testament law
That sounds very much.
Legos libertarian values Iver
Absolutely what you want to do
Don't eat shellfish
Oh no
Debate the viability of states seceding from the Union
Which they are really into
El Super in
Sure
Denise Institute
Is based on a major player what are the
Intellectual grandfathers
That was a major player
Austrian School of economics
It was named after him
Any sort of beat what one of the big
Think tanks
Publishing houses for
These
Weirdo libertarian ideas
Masquerading as school of economic thought
I don't know I want to
I read a bunch of
Public post
Spider meets Institute but they're like soda policy position and all of them
It's going to be too much
I'm getting know what I'm going to do is I'm going to read you one and then a little bit later
If you can hear just how f****** stupid
People are okay
I'm going to start with the other take on a Christmas
Carol okay
You don't get no That's a classic Christmas movie sure you got screwed
Yeah you got the ghost
She got Marley Jacob Marley
Money and beer
It's not the message they took away from it
Titanic now they're really like it being cool to be a miser
In the store money
Because they believe basically that if you saved buddy that's investment in future thing
Which is good
When in reality there's a people Gathering up billions of dollars that isn't being circulated doesn't help anybody
So they believe that actually the Bob Cratchit
VA employee
Is the villain
Christmas parade
Scrooge from
Because he's he's making undue demands
Just by virtue of his existence
Unscrew has every right to his money
Here's a quote from their write-up about it
So let's look without preconceptions at Scrooge's allegedly underpaid clerk Bob Cratchit
The fact is if Cratchit skills were worth more to anyone than the fifteen Shillings weekly there would be someone
To offer it to him
Thugs no one hasn't said scratch its profit-maximizing boss is hardly a man to pay for nothing
Scratch it must be worth exactly is present wages
No doubt Cratchit needs is a want
More to support his family and care for Tiny Tim
But Scrooge did not pour scratch it to father children he's having difficulty supporting
If Gretchen had children while suspecting he would be unable to afford them not screwed is responsible for their plight
And if didn't know how expensive they would be why am I screwed assumed the burden of cratchit's misjudge
That's for that one lump of coal Scrooge allows him it Bears emphasis the Cratchit has not been changed his chili desk
If he stays there
He shows by his behavior that he prefers his present wages
Comfort package
To any other he has found or supposes himself likely to find
Actions speak louder than grumbling
And the reader can hardly complain about what Cratchit evidently find satisfactory
This sounds like
What I really nice
Nice Republican with
McDonald's
If you don't like it go get a better job
You don't work here you stay wherever you are while you're being attacked
Stop having them.
Kids yeah
Especially ones that come out
Charles Dickens wrote Christmas Carol
Look at Charles Dickens
He was born into like a well-to-do family too much money
His dad Father John
Was committed to a debtors prison
And London because he owed too much money
That point
Dickens was
12 years old
He was forced upon his collection of books leave school and go to work at a shoe black and Factory
A dirty and rat-infested Factory
The change in circumstances gave him what his biography of Michael's
Personal
And social outrage
Which influenced his works
Because Charles Dickens lived the reality of these hypothetical bulshit thing
But these dumbasses at the Von mises Institute are talkin about
Himself exactly everything was fine up till 10
On those books and go black some shoes
And I say hi to rats
Bucked up
Gamble on himself
Haha
Absolute
But he you know
Ryan
Is work ended up having like a really socially-conscious vent to it be
Because
He experienced
Child labor
Experience
Debtor prison stuff like that crazy how
You can look at anything
And be like
My take on that and everybody else
Like somebody shared a meme
Are you off
I'm on but only to really use our group I don't really
I don't engage much
Somebody post
A meme
That
Clearly
Lunatics
Is the guy who stopped
Yeah yeah
Shooter at Waffle
With his bare hands
So next time
Cops
Next
Intimidated by
Play blackmail mix
Helicopter
Who boy
Think twice about that
Wow that's hot
Yeah this is I mean did I
Heroically in the face of Catholic
Are there mutants
But that's the world we live in now you have this
Just like
Is that what it was
Two words just like
I'd never let my
I could watch that in your like wine
Because of this business you're like
Where did you go
Christmas carols oppressing Scrooge like this
Top music
Little better
Interesting
I could see an argument against Christmas Carol again
Some of the material is a minute
Like a goose
Yeah I don't know I'm trying to rip some complain I don't really have one
I don't know I don't like Christmas much so it's never been my favorite butt
Yeah this argument
Stupid
As it turns out
Glenn Jacobs
Call Zona
The interview and here's what
What do you want to talk about
Libertarian and economic circles right now
First of all
That's interesting
That's really fun that you like competing currencies Glenn Jacobs also known as came
I keep forgetting to call and Kane
Here's the thing
Everybody other glibertarians loves talked about
Competing currency
Please know that s***
Government free currency
Electro gold
Spoiler alert in the Austrian School anime
Student
And even
Kane is going to say this later
Bitcoin's great
That sort of thing
I'm so interested
Competing currencies
Did you know that we've tried that before
We've tried this
So early in our history individual Banks printed their own currency
Which word exchangeable for gold and silver
Before the passage of the national Banking Act in 1863 up to 8,000 different entities issued
Their own money
Just different banks
You had tons of banks
You guys take a
Chase money here
Cuz there's a whole situation where like
Charters for banks in the United States like New York and a couple others
They just had Free banking if we could just
Make up your own bank or whatever
I want to print out some sort of promissory note
In order to like
Have people have your currency
Interstate Commerce Act like I've Got a New York
Work dollar here
And it's worth in New York but if I go to Michigan let's say maybe they only accept
Now your money is worth less in different places
It's absolutely insane
Also
Who knows
Who honors what currency
You might end up in a place where you got tons of buck
Like
Are they going to be honored at every store in West Virginia
Who knows
Also a comically easy to counterfeit money
Except
Cuz there's so many of course so many f****** currencies
Look at it I D from
Indiana here in Illinois they look at it like 4
What is today
Any fake is good out of say it
Absolutely you can or you can't possibly train people to
Be able to tell if he like
This is valid currency complete Madness
So of course
This
National Banking Act of 1863 habitat
It was right in the middle of the Civil War so historical revisionist look back on the app doesn't temp by Lincoln
To centralize power in and states rights
But in reality it was trying to save
The entire
Try to knock off the b*******
Interesting bit of trivia do Marty
The Confederate States also printed and on their bills
Which kind of hurts their argument that slavery was not an important piece of the secession
Also
Two US presidents were featured on their money
Two presidents who mysteriously the right-wing and Alex Jones
It's their favorite
George Washington
Editor Jackson we're on
Confederate money
Yeah
I think they are
Pictures of
You know like it made it look like
Slavery wasn't so bad
David sort of a Kanye West Selah
Also has lost almost 50% of its value in the last 5 months
Also 1000% increase in value in the five months before that
It's a completely inconsistent currency
Is very dangerous
And if you don't have money to lose you
Competing currencies
Before and it does not work
It doesn't it's not
There's even more evidence of this
If your if your came
And Alex
It's kind of like
Have you out he has you on his show
Adidas like so
We will talk about
When you going to be like I don't know man it's your show why don't you f******
Figure it out
Say something okay
But also
Another thing with its Monopoly of currency thing is the Federal Reserve System
And another libertarian
F****** hate that Federal Reserve
Think about
Is that
The reason that
Federal Reserve exist
Is it between 1836
1913 we didn't have a central bank
The second American Bank Charter ended
Until 1913 we didn't start up another one which comes in the form of the Federal Reserve System
Isn't One Bank
District Banks
Better run by a board
There's another f****** thing
But like
To audit them just not you might want
It's not like they're not being audited at all that there might be no money in there or something like that but
So here's the thing
The reason that it started in 1913
It's because we had
Major Financial panic
In 1873 which lasted a couple years 1884 18
80s
I got eighteen eight
1893 Attica juxtapose couple numbers
Since 1913 we've only had truly
Three major Financial panic
In 100 years
As opposed
The week periods in that 34 year span
It is done in
Incredibly well good ratio
This money goes up as money goes down
What are you going to do how are you going to protect people the Financial Federal Reserve System is done a spectacular job
Other complaints that you can make about it some of them might be valid but in terms of Psych
Protecting people
And their assets
It's done
That's okay
It is
And Alex is trying to come in with a cattle prod
Kane is going to pay a little bit more about that
I have
On the market
Where's the beef
Economic history
Because of what they are and I really feel bad
Bitcoin
Inference
Monopoly
Very well said plush
Independent
We've got to have some concerned investing
Other than gold
Do we have any concerns about investigating anything other than gold
Golden rules
Jerker Goldberg
Pick-n-Pull back we're back to that
I don't know man I think that they're trying to sort of dance around the issue that all cultures have valued
Precious metals
Yeah we're not taking into account that like a lot of them didn't have a monetary value for them they just valid them cuz they were shiny
You'd end up with cultures
I mean even in
Fairly modern times it would have
Gold ever to be like
Temecula
I don't think it looks nice
Or whatever
Gold bro
No-go
Need to know nevermind
I got
The idea of going back to the gold standard is really appealing to these people like Cain and Alex Jones which is a weird group
I never thought we'd there's someone
B of A
Doomsday prepper
Type of men
Roped in there
No they're victims of a really think they could live in like this
The society we live in
And be like
Like they're victims of a centuries-long Khan
Basically
Some of it comes from the fact that in the early times like in the late 1700s and early 1800s
The United States did
Coin
That was made out of actual gold
The gold
Being printed and made into
DuQuoin
In the same way that nickels and dimes were
That on some level off a little
Block of gold or whatever you have like a brick
And you just
Bitcoin ATM
Around some places now
So that allows you to like
Exchange Bitcoin for cash
You're still getting cash
Yo it's still
Only a secondary way for you to get
I'll talk now
Not physical
Arthur our friends far out big shout-out to far out he has a little
Someone gave her a bit
Someone gave it to me like a long time ago nice worth a bit
So it's not
He's not a millionaire
Kind of pissed off that I didn't buy when it was like $0.35 and hold on to it now
Get out five months ago it was
Almost 20 grand
Great I think there were
Dropped 50%
I would have to assume there's a lot of people
I was going to buy some BB stock
What it was
Should I look at it look it up but check on that
Be higher now
Do you think the
Do Saudi Arabia show help their stock
Possibly
3.8
CS up
Look at this
Over the last
Year
Woo
What
Double DIN about they have there
About that
It's still pretty pretty nice and I've double on your investment over a year stand USA
But that
USA I have no idea how to answer that question
The possibility
Impossibility not a possibility
Play
I can't imagine
Cannot play with fox
Rob go on
Okay
The cable channel
Be straight up
Local news Outer Road wgm
Lineup that's it
So
That's a possibility was Smackdown going to like
Like FS1
Sports analyst
Taking off
They left you a text
You know cuz you just answer to leaving them in the lurch
The be brand anyway they always try
Hey what's weather jessb live now
Here's a
But it wasn't the whole time right now
But it's ever been
Means something
I thought it was just gone for maybe five
6 years old
Furlough
Do the Nashville Network
Venipede
Spike TV
Spike Lee tried to get involved
The government would like
Add
But copyright Spike
When they decided
To go back to the USA Network
They were having their last straw this last this route was a
I kept mentioning will be on USA
Beeping am out
Okay okay
That's great
That strategic thinking
I respect the hell out of it
Seems like a long-standing relationship
Well they help each other
Because they bring in
Big ratings
Cable
Channels that's what the
USA content is not great
Well so shows that I assume
I can't imagine people watched
The big deal July
I love suits
Lady married to the prince doesn't mean the show is good
Monk was a big hit
Mongoose huge suits
Munch
Mr. robot
Bike
Psych was on USA right
I've never seen any
I can name shows but alright no f****** idea what they are. USA is full of
USA
Church welcome
That which I don't think
Meijer was a doctor
Something like
Not
Doc Hollywood
It was something like that where he was like a Hollywood doctor
Royal Pains Royal Pains
Mother was the guy from
Road trip
Paulo costanzo
What is a stoner from
When the health explain
Breckin Meyer what the rump like
Cuz he was really high all the time and like wrestling
Yeah the guy who wasn't wasn't Tom Green
Paulo Costa
Tanzo
Also star
Josie and the Pussycats
Star is
Was that right up your alley
I love it so much
Great soundtrack
Picture love it
Show band
We've two I think we've talked about this before
I think
As I recall bif naked was involved
But I don't know
She did all of the music
But I don't
I do you watch the video for
3 small words
Yeah that's the big single
And walk away with is like
Is not good at pretending to play drums no no way they played their own oh no
Wasn't Rachel Rachael Leigh Cook
Rosario Dawson Rachael Leigh Cook
New
Big independent
Realtor
He was always better than than her career deserve back then
Eyeglasses when she's hot
She's All That
That's it
I think
The great satire
It's pretty funny yeah
It's a
It's dark material
Okay I like that I like it
It is obscene there were I felt like there were those kind of booze
I figured this was a thing
The late 90s as one might have been to borrow that joke at that end of the 2011-12
I'll tell you that
I have long road trip the other the other weekend and I just
Ruined everything
I hate to sound old but it was just a simpler time
Josie
Because this one
Scooby-Doo
Cats
Every once in awhile take
Did the Mario Brothers
Johnny legs
Would they would do one of those
They would make it real
Weird you're like all this
You just
It happened
I'm in the whole plot
The like
Creating a band
And how pointless the people in the band of disposable they are in a cow
Abusive the music industry is to the people inside it
No not a chance
Anyway
We're a bit off track and I don't remember
Cryptocurrency
Maybe gold
We got off on that
Yeah
Shows
Did we
Yeah
Possibly remember I was talking about how they were going to leave
USA Network
Is that they made gold and silver coins
This is one of those things
Oh man
So
In the 17 and 1800
I don't want to teach you a glass
But this resistor might they was one of your thoughts
You don't Kevin
Smith
Did you hear his
A story about that or anything no but I saw it
About it and I felt so
I felt sympathetic
Yeah I don't know I lost track of Kevin Smith and I would say five years probably
Tibet
Like I like Scott Mosier a lot and all but
I got that look way
Hypothetically talked about sucking dicks while they're really hyper
Walkaway
Hip slang
I would like that
Cat dick
Save the world
Innocence of life
His career fascinates me and
How he sort of
Figured it out or whatever but anyway
He was
I was to do his part
About his
Heart attack
And
When he was on the
Cooperating
Table
Condor
He was thinking
I thought about you
Wow
You have to save my life
The doctor just got
I'll see what I can do
Whatever
Can make it
Operational song
Some people have lamented the n
Yeah
34 years of age and you're like
I can't talk about that tween drama and more this. This the show
Degrassi going on
Oh yeah that works original
I believe I think
The Ennis people watched
I'm sure it's good I'm sure I'm sure it's a positive thing for
But I just
I can only talk about it for about 2:00 or so and then
Then I got to check out
Giving pages
Rapper that guy
I just saw the graduations Lauren Collins
Good job Lawrence
The weirdest things happen in my life
To get him on the Pike
New wrestlers wrestlers are child actors
From Canada
But I've also been very public about that I don't want it
The idea of him showing up
We say don't
But hey at 7 so they were talking about you on this
Joked around about what it would be like if
If you dated this
Don't do that
We want that world
He wouldn't tell me that for sure I know that
Yeah I know that unless he wants to impress me or something
Man
I don't know
Is Billy Corgan
He
He seems like he loves Alex you know
It really does you been on a lot really does
And I think he can really
Alex the smart is a very smart
Celebrity interviewer
Really pump
He make Billy
I feel like it's a
The king
So lucky to have you here
Although
But that's
Recall strfkr
Sure that's called being like
Manipulative
He does that with just about any dangle that cared about being with the wizard
Person sexually and
Front of him
Did you get into that
He won't he
This is when he writes a book
It was a lizard person
He told Rogan that
I have
People I've got to watch
I will say this cuz I like to make
And a lot of s*** talk
When he talks about the music industry
Fascinating
He's clearly
A bit of a wounded
He's got up
It's like yeah
He feels I think he wanted to be the guy and because of the time that he came out he was never the guy that guy because
You just happen to be the same
In class with a lot of
Nirvana
With very Poppy
But like
If pimping was super bitter
Sure I would like getting cuz you eat
Be Jordan yeah you can't and then I think
He still won't quite let go that like it's cool it was cool to be Pippen
He still can't quite
You know like
He still like there is ways where he
Michael stay like
You know how we did
Can we put up with
Double H nobody
Like it's interesting
He clearly has like forever come out
Cuz there was a double album
They're hiding there.
Is that like
And in both cases
Could have been a single album
There's that there's that thing I think Alex
Kind of brings them back
Being worshipped
Well I mean a billion very interest
Thoughts about the
Celebrity
I think everybody has something to
Iuka
Talk to you and like if you talk to them long enough they probably have some interesting insight into
One thing
I don't know how to jump back into this
We got we got it okay
What's the next topic
Talking about how it's like we should
Get more into gold bring back the gold standard
I don't know I don't know if this is what we're talking about but I'm just going to talk about
Weekly reading
We got in this cuz I
These guys are all like
Oh yeah yeah
I've been conned what it was
Found it
Who's 5 years ago
Okay
The problem with making coins out of real precious metal
Is that
The price and the value of those Metals fluctuate wildly
Last year's dime
It has x amount of silver in it
Bond value of silver goes up or down in the next year you have to make dimes that adjust to the silver content
Are you either make them with less rights over or more silver in them in order to keep the price consistent
Or value of that dime
Or
You have to just
Assume that last year is Diamond worth more than a dime
Just assume that doesn't really have a value attached
Also want these
It's kind of more
Porter porter
Gold people be like
Michael
That wasn't so much of a problem back then and I'll explain why
That is going to come into a little bit
A further problem
Is exemplified by what happened in the late
1820 huge silver veins were found in Western United States
What happened
Situation like that is
Live silver goes up massively
And the price goes down drastically
The only way to avert these sorts of events
Wikipedia artificially manipulate the public
Perception of the silver Supply which at its core is exactly what the Federal Reserve does
With restricting or
Expanding the money supply in terms of dollars in order to justify and rationalize
Otherwise
All your money is going to become valueless if
Some random occurrence happy
Especially with pressure
Precious metals
One of the reasons of really rich people love the system that was in place with the the golden silver stand
We had waited bimetallic standard
For a long time
The reason I loved it was because things
Like the bland-allison ACT
Which was passed in 1878
I require the government to buy between two and four million dollars
In silver at Market
Good prices from them in order to make coins
Literally
A government subsidy of
People who
On the lot of gold and silver automatic every year
In order to subsidize their businesses
So
For that is one of the big reasons that really rich
People pushed for
Keeping those systems in place
Does it matter
F****** ton of money off this scam on it
And that continues to this day in Summit to some extent or these that mentality not the
They need to buy all this to make coin in Warsaw got like nickel
And now
Useless Metals in our coins
FDR
Is largely credited in blamed
Trending the gold standard
But in reality was Richard
Who ended the convertibility of gold to cash
For that there was still
Not necessarily
Strict Ian of gold $2 or anything like that
It had been
Diffused by FDR
But if anyone wants pointing finger at anybody
About gold stuff
She probably wanted
Yeah there's a lot
Disease that you suck
That was meant for
Okay
I feel like anytime breaking this information out and they
It ruins our flow
It ruins the fluidity of just rambling about others have Smith
Billy Corgan
Degrassi theme song Josie and the Pussycats
Well let's jump
You want to talk more
Okay
That is the problem
Dollar coin
And then
Handle
History demonizes
The idea of computer currency
I'm fascinated cuz in that Cliff Cain is totally right and totally wrong at the same time about what
What happened with Bitcoin
Cuz since 2013
You saw that like train leaving the station baby
20 people
Worried about $9,000 a coin
It's exactly what happened but it wasn't because people demonized it over there some sort of
Nefarious conspiracy against
It's just
It's an honor
Stable
With a guy
Like cane
What sort of rude
Await him
To the office
Charge
You're talking about him being for the governor
Apparently
Right for the Republican nomination at 4,000
And he got like 30
So he's going to cry
Okay
Well but maybe the Democratic primary wasn't all that interesting Maybe
I don't know
I think it's a wedding
And once he's won
But do you still only 117 okay
They got they got
Way more votes
But there's still a chance
Vote is such a slim margin is jaundice
You've got to look at it
There's some
Number of votes
That like
Still haven't
Yeah we'll see
But I mean
It'll be answering to see like
What is hair
Play me Ventura talks about like when he became
Jesse for the people
Watching
He talks about some of the rude awakening is that he had
I think a lot of it does comes on Alex
The show
There's so many times that Alex wants
What's the talk about like
Real bizarre libertarian ideas and like
Closing the border and stuff like in Japanese
I've been in the State House
Lake in the kitchen
Likes
Taxes in
You understand I was in there
Call that
I think I'd give Kane word to get in have
Fake
Government employees
Giving Alex
Barely.
I don't know what the responsibilities of mayor has
In terms of like big-picture stuff
He might not have a come-to-jesus moment
Yeah he might have a come to
Like
Yeah yeah
Do you mind
Realize how difficult it is to cooperate
You can't
You can't have these
Hardline
Libertarian believe right
That would've been a fun character
Parks and Rec
Leica the libertarian
Kind of like Ron Swanson was but like or less
Bike
Give this a try and then
So
This is the reason why
Like getting along wouldn't work
Going to read you another thing from the
Von mises Institute
Institute
Alex has the name wrong
Can make me have a name wrong a bunch this is about blackmail
What exactly is blackmail
Is he offering to trade something usually silence for some other good usually money
If the offer of the trade is accepted the blackmailer maintains his silence in the blackmailed pays the agreed-upon price
If a black male offer is rejected the blackmailer May exercise his right to free speech
And publicize the secret
There's nothing amiss here
All that is happening is that an offer to maintain silence is being made
If the offer is rejected the blackmailer doesn't know more than exercise his right of free speech
They're fine with blackmail the mugger is offering a possibility
To keep your life if you give them money
Yeah buddy you could make more up later down the road if you decide not to give the mugger money
That's your choice but you can also get murdered possibly
Also threatening
Emotional violence
And also hate guess what
Bunch of blackmail is based on this makes me want to Blackmail.
Based on information that you got
F***** up memes
Somebody yeah
There's legal ways that you can get
Information about people
And then use it to Blackmail our blackmailer
Probably usually come across that
Information in Sumner
Nefarious means we just heard
Kevin Knox
Kevin Hart
ShopRunner s******
Just found out it was
That's crazy
But I mean
He has the right
And if he
Chooses
That that
See this is what I want to get to release
Specifically
Is that Libertarians like
Trot around
15 is even going to say as much
It just say like you know what
How can anybody disagree with us
Sure all we really want is the most freedom for everybody and I remember
Hearing about this
College
Like what's a libertarian
Do whatever you want
Just don't bother me man
Yes it's down to hippy-dippy in like kind of cool Wonder
Yeah it's great except
Problem is when you really get down to what the beliefs are with
A lot of libertarian
I want to paint with a broad brush there's
There's different it's not a homogeneous group or anyting
A large
Large portion of the libertarian Community is
Super f***** up oh yeah it's very sexy
To those people
Yeah that's like oh what yeah I'm not Democratic Republic
I'm at Liberty
And a lot of it comes down to making bizarre rationalization
To retain your wealth
And baked bizarre arguments as to why you can be a people
Like
Hey
I'll give you an argument why you shouldn't blackmail people
F****** dick move
So he remarried one more real quick just to really bring this f****** home
Here is one of their beliefs about parents
Quotes
A parent does not have the right to aggress against
His children
But also did not have a legal obligation to
To feed close or educate his children
Such as such obligations would entail positive X
Coerced upon the parent and depriving the parent of his rights
The parent therefore may not murder or mutilate his child
And the Outlaws parent from doing so
But the parent should have the legal right not to feed the children
I eat you allow it to die
Therefore may not properly compel the parent to feed a child to keep it alive
This rule allows us to solve such a vexing questions as
Should a parent have the right to allow a deformed baby to die
EG by not feeding it
The answer of course is yes
Following from the larger right to allow any baby weather deformed or not to die
Though as we shall see below
In a Libertarian Society the existence of a free baby Market will bring such neglect down to a minimum
You want to buy
I have a baby I don't want it you want a baby you have money I want that
What's the problem
Why are you getting in the way of Commerce I feel like Libertarians
It's burdening you with a responsibility with your child
I feel like libertarian
Are kind of like
Sociopath
Guess who just want to get rich
And it's like or orbit
Comfortable
It's like they have no heart
So it's just like the guy don't
Mcscrooges wrong at all
Clothing
By Mike it yet
I should not have a
Constable for this thing
People being good
Partners in a row
I can't even imagine
I think so often
Is that like
It is being a monster sociopath
Time will
You constantly
We hear from these assholes
Is it like even in the blackmailing example later in that article
Is there a moral responsibility
Who cares
That is
Why would you recognize
Senior defensive
Not speeding kids
Probably deeply immoral
Special like that
For the
Scrooge example
Black male cats
Why are those your example Libertarians also or contrarian by Nature
Are the positions will see them take
AirG
Intentionally
You know how to read Michael does comedy ta reverse Engineers yeah yeah
Politics
Libertarians like to say the n-word on stage
Bright jokes
For those are whatever I think it's a lot of stuff where
Yeah I can
I think it's a little that the shock in the
Contrarian
I don't like that will guess what I'm going to show you why it is
Okay
Blackmail peep
It's pretty remarkable in comedy
Because all you're trying to do is make people laugh
Is it weird
Like
They also driving should be
It should just be illegal because hey Manuel.
Navigation
Be at the argument is that like
Being drunk isn't
The crime
The crime is that you killed someone o-okay
Yeah course
Say that
If you get home without hurting anybody
Rape that already works
You know
Even with it being illegal you're never going to get pulled over in Lazada
You know you have your car or you don't swerve
People are like I'm not paying taxes and here's why
It's kind of like I'm very drunk and here's why
All those are the same
Sure
Crazy cabbie
The Howard Stern Show
Yeah he's probably a libertarian
Yeah it's wild man I do respect on some level
Great marketing
Feeling on
Back the layers though and I think we're going to do a much longer
Josie the Pussycats
So much of it really boils down to like
Trying to make rationalization
Four states to secede from the Union
Sure it comes down to like trying to break up the United
States on some level
These guys is like
Show me your
Through a day
In the life
Your perfect Society
I mean like
I don't know what it would property
That's my god-given right is my kind of my property
Came over a little bit later in the day or pissed off that I killed him and buried him in a shallow grave
Okay well you're what are you going to do about it what's the recourse for weak vocal cord
Deep alliances with that local Court
They found in my favor and then
They have their own Court
Absolutely not
I have a lot of money in your spine
I ended up giving me $5 until the be on your way
Not redeemable any anywhere else
But if you give them to me I will give you gold I don't know I don't know probably not
It's a very bizarre
If you want to buy any
You can I sold six kids already
Yeah my wife is pissed
I've even yet even though Utopia version of like this like this
This presumption that sounds good like more freedom for everybody
That presumption even
Taken to like what their version of more freedom is
It just says away their sucks and even when you get there it sucks
I don't want to live alone
And a mountain
They don't it comes down to an idea largely
Christian reconstruction
I want to recreate the United States
As a Christian Nation
Yeah where they don't have to
You deal with gain
They don't want to have to deal with black people they don't want that is there a gay libertarian
Party
It's not a party
Party I want to go talk to them as right now it's a party
I don't think I don't think there's a strong gay libertarian faction
The log cabin republican Republic
Yeah there's a
Navigate Republic
That's a great to another song
Alma de Republic
They was talking about like slavery is a choice
Republican
Jared what Nas black Republican
I have not now
It wasn't on Illmatic and I'm not listening
Also he's have a new album coming out
Kanye West which might be
Be part of
Kanye West in media blitz
I didn't
It's awesome tweets about it
The show is that
I'm largely emotionally checked out of all of this stuff that's going on because I'm already convinced the Kanye
Trolling everybody
Yeah basically
He's doing the outside of a large-scale think
Peace in some way
Yappy unfortunate consequence of it is that
We live in right now is way too dangerous stuff like that like
Stunt stand
It was okay
Now you can't
Can try to stand
Create more stands
I would argue
Find write the song
Not fine
Stir the pot like that and I'm not sure if that's what he's doing cuz there's a decent chance
Is wrong
Talking with everybody
You have
Militant
Angry
White nationalist forces at play
And
You
Phora
Pretend to be on their side
Yeah
It really
It really can cause
A real problem
The ripples to it that are not like
You can't account for
The light in the same way you put a little better
Silver in a dime today and who knows what it's worth tomorrow
You retweet
Conservative propagandists
Yeah and say like
This is great stuff
Are Carnival row
Affected
Very f***** up and that's why there's an outside chance
That he would go on
Infowars
But I don't think you would understand
An elaborate
Infowars
Perfect perfect
But I don't I don't think you understand what the ramifications that way
But yeah I really don't I don't think that most people
Who know about Alex understand
What he's really about
Butcher
Jones
Infowar
Guy
Oh no
Benefit a lot of return business
Infowars
But you're just like put me on every show I went to Market
Get my book or whatever.
Perfect
Spoiler alert I don't think King never came back
Caden come around this time of year I think he might have gotten the message
That
I was like
How to talk to your pal
The bad for business
This is not what's best for business
So at this point the show we get into a course
Every libertarian
And the Alex and Kane are no
Gan-gan
First of all I would argue that you take the sports stadiums out of there any Transportation safety administration
Creation has a reason to be on Road
But the other thing that he's staying there the end there Alex
It's like when the reality is we got to have guns and everyone in order to
Be safe
Professor John Donahue
Right to carry laws
Show an increase of 13 to 15%
In violent crime rates
In the Ten Years After
The inaction of those laws
The quote.
There is not even the slightest hint in the data that the right to carry laws reduce overall violent
Crime
Also in 2013 and study by the National Crime victimization survey
Found that 99.2% of violent attacks
In the United States
No gun is used in self-defense
It's like no one another person
.8% of violent attacks
In any way involved the defensive
Gone
13 to 15% increase
In violent crime in places where people are allowed to carry guns
With right
Scary alarm
You start to see a picture where no everyone having guns is more f****** dangerous yet
Did John Donahue the guy who wrote that study
Get a really good analogy that he made
That's like
Allowing everyone to have guns is sort of similar to
Do you saying I want to get a brain scan every week to make sure that my brain is healthy
And like well yes you will detect whatever tumor might be there
We're going to get radiation
Can poisoning
From that so it's
It's that same sort of thing it's like
Not taking into account all of the factors that are there
It is imagine the scenario where
He's getting
Gift mug filled out a gun
If you go on Alex's website you got info
Bright
Scroll down a little
It's always going to be
Story of
The guy
You know it was at the
Convenience store
Getting rods he pulled out his gun
It's always
They celebrate
Tell stories they love those are 8 years
Sure tell em that it's that way it's either the
Hades record
Gigi's gangraped
This woman
In front of her family
The hay this hero was at a McDonald's that was
Been held up Anita
Texas gun out in
And took out the the robber
Waffle House
False flag
Also not talking about that fundraiser and gave all the victims
Also not talking about how the guys who got arrested at Starbucks agreed to a $1 settlement from the
They'll be more money for small business
How to pronounce complete bulshit all of the things that you seem to believe in by everybody else
Which all you have is your bigotry which you shall have you showed a couple episodes back
That
He was for the
People getting
He what he was be with Aunt doing it for the Vicky was it at Port of the victim
I was just like
Oh Alex
Yeah
Add some of the right side of history and we were a little too far I think
Shotguns
Guns are great around on the eclipse
Prim8 where it is much as he agrees with Alex's statements
On his own accord about guns
At all
Airport
Every week
Of his life
Together combine
But
Where is that club
It's got to be somewhere
You realize how many flights
Buttermere baby drives a bit too
Coachella pretty close to each other but they fly
Places then drive to the
The shows
That is not a flight every we going to play Never
Yeah probably
Not like came out
20 years
Yeah that's true
That's true he talks about the IRA I didn't include this clip cuz volume answering but all you really says is like the idea
Of the TSA at the airport to the violation
The 4th amendment
Unreasonable
What they
I'm just trying to get on a plane why do I have to be searched by
I agree to Annex
But I disagree with what they would think
Is the
What's reasonable
Reasonable search
I do think
We live in now
And the fact that everyone safety is contingent on each other
I do think that a business
And the government does have a responsibility to make sure
You're not bringing
The f****** weapon onto a plane everyone's a Sitting Duck Oregon
Bad for like fruit
From another place that'll get
Sure or could introduce the new virus into the ecosystem
Legitimate
That is a reasonable chair that's not a violation for Amendment
It's weird we have to take our shoes off
Yamin
I'm in on that level
But
I don't know they just want nothing they weren't just want like
I know
I should be able to smoke on planes I should be able to
Exactly
Brandishing
I just put it on the
Table the table
And their argument would be like of course I would never do that it should just be allowed to do that every
He was going to behave
Right
Lots of people aren't f******
Batshit crazy yeah we know a lot of people
People that are batshit
That's going to it's like
These people that live in the
Sort of
I don't
Where
Like that
Down the road
Like that it's like
Boston
You really think everybody
Olive Garden not needed
Some type of background
Mentally ill people
Here in Chicago vary
I'd like a half hour trip
The entire time very normal-looking
Permit 50-ish looking guy
Was just muttering to himself but I was going to kill some people
Yeah
Didn't phase me
Just staring
Everyone
And that you
You disappointed
Well
It's not my problem you know I hate to say it
I will I will step up if that's it for now
I can't protect you from look
Disgaea flexes then we'll do that
Too much risk
Cuz he might have gone on the bus
Mega bosses in
Greyhound
They're reasonably more dangerous because there aren't those
There aren't as though
Real of security
Absolutely
A couple years back on a Greyhound bus and
Help people sell drugs on Megabus
Because that says who the Wild West
So
Change
There's a lot of discussion about like
Alex wants them to say that we're at a Tipping Point
Yeah I've got Obama's in office again
Yeah the re-election
They just
Rambo about
Federal Reserve
To the point where like they're not even
But yeah they just they say like you know what we're probably at a Tipping Point
I thought 2007/2008 was going to be a Tipping Point
Maybe we'll become the wine bar Republican six months maybe we never will
You are not saying anything
It's absolutely not
Obama to do all the
Cephalic
He was going to do
Yeah I didn't do all the stuff that you were programmed to be afraid he was going to do
Electrical
Yeah maybe
Because of you I mean
I like to think
What was that
Lit up
That was the White House Correspondents Dinner started at all
Batman but I do wonder if cuz I know that Rodger
Yeah but that would have been
4 years
Earlier
Real talk
Root beer talk
That could have started race riot
I mean the shed he would have said about his nicknames for
Jet for Obama
Duffy unhinged
Way beats
Obama bopping down the
Mystere zverev
Air Force 1
Thinly veiled racist
I don't think that enough
2012 I mean the internet wasn't good
But it wasn't as bad as it is now
So I don't know I don't know if you would have had the same
Matt Stafford
Bean bag then
Black man
I'm saying though I don't
Yeah
You know I think
Easier for people to wear
You know Trump that b****
Versus like yeah
Except except
But that's a part of the progression of how bad the internet
Trump
That if that's what we're talking about all I could have done
Some really good work
There
I do agree with you that like hating a woman somehow more okay than hitting a blackout
But I think a woman
I am and it was funny because after the like if you had a black guy in a black woman and you were targeting one of them everyone would be so much
More thrilled if you target
Black women
You sure there was a
Everyone's kind of like
When do that when all the
Republicans are after the
Correspondence
The guys who
Worthy shirts they showed like a man and a woman
F*** your feeling
Trump 20
Shut up and Shapiro
So
Way more extended Maga hat
You know
Trumpet B shirts
The man
We're both wearing
Hillary for prison
That to me used
Just like a white couple
Can go out
And where they're Hillary for
For prison shirts
Girlfriend's butt
It's I mean like that girl if he came out
And whatever
Let's go to Chili's
It came out with like an Obama for prison
You got tickets
Because there might be more blowback also but I also think about that
Is like
I think
How bad
Culture is just because we have to keep variable similar was running against
Obama in 2016
Confirm if the two of them were running against each other in the climate we are right now
No but like
That just by historical coincidence
Let's say is that George h.w. Bush got his second term
After I pushed everything forward 4 years
So all of everything except
You're going to have trouble with 911 is Howard Bill Clinton's term
Comic book series about
The sake of everything let's just assume everything is the same
Except Trump
Obama running in 26
Hillary for prison shirts
You would see Obama as a monkey
That's what you would see
But I know this but yeah I've been to gunshow
Gas station gas station bumper stickers
Would see about Obama it was
Unhinged
Even the most
Racist sexist homophobic s*******
It's easier for them to wear the Hillary
For prison
Versus the Obama
Get out whatever sure right
Cuz it's like we're this in a bunch of black
Oh wow but it's your shirt and some people still wear
Swastikas out
True that's why I'm sure it's those variables we had its way
Probably legit
Like there'll be way more and act
Or not one
We would have had some bad Hombres on
Sides
Not on both sides sides
Do you think and I do want to get off at
I got to be honest
Penis Superboy
There was a part of me that was like when I was cutting these clip I was concerned because
I know that Kane has been on Infowars That's so exciting format
Is not allowed
Charismatic for you where are they talk about Kane the character okay we'll get back to
Whatever you want
Studio lights
A little bit
Bills and homeschool
And when I say
Hold off
A violent revolution
We can just restore our Republic
What does
I think about all this
A lot of laughs there from Alex
I would have hooked up
Jumper cable
Shane McMahon
Testicle
Electrocuted
The character came probably wouldn't be
I mean it came would want Society to have all the
Break break
Cuz he's so big and cousin
Then what's the point
You want to World of John Cena's where that you could really be
Exactly
View of libertarianism
They've made a number of arguments for like monarchy
Good
But it's got to be like tomorrow
If they're just like if you would
If there's a heaven
Play cool
Going to be bad at all
But benevolent
He loves you
Do you think we can't get them out of
People
Do you say
I don't know
So Trump would say
He makes it
Presidency
I think I'll make it
Whatever your question is I would say
My only real firm conviction
Is that if he does
He's going
Yeah
What I want
And I thought I have
I think also he
When that's done
And
Do you think
Will it ever kind of not it's like ask
Going to go back to life
Hey are we just on this course this
Is that there's no going back if we have eight years of
Trump
We are but I don't I don't like they're all like this negative
I really dislike
Sword of Doom and Gloom
I'm guilty of a toothache
But I really dislike it to an extent so like when I when I say like it
After eight years if we have eight years of this
Yeah we're done
I really do think we're done but it just is
We have to transition
Direct culture has to transition and we have to racket
Naya's is that like
Politics isn't real
Anymore
What will end up happening I think
Is will have
Another conman become president sure and then we'll holler woman
Turn off
We'll have a situation that comes into play
Where do you have like every like stockholders
Create local support network
Stuff like that
Is people trying to take care of each other and
Looks like you had the
The hippies were like
A reaction
Into everybody being
Straitlaced
And then everyone
Amanda
Protec disco arousal
Glow in the bathroom
There a Benny's cultures that have come out of
Reaction
To the previous
Sculptures the ping-pong.
I can't imagine
8 years of trump
And then some new
You know
But here's the problem with that historical Theory as we're experiencing it right now
Already
That are good examples
So like
With the Kanye situation
There's a half of the world
And yes the world is
But you half of the internet that saw that and there was like
Wow that's really f***** up what the said
That's really really stupid
Whatever was saying that like
There's a 400 years at some point why didn't you get out of it
Not realizing any of the realities of what
Slaves existence
What's lichen
Brutal murders
Yeah and I
Even just the displacement aspect of it originally
Go so far into
Anyway I don't want much better scholars in terms of the reality of slavery I don't want to
Get into it
Do it
And then the other side
The trumpet people their response
Do it is
Oh my God Kanye getting them off the Democratic Plantation and stuff like that
So you have
Two people there two groups of people experiencing the same thing
Emporia
Polar different way
I meant last night as we recording this on Thursday
Last night Rudy Giuliani was on Hannity Show
And he said
The Trump repaid
Michael Cohen for the payment cuz he's f****** bro
Well now in payments because if you paid it all at once it would be a violation
Have to be reported which of the lobsters do
But like
Probably what Alex told us in 2015
But like New Jersey
Bleecker Street
These are in the Consortium is on the East Coast
A lot of the internet heard
That interview I was like holyshit
He just said that Trump repaid Cohen for the hush money that he gave to a pornstar
In the middle of a campaign
Really is a damning indictment
This morning they're all high-fiving each other and they
Zeds Dead wine out to
But you look at the other side of the internet
And they were like
It wasn't
Champagnefun
Throughout the entire story
And that the Russia probe is b*******
Like hey
Higher choir boy
Any page
I saw that exact
Over and over again we didn't hire Dana Point president
You have these two sides of the internet that are experiencing events
Wheatley different ways
And people are galvanized
Into whatever their camping
So the ping-pong theory of like
Reacting to EXO I work towards why
Or whatever you have two different groups in different directions
They're going to react
To whatever events are coming again
Different rabbit alright
But then black
I don't I don't know how
I don't think that's possible
I think the trend that were experiencing leads towards anger on both sides
This is like sports for
Yep
And their team
And winning
You know
That's why everyone
Keeps bringing up Hillary but it's only the people on the right or bring them
They're like she lost get over it that's what's up but I know ever is like let's get her in
Annie brought up the Clinton
Both of them
Trump hired Bill Clinton's a lawyer
Yeah
It's I mean it's so funny
It's it's a farce
Yeah it works. That really is
I don't
I don't know I don't know the reality like I don't know I don't know what Trump did or didn't do but I'd know that
I don't know that but I do believe that the investigation that's going on isn't a witch
I have a certain amount of faith that if it is a Witch Hunt
I think people will be able to
See through it
If the end result of the investigation is
Lackluster
The evidence
Presented isn't compelling
Then I think we can have another conversation at that point yeah for now
Tumi
I dunno
What is publicly available
It looks bad and it's a lot of
But let's not jump to any there's also a lot of
Bad dump
What's the cast
The characters that you buy.
But I but I think we've
That
Some of these guys
Got roped in with
The dummy I mean that's like
Every business
You'll talk to you all.
But feeling is way up
I think there's a lot with cousin there's a lot of those guys
Sure
Or just like
F****** monsters monster like them
I thought you were going to say
People like no kill kill
Can get this deal made me like don't worry about it like
Prince
So it's like all these types of
You got like
Bad p
Dump
People who have just been
You know
Lucky to be around
All sources
But I think
If Trump can make
Get past this though I agree
Yeah I would say
It doesn't matter
Like even if he fires all the people Dorian is way it doesn't
Either safe or
I'm a
I'm going to just
Skip
A couple more facts in
Alright Degrassi
We will we will
I will get right back to where we were a second ago but I have I'm just going to run down the rest of the street
Patreon
We will in a second
I completely forgot cuz I get it I got excited about talk about Rocco
So
Alex Alex
Meant that the American Revolution is the only good Revolution that's ever happened
Which I would argue is not the case for India
Native American
Or black people
Which brings the most freedom and that's not true for many groups who aren't
White
For a very long time a shockingly long time
Pretty smart
People in modern-day
I don't think people realize
How long
It took four
Basic rights
To be applied maybe you should talk to Ernie Ladd
Ernest Miller
Yeah
Senator Kaine brings up the red pill
I got really excited cuz I was going to make a plan about how he's a big red pill machine
Clippers Rap God
Kevin naso degrades called The Big Red Pill Poppin
I mean you just talk about it talk about writing for the Daily Caller
Which is publication that's owned by Taco
Tucker Carlson
Full of s***
You're right eroding article about wealth inequality and how the government
Creates it
Bunch of bulshit doesn't actually cite any evidence
The same thing
The Alex and him talked about how bad Health Care is around the world
About how like
Alex has a New England
He doesn't you were going to get that black lipstick
Obviously pay for himself
Company
Would have health in
Provided by
Talk about how he has an employee is dealing with a terrible British
I don't care what he say
And then
Canada who needed an MRI
And so he had to wait awhile face on the Canadian system
Troy and I went and got it and I would say okay well your friend has $3,000 to
Despair
Good on him fine not everyone does
Not everyone is
Also
Canadian Lakes
Maybe Jericho
Certainly
Kickstarter
Yeah I saw that again
And all those
That's the one I remember seeing it
Yeah so also
He got drunk and jumped out of a window
Healthcare got 32 got
Questions everything was taken care of got a bunch of surgery
Hey I got an example to dumbass I don't know parts
Talk about Healthcare
Are there
Demon doctor
I'm going to finish up my all my rambling
By giving you a little bit more of the Von mises Institute cideas
About stuff
They believe in child labor
Child labor laws are stupid
Charles Dickens certainly
You got forced
Build diamond
Exactly there's no other way to create
Their argument hinges largely on like
Stupid anecdotal
Hey kids no more about computers than adults do why can't they make money on it build them more money
Answer my responses
You know what I when I was a kid I
Charge people to mow their lawn
Any kid can do that with I will help you with your computer
That's not child labor
The child labor laws that are in place all you can't have kids working at your f****** Factory building
Exactly the problem
The Thin Line
If a kid wants to like start up some sort of
Warehouse just
Star build computers
Warehouses
Yeah and they're they
Pretend that it's like
Kids
Can't make money but what is their enterprising
They f****** can
Detroit Wright
Need three grand that was at the Home Alone
Proposal
My head is how that would work as a movie
About the Institute
I want to talk about their own oh they're racist
Quotes from Devon meet
Racist it is nonsensical to fight the racial hypothesis obvious fact
It is vain to
To deny that up till now certain races have contributed nothing or very little to the development of civilization
And can in this sense be called inferior
That's that's Von mises right there baby
Here's another quote
It may be admitted that the races different talented character
There's no hope of ever seeing those differences resolved
Still
Free trade Theory shows that even the more compatible
More capable races associated with the less capable
Emmet's social cooperation brings them the advantage of higher productivity
And total labor price
Exploit the less
That's probably a guy who existed
In the austro-hungarian Empire
Here's Murray rothbard
He's on Twitter here's Murray rothbard
The official the oppressed of American society which
Just called in this case were black people women
Xcetera
They are a parasitic burden
Forcing their hapless oppressors to provide an endless flow of benefithub boy
You're making us all into Scrooge's
Exactly so he also doesn't like women
Murray rothbard
This is from the Southern Poverty Law Center they wrote this up about him
Equality is a siren song
It can only mean the destruction of all that we cherish is Being Human
Rothbard blames much of what he just likes on the meddling women
In the mid-1800s
Allegiant of Yankee women
Who are not fettered by the responsibilities of household work imposed voting rights for women on the nation
Later
Jewish women
After raising funds from quote Top Jewish financiers
Agitated for child labor laws
Rothbart ads with evident disgust
The quote dominant tradition of all these activists women he's
Suggest is lesbianism
Kiss each other
To the current to head of the Institute I printed myself
Hi is a guy named Walter block
And he's responsible for a lot of the arguments movie
Read from the nice Institute website.
Defending blackmailers
Some stuff like that
He's a real contrarian a******
He had this to say about
Slavery
Think about this in relation to
Kanye West
Free association is a very important aspect of Liberty
It's crucial
Indeed it slack was the major problem with slavery
The slaves could not quit
They were forced to associate with their masters when they would have vastly preferred not to do so
Otherwise slavery wasn't so bad
You could pick cotton sing songs be fed nice grool etcetera
The only real problem was it this relationship was compulsory
Violated the law free association
And that of the slaves private property rights in their own person
The Civil Rights Act of 1964 then
I to a much smaller degree of course made partial slaves of the owners of establishments
Like Woolworth
No boy
With Matt bad
First of all there's that
Yeah ditto the problem is you couldn't quit at all the other stuff Niels song
Saying don't you know a damn we both
You're not allowed
The same way we were
Why would it happen
Back when you are starving
Expensive thing in the whole time
Why does my brain immediately.
Maybe cuz that's exactly what he's f****** talking about interest
It's crazy
It's so crazy I mean there's the really basic
6 versions of this bike
Most Libertarians are again
The Civil Rights Act cuz they're like
Why should your business be required to serve black people if you don't want to
When they talk about freedom of Association
Talking about
Like if you're in the underprivileged class
You should be allowed to
To associate with people who are pretty
They're talkin about if you are
White
You shouldn't
Have to deal with other people
You shouldn't be forced to associate with other
Labor laws and stuff like that
Absolutely most Twisted way
All of this is bull
F****** b*******
They're all racist comment
Sounds like it
I want more clip
It's close this out
Kane about the WWE
No it does not
Associate
See you then
He was in for my money
Yes about WWE in terms of libertarianism
And this this answer is super f***.
He's going to wave that
Aflac
It's
If you're not far off but the details of the answer are so weird
Cobalt
World Wrestling Entertainment
Liberty
Fox now
Merle Norman
Where are we
PowerPoint
Her brother
How goddamn stupid do you have to be
To be so mad that you have to pay your taxes
Libertarian as opposed to
This business
It has been
Exploiting my labor for 20 years
Plane first of all characters
And then this demon from hell where I get accidentally burned from time to time
The same business that's destroyed
Most of my co-workers bodies
Point where they all need surgery
Family drug abuse or literal suicide but you got to remember this
Was Gwen Derby
Who is Big online
Hey you go to rehab Weaver wellness policy
The oldest wrestler stop dying
Sylvester Patton
The back real hard on that turnaround doing work for them
Modus operandi
Just the normal things
And as well
You know the free market dictates that you must enjoy getting hit in the head with a chair
Real hardwood chairs
Yeah
I mean this is so crazy to me how
Except for
For his performance
Interests buddy
Indoctrinated him in
Libertarian ideas
Lot of time on the road
You know you're reading a lot of books to do a lot of Rush Limbaugh on the road
You know I probably got a doctrinated
Like yeah
First of somebody being like
So down there.
Who's won cliff
Kyle Bass
Okay who he subscribes to like
Subscribe to his beliefs is a hedge fund manager
I wish I still have this weapon because it turns out that
A hedgehog
Heyman
Oh wow
Okay which is interesting.
Just for the parallels
Someone must have like
Touch20 little bit check
Cuz you can't you can't
Have a personal situation that is this bike as exploitative as professional wrestlers have
And then be like
Oh no the problem is that the business should have even more power
Like Adventure give you guys insurance
Gogoanime
That would be so bad for him
He could have told Shane and Stephanie heading that one of that burden
Kind of did
So so that's the end of exploration
It's a mess
There's so many real issues that he could wrestle later
Spoiler time
But he didn't tell them
It's why I think he's one of those well
I made my fortune
Doing my own thing
He probably was
You know how you hear those stories of like a professional basketball players
To squander all their money yeah
When you hear a few who invest well I had
They're kind of dicks about it
About that
A sense that maybe can you make a lot of money pretty early and was smart about it
It is now so secure
Like maybe he invested in
Property to rent it out to
People has like some rental properties
What's that proof of Maya
IS300 gym
That's a good way to get some
Coin coming in
I mean there are these things owning retail
Basic retail
Properties and
Apartments
That's her thing at any kind of land you can own is
Vince Russo open day
STD store when the
Right after I mp3
Pretty much
Did not work out
I don't know I think it's pathetic
I think I think all this is pathetic
Meat Institute
Pathetic
Figliastra
School is stupid
There's a lot more complexity to it to Mariah dealing with it in like a
The sounds great at a bar
Of like
Yeah man government taking all our money
Okay only humans can act man besides
Okay okay
Stats are real
So that's that
Marty it's been fun Dan
Zebra
The pleasure
People should check out your podcast
Marty and Sarah love wrestling
That's right
Hundred hundred Avenue
Holyshit
Celebrate the 99th now forget about the hunter that's my my advice to you also we got to like episode 100
Fifty or so of the show and I didn't even notice
We should we never number.
No problem
You putting up some
Chewbacca
You doing
Jobs work
Too much
Quran ayat Quran
Not
Stand up
I do comedy
Dollartree.com
That's our website or on Twitter at knowledge underscore
Patreon
Stroop
I appreciate that very much
I appreciate all of our policy to give a shout out to a couple
I forgot the beginning the show Chuck talking too much Reddit
But I don't have another contest
I was going to cut just
Racist
New policy Waka destiny destiny
Thank you so much Destiny we appreciate it
Also, the band
Denny's child no that's no
Oh that's right
Mother of Destiny's Child
This one is big
This is a buddy of ours he came to town to visit
My back is a cool dude
Triple tide lunch
No are you okay after that I shoot my
Knighted to my pants
I was fine
Wait what
Report report report
And we went to the
It was a
Is a photo finish
I don't remember after the art thing
Is Jordan and his girlfriend
And after that
It was touch-and-go for a minute but it was fine
I know this gentleman came to town
Months ago when we met up in
And I
Okay
2 bullhorn Alex Jones a studio but fear land
Appreciate
He is now a technocrat
Don't get mad until your brilliant someone sodomite sent me a bucket of
I don't want
Backdrops
We have a group on Facebook, tell your brother your brilliant
There's a lot of things that I wish I could rename name
No
I am and I'm not I'm fine with it now but I wish I would have called the show they're all comments
More the point of all that everyone is running a scam
Yeah they're all papers get-rich-quick
Peoples are all people who generally have ties to gold
Sale operation
They're all f****** with you
And that's all good the right way
It's all scams
But anyway
Martellus Bennett
Thanks for coming
Until next time
The end of the show someone's got to be told to f*** themselves and since you're the guest you get to choose
Obviously the easy answer is Glenn Jacobs AKA Kane
It is
Bright Eyes
Star Wars
Jeff Jarrett come up I loved
A very cool day
F*** off
Alexandra Thurston color