Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody
Talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Yeah
Corrosive
Since I've been here
I don't even remember what the hell are shows about so could you refresh my memory
A half ago decided to learn everything there is to learn about Alex Jones
Cuz you're
Decided to live a normal life
And it did you know very little about Alex Jones or retained very little of you
Defend
Not much about him
Especially after working all day your
You're going the extra mile and I really appreciate it
I think I'm on 3 hours sleep
I did not remember getting
And I don't remember how long it's going to be going over what is this
January 21st
One day in most presidents
One day
Alright keep that in mind
If we look back on what you said in the present
And compare it with what he did now
Obviously really believe
We all got caught up in the fireworks
I'm assuming says
Here is what we hope Obama
And here is what we think
Obama should do to fix let's have reasonable expectation
Inauguration Day
Be reasonable
Hands Across the aisle
For a big hearty handshake
We will see
He said give me hope for the future
M
Thank you so much
Sweet potato
Thank you for becoming about c-walk also
LaserShip
Got a weird mood and you
Furious a Jonathan
Friends and for some reason you are I'm fairly tired
Pull up my mental Rolodex of what I think about you
I'm not totally sure I'll never get back to you on the next episode
Autopilot
Thank you so much to our new donor Sam thank you so much
You very much
I'm a policy wonk
You all are not policy want
That really helps out
They're being sent out
Hold on one second
Eight different goddamn button
He's returned what
He's returned
2 months ago and it showed up in my mail last
I'm trying to send you now granted
Good job at it
Japan
It might just be my
Also I think one of them at least
Was probably sent overseas
And we don't know how to send things over
I think if you got one that I sent you from overseas
You requested about in a couple months ago and
You can send this message and I'll try to gmail.com
I swear to you I have put
Everybody
I believe you
The s*** out of an envelope after the first at
I requested a button
You did not get one
Remind me and I will
Adult
Tons of buttons
In Austin
When we're down there
Beer lamp
Christmas through the crowd like at 6
Situation but if it is
That might be trouble
A two-hour-long podcast about Alex Jones
Standing room only
Life by some chairs
I don't know I didn't eat a lot
Maria Bamford
Would be us sitting down talking about Alex
Yeah probably
Pictures are out of context drop for
Cigarettes
Alex
Drugs they were offering me
And then later on I smoke
Did Joy and I'll tell you right now did you
DeRuyter for a 21 Jump Street
I want to say first of all Alex Jones seems to do every drug twice
Every single time we bring one up he's like I've done it twice
You don't know for the fur
It's true
Two isn't even enough
Pattern that called the scientific method also
Doing drugs
Believe in science
Smoking cocaine in a joint
If you inherit like if
If you breathe some of the cocaine into your mouth it'll make your mouth numb
ADI I don't remember exactly what it is but the point at which
It would be combust
Sabor boilable
You're not going to get it with a cherry on a joint doesn't do anything there's a smoking crack
The cocaine
Boiling point
Cook Auto
This is my movie files
Maybe maybe they're going to like
Anyways
If the story is true
If it is true
Alex
They were f****** with you
It could be
There's no way
16 probably
I would assume so
Back to the Mets in the matter at hand
That is Barack Obama the president
Smoking Coke
For one day
Here's where Alex Jones
Stupid head
Again
Not giving him a chance
Spidey
Superman fighting
Familiar
FairPoint
Mr. Spider-Man with
Alright so
Told their under Marshal
The law based on the War Powers Act
Cpu-z
Lot
The lot
The budget is
Is it
50 to trillion dollars
Billion dollars a week
Could be stolen we not also
I don't know I don't know what
If it's in the present or in the past
I can't refine the clip but he's talking about how like
Globalist who are making
20 billion dollars an hour
It's a lot
To me I just think like I don't I don't know how that
Possible
Average
They work it's like stand-ups
You know you make
Play exactly
I don't know
The full 40
Bianca
Also the War Powers Act is
Colloquial name for the War Powers Resolution was passed in 90
Team 73
Has nothing to do with telling
Congress that you're under martial law
Which we weren't also
What
You can just tell Congress
Specifically I think he's saying that Barack Obama
Obviously
Who sang Congress that the United
States
Is undermined Powers Act
Was made after Vietnam
Because they wanted to try and clarify what the rules of
Congress
And the president are in terms of
Deploying people in chat like that
And I read over it most of it has to do with like
Just strict guidelines about if you
You send people you have to tell con
Operating off of that and it makes
Well coz we know
Wework
Under martial law
And also
Fairly certain
No matter how
In America
I don't
Any sitting president could ever
Just raises hand and just be like
Under Alex
Conception under under Alex's idea it's not the president
100 year-long plan of the small
He's telling Congress what they already knew cuz he's
Absolutely
Set the bunch.
The next
Today already
I would have piss on Obama
Come on up for some reason when I look at him I think bad press
I don't know why it's what I mean is when I look at him as bad president
I don't see any possible reason for that
People smell like sulfur
At least the narrative Progressive slightly I will give him credit for that
Jordan
Generally when we like to have a good time on this show we end up seeing Alex Jones singing along
To the highway map
We also saw Eastbound & Down
On the last one
I have to make
Public admission
None of these songs are Alex Jones is favored
Birdsong
The favorites I'm pretty clear that this next song
Is Alex Jones
Literal favorite song on almost every show
And gets really sentimental Victor
However on the January 21st episode
Besides
The Yeah Yeah Yeahs
Interesting what the heck out of there
You seem like a very basic
He likes that he doesn't like
The singles I'm going to go with maps
Did that come out by the
Take it away with that Melody
By Willie Nelson
Came out on
2008 album
Forever and was forgotten by literally everyone
But here it is
103 this forever
First of all
It's terrible thing I do agree
Does not understand meter in Reading
You saying after that
Reports on airplanes
ORD airport
Respond
Man charged with terrorism
Stop nice
It's a business
F****** Alex Jones understood 1009
The prisons were a business
And they're being filled
We could look at the
Pacific Supply that it's mostly being filled by black people
Talk about how I like Heroes
From what he just said
They're even coming up
Us
Which I understand
I understand what he's saying in the content
For the racial stuff later
Those who would resist
Perhaps
What do you think
Really troubling
You know that
He's fully aware in 2009 that prisons are a business
You going
The prison makes them money
And also they can profit off of your labor
Crazy
Weird
It's almost like they have a financial incentive
This story that brings up
Maybe 10 times
Throughout the rest of the show
Terrorism
Play Rihanna's
Set a terroristic tabei
Who's all playing
I thought I had to bb8 from the LA Times article
Just redacted
All about
Probably
Here's that from the article of the alley time to decide
Tamara Jo Freeman was on a Frontier Airlines flight
To Denver in 2007 when her two children began
Window shade
I've been spilled a Bloody Mary in her lap
That was booze
Virgin Bloody Mary
Each of them on the side with
3 squats
It was a small incident but one
Heightened anxiety after
September 11th
Directions for Freeman
And her children
Confronted Freeman who responded by hurling a few profanity
I'm throwing what remained of a can of tomato juice on the floor
So then she got arrested
I think it's a little f***** up but I
I understand this
Friend
But at the same time at the same time if she wasn't wearing shoes out of
Totally fine with it well
And they just did it for that
God damned if you aren't going to
I'm even this article noatime says that
Security Experts say that the use of the law by Airlines and their employees
Criminalizing
Incidents that did not start out of
Threat to Public Safety
Much less
Terrorism
So even this article is
It's already making a more nuanced
Criticism the knowledge
So
I don't know that's the mainstream media
I don't know what point he wants to make your like there's actual facts
Patriot Act give an airline
Problem
Best actor
Flexibility to clamp down on unruly Behavior
Intent of the Patriot Act Provisions with put terrorist
In violation of the law before they could X
Execute an actual takeover
Says Nathan sayles Allah professor
George Mason University
Who helped to write
Patriot Act
He served in the jump
Just Department
But sales acknowledge
That in the perverted
Protect the skies the practical application of the law has sprayed
Your child is not as great a threat to Aviation
Does members of Elkader with box cutters
How much is
Is clear he said
Cool
I do not like hearing
I do not like here in George Mason
More like
A lot
This is Maurice story of
Airlines
Misusing
Discretion
Proposal
Police save Crackdown
This is something that the the airlines
Can deal with Jose
Opting for the latter
In order to criminalize at Behavior
People do the airlines are already a card
So why not give them
No
Dammit if those corporate
Love us
At this point
Alex
Micheladas
Stuff that's on this episode
Little tiny things
Inconsequential because he launches into
To like I would say probably a little over an hour
Breakdown of Barack Obama's inauguration speech
Statim in up
Dap
Analysis
Ears
It was a very inspiring but also pretty boilerplate speech it was very much like
Well Alex's take is a little different
Here's the beginning
Okay
Monument
The Presidential Inaugural ever
See now
He would argue that now
Right
Must mean it's terrifying
Cult of Personality leader
Yeah
It would be better for him if there was people there
Get ready for 40 more seconds of this metaphor
Still going yard
President
They are now
Fresh bird cage liner
That is the bird special trip
Text Mario Flores El Rey bird
My God
This is a very complex inner life for a bird
Alex
Have some problems
And one of those things is not being Spa
Pacifica
Google allows you to
Search Within website
What's the naval and army
Here's what's interesting
First within Infowars
Corsa
Google
Play search for naval war College
And pretty much every single article came up reference
One guy
As a couple articles that had different
People but it was very sporadic
I would say seventy-two 80% of all of the articles
The come-up reference John Schindler
Specialist
From
About but I couldn't find
About North, admitting that they're run by the bank
In a military industrial complex
Also
Invites
Yes and all of these
Do you know John Schindler
He's an ex-nsa
I believe
Or research
You got fired for like emailing a picture of his dick to somebody
Just bad spy Behavior
And then now in the
Of the
2016 election also
Pretty prominent
Louise Mensch
Twittersphere
Great great showing up in that much about him he might have
Some credentials and it does appear that used
War College ever the head of it
And there aren't any articles on Alex's even
Talk about this
This would take
Days of Googling
The traffic figure out what are you saying it would actually be a Monumental amount of effort to do that
Instead of just a
Googling once and then writing down notes
Yeah I suppose so
The other thing is
Brent mentions the army war College
Alma
Every single article in Alex Jones
Infowars
About the army war College
Is warning about
White
That's why I write it
Called Known Unknown
Unconventional
Strategic shocks
Defense strategy
Development
I came out right
Before this episode would have come November 2000
The reason for that is
Explain
From the first page
The current defense team
Confronted a game-changing strips
Pedic shocking
Turn office
The next team would be well advised to
Expect the same
You understand what that's saying
Yeah
When Bush came into office
His defense team within 8 months
Add 9/11
Which was a game changer
Dick shot and what they mean by that
Is
Not
Anything nefarious
It's just that
More or less
Strategic shock
Let me see you when we see we're okay
Kids what it's about
The document says
Military-industrial complex has taken over the government
All it says
Is the Strategic shocks occur in our history like 911 or Pearl Harbor
And all relevant analysis
Self-assessment
Have to do with solving the problem that has already occurred
As opposed to looking forward to what is coming
This because up to
To this point
We sort of all into these laws repeatedly through history
Reactive in nature
Paper is about
Situation now there because
If you go back and you look at
The
The way that
Economy always
Whenever things go good
Everybody D regulates everything and allows everything to get
This was going to last
And then we get back cuz nobody is nobody
Capable of a long-term
Strategy
Like
Just keeping up
If you think about like
Everything Auto
You just scale up slightly
Everybody
Even people
Foreign policy even people who were working for the defense department are somewhat just
To keep up
Like that's all we
Plan Alex's narratives in advance
Yeah that's actually probably do a better job
Ubiq
In the end
Tire paper
Maybe a little more
Again I read
The I read a bunch of different things and they were varying length
Quite frankly
But the only thing I think you paid attention to him this is about a possible domestic emergency
I need some more Powers there
As a community
Protect and defend the Constitution
Against all enemies foreign and
The department of defense's role in
Has never been stopped
Examine
Dust
There is perhaps no greater sources
Strategic shock for
For the defense department
Then operationalize exact component of the oath of service
The widespread domestic emergency
Entails Rapids
Dissolution
A public order or
Significant parts
The United States
They described
As likely not an immediate
The paper doesn't
Anything prescript
It's not something anyone should do XYZ
Literally all it's saying is
The situation would be an immense
Challenge
For the defense department
Unlikely
Traffic
Could happen because there isn't a plan in place
There's no idea what to do and so it goes through like
Here is one problem that would pop up
God you know having to
Get on National Guards
Where
Governors have control of whether or not they operate with him that's an issue that would pop up
The government would be at
The best of the state
It's not
It's just describing a problem
Not even a problem it's describing a shower
Well I mean you consider the possibility that
Rightfully impeached
Extend removed from office
Hopefully they had it in front of everybody and then you have
Possibility
Nationalist separatist movement growing up
And then you think about the white catechism
You have a white nationalist militarized
Government
Riverside ice already
Like me
Like a literal domestic terrorism
Worse than my heart
I can't
White supremacist
Nationalist governors
Abstain
Santa Rosa
Live at least I'd Steven
What's underneath this nightmare scenario
What a nightmare scenario you're describing right now we're already in the Twilight phase of falling asleep into it even though we should
Should be jolting awake
Fighting
Forever lives
The only reason to have a
A professional military
Make sure
We protect our borders from Florida that's really
Florida coordinate off absolutely
Uber in Borden
This is at the top
It says
The views expressed in this report are those of the author
I do not necessarily reflect the official policy or position of the Department of the army the Department of Defense
Or the US government
Just a guy right now some ideas it's like a f****** term paper
All resemblance
Person living
And then
Dick Wolf
Right exactly I'm at
What what you're dealing with here is Alex
Again
It keeps peeking
Specific
I could
Do a better job
I can go on
Context clues and everything he's ever published on his website
Now
If he wants to post an article
How North Cobb
Anyway
We got to get to this
Already
Going to happen I told you was going to heat up pretty quick
Bristol Road
Bingo
What is happening
Right now from Barack Obama
Play does he
I stand here today
Humbled
By the time supports
Break room
For The Truck Store
Mindful
The sacrifice was born by our ancestors
We're sacrificing
About you
Abortions
Birthday
Does everything is deception
Yikes
Why can't it be a tip of the hat to black people
Repast
In this country and also be a message of unification
You early
Tip of the cap to a
Is definitely not
Colloquialism
But if it is
That should be a unifying concept
If we are all capable of recognizing that sacrifice
Unified is a country
Grab the things that he's most
Is the fact that so many white
People don't
Country was built on the
Facts of black people sacrifice
Niagara
Even think was
God the
The phrase
Real extinct
Just purely engaging with how stupid Alex
Remember all the times
Pick-A-Part
He was the same guy in 2005
Do you still have that inability to deal with more than like
Exactly
Sacrifices born by our ancestors
I think President Bush
For service to our nation
I don't I like to apologize I
The order
My bad
I think
President Bush for his service
Robert
Pat Robertson
I will save you
The craziest thing you said there is that Pat Robertson is being like socialism
Notorious Christian right fascist racist Pat Robertson
Well now that it's in the form of this guy
Clearly I remember Pat Robertson being very supportive of Obama
Remember that really Great Khali Khali
Peaceful transition of power has given him a day
Is responding to the affair Robertson
Didn't say
Add should about it
Get them or anything like that at least
At least he's made peace
50th president
Blow Bar
But Alex
He's at least not saying like
He cheated or anything like that
Obama sent
Didn't come out until Trump
And that one guy
Tweeted
So
Good stores
Narrative about Barack Obama
Said the wrong words
President
Fairytale Lupo if you listen to
He's supposed to do is Repeat after John Roberts
Chief justice
Record you just repeating what John Roberts says
Administer DLC after work because it's
Dom formality signal leaves the pageantry
It's like
Just like
The fairy tale
Where you at
These tiny little
Time Warner
I don't know if he'll bring that narrative back up in
Days
But at least
At this time
He doesn't seem like he's
2 into pushing that
I'm not dispute then I'm not going to dive in on this
Compared to the other stuff you.
To I'm shocked
Doesn't do that
Another thing
It's really fun
Is that Alex
The show
The 2009
Breakdown of Obama
Getting caught by brakes
You trying to jump in
And you have to go to break
Weather of General Flynn
Operation here shown throughout this transition
34 Americans
Have not taken
The presidential
Words spoken during Rising tides of prosperity
I'm Still Waters a piece
All right now he's calling upon history an American tradition
That's pretty strong
Jump right into it
44 minutes now taking his oath of office
37 of which word
At least three others were miserable.
Carter was a good president
Actually kind of glad Marty was here for the discussion
If you were here about Andrew Jackson
But it turned into a 15-minute
Spoken Reasons
Nevermind
Civil War coming
Not according to lore not according to lore
Slides
According to lore
Find so he goes to break
PowerSchool sprake
He comes back
This analysis
Boy
Good
To Barack Obama as I analyze this
Generous generous
Neversong
Gathering clouds
The Raging storms
These moments
America has carried on.
Simply
Because of the scale or mention of those in Ohio
The main baseball to the ideals of our forebears
Intruder
44 president
I need you to help me
If you didn't
I need your help
Mycourse
Appellant had inhibit
Alarm 8
A government service
Dot-org whatever where people just log community service hours they did
In order to make everyone feel good
That's another Army building
If gamifying
Also I need to be very clear about this
Because I think that you agreed with what Alex was saying
In a bad way
Alex's inverting it
And you not saying I need your help
Only all of us can do that
That's
No I know the reason that I laughed at that immediately is because I was waiting for him to then be like
We all know your money
Be able to do this I represent
A h
Trust me
We will get the sponsors in a little bit
But
Go to destroy America
Trying to build an army
Volunteerism is evil
He says
Our Bill of Rights our constitution
Write our form of government
Yes
But he's coming
Subways
Now see what he said
Wisdom
Nice to people
He said it was a bad idea
People
Bad idea
I didn't say anything about it I be like
Right
F****** a******
About how we got to work together
The reason this country is so great is because we stuck to our tradition
We're stuck to our
Respective law and each other
Even through hard times
Absolutely disagree with who is a war criminal that should be punished commence
Even then
America is still like well we're going to f****** move along
We got another president
This war criminal fine f****** that least he gone now
I never got another workarounds
Also I think Debbie at that point
I don't remember Obama being like ridiculously
Set we are at where we are right now
There was like a smattering of Boos at the inauguration for but that wasn't Obama doing that
Also
God do you remember when the
Could use a metal
Do remember those days
Used to be able to speak
Feel and respond to an image that appears in your brain
But called
Writing well president made a big old mistake
Presidency was diminished
Play the rest of this at least a lot of it cuz
It's just going to be redundant
Play the stuff that I think
Worthwhile
What has been
So it must be with this
Generation of America
We are in the midst of crisis
History
Rrrrr
Incredible
Star Wars expanded universe
Just
Devastating to Freedom
Sure how good was Obama as a speaker even Alex after
Claiming that everything he said was a lie that means the opposite of it it's still like
He gave a pretty good
He said it's a great speech
His speech writer
All over it
Because Obama was a good right now the same is true of trump but that's just going to keep spilling Redbox
Terrorism
Here's something you
Our nation is at War
I guess the far-reaching net worth
Violence and hatred
Our economy is badly weakened
Charlie Chan
White back to the Cold War
Emmanuel
Interconnected
And they are negative things that our country is
Use the metaphor of
Gathering storm
Perhaps even literal eyes is it
Later on in the
Hate
For Alex
Do you have me go through a bunch of things and see what things he mentions back-to-back
Nexus
In his audiences brain
Would be hard
Pretty dark stuff
I imagine
A lot of it
Thrift
Everlywell
Especially as we get closer and closer to the present
You know we got
You got
Soy boys running around now
Triggered by everything
It's triggered by Obama
And prepare the nation
Runaway
Can't even f****** say on New Age
Language policing
Obvious
I know what you mean I told you
So
Accuses Obama talking about the environment for being about carbon
Cuz we don't really need to listen
Just sort of like
Jeff is dumb but actually kind of funny cuz that you see in real-time Alex needing to take
To get his rant down
This is a mic down one
These are the indicators of price
Subjective data and statistics
Les Miserable
But no less profound is a tapping uptown
Across our way
And
Losing our houses in losing our jobs
These are the indicators of price
Les Miserables
Manolas profound is a tapping of compass
MacArthur Lane
He's like I forgot my B let me take that one more time
I met up the punchline I'm going to go I ended with the part that I should have started with
Everything let me know
That's good that you to be construct
Yeah
This point
He thinks that many people are listening
And so it's fine to do that
Cuz otherwise if you're listening
Do that again
The next time he just says basically the same
Nothing but just be arranged they made it more accusatory
They did this
As opposed to this happened and it was them
It will make a difference how people
Feels
Kind of
Surprise me how
How stupid these people are
When they boil down
Massive
Cated interconnected
System that has chain
More rapidly
Then it ever has
The history of the human race
And calling it
Just ate
They planned it
When was they want to make us from a Manufacturing
Who is service economy
As though that was a bit
Destroyer
To do with f****** automating
We can get rid of
People in all
Whatever whatever
Friends but Alex
Wants to blame on subsidies overseas and stuff like that
He wants to talk about like
Given
A little bit more time even if we didn't do that stuff it would be robots
Manufacturing jobs all jobs
Trump pretends are coming back all of that stuff is just going to end up
Inevitably not even
Being done by cheap labor being done by automation
So
I think it's point is ultimately stupid
That's what I was getting into
Perfectly what's going on and then
To this day
So basically what he said was
He's wasting time and so early I don't know
Like at the end of the day
Here's why it's wrong
Texas information
Use it later on in your life
In the context of our show
To get the top of it happens a little bit later that's hilarious I promise you that
Because Alex has
Mad about
Obama being rude
He's mad at Paul Reiser
Missouri
Cuz right
Totally wrong
Oh absolutely
Alex's toad
Really wrong
We remain a Young Nation
Put in the words of scripture
The time has come
Dakota side childish place
United States
System in the world 35 years old
Funny quotes scripture to manipulate people
Levi crazy
Frankly
Putting scripture to manipulate
People that steal
That reminds me of a quote from the scripture
Even the devil can you scripture for his own purpose
Scripture interesting
Manipulating
Unnecessary
Confused
Got nothing
So Alex is the United States is older than the Roman Republic
And the Republic.
Started about
9 BC
27b
Empire
Right so that's
Longer than the United
And if you go
Further than
Let's talk about America really being a republic
When did women get the right to vote
Somewhere in there
Yeah
Fair share a lot there's trouble
On paper
We've really only been
Speaking black people do have the right to vote like a functioning democracy Republic for like
Attract
Compared to
Whatever
Knock knock
Like
Grover Cleveland there have been very many non-consecutive sex
Directions of Funk
Absolutely
San Marino
According to Legend
Lure
Lower
Themselves Republican
Consistent Government Center
For 1716 years
Existed as a self-governing republic
Never ended a lot of people would say that they're legal part of Italy
But I stayed closer Marino
Bush-league it's like I don't count but I don't count Babe Ruth home runs as much because he didn't play against
Even have any competition in the Republic game at the
Time
Doesn't count
There's also a 2ez there's also a couple of governments
And you're up like a
And the Netherlands
Much longer
Publix
Just good
Surroundings
Example of the Roman
We could use some Alex
Why would you even
Begin to say that
That is such a
Stupid thing to say that even if you were stupid
It seems stupid if you really wanted to get into it you could try and make the argument
There's different
Periods Within
In the Roman Republic
Alex
Level
Rick is like
Republic
Nationalized
Publix
Anyway
Who's all the society
About
Biblical scripture again
Every time I feel like we need to have
Alex
I challenge of Apple trivia challenge YouTube
And every time
We done
You get.
Baby great
That would be fun we're being Austin
Going to want to wear light clothes
Himawari description
The time has come
Just got to side childish things
Okay
Wheels
Speeches about how
Not present
Proceed
Guess what America you've been acting like f*************** this whole goddamn time
And let's work together I don't get why you don't see what that means
He's actually saying president of the world
Jabos make
Suffice it to say that he doesn't h
Plus out of this
It can't be if I took all the clips it would be as confusing
You just saying he's digging too deep
The Jesus to bring out themes that aren't there like a first-year creative writing student in a workshop
And it would just
Like we're already at a point where we've both been up too long today or were tired and we would get
Still bored
And so Furious
So I'm going to skip the rest of it now something really weird
So he doesn't hour-and-a-half
Speaking of sponsors
Who do you think
We got a visit from
One of his spawn
Is it
Who's postcard
One sentence it'll get you out of
Doctor Rima labo is not in play in 2009 as far as I
Profound
Is it pop out until 2014
So
And I'm assuming that it's not it's not our blessed
Flashlight
Way better than the diamond gusset it's Marty Schechter of the Soap Company
A welder
I also adores.
Stokely
So Alex
Moisturizers better than Irish Spring let me tell you
Something about this
Alex
Hour-and-a-half
Obama's just lying through doublespeak
Buy soap salesman
Sponsor
Real soap
Why not make the Obamas
Speech analysis also about self
This is really troubling
For an American company
Making America
Product
All all people All American
I were very very happy about that
We got the biggest sign
And eyewear how's your
Alex Jones
That's how God over here
I've troubled by the Alex Jones is God
We're all Americans
Cuz where I cut the clip
After that don't say that I'm not Obama
Knights kind of thrill
Alex
Loki was getting scored
Marty Schechter
We we grade on a curve
Reactor
Low bar for he's coming in
Soap American soap
American American
White Factory
Call Alex Jones White God we love it
So American and Irish Spring is a fence
F*** is this green s***
So speaking of Irish Spring
If you'll recall
The last time Marty Schechter was on
Very embarrassing we had to ask him
Deliberate
Ride
Oh my God
God
BDubs
Deliberate
His f******
Limerick to Limerick
Limerick
Proud of it
Does liver
He doesn't like
Violinist
At a recital this guy has them
In the chamber clearly insist that Alex
To do a limerick
As he was like I got my
Please
I have to listen to this guy
And lo and behold interview
Packages
Unicellular limerick
Fasho
So you Ned
Bring the neighbor
Ring the bell of his neighbor
Husband said why
When you stick
Stormfly
There was no need to fight off the thread
Amazing my friend
Loan
Great
Alex for the perfect life
Disrespectful impossible logger and he's confused one sec
Shorter
It kind of disappointed
To throw the correct amount of I love it that I think he's
Fuse
Confused
Cuz Blake every
Find me asking for Olympic the last one was f****** sex
Actually about a b******
Limerick
New
Notaries off
I think
You screwed it up in the middle or I would say
Beginning at the very moment he thought
I could be deliberate
This is such a delightful
Reality
Repeating
This is what Alex was
Forced to do
In order to get this guy to sponsor his show
He has to have him come on
Hearing his voice
Hey Marty
Long pause
Awesome my friend
Great
Alright where can you get yourself
Man it's good
Can't wait for his next appearance
I just want to try out there's no way I'd be able to like
Just time it out to find
These are
You didn't make these limericks
Deliberate
To hack on hat
I've got it so great
This picture of his life back then
Somewhat delightful
Beyond sublevels because
You know we talked about some
I don't know if we having a really long time there was a thought of like
How Alex Jones would make a really funny
Sitcom
Like this
Bigot propagandist yelling in the booth
And what have you
Those kinds of moments
Would make
Absolutely baby short films
I can see a Larry Sanders show for sure you can just hear after awesome my friend
Staring at the
I'm like what am I doing
So
Michelle
Apparently we're doing. Johnny Carson
Swiss gas
Is a guy by the name of Barry Cooper
Have you heard of berry
Superhot
He is a former cop
Dave Barry Cooper
For a living
Cdb Cooper
Mixing bowls
Together
So Barry Cooper is a guy who started
Picture of a Jordan
You're going to have a tree
He looks crazy
You could do that after the shower
At the time a 2009 was running
State called never get busted
Definitely shouldn't come anywhere near
Buster
I want to say a lot about him
The first is
I think
That probably he was doing some good 2009
Because one of the things that his website is all about is
Teaching you how to pass drug
So like
He's teaching you how to like what you should take in like
Either I have tested a lot of these over-the-counter head shop on
These are ones that'll happen if you want to pass
Hair test to go to bleach your hair
That will I like a prickly
If it's for weed you should just
Use fake piss
Because they're not going to do that much of a test
Probably you have HPV
TV
So
I don't know the rest of the trapping
What he was into
But I do agree
On some level that
There's abusive practices
I don't think there's any reason if you're on probation you want to get high or something like that
Don't feel like that should be like you have to go to prison now
I don't know if he was giving good advice
Let me be clear about that show I have no idea
But theoretically heart might be in the right place
That the advice you was giving about drug test was correct
I think you probably help some people and good on him
Good now
There is some Dr.Oz going to happen is
If you Google him
You'll find
To Wellness love it
Excuse for crude but okay
Good business
Hugo ibogaine and Ayahuasca both
Piano touted as good ways
And
Volume Sonic
Iffy
But at the same time the United States
Can't really do. Studies on these things information
Isabel is pretty
If you really look into it is
Everybody who sells
These vacation packages with ibogaine in it
Will tell you
You will be
Two before you were addicted
The drugs
People who don't go into
The treatment
Have like
Percent relapse rate
So once again talking about how there's a support structure that needs to be in place
Not just a quick fix
Right but at the same time
The studies of the information that is available show that it's markedly higher
Then just like
Detox
It's
The indications you can get are like
2240 22 50%
Success rate when people
Go into treatment
Weird terms of like a
Support group or 12-step program
You're having the street
Whereas before it's usually like
At the same time
If you don't do any of those things
Thank you just go back to your normal pattern
Your relapse rate is
Almost
Inevitable in the meantime
Time
Disconnect by brand off
U2
Puerto Vallarta
And gives you a game
On the other hand
You still
Blown to Puerto Vallarta
You still did that it also occurs to me
Yeah it occurs to me
That there's low overhead on this
Operation
Vacations start at $4,950
Start
So probably option
Could be higher than this
But
To keep our prices lower than all three
We offer phone calls only to those who are ready to book their trip
Okay
Nobody
Nobody take certainly not
Got somebody
Send us an email
Yes
Call has no
If you have question
Don't
Again
Bears
Repeating is like
Just based on the fact
I think a lot of
People who run business
This or not
Totally Above board
I think that there is a lot of
Absolutely
I think probably there is good in
Because
There are indications
This is a better way to treat addiction
Damaging than a lot of others can't
I think
You go in
With the unrealistic expectation that I'm going to go trip on Abba gain
I keep pronouncing
A different lady some reason just comes out of my mouth
But I'm going to go trip on this stuff and then I'm going to come back to her
And then you're not
I think that could lead
YouTube a feeling of I'm trapped in addiction
For the rest of my life
Reminiscing
Stream $5,000 vacation couldn't help me out
Right I'm going to do
Just being a dick for life
I don't know
What is whole process
I don't know if like if
When you get off the plane he shoots a blow dart
Right
The first 3 days
They give you drugs
Because they don't want you to have withdrawals
Drugs
Whatever whatever
Will supply you with h
The rest of the time you just do whatever
For the first 3 days
The tester do sand
You're not allergic to it
You get the full dose and then
Trip your balls off
For 12 to 18 hours
You freaked out
When you go to bed
Then on day 5 here's what it says on the itinerary
This is why
Favorite Maybe
There isn't
Indications
When you get home
You need
To answer na
I'm going to be reset
And you will have no Cravings or withdrawals
Alex will check on you throughout the day not Alex Jones
Because you naturally
To rest in bed
J7
Expository
Receive chelation
You're free to vacation and enjoy your new life
You are free to vacation
Enjoy your new life
This is not a great
I like both
Never been to a business comp
Conference man
You got to have fun
11th I want one PowerPoint presentation
At least in this whole thing
AR-15 to get
Personalized life coaching
Love it
No I don't know if
Hey
Bad
Again a lot of it
Would probably be funnier if you knew what you look like if you look
Crazy
I don't know I'm Soto
I'm really really really torn
Natalie Imbruglia
I mean you are
In theory putting someone up for 15 days
But I do think
To pay for your own food
Yeah meals r-52c
$7 each
Look
Flight hotel or food
Oh that's a problem
Text
Definitely starting at 4950
I think if it included airfare good on you
But it doesn't
The clearing of money
Urinary
Yes
To trying to find Solutions
12 to 14
G by the time you're out of here
Arlington rely on
Make that decision I don't want
Like beat this up
Too much B
Because I'm sublevels like
Do look at their relapse rate
People who are treated me like
Conventional
And you look at
Like the difference
And like let's say twenty 25%
People are dying
You know
Ibogaine has been shown to
Effective and helpful with opiates in particular that's what's killing the most
People so I'm open-minded about like these ideas of alternative treatments
I hope
More studying is done about it but
I don't I don't know if this is helper
That's what I'm saying
I don't know I'm inclined to Coronavirus
Don't think that you run into his orbit unless your account
Also I don't like this perspective on drugs
Consciously
Starbucks
I'm not sure it depends on what they're at
I'm getting this marijuana
Because
Backup
You're just a bad cop
If he's only talking about weed
Fine
I don't think a lot of neighborhood have someone selling drugs at a park
You hit a deer in a different community
But at the same time
The way he ends that you like
No I haven't seen
80 people overdosing in my community
As if to suggest
People are
And that is really really sucked up
Because people are
People overdosing
You can look at the stats
They're very thousands of people every year
Various substances
Okay benzo
People are dying
Everyday
Because of Miss dosage
Congrats
I had a friend in high school who OD'd on heroin
Like I know people kids
Who died of overdoses
It's not something that's made up to
Demonized
Get away with being bad guy
Right I don't like that
It really bad
Make me think even more that this new thing cuz I'm right right
Because the dentist perspective on it then
I don't know
Schedule me for a big loop
Yeah you're you're
I much prefer talking about the soap guy
Good deal I wish that
Seem like
New policy won't go
We will go to this program I would go in a f****** hard no s***
Get 3 days of free heroin come on
No cuz you can only get the drugs
You already do I have to get a heroin habit
This is not in the cards
Problem is that like in the middle of their energy about smoking cocaine
In a joint
Yeah
Know that that's
Then
Alex
Is assault
He was a kid
And you talked about them buried
But it is not
What these results hyper-masculine
What these guys are doing
The same thing that
Local news
Are your kids playing the b******
You guys are making this b******* up because you don't understand
You're just making up weird
Bulshit
Here's the deal
I know what
Happens in this last clip
Kind of shading a lot of my life
My feelings about this guy
So conflicted is that like
I'm into the
But I don't like
On business
Anyway
Business
This isn't
I don't know
I don't know how to set this up
This is one of the weirdest things I've ever heard against they on Alex's show
That's crazy they're talking about the idea of like
Chastity and abstinence education
So f****** weird this is another Mike down clip listen to this
Work
White slaves
Dysfunctional
And we keep talking about bringing
Concentrate
Teaching our kids
Teaching
When you do this cuz jealousy
Tell somebody you're attracted to
Partner because I was married to a lady that was very jealous
What we should be doing
Is teaching kids how not to behave
She was the wrong person I know what you
She was doing wrong absolutely any responsibility
Girls are jealous
That
No
Dare to not
Clip
Because you're starting down a road where you like
Yeah this tragedy in dope
You know that it takes 6 weeks to get girl done to be jealous dad
That's just that's just retarded
Notes
Wichita
Are you like
That's a weird idea and then
I want to start a life coach
I'm just sitting there listening to this s*** I don't like
How do you not know what you're saying
Just
Just cuz I cheated on my wife a few times
Really wasn't she I made a man
Get what you're going to be jealous about everything now
I'll give you 6 weeks of training in this first Friday
His whole thing even at this point 2009
Cuz he was like a cop
Necessarily believe it
He's talking about how he would like to
Set them up
It sounds like
It's from a movie
I don't really I don't
He probably did
Start smoking weed and realized
The better way
For that kind of a person
To come out of that tree
Information
And still be like
Girls naked
Take hallucinogen
That means to me your hippy dippy Enlightenment moment
Is false
And all it is is you weren't cutting it as a cop and maybe
Should be setting people up but I'm saying
You didn't want to do that and you wanted a better story
Anticipatory
Forecast
I don't know how I would
Figure that out
That brings us to the end of our show
Sure
You take a six-week course into whatever you want
Jealousy
You know one of those basic human emotions that is very very difficult to control
I really
I do
It's one of the behaviors
That most
Cause
Buy someone else's Behavior
You know what I mean
Like I do think it's some people are are pathological
Play Jealous
I think a lot of it
Can be triggered by
Someone not being responsive to a person
S*** like that yeah I think I think how much insecurity is how much of your own
Security is the real cause of your your jealousy
What I mean I don't care
I was trying to say I didn't
That's 1.4 that was trying to say is
Number of
Who would be
Anyway
A six-week class on jealousy
Six-week boot
It's a very small
Come out of
Pretty whatever
Boettcher you're sexist
Bulshit
What
What you should be doing it
Six-week course about how you're willing to be staying at home
I mean you're not far off from me
Six-week class
How to beat Gastly
How to not trust your own Prosecco
Them folks like that
Tell is that it's actually an aspirational Stiller
You should want
Eli
Zidane not cocaine
Limerick
Sup limericks
Talking is a productive
I know he's done Mass twice
That's right
Right I've got to figure out where you're at
I don't know
You think he's drunk
Today
Is a lot of Chile
It's true
Dot-com
My lights are on
What are handle
Aetna
Are we on Facebook we are
We're also minding your data I do
No we don't do that
Most of criminal Enterprises in will be like
I got to listen
Project Camelot
Wheels of a group on Facebook
Means a lot
So beyond that I don't know
I know I'm going to give it to you I think I'm about to pass out
You know what we only have three real people here Alex Jones
Again
I feel like it's one of ours
Tonight
I find
Soap Limerick man delightful
Although he does seem to be like a white nationalist
Is 2 to life
I've got to say Barry Cooper
Please go fuc
Alex