Alexandra Thurston color
Novelty beverages
Talk a little bit about Alex Jones
These intros are becoming very tortured in the link that they are taking
And I for one feel like the intro should be short
Should be
You get in you get out
You make sure if I did I everybody knows
Right now suppose llaman how to shorten the intros of the 12th let's do that
Are in our listeners time the brevity is the soul of wit
Alex Jones
Camelot easy in space
That we are drinking today
Too much of a surprise anybody as I told you I believe this was on Arrow
You had a couple of Project Camelot episodes
Keeps going
Monday we making up
For lost time when she was in Egypt dumping a lot of s***
In the foreseeable future while you have your Zanies
Here in May
At least we will be doing Project Camelot on Monday livestream
So that's what we doing today
Very exciting
Thrilled to be doing it
Vamping while I get our headphones
So approved get to it though I'd like to give
A couple shoutouts to couple new donor
First of all like to say thank you so much
Josephine
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you
I call it a t
I think somebody who took their donation Pump It Up
Someone sodomites
Damn very exciting
Fusion there are multiple dogs
To donate to the show and I'm doing a terrible job differentiating between them
The same night we got a number of Mike's
I'm not doing a good job but
We appreciate
So there's that still representing the ducks in the Mike's
In the world
Absolutely
You know what actually I did check
Statistics
We are fairly low in the overall record
In Doug's and Mike
Number one all dogs all Mike's listen to the show
Absolutely
I'm glad that iTunes keeps that kind of stupid yeah that really helps out
Not good you like audio check without
Recommended podcasts
Like the show dogs agree knowledge fight
Pretty good
Today like I said
We are talkin Project Camelot listen to our show
On a regular basis
Oh and Kerry Cassidy is show that you does on YouTube called Project Camelot
Where to talk to crazy people
We
Like the world is so in
Only way to relieve ourselves of the insanity is to raise the bar
Right right fun level
From some of the research that I've done it seems like the guy we're going to be talking about today likes to soupy
Okay
Absolutely
So here is the introduction where Carrie gets going with her interview and I'm not going to tell you anything
About what's going on
Until we get
But my way of saying
No setup
Gotcha
Okay Simon it's lovely to have you on my show this is
Completely bizarre but
YouTube seems to
Have have stopped to work
At least for the moment
I'm going to check back in on that during the
Conversation but we figured we'd bring it on live here
Just cuz we shouldn't let anything stop us
Mother
I love that
Well done
Believes
YouTube
That's one theory is that she's being attacked
Text Cody.
To get out there
So just for fun I'm going to drops
So knowledge on you about her gas
Before we get into anything for guess this guy named Simon parkes
Simon parkes another Simon parkes
To do drawings arrested for like tying a pig's head to a mosque in London
Spray painting racial slurs
And that was not him
That wasn't
Provable
Yes I seen pictures of both of them
About to say
It's true it's not him Mission Impossible style mask
It's not him
Google or anything get the wrong
Idea
There's also another that goes an adventurer who went missing
Haha
It's not that
Yeah she's about to have Amelia Earhart
I'm going to read you from a 2013 up at 7 Park
Quotes
A Labour councillor has claimed he has fathered a child with an alien
And that the regular sexy has with an extraterrestrial is causing tension in his human marriage
Everything track
Logically
Fuse in an elected office
No he's a counselor
He's like Aloe Blacc I think it's like a mayor of a small town
Is the equivalent
Simon parkes who represents steaks Beyond Whitby
Town Council
Bixby on Whitby
With an alien he refers to as the cat Queen
Not the Black Panther be
Her name is the cat that's what he refers to her as
Certainly not with the person who is the mother of your child
Or person
Childbirth I don't know I swear every single Cent
Bike makes this weirdo
The driving instructor
Three children with his human wife by career yes
That's allowed
Driving instructor was also on the Town Council of steaks beef on Whitby
I got my driver's license from guy f***** an alien
Children
Important distinction to make
He says a beginner course
Alien happens about four times a year
Quote
What will happen is that I will say I am ready
I bet
And then the technology I don't understand will take us up to a craft orbiting the Earth
He said right the Labour politician is also claimed he was abducted by extraterrestrials as a child
And that his real mother is an alien with eight fingers
Alright alright he said
I think it's total
How many hands
That's a great question he did not specify he said quote it's a personal matter and doesn't affect my work
Personal convictions business Nevada
Kohl's people don't want me to talk about aliens
I get more common sense out of the aliens been out of Scarborough Town Hall
Okay okay wait
Alright
Cool
Fellow councillor Terry Jensen told me
Okay alright
He told the Yorkshire post
I'm completely in the dark about that
Well it is a personal matter
That's a good quote on background is amazing
No comment
I found another article from The Daily Star in 2015
That's exactly the article start
Apartments of Simon parkes fifty-three-year-old of turning Whitby Town Council in North York
Into a laughingstock
With us outlandish believes in conspiracy theories about government cover-ups UFOs non-humans of the Illuminati
Earlier this year he claimed that the armed separatist conflict in Ukraine have been sparked by an alien race called the nordics
Sure keeping this effort from your work
Hold on let me ask you a question
What are his policy position
Because frankly if he's just a really good counselor who believes in saying s*** better than
Maybe maybe
This guy over Paul Ryan
And you can quote me
On that
Alien newspaper
I would like
There's not a lot of Nordic related issues in the stakes Beyond Whitby community property
Right so maybe he could keep it separated I'm not entirely sure
Still going
2015 is what he's stepping down from office
Driving instructor mr. Park
The announcer yesterday he was resigning as a Labour councillor for States B Ward
Because his workload left no time for his Civic duties
Need more time to teach people to drive
Fair enough
Former Whitby mayor and leaving local Tori Scarborough councillor Dorothy Clegg said quote
I don't think my real opinion of this is principal
Bring me because her real opinion
She's a Tori Mare
Which makes her a worse person on
I just love the idea that these articles reached out to other people in their answer to like
I'm in the dark what I have to say about that
Guys do a little bit of the flavors I'm in Parkesburg
You want to take a look at
His voting record
Astonishingly good
Is all about income inequality
Being an issue and I don't think it matters
If what he really thinks is that income inequality is an issue
Because the Nordic
I'm all about it
So these are worse than people who believe in
For the series of episodes
What up brother
You understand
Project Camelot Richard episode
And then this week we were going to find out about
The people
Remote viewed motor
Talk about that this came out and it kind of relates to Mark Richards
Okay
Immediately off the heel
Nobody does know somebody Aaliyah
Wait like this email
Well you'll remember in that last Mark Richards episode talked about some concerns he had about
About the
Because we've got some disagreement
On the Mantis
We got issues
We got it
So
Why don't you go ahead and
And we're going to talk about the Manta
Agenda
That's one of the big subject
Stewart Edina
Remote viewing
Real quick
I watched a good bit of Brett Stewart
Remote viewing
Amman
It looks good
I mean about viewing the video itself
Really well there's a lot of a lot of you
Freon
We have five times the amount of numbers
Donate to that
You do want to watch the f***
Exactly
The reason his rub
Mobile
Stewart
And his team
Got excellent results when they've used
Alien
And so that's why we really
Want to be able
Talk about that
Because
Before
Their investigative
Came up with answers
Brett Stewart
Particular story
Checked out
The real world
How
I do you mean love
What do you mean
Bye-bye
Is all the stuff
That I am just like
Of course
What is the man
I'm fine with that
We'll get to the mantid agenda here a little bit
Remote viewing got great results. Even know what
Good
Two great results would be let alone bad result emailed the f****** Nazca Lines before anybody
The real world
Another crazy person had
Remote viewing
They they like
Hold on
Cuz
That might be what we're dealing with educated to this remote viewing
I don't want to tip my hat too early
Simon
Not a fan of this remote viewing
Hurry up
So that's kind of a unique
Situation
Gotten
Yeah real evidence
So when you remote view dries
The author of Urantia book
Worcester
What's the target as well
He ended up with
And then he ended up
With information about the method agenda
The mantid agenda
What is the
Where to find out
I promise
What's the author of the Urantia book
Rancho
Sorry
Do you know my kind of mix that in 3racha
Always have it on hand
Do you know what to your Rancho book is no clue
So it
Ebook
Spoiler alert
I just prefer El Rancho mexican restaurant Columbia Missouri
Love Caso Cerrado
Look
It's a book
I keep it in the truck
In his Christian Alicia
Nope nope
It's
It's a choice I was fine with the second
Are the second
-1
Material that has to do with like the nature of the universe
Like solar system and we perceive ourselves to be and there's lots of aliens around
Okay. Is like
A complete reinterpretation of
This Christ
Some of that here in a little bit but
The idea that this guy brat
I can't remember his last name to remote view the author of the Urantia book
And he found
Mantis beings
Wait
Behind him while he was offering it or just like
For it or whatever
I did a lot of looking
Into the Urantia book good idea because I was like
So I started looking into it
And here's the story
Of the ranch
Business
Perhaps one of the weirdest
That we're ever going to have to have accidentally stumbled into
It was written by this guy named dr. William Sadler
Do not trust the doctor in front of his name was Freud for a year while then I really don't trust
The doctor in front of his
So he claimed that he wrote a book with the help of a mysterious individual another man
Invented
No
Andy was married to Lana Celestia Kellogg
Nice of John Harvey Kellogg inventor of corn flakes
Founder of the race betterment foundation and all around
Of the three enemas per day
Great way to live your life solutely
It'll still you're out of jail
Alot better breakdowns of the Kellogg
Have been done in the past was great dollop about if you want to listen to
Wackadoo
Not a lot of document
Listen to something amazing
Man the lot of it had roots in Seventh-day Adventist beliefs
A lot of it had to do with like eugenic
Maxi beliefs
Stay at a deep
Interesting popular at the time
Play started the race
Betterment Foundation
In you was just a few days ago
Sew-in 1906 John Kellogg Battle Creek sanitation where previously been in
Employee I was becoming really profitable and a bunch of celebrities were coming
You were all about it because they owned the property where the San Mateo and was
However
Is there any more Battle Creek Michigan
Battle Creek sanitarium is not
Not it's not like I don't I don't trust their pillows in their pillows down to Grandpa's
Money coming in and everything
Kellogg took the sanitarium from Seventh-Day
Ownership and they'd
The fellowship
Cuz he took his sanitary those super profitable you're out
Basically got excommunicated
I went Kellogg got kicked out of the shower
About money
Until when Kellogg got kicked out of the church
Sadler left with him
Is I guess uncle-in-law it would be
He left with him
Sometime in between
Between 1906 and 1911
Become a psychologist
S10e ended up with a patiently
So he ended up with a patient with a stamp just be like
Armasight College
Today the patient with a weird sleeping condition
Apparently came over as I hate this guy needs my husband needs your help alright automatic writing
That might come into it eventually
Weatherman
What he spoke to Sadler and claimed to be an alien
Naturally being a man of science that Saddle Ranch
Test on the dude determined him to be
Be completely saying
And that he was actually channeling aliens in Eastlake
Kitchen rugs
Capital of Dominica little rubber mallet
Primitive life
Oh well clearly you serving him for years
The real alien of
Resume the test
Waiting is he going to show like real manifest
Super years he he would converse with a sleeping man and write down what he said
IOffer
And all that work would eventually become the Urantia book
There's other pieces that end up
Coming into a 223
Because your answer is the name that these aliens say is the actual name of Earth
That other aliens call Earth
That's the official name of
Well wouldn't own name for
America America
Instead of whatever name
The native LazyTown Zuni
I don't disagree
Sleeping mat
Yo-yo
So
Would keep this man's identity
Allegedly because he didn't want any ill repute
To come to Amber court case things go bad but multiple researchers who looked into it and suggested they believe it was his brother-in-law
Call Wilfred Kellogg
So
People running a scam
This is an elaborate scam.
Discussion groups in his home attended by friends colleagues
Suspiciously former patients
Odd
It's probably just
Believer
Right right I want to keep up with you
Atopic
The fourth such meeting the topic of this Geico
Came up that he was talk
Asleep
Sailor would later reports of the group that they had been given permission to discuss with a sleeping man had said
And try and come up with Workshop good questions
Next time you go
Now
Frankly
Alright
Good organization
Who doesn't want a very solid
Plan if you if you know you have a reason
To really dig into that
You can't just go in there half-cocked
You got to get everybody together
First question
The fuc
Next question for real
Question
How do you
Feel about all the
Right right
Do you think it should be called Earth
We all do
So that group would go on to become become known as the Urantia book for
Annie96 became a formal group and sworn to secrecy
Throughout the entire
History of the Forum
Only five people ever knew who the sleeping man was
Including the sleeping man himself
Pruvit Sadler and his wife that's for
The sleeping man
Kellogg
No, is the brother-in-law
No that's what I'm saying
The dad John Harvey Kellogg
I don't know
Thousands of pages of
In the spirits
Ages of Diaries kept by Forum members Harold and Martha Sherman were released
They paint a portrait of Saddler as a witch
Surprise Noah
In them he describes the papers Herald
Describe the papers about the life of Jesus
But ended up
Stop being channeled
As being golden tablets he describes them as quote fictitious unnatural hackneyed uninspired distasteful
Offensive inconsistent
And peppered with cliches and time-worn phrases
They are poorly written Hodge
To the Core
Is
Thorough
Down but you know what
I'm off work just like the golden tablets
Them
Edward himself resides
The Jesus papers
Perhaps even wrote Porsche
Constantly lashes Sadler for burning the original manuscripts making it impossible for
Scholars to learn how radically they may have been altered
Yep
Literally the same story
Exactly
Analysis suggested that a great deal of the content
In the the book itself is outright plagiarism
Princeton's on page 3 of the book there's a long passage on 7 ways to
Define absolute
Perfection
The passenger take his memory has taken almost word-for-word
From philosopher Charles Hartshorne
1941 book
Man's vision of God
Is a flagrant shameful plagiarism that could have been the basis for legal action
Departure on had known about it and wanted to sue for copyright violation notice
Septic Martin Gardner
Who wrote a book about the
Books
Call The Ranch at the great cult mystery
It lays out numerous additional plagiarism
It also notes the Curious presents
A very specifically Seventh-day Adventist beliefs in the material supposedly channel for aliens
Such as the doctrine of school sleep
And
Soldier
So sleep is the the belief that in between lives
Look for you
You come back right then your soul is
Your soul is resting
In between any reincarnation
As opposed to their being a time before you were born where your soul is alive
Jumping out yet there's like a rest.
Specifically as Adventist belief that they
Including their weirdo
Is annihilation
Which is the at the end of
I don't know whenever Godwin's a lot of people and fallen angels
We'll just
Not exist
Dark Souls will be completely destroyed
Whereas
Anna lotto in normal Christian doctrine that's
So whatever
It's suspicious
Interesting that you have very specifically Seventh Day Adventist
Beliefs coming through channeled miraculously by
This Fallen Seventh-Day
Just you left for his weirdo
Kellogg
Uncle another relative was probably the guy who was faking being asleep
Like
Teresa Library
Fallen 7
So it seems like maybe those beliefs were just sort of in their heads
And I
And came out on the page
Kitsap Direct
It's all 7th Avenue
Because they have been removed from actually being a part of the church
He just
Probably whoever wrote it was
Going off the Dome trying to remember it couldn't
Couldn't find the book
Yeah some of the doctrine of Seventh-day Adventist
Do they Bible it up or are they related
Hello
But do you
There is a time
Rancho book was published in 1955
And that's a long time after this group started meeting
One of the reasons that people believe that
Took that long
And Saddler when it got published
Was like I have finally gotten permission
We can publish these
Aliens
From
The reason that this Thai Garden
He believes
If the reason is
Is because a lot of people in the group
We're his expectation
And he was using this as a way of sort of
Haven't they caught like
Environment where he leader
The only people with access to information
And you didn't want to lose that control my publishing all of them and so he waited until
You got to do that now you got to make sure you live it up
Jordan
You know where they did
Battle Creek
On the 500 block of
Diversey
Tear in Chicago
We got to go to that building
Image to where the Urantia book happen
I've been outside that building
Not a real place
I don't know I don't know
You know the building
From outside of yourself
Coincidence
Is the Trump Tower
Pretty hilarious
Hypothetical too far north
It's like that's an area I probably over there by
Farm
The basement bar
Let's do an intro again where will it last another ten
Forget
Whatever problems with the Urantia book
Based on
Pretty talking about Galway Bay
Yeah that's it
You can come up with that either of you.
Appreciate that
I have a problem
With the ranch
A book based on everything I can
I can glean from it
Pic dude who was running a elaborate con
And you never heard of a sociopathic
Good autumn
I respect the hustle
But in hindsight
Come on now bunch of passages from it
And they're all just like
They belong on it
Inspirational word add a calendar add a calendar
Yeah
Crazy look
Franklin
It kind of
Makes more sense for aliens
To be just as bad as human beings as
Is it as for anything else
So we have a problem
Three times now
Not your fault
I've blown it aside
Portside 5th time
Parks with a different problem with it
Blaziken
Regarding this
Remote viewing
And I'm going to tell you what that is great
Concentra
Please do
By the U-Wrench-It Foundation
First correct
Monica section
You're well
Old
Are you on the planet
Sat
Can
Betania
Well there you go
UniFirst number
5 trillion
Thousand
The word America
Is it
Like fully understand
Fair enough that's a good point so he's good
He thinks it's of the devil
If he comes to the conclusion
But this is a dumb f*** thing
To do
What does it really matter why
No no no no no don't believe our at least it appears he believes that it was legitimately
Like Channel
And the backstory of it is true it's just that whoever was channeling it got
Trick
Is it thinking that it wasn't satanic in nature
What are you saying yes
Basically
Love it
I love it when Conrad are like you got caught
Dial
So
Now we get into his
His critique of this
Remote viewing
Brett whatever dick
So here's that yours his take on it
It again if the end result is like yes this guy is full of s*** then we can agree on that but
Ontario
Send me videos
I just called
Everything
Extraterrestrial everything
First of all let's take a moment to enjoy
Carrie's lasswell haha as if they could put that in one video
It's a very simple title
In the presentation
Brett Stewart
YouTube videos
And I'm going to keep everything so far
The one point
There is a drawing
Reedley
Similar to the drawing depressed
Uses in his presentation
Puppies
Music
For what
The presentation which is
Along the way
Rob
Because they
Listing
Direct
Also
Reset.
Extra joints on the next underarms
I don't
Hardcore rule of Threes right there
Exactly
I have
This problem with it I have this problem with it and let me tell you something
Manta don't have oily skin
I have to I have to tell you how delighted I was when is he and he's like
I am
Shock
Basically what he say
I will meet you for pistols at dawn
He's saying that Brett's
Stewart is
100-percent what he saying is that he plagiarized
His remote viewing
From this YouTube video
And he's not talking about mantis
No sir
He is not
Go get to that
We need to deal with the plagiarism a little more in this Mexico
I believe
When you accuse someone of plagiarism
You're in validating
Not only the work
Your invalidating their process
Anyway here's
Ears
Here is
Can't remember his name
Assignment
Sleepy here is Simon
On the pleasure ism
It's time can I just break it
Can't hear
Asking you which
First
Brett
You ignore this
So-called website
Great question
Okay so it was a year before I stopped very very
Christine
Well aware that we're doing
Discussion today and
He is going
Come on
Traveling at the moment
And he is an admirer of yours
Now you're not
Anybody who knows me
That's what I'm doing what I'm saying is
Shoes with this particular
Piece of work
The weather's issues
That's a that's a weird line
Also what you ask their what is that funky this
Kind of sad
You know how like almost
You don't know the
It's cuz you don't watch the actual full videos
But Kerry always has Tech troubles
Like there's always long periods where they can't hear each other and they're working out their Skype
Mute your mic
When I'm talkin releases them
So in this case because she couldn't get the
Lost in a year-and-a-half
Episode
I don't know why but maybe because she couldn't use YouTube
And she was using Facebook
She could get the picture in a picture going
Sew-ins
She has a laptop that she's holding up
Clarksville
This is my favorite thing that ever happened
F******
Beth
Enterprise six-year-old that's what a six-year-old would do
A six-year-old
Like not a six-year-old now they're far
I don't I don't like I don't like you impugning her for that because I think in a pinch
That's a pretty creative solution
It looks bad
Do it as opposed to like
We're going live but my laptop over here with the picture
She is for party
There might be a staying at some point
He will or something
But if you're holding if you're holding it with your with your little
Your little man
I believe that both happen
Difficulties and it's because you being attacked
She's being hacked of attack
YouTube D. Brett Stewart
Clearly plagiarized this based on the evidence they presented obvious fact that other video came out a year before
Is remote viewing
And has
Certain
Hematic and
Verbal
Literal verbal similarities
Turns of phrase uses of
Viewed video
Go to remote view the video you days before the
Could be its original material
It's him it's only that he couldn't
Until after the
Z play Droid
Obviously
Yes
The nakiri says
And he's a fan
Well in the past
Went off the rails
Friend if I weren't calling him out for
But the implication of this video existed a year before
Very
Clearly is instead of remote viewing what Brett
This video
That is the importation I mean
Light.
It looks bad
All this looks bad
Is there a but I feel like there is that sap.
Brett should not
Ifucking talked about the Manta
That's a good point Uruguay
Yes
I guess you didn't hear that
What he said is
This isn't the actual drawing I've drawn a drawing of the one that's in his video
I don't know if I understand correctly what is happening in the video
Yeah
Looking at camera
Hahaha Simon
In the laptop
Looking at camera
Simon
Holding up a dry death
And it's a drawing of a drawing
This is Phantom
This is an Ouroboros of lunacy
What I saw
Just use the word mantis
She look like
His mother Drive
The Mantis
This is cold by the United States
Hello
No
They're very
If I do not like Mike
Conspiracy alien b*******
To split hairs
I don't like it I like it
Jordans
Last episode Obama told us it's time to put away childish things
You have apologized
You're right.
So it's not mantises
Which caused everything in
Absolutely
How can you trust this man
Yeah and so he believes
It look dude
Does he goes on for
Forever about this
It just you know like
You know that
What what who are the mantises good or bad are the insectoids good or bad
Are the insectoids more of his insect or insect more of a general term
Are we talkin like kingdom phylum kind of s*** there's a there's no
We're going to eat all of it don't worry about it you're getting ahead of the horse
I just have question
I understand these questions with but like
I don't know I don't know what to say without giving it stuff away but
It's it's
Hugo's on
Not all mantises are not all insects
Right I don't know if that's the case
Whatever spelled out
Like that
So I don't know
And I'm not one to make assumptions about
Alien phylums and race
But we don't have the reefs
Something happened on this episode
That's straight-up
Blue my mind
Yes
It's taken us awhile in heaven Carey have bulshit said to her
The cheese has been like oh yes
Finally
We get one
We're Cary
I don't know about that I don't know about that all right
I myself
Outside
That doesn't mean the whole thing is
It just means that there may be some issues there
I mean it
It's jarring
For her to have a problem with man
I don't know how I feel
I don't know how I feel about the skating is a little bit like
If your book is not gospel
None of that book is Gospel
If you're in for a penny in for a pound
Conserve website
If you sort of elaborate con app
So you asked about the mantid agenda and I'm sorry I couldn't
Answer your question
But here I believe it's about adopt
Yeah
International adoption
There in 300,000 kids who are in The Orphanage system
I'm fine with Manta.
I think we need
We need good homes
For all of these children
Regardless of your
Toy sexually part of The Magnificat
Can a mantis kind of dark
Look man
Imagine
Do you know how Mark Richards says the Raptors are cool and that makes us suspicious of him right and the Raptors
Makes it seem like a cool
The pretty cool too
So in terms of
To wrap up this man to the agenda
Could you
Understanding
Tell me what you think the mantid agenda is it
And
And then we'll move on to
What insect
It's actually one
Ximena teachers
Reptilians
Which actually wants Humanity
I'm held
Slave
Malachichi
Realtree
Come from this Earth
Save-A-Lot
Ashley
Something like that
When they first it sold
But that the Cretaceous
Humanity
Presentation
Involves
Goes to the 5th Dimension
So will I
Now that's cool
Before
Restocking
Reason
Comenity V
They do not win
If we're stuck in
Minnesota
That's a good point about how
Align
How can you not trust them
So you're asking about the dimensions
And this is this is a part of illuminati Theory that's been going on for a really long time at 8
If you reach another a new denture
Do you like
Today you become a lot about people who don't understand
Years ago
From this idea that of the Illuminati
What day are is the Alexa
The Darkside
Of whatever it is
There's a there's a
How many points
And every time there's something that happened
People online
Get boners
About how this is at like 2012 was that for a long time
It's whatever coming point there is is that is the point
When we will either
Ascend
To the next level
Stay
The Third
Or 4th Dimension
Depending on
Definition
Makes as little sense as anything essentially is that
Life
And your time in this density or this dimension
Is 2
Teach you certain lessons
And get you to elevate to the neck
Next level
Specifically
In the context of putting yourself
Before or putting
Others before your
A Brief History of Time
That was Hawking
Main Theatre
Weather
Your snickering
How far back does it go
It goes at least a Carl Sagan
Demon Haunted World
But those about the
Look dude I don't even know how to spell it out but the point is
There's this belief that we are faced with crisis
It's coming
And get ourselves
Elevated
So it's all the same talk raise your vibration
Elevate to the next level as opposed to getting left here
Yeah the mantises
Semantics
There are boys
Come along with us
Whatever we go because they're probably because they're 144 million years they came up with
That's or whatever left I don't know why not
They're not busy
Yeah
Now
This man
Be stupid
On my part
I would save it if
Mantids
And I know I saw the drawing that he made
They look like bugs
Exactly
Betty Boop
Consciousness
So
Difficult for me to imagine that 144 million years ago
There were Manta
It would have taken
Them millions of years
To evolve into the form of mantis
That would be able to
Sprout was an oxygen-rich
Environment at that that's why everybody grew so much
Of any other
Earthbound episode of
Coming close to space technology race
Animal
We all know that was Patricia
IFixit mantises based on their arm
Being
Not cleaning up the Earth and leaving behind no
Sign of them being here
They got those
You're not wrong
They got wrong mantis beings are also somehow wrapped up
Into the hollow Earth stuff
So there might be honest to Earth I figured there might be some of that rap
Wrapped up in there
Sure
All the stuff is stupid
But
I'm thrilled their honor
What I what I always
About all of these
Is that
Fundamental concepts that I think
Everything
Every religion every belief system
Is
Obsessed
Which is the idea of
Ascension verse
The slavery thing to me that regardless of what it is you believe
Everybody has a general core
AAA
Concept
Of
Weird
Currently
It is medium level
Yeah we're in the muck that we could be worse
We could be better
Fascinating
Even more fascinating when you put it that way
It becomes really troubling that like
A lot of especially
Western Oregon
And a religion
The
Good ending
You know like if you play the game right you get the good good video game end
That ending is
Your individuality is absorbed in
To like
God or those who worship
Completely gone
If you succeed
Yeah whatever that that to me is
How to be a kind of weird
I don't like that
I like my individuality
I like my autonomy
You know I'm kind of into it
Well but don't you feel like maybe maybe there could be
Ultimately so many of your problems are baked
In the fact that you
Have have complete autonomy
Like you don't know my problem
I apologize
Even though we talked about your problems for countless
I like bad pictures
Grace
It is kind of interesting
How
We all
Regardless of
Where your beliefs
All have this yearning
Better
Overriding that is our fear of
Yeah like ultimately that that risk
Aversion
That everybody has you know
We would rather you would rather avoid losing $5
Then went and
Like it's it's a really interesting thing to
Recordings are wired
So much of this comes from
Just this evolutionary need to tunak
Get f***** 1800 in that is that all of these even if you go this crazy
Senor Taco
Or you go Christianity
Steven other religion
Earthbound religion
Bright you don't cross the game
One of the connective tissues and one of the threads are almost all of it is
This
Is meat
Like this flash body
Inconsequential and doesn't matter
It seems like that is
The through line through every
Like this
That's the prison
The prison is The Flash
Nothing
That goes there old-time picnic gnostic
Like all of it
Every single but you have to do that
Because
Visceral impulses are really powerful
Yeah if you want to get people to fall into your line of thinking
You have to convince them
Absolutely
It is it is the
Through-line
Into all of these religions that ultimately invalidates all of them
Yeah if you believe in Christianity your end
Cool
Is the exact same as the guy who believes in Manton
Yeah it doesn't
Matter
There is a fundamental conflict
Between
Consciousness and insta
And we're not
Capable of proper
That may be the case
Still not hanging out with
No
I would love to
Drive on the wrong side of the road
Cuz he is
Real crazy that's a bunch of stuff
That's the right side of the road
I caught a bunch of
This stuff
Politics a bunch and
Simon
Knows a lot
What are his political beliefs
He believes that the Syrian stuff was a false flag
That's not great but I only bring that up it's really it's really boring
But I bring it up because
Is Daigo this is
The same as Alice
I think a lot of people who listen
Not a lot of people but I'm sure there's a small minority at least
It's like why do you cover Project Camelot
El because
You got to recognize that
Lot of the time
Believe the same thing it's just
Terry talks about this
Other man testing
Mark Richard
Ultimately we get to the same conclusion right on these guys
So despite
Syria gas
Supposed to
Stop also I don't think anybody is at this
Why do you cough
Right now I asking my head though
Not everyone's asking baby like I do I do feel it like it's weird
It's weird that we're in Alex Jones podcast
For some reason we just f****** talk about
Look what we could talk about megachurches
Walking shitted mantids
They also talked about
Just that there's a bunch of like Russia
There's pro-putin leanings
Even though Simon has come out and said that the nordics are advising Putin
He's still he's saying things and negative about Putin
But based on reality
Is it you're letting him off the hook
4 things you know like the reason that the Holocaust
It wasn't it wasn't
Nationalist German
Is Nordic
Integrate
Mercenaries
Did particular things they talk about is the gas
Sing of that spy
And London
And it's another
But it wasn't Putin
You wouldn't have done something like that blah blah I was great
Mayonnaise sure fit in with everything Putin's ever done though perfectly
Exactly
It's 2
Until they gas people in order to make it look like him
I don't like the idea of States being copycat killers
That doesn't that doesn't music
The other thing
The other thing that I forgot to bring up is in the conversation of the Syria being a false flag
What they were getting to at the end was that
The
Kabbalah
Cabal the Zionist cabal and Israel
Find it so
There is a table
Comes back to an
But here's the problem is like yeah Israel's doing a lot of fuckedupshit but the world
Conspiracy theories and then throw Israel in it
Guess that you have a different
Angela
And I don't think is real
Because they're run by the goddamn reptile
Take me to bring in the Raptors
So it's just weird
I'm sorry there's been a lot of talking
But it gets too
Probably my favorite thing
Project Camelot
There is a
F******
This is
So weird
I don't even know how to set this up and there's no f******
You to just enjoy the show
President-trump
He's talking about
In South Korea
Is that you saying that Trump finally put pressure on and that's why
It's not important what happens if
Just wanted to give you
Pieces
China and Russia
Set to Meraki
Go ahead and do it
Change face
Was because
North Korea has
Nucleus
And a missile
Could reach
Real estate
David China
The first time
Yes
North Korea
And the Rothschild
Financially control
It's cool
So
Do we have with Carrie
Got a lot of coffee
And then we have the Rothschilds and Rockefellers
Just one control the North and one
Control the South
Is the proxy war between the Rockefellers
Is caught back in the 2009 era of where Alex Jones is
Conspiracy mindset
I think I have her carry talk about Soros
Right but this guy isn't
Simon's not bring him up
But
We should see
Again another parallel
There to those two World bring up the Rockefellers in the Rothschild
Has big villains
General operating Theory now on North Korea is that
They realize that
Their nuclear program was
Read about the whole situation
The the
Nuclear testing site that they have that was a underground or whatever
Collapsed
I'm fairly certain at this point they're kind of like
They figured it out
Possibility
Another possibility is that negotiations
Dawn understood of like
Text like the idea that he's offering
Some sort of denuclearization
If you look at his statement
They do
To imply that we have to also
Like expectation is like we have agreement
But everyone
Gets rid of nuke actually a good negotiating position
I like that the problem is I'm kind of on the side now of
Everybody should have nukes
Like realistically what America and Russia should do
Is give our nuclear stockpile
Invading Iran Iran
We've got ten now distribution
Of mutually assured
Jordan
Now
Jordans
Let me introduce you to my dear friend Ollie North the new head of the NRA
I think I think you two now have a lot in common cuz you have just described their position I'm going right
Gun rights are slightly different
Insofar as
Oh didn't tell me tell me how this is an equal position
What do you mean
I mean a comparable in order so no one can aggressive on each other
Everyone has gone so no one can be violent with each other
Same thing on a macro scale proscale
Situation
Ridiculous
Everything
Everything alright
I don't like that
Cuz that is a false
No it's not entirely
Because killing is killing
No
I understand killing Eve
I get that
But what what are you what are you talkin about
The threat at its core is
Whether it's master
Your death
Norton massively preferred
Nobody had nukes
Don't don't disagree don't don't misunderstand my position
Addition is no guns
No f****** I never one position
Massively nuclear powers are a capable of threatening everybody else
At this point in time f****** International concept the only way to avoid being
It's too hot
But you look at the you you look at the Sons of Guns
Gangs and cops
How you going to protect yourself from both of those got to have a gun
It's not a good metaphor
Who cares not right
Agree to disagree
Sue
Remember how Carrie was coughing
She was
Actually it doesn't
Stop she does she runs around in circles
Raditz Arcos Ryan Circle
Sorry sorry it's not
Anyway
So
Sure
Energy
Thanks Simon
I could just have
A dry throat
That's what you think
Wait she's going to jump back
Wait no wait no
I don't know you know how much you
Pay attention
Hear anything about my work
Fat Joe
Recently Mark Richards actually leaked
Something that was very very interest
It is about
North Korea and maybe this is why
What's happening
Attack attack
My throat chakra is being used
Protect yourself now
Anthony
And this visitor is gone.
It is just go to stop
Okay thank you
Wow
Hi I just got taken back
I just got taken back
To when I was
When I was growing up
My mom
Was
Really really sick one
In the middle of the night
Uso
Sac-like
Screaming out
In pain woke up the whole family
Even in the base
And we're all just running
Into the
Into my parents badge
And we're like
For real
What's what the f*** is going on
And my dad's like
Fine I'm laying hands on her and pray
School
Immediately Hands-On bulshit
911 please
You energy
There's a lot of love
To protect you against the state Anna kenergy
The f*** off
She coughs later
And I didn't take a drink of water but not on camera
Right now
Information of a bottle and anyway
But I just love
I love the idea that you thought that she was
Dismissive of his idea that it's an energy
We're talking about Kerry Cassidy
Really I was really hoping
No such luck
Stop just like
Pretty close to molarities between
Simon
Project Camelot and Alex
In its first money talks about brexit
One of the primary race
Great Britain
The European Union
Night of the 9th Premiere television
Thousand people screaming across borders
If you take a comfy
And you
Try to change
By introducing
Riots
Revolution
And I believe he meant the cases.
So cultural replace
Is behind the fears
And they are doing that intentionally
That's exactly what Alex says
Yeah that's a hundred percent is whole idea about the globalist and how they're trying to have no borders
Enchiladas with cultures
That's
Really
Ridiculous
Predict whether his assessment is accurate and it want to talk about that
What he was saying is that propaganda made people afraid about cultural displacement is effect
I'll agree with that
He was he was so he was at my
Amanda Cerny
Consent if he is dead
Cambridge analytica instead of raptors I've been like
You're pretty
Close to me
Whatever
This is just so they're not the one
This is just about the Rothschilds in the Rockefeller
The human
As it were
There's no doubt about that
Has been really
Talkin about a lot
Is 5G Tech
Technology
Right then I really understand that
Vegeta stance
Regeneration
And knives
Jean this bunch of times in terms of upgrades
Technology is it where
Frabill to heaven
Every time there's been a lunatic fringe groups
That I've been like
Fight The Future
Having access to the internet
And so
That's why we should
Deregulate
What
And turns out Simon
Little different
Richard Stokes
Faction
Attempting
5G
G5
Wichita
Wi-Fi
What's the weather
Affects humans
I'm going to try to
Mac strain
Wife of brain control
Large numbers
The reason that
Not which is probably not allowed to have public
It's because there is as we speak
Between
The cabal group
What is the outcome
Sup
Could be the real
A fourth-dimensional enter
5G
And then and then
Classic conman move
This is something you
So I'm going to rename it into something that I only understand
It's G5
You don't like that kind of
Always always always
Childish
That's what it is
1/2 what it is
Yeah I only played that clip
And play the last two to specifically point out that like there's
Be mad at correlation
Dream
The things that they're afraid of
In Project Camelot world
More less Neighbors
So the other thing
What is that
Last month
Simon parkes
Fired from a radio
Radio show that he died
He's doing a radio show
Radio show
Of some sort
And he got into a little bit of a
We couldn't
Never get a radio
Are we good
No we could
Not like I really low rent
Like operation
Literally but it wouldn't
Help us
No that's not what I'm saying at all in our world
There are look
When I say radio show nevermind clarify
I mean like an online
Pub
Of places where they do
Or whatever like they still wouldn't allow
But like
About white genocide
Nah
Please play soft jazz
Podcast Network
So he had a show
Eventually
Only bad guy
So
Ghostface on that'll be fun
Hell yeah
He got he got in trouble got
Kicked off this is this
This radio network
Did you get into a fight with another YouTube
Subaru talk to aliens
And such
She was making the world I get to livid because of you she was making some accusations and like I don't
Think a lot of them are true probably I don't know what the deal is I don't know what the deal is but somewhere
Rough
Like a I didn't want to repeat them on air
If not true
Keisha
But 1B accusations that was made
Was that
Defraud
Old women
Money
And I don't know if
It specifically old women
I went to his website
Parks.org
Call Park
Omni provide
Some services
So British
50 lbs for 30 minutes under lb for an hour
He'll give you a soul reading
Those are sex line price
No sir
No soul reading aloud Simon
The clients soul
And all right
Determine their star family heritage
Starfam
Like
Like Beetlejuice like what we talked to Beetle please
Batman always at all I don't know
I'm also it'll just do Dollar General consultation
You just talk about whatever you want
Also still
100lb for an hour
Alright
I also he does deprogramming and healing
Wouldn't it be amazing if he was actually a really great therapist
He fixes demonic possession
You could call a lot of my mental illness
Number of clients are afflicted by dark energy
CBN
Jinnah being one of them
The Jinn
Rebecca mythology get jumped
Spell Flash
Be free of such entities Simon
To bring this
In the meantime
Abused wanted to hang out
I just want to have a ghost friend on my shoulder
So yeah
He does all this for over Skype or over the phone for $100
An hour which
100 lb
We have it's just more than $100 an hour
What's an hour
I don't know if he's defraud people but
Smells like I don't know
Anyway what's the average
Like talk therapy, whatever is
Talk-space that's it
I'm sure the rates on that are
What Siri
I'll tell you that right now
I don't think I would take a talk to me that either
I think they're probably
Borderline
50/50
But I am driving
I've one last clip this is the
The punchline
Boy
Boy howdy
Richard's wife
And as far as I'm
He should not be
Batiste
Immediately
No know he was involved in
Murder
I believe that Joanne Richards
Genuine
That's not what I've ever taken issue with
I've taken issue with the fact that
Tucci's
Being
Defrauded is actively participating
Serial killers wind up getting like a
Let love letters in naked pictures from random ads women
Going on here except it's just
Aliens
It's slightly more fun because it's at least shows a bone creativity but man
For Mark Richards
Nothing is that per serving life in prison
Whatever it is you're probably
Has a baby
With an alien called the Cat Goddess
Fan
Space probably I don't know
ENT
Too concerned with it
The seasons what a good boy
I'm exhausted of talking about this year
It's
Gw2 say about four times over he's like
4 times a year
Jordan
This town
Exhausted of talking about this
This guy who
Well as we all do
Aliens live in the temp
Zone do they prefer Four Seasons as opposed to
Go to China
Do you know they don't they don't allow like monsoon season
Brutal
Never go to volcano
Itworks.com
We do it was my way of not trying to
We are on Facebook
You can go to that I can
Make sure you recommend us to all the drugs at all
Brittany the weenie
What else do we got
Space
Spotify
Faceapp
We are currently we are only capable of existing in the 4th
Engine but perhaps
Sombrero
Yes we're working on it in the mantids
There are trying to make
Make it work
And I think there's only one
Possible
And this
I think you have to say go fuc yourself
Insectoids
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work