Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Everybody welcome back to knowledge fight I'm doing over here
Around and drink wine
Alex Jones Infowars
But the twist
I know a lot about listen to his show
You do not
This is like me watching the Sesame Street at
Conspiracy theory
I wanted to start Today's Show we're going to be covering the February 24th episode of the Alex
I want to just have a little bit of an atom
This is going to go up there in the pantheon along with I'm a policy Walk Straight Out of Compton
Text Alex Jones
Bro
Alright
I wanted us to have that fun before we start because today is going to be rough
Is that a new outro
This looks like pedophilia
I want to be a little murky in a little bit difficult
First time that I've raged turned off the show episode
Stand getting through the last hour
Holy cow
So I don't know what happen
The last hour all I have is about two hours of the show that I
Documented
I watch the last hour and it was just an apology for the first
I feel like
We went to fart a lot of globalist
I really joined the globalist
Joining the globalist I want to make this announcement up top also this month
Take donations at patreon.com
I am for reasons that will become clear throughout this episode
And just because we are
People who have heart
I will be donating all of the proceeds that we made over donation
Much but it's something
Do the Ali Forney Center in New York
Works with
Homeless gay and trans
Supporting
If you don't donate to the podcast donate to them anyways that would be great
You know we don't need the middleman sitter that a donation to us if you're going 14
I just want to own it
When we last left you
Alex Jones did a 13-hour live broadcast
Because you lost
How to sponsor with a draw
Cuz he was broke
Telephone for the underprivileged
Tim's of
Yeah but
We're all that free speech
He does this 13-hour broadcast most of it
He just does his Regular Show then he leave
It comes back to do a Reddit Ama
Okay he doesn't Ama
She doesn't answer any question
He just screams about
Wild vultures
Or was it video
More
Question and answer
Reddit proper but you did like an hour and a half of it on his show to work.com
So he's answered all these also people got a little suspicious cuz
A lot of his answers ended up with him Hocking product tamao
Waterways
Does that
Broke Alex
Development yeah it's like a whole different character like words
And it's a evil twin of Alex Jones
I don't know
So he going to call him
What's the thing that was super fun was I was checking in and watching that 13 hour podcast
And you have like Rob do hosting an hour and well he's trying to host Alex would storm into the studio and
Start screaming
Sonia and you can see in all of the people who work at Infowars face
They are scared of him cuz he is enraged mode
Dinosaur
He's trying to build a
Bunk beds at IKEA
Takes it out on those two twin kids that he never want
Robert McAdoo
But he's screaming at everybody it's great
He doesn't come in
Paul Joseph Watson
The posting which is
No good for anybody
Friday
Tumblr
Are we get to Friday opens the show
Much of the same way if you're running late for work
Call Lannan V your boss
What is Friday Alex Jones here I am on the road I will be in in the next hour
Wow
Junctures right now
By the way they're trying to make me have a civil war inside the government block Trump is amazing
Absolutely critical and we support him
Stephen Colbert
Misrepresenting what I say and what I do is the same type of yuuzhan from
I want to smoke a full cart
Nicole's the night
Google
13 hour Telethon and a 13-hour drink katanas what words
Deeper into this a little bit later
But he brings up this Stephen Colbert
Yes
Stephen Colbert
I want to say this and it's not because he's treading in our turf
Are you with Alex
I kind of unfair
Little bit
Pre-roll this episode as he says some of the worst s*** we've ever heard
Adele before that you're saying is I had your job
I think the Stephen Colbert thing in in particular is a little bit unfair
Eclipse stuff out of con
Okay we talked about that whenever you're trying to run a clip package
You have to run
Shortstop
Yeah you can't you can't give it the proper context
Interesting
Is it
Stephen Colbert is making out
With context
Is what you're saying is unfair journalism but it could be on the wrong side of it
Is left
Of the monsters
The crazy person
That's not fair
Bi-Rite
Just a crazy
Dave Chappelle things like calling someone crazy is the worst thing you can do cuz it takes away
Whatever else they say
And for good or for bad that's true
If you just call Alex Jones crazy
You're not dealing with
Did stuff that he saying that he believes
Exactly
F****** president
Specific
I do think
Much better job
Anyway
Ways to
Immobilized
To ensure the weeds
I think this entire program we also have a Judas goat one back on all the shows Stephen Bannon is dangerous
Nationalist
One back is openly declaring himself
Conservative media this year
Once again
They're doing
What they say we're doing
Hillary would have been
Conservative
Media so it's totally fine if Trump actually bands
What actual journalistic
Institution
Alex spells out a little bit more what he's talkin about disbelief
Stuff a little later
Look so just like
Starting it now
The Glenn Beck openly declaring himself a
Globalist
Seems like a very out of character
Yeah he talks a lot about going back on this episode
Explain tail house
He became part of the global
Small gas hole
Conservative
Conservative who then
Play longer system at controlled opposition
But they lost
Because America wasn't such a critical prices for the intelligence agencies
Ensure Hillary Clinton
She did steal part of
And so now they're in such panic mode
That's why the government in the shadow government
Behaving as if
With total arrogance but they're failing
We have the initiative we have the upper hand
We have Justice in the right side of history on our side and
Most important
Thank you Don your knees
Repent everything you've done I do it all and humble ourselves before the Lord
Fellow Countryman
Alex Jones this is the infowar and you are the key the critical
Online advertising
45 ways to defeat that thinks your support so thank you all. Back to the mission from Austin Texas
Didn't David Knight is
Is in the studio
You got a little bit of the theatrics in there with
Whatever he does not voice
Whenever he does that
I've been keeping a spreadsheet of the times he took this year
We will be auctioning off the data file
It's not a hundred percent of the time this is the case
But every time
He insinuates that everybody knows something
Or whenever he insinuates that this is widespread information the crazy bulshit
Really
It's very consistent
Every time you like
Like
The kids version of holding your crossword
He knows he's lying
I think that's the very least subconsciously we
There's a piece of him that struggling to get out
This part that knows he's lying is tweeting against his
Conspiracy theory
I like this
Okay
Twin is the good twin
Danny DeVito Arnold Schwarzenegger
Mega buddy,
Now the twin
He's trying to escape
The best way I can
Through the ear
As we all know
The good hobo Johnson
It's possible
Pretty good name for a The Shield
Hobo Johnson
What's up Kickstart that s***
Ludacris I thought I was right
Now I know I'm a hundred percent
Nailed it right on right on
So he has he has a bunch of thoughts about Glenn Beck
Misrepresents the history of culture
Along the way
It's very dangerous
Affairs
Capture
Organize
Good as ideas
Spiritual assistance
Has he come on
Lesbian for Union
Not really.
What you're saying is he doesn't like it when a large
Get together to fight against
A very very rich
Not in that context now
If you're against the globalist
You can do tonight
Eeo
As an interesting question I don't think
He's a classical liberal
Rachel Jones
I don't know.
Leave a message by our pills
I think he would say that he's into unions but what unions are now isn't
Supposed to
I think that's probably the
Cuz that way he can play Both Sides
Right piece for unions but not in their current
Incarnation
Something like that
He's in your voice
Rationalizing dumbass Bowie
On four different things that they strive in
History
During the murder death cannibalism
Literature and culture
Wages war against humanity
Paisley
So that's a wild over-simplification of culture
No.
It's also have a lot of culture
Absolutely
Amazing culture
They created art
Better whatever shape
They had sophisticated understandings of the Stars
The calendar one time is turning for awhile until we found out it was
It's still a great calendar
It's the word of the day that it has
Everyday
What are the days
The Apocalypse
If you look culture like this it's so black and white
Dumb it's very dumb
But I think it's in our understanding Valley
Nuances never been a
A big portion
To try and see the best
In both world
Historical
Thousands of history book
Probably not about.
Except I think that's what it
Yeah anyway he gets to the headline
Times of the day
Transition
Misunderstanding
Into misunderstanding
Everything
Jaywalking
The one worried reset
Hey look at these people
F****** awesome would it be if Alex Jones
Here's the headline
Frank
She sounds glow
That was a good one
Father
For 12 year olds
Because they're told to
Sexualizing
Is pedophilia
Is a promotion of himself
Locker room with his penis
He totally called Cuomo pedophile
In this episode he does call him a predator
Slander territory
But more in like a group situation like he was rattling off a list of names
And he happened to be on one of them
Yeah
Pedophile cabal
Sure
This is one instance on this episode of maybe three or four where he runs afoul of what I think is illegal
Okay well I mean like calling Chris Cuomo
That might be legally action
You are
Misrepresented
Nobody they wouldn't be able to take him to court of course because
They wouldn't be seen in quarts
Throughout the show
About how
Your you're
You're being called
Closed-minded and a bigot if you don't want men with their big old penises
In the locker room with your daughter
He's not talking about
Trans bathroom
He frames the trans bathroom bill
The judge
Of a daughter
Yeah because
It seems like
Your daughter is going into
To a bathroom
Yeah we're a big old man's penis
Waiting for
Yeah
Cuz you're like but I wish there were no penis there
Alright
Feeling that that's not the angle that the
Bill axe
No it's not it's not
One penis for all bill
This issue
Because I tried to find
Annie
Instant I was trying to be overly charitable I tried to find
Of
Twelve-year-old girl
Attacks or assaults happening in bathrooms because
The trans individual
Yes
Okay
If you break down what those five are
The only article
And he's the only five
This is the only documented
Things I could find
Insinuation
No
These instances were all
Dude
Dress up like women to get into bathrooms to videotape people in the back
Write this is not
The issue that we're talkin
That can happen with or without this pill
Yes just someone
In a bad 80s movie
Do you want to work
Soju
Is that how
Woodside movie
Text bones pornos where guys dress up like women to get on a all-female cruise MMA fighting everybody
I saw the Love Bug
This is the kind of toxic
Cancerous thinking that is really plugging a lot of people and Alex can't get his head around
Is you judge
An issue by
People who aren't
What the conversation is about
As we all know that is
A straw man argument
Which Alex Jones
Doesn't understand
That is an argument about men made out of
These instances can find
Concrete
Aren't indicative
Of what trains people want
They want to be able to
To go to the bathroom
In the bathroom
That suits
What they identify as
These
People
Have assaulted people
Harper Woods
Who are trying to pull a fast one
Right that's not what this is about
Is this is so this to me has that same
I feel of like
Homosexual
And you're like okay
So
Amanda man and a woman
Think about the woman
Woman parts
It's dudes
Johanna oil
Sing your daughter
Protecting your son from a creepy it's never been talked about female to male
Which
Seems like the moment they do they have to start talking about the fact that
Men
Are far more likely to
To sexually assault another boy
In the men's bathroom
Just do to identify as
Pedophile
Yeah
Look up much more likely thing there is that if you are
You're going to go into a bath
And there's a
Of you being sexually assault
Altidore physically
List of five and they are real
And you can find
Centers of
Absolutely
I mean the argument is
Makes me Furious
100%
It gets
So much worse on
This is the thing that I think about
My parents are almost certainly for the transmat
I don't think they've ever met at
I don't think Alex
The argument makes sense because
To them
Transfer
Crossdress
They have this image in their head of what the reality is
It's not they don't understand that you
That you're you're not
You're not the
Sing that they say you
When you go in the into the bathroom
You're going into
To the wrong bathroom
Yeah that's
That's how your life
Every
Time you gone to
The bathroom for the most part
You felt like you're in the wrong
Yeah and then now they're telling you
That you should go to
To the right place
That you should be
Force
To stay in this wrong place
Bucked up for the worst
Yeah
Infected you're asking to do that makes you a
F****** evil
Anyway
Let's save some
Righteous indignation for when
Really
Leaves come out
I'm already out I'm out of racism
Sexualizing your children
Volleyball
Wellness
What is it what is it that
He's mad
That Liberals are saying be nice to somebody who's not
Bothering you
I don't think that anybody who supports
Trans rights
Would be like
Is out
You know what
Here's the thing that has happened
I still think you should be nice to them
This person wants to be a dog
What are they
Hurting anybody
Sometimes they bark when I walked your dog is a dog park
Because they're not hurting anybody
But you know what Alex Jones one of those big things isn't about how
Doesn't hate people
Alright
Mental illness
First one
You're free
16 year old young man
Little girls
Bored
Call
Michigan
University Pointe
No
So I apologize leopard screwing up eclipse
You can't go from
From
Showering in high school
Silly no one's really doing that have been
For years and years that
People don't shower
I was I was afraid
The transition to the white boards down the article that he was talking about
With whiteboard
And Michigan State University is band
Whiteboards on dorm room doors
And they did this
Specifically because they recognize that most communication that's done between people now is on texting
Anton
Twitter
Facebook
There's no real utility to having thing on your wall
Additionally
They had multiple instances of people writing racial slurs
On them
And attacking people
Really helped in the
People have been being victimized we're just going to not allow white boards on Doors
Alex
They could do
Absolutely they're not combating any of the horrible
Slurs or anything like that
You know what
This doesn't help
And it's used to hurt
Sometime so why why
Let's just not do it
Point about it one agrees completely with what you're saying is that you're dealing with non-issue and not dealing with the real issue with
Why would someone
No
But then the other pieces that Alex is like they're going to ban any kind of public
So wrong
Yeah like all the teachers want to teach about
The evils of globalism I don't know what they would be
Teaching about Teddy Hayes
About how
People should be allowed to have Union
Unionized
I can't I can't
Can I get to book burning
Stupid
It's just
Credibly stupid
Is even stupid
You know what I actually just found out today
One of the big things that
What are the big book burning
The Nazis had
Was actually oven in
Institute that did a lot of trans
Interesting was for a long time in
Kind of a you know we're all paying attention
Into this kind of thing we're treating it as
Something that
Real that's
This kind of gendered
Dysmorphia all of these
A lot of amazing research
It was done and then whenever that
Nationalist
Assholery
Started
Then they went to those places and burn those books
Because they
Again they
Master reset
Yeah they wanted to do this stamp out anything that would
Just otherwise
Nothing
Hate
Trans people
Across
You know that we can't make a false equivalency
Nazis a trans people Alex
But we can say that Milo is
I've established
I'm never going to let that go
Leaked
Like I don't know hundreds of hours of behind-the-scenes audio from CNN
Listen to a little bit of
Boring I've lived a little bit of
Leah and anybody who posted anything about it is all fake
It's all like
Someone posted a clip of
The Dog the Bounty Hunter
When he left that really racist voicemail and they said it was Jake Tapper
Ethics
Even that's what are you doing
So Alex has this little
The statement about the CNN leak
Pick one Vietnam
None
Tell me you've listened to
More than an hour of it.
Listen to any event
Pitch meeting
Probably
I don't f****** know I don't I don't care if it's someone wants to give me a nice detailed non Pizza Goethe breakdown
Uno's
Listen to the hundreds of hours of very boring conversation
Repeat
One of his Old Chestnut
Glenn Beck
You have a country
False equivalence
And not true
Even if what he's saying is true it doesn't make sense
And it's not even that this is indicative of something but I want to take a point
The time to call out which is that
He has Ally
Which is wearing
The truth is because there were groups of students
Threatening
It's very much.
Situation all over again going after the real problem just making it a step
Sure they're forcing that creativity of
Racism and hate to go in another
Directions
Repeat
So we can go on
If you're not
Okay and those endo's become like on the Pats
He steps off of this
Long big narrative and then
Conflate that with the waist
Plan
Is bad
Just like as you guys already know
Burning Flags
If I could just talk to him
Call Savannah Coronavirus
It didn't cut it
Krowd
Play Weezer everybody gets a big
Because
He didn't
Like he's
People haven't done no the KKK
No
Even though even though everyone's against them everyone thinks they're a bunch of assholes because they are
No one
Band The kkk's Steven start Banning the KKK
But even liberal people aren't like a listen we need to not allow them
Horrible s*** that they say
In The Blues Brothers
Even in Liberal bastions like
The Blues Brothers
You guys should probably allow these Nazis
At least say what they need to say it's America slippery slope that even the beginning
Part isn't through
He tries to do this repeatedly with the first they came for blank
And I said nothing
Unnamed black racist
Cuz we can
We can't pick one
I assume he either means the Black Panthers or probably now black lives matter
They're all there are about is cop killing
Sweet sweet good times Alex
This he's talking about
The comments
Melissa harris-perry
I'll get to explain why
Cinnamon
Complices coach
But okay
Your daughter
In the showers with your daughter
Gator
Hours
Melissa harris-perry
She was talking about there's a 30 second video that was aired on
News station
And she's talking about how
We need to take a more community-based stance on children
Like we meet
Recognize that
Children are the property of their parents
It takes a community
To raise children
Essentially literally an old
Maybe she
Who is maybe a little
On careful with her words
But what she was saying wasn't with Alex's
No she says is that
Children belong to the communities that they live in
Which is to say
That they are
Apart of the community
Yeah it doesn't mean the community's own the children
It means
Everybody is a part of the community
And if
Parts of the community are hurting it hurts
The community as a whole
Raise a child
In such a way
That your child goes out
Hurts other people
Your
You're the one doing
Like a child affects everybody else
Your child can damage
Everybody else
Whenever you
You say you like
We are all against you
Being a complete and total a******
Yeah
Yep
That's the point of all I'm stuck on now all the rest of the ship that he's saying I'm done
I just want you to be nice to people
Who want to be.
Waterworld
Is do we have a charity for that money to cosplayers
I guess I don't know
You're right anyway
That's stupid
And I really think that Alex
If he goes back to his inability to comprehend what he
You see more here
At least they want to destroy the family
Now what you say
There's no way that
What she's
In the worst possible way leads to
We got to Destroyer
Way
Veterans
Who made up just
That one is the
I don't like that one
Well
Well for him
He didn't
Listen
At all
Yeah
Let's just keep a running tally
About
You know
Trans people in bathrooms
Chalkboard
We have lies about CNN
We have a lie about the knights
Circuit about Melissa harris-perry
Nhp
And now we're going to get to one of our old favorites
I don't know I don't care to stand up for him
In South America
You talk about
The Pope
Gotcha
And villagers by the controller
You'll have Tommy's on your country
Megabucks
The elite
Yeah
Obama said
I want to say that
He said to himself
Twin absorbed in the womb possibly trying to get out of that last-second
Just like
You can hit if you can hear me out there if you can hear me out there that sounds racist in classes
Another lie
Known as rounding up thousands of
Priest and villagers
Sure in South America
Sure
Toledo Jersey
No no
What streets
Where on the streets bathing suit
America
We are
We need to send a correspondence
The other liar
Figure out that Obama air conditioning went over internet
That is not at all again
CDs are all these things we have
Like examples
6 complete
Within the span of probably half an hour of his show
Crazy
You need to keep that in mind for something he says in the future
What is
Fabrication
Implies that he
He's like mischaracterizing
The truth
Can fantasies
Like you write
Fan fiction for real
Yeah
Paranoid fanfiction
I mean
I hate the term but
If you want to talk fake news
I know what it is
To let this we can't do it anymore
Anyway
Fake news is meaningless now it's fake news is
Its own
Fake news
Alex
But he has
Serta trick the media into covering thing
This is his fourth dimensional chess
Colbert attacking me
Eclipse
But we're not cut some more a bunch of real quick clips
Analyzes propaganda
Shelves
I love that line
Debate on the
Pickles I love that
That's our first shirt I knew they'd take the base of a pickles
He's arguing he's arguing that like he makes
Sensational claims
But you know there's truth behind
In order to
Confirming the things that he says
Now these example to give
Is Hillary Clinton couldn't open a jar of pickles
As we all know
So f****** meaningless
So I mean like you're bigger points you haven't proved it all but yet
That on a f****** Night Time TV show like some late night show
Big rigs
Jar of pickles
Cuz they're doing a bit
Of course they did they also
Set up all the conversation we're going to have
Because it's a show
Is that
What is pickleball
The fun little turnip
As a joke
On Jimmy Kimmel show
Because ever was talked about how weak Hillary Clinton was ever open a jar of pickles
To prove the cheese strong
Right
I don't understand
Elizabeth like borderline
This thing right
Maybe like you need your husband to open a jar of pickles
Jimmy Kimmel
I'm sure other reasons be mad at him
The argument that Alex had was that they rigged the jar to make her look strong
Incredibly powerful it just opened
I'm a thirty-two-year-old man I'm in my Prime
I'm fairly strong
Sometimes I can open a jar pickles
I have to hit the rim with a knife
In order to
Is it open
Iron Man
Victim I tricked him into telling people I was right
Again congratulations
A flagrant bulshit points
Anyways
He is influencing
The mainstream media
To investigate
The
Use claims that he
Any makes them
Sensationally
Sensation
So that they will invest
Instigate
Disprove
Some of the lies that
Detailing
Get to the kernel of Truth underneath it
Subway
But
Sort of
Next clip talks a little bit more about it the trolls the media
He said about JLo
How do you say something about JLo
Grammy's
About how
Times like this when artists go to work
And this is when artists
Scump most impactful
When we're dealing with
Power trying to crush
The disenfranchised
Yeah cuz they crushed in the second Vietnam War
Sure
Phil Coulter
Their society
Beyond
Beyonce
Nope sebi on Sunday
Beyond Road
Warrior
F*** you
Yeah
That's unprofessional
That down
Absolutely
Women are still sold on slave block
Slave
Saint record
Infowars.com
There
As long as he's bringing
Listen to the fact that there are still
A lot of
Women track
There's a lot of that s*** going on Ensure
Horrifying
Minimize it by using it as your b******* argument for
That's a very very serious issue
Is
Really f******
Destructive
Using it as like a
Parking
JLo
The culture War
Great take her down what he says
Still even worse
Try to manipulate people in the inner cities
Really short clip of me saying
I know we're bigger than they are
Discredited
Abusing women
Alchemy abalone the Alchemy
First of all knowing
Yeah actually did you look up anybody he wants to Jennifer Lopez
Even on his evil Boogeyman
Beginning raped
Which is what he say
If you unpack it what are you saying is like if you love it so much why don't you go over there
If you love getting raped so much why don't you marry
To be your anything like that
Taking him a little bit
I do not I do not like
That
Because
AC by exaggerating what he
He's actually saying
You're not dealing
Exaggerating a little bit
It sound more like this
You're not dealing with
The damage that
What is actually
What would you try to take Alex and turn him into headline
That's where it becomes difficult because
You can't just say like Alex
Hope Smith
JLo's gangrape
And the whole point of this
Is that when you do that
You dismiss him
As a crate
Yeah you know like you see that headline
Nobody would ever live
This is going to be the
The thing that you
Come down or gets rid of it
Do that whole thing
When what he's really saying is
Just lying about her
Man
Yeah
You're going to hate him so much more
That's terrible but
What is
Substantially worse
Before we get to the really really terrible stuff Alex 2:30
To talk about his financial
Situation
Advertising
Ocean
If it's admitted in the trade Publications
That's not his
So what is he actually saying
Is he saying
Or is it in his opinion
Cuz I can't
In one the train public
They quote Alex Jones
That
Would be an opinion
I'm out on Monday
And said you no longer have a right to advertise
Google
Black or whatever
You know you're Jewish
You know what that sounds so
Eerily
What's up
Yeah they won't make you up
F****** cake cuz you're gay
Yeah that sounds like
What kind of sides with
They should have made
Kind of
Is it
Yeah but he died on the side of a cake and then give them
You're like if someone wants to put an offensive message on a cake
He's like I'll be concerned that it was a trap
Or something like that
And yes I want a moment to layout a couple of things that are b*******
The desert is personal thing
That is still the argument
That
Those people married
Coaches on their values
Free speech is that will think the moment it's an happens in their Direction
Conservative
Bingo you nailed where I wanted to take this
Note to self as a Libertarian and libertarian
In one of the main principles of libertarianism is the SS
And
If you are a Libertarian and you believe what you believe
You legitimately have to believe
The company should be allowed to not sell things to
That's part of the free free market
Which
The author
You should be allowed to
Not have to sell things
Conservative
The argument is if
In the marketplace if you are a business that doesn't serve black people
Everyone will be so offended
Right that's your that's your pretend little
To see event how we actually
Get rid of racing
Economically
And now
Libertarian values go by the wayside when an advertising company doesn't want to work with that one
We are values are
Glad you having a
You don't believe
In the free market
Crushed me with
The whole political system
For the past eight years is
As much as I loved Obama
Did expanded executive power
That's why we're in trouble
That's the big issue is that if your
You're making this Muslim ban
If you do that
Even if it works
Even if it's legally justify
That still means it somewhere down the line
Someone can do
A Christian band
Within the realm of possibility
Exactly
Thinking about yourself
You should be again
Because Adventure
Can be used towards you
And that's not a slippery slope
Situation in his economic and I will poke
You are involved in politics that's LOL
First of all one of the supplements that he sells
In the past
Just kind of insinuated the taking it will help you live to 100
So the milk-toast isn't really real
Like advertise their products
Affect
Possibly have
Right
Second of all
He's complaining that they say that they're fake news
Listen to the beginning of this episode
We have documented at least
The news
Really misrepresented the truth
Meaning
Told fake news
Yes
So he doesn't have a leg to stand on
All of these stories everything he brings up if you look at is full of s***
Anyway
Federal
Election Commission
Alex Jones
Well you won't tell me so I know like
That's not true
At all
Precede
Oh man if he did see
Republic
Haha
To say that he is a giant liar
He is so open to all kinds of stuff coming out
Like the counter
Sing
Be nothing
Compared to the
Billions of Lies
Class action lawsuit filed against super male vitality
Beautiful
So anyway
Of our own Spirit show
OK Google
And that came in and they said you can't do that anymore
Mica countertops
We have proof
This episode
I'm not saying he's a bad person he might privately be an awesome person
Also privately
He is
Weeping on his
Is it a draw
How do we get our money back cuz I'm publicly trying to
KakaoTalk
You guys you guys was literally no way he's going to snow
Will tell him do not do this
He does not have it
Well that's his lawyer his lawyer is very unaware of his goings-on
Legal person will be like please don't do this
You will put yourself in the hopper
I'm not because Google is some shadowy entity that's going to destroy him but because
His entire operation is built on a House of Lies
There's obviously some shady s*** going on and
Discovery
Mission of that going through all of his files
Can you imagine
If he does do them and it turns into a long protracted legal battle
What we will end up having to cover will be
Calculator
I'm already jerking off
To the possibility right now
That sounds like pedophilia bro bro
It's not
Federal Federal
They're not
No no
So I mean
It's not it's not
Attacking free speech in anyway
It is
Very legal
Superliga
The most legal things that you can do as a business
Is to have is too far for somebody based on
Reasonable regulation
Anyway
We're going to get into
Depart of the show that is
Fuckingawesome
Then we're going to the darkness
Alright so this is our final
Gasp of air before we go underneath and drowned it
Breathing breathing this money bullshittin then we're going under
Ford
That's gross.
Thousand dollars
Most of the show's canoeing like that
I agree that Elijah's couldn't do that
Crazy crazy
They're taking a bath on the pill
Nuts
That's what like
Nobody said a million 50 didn't work
Profit margin
No that's not good
He's got to work on
Multiple be like this
You just putting out all of his business right now just everything
Hey this is how much we're marking up our product by like you know what else to a couple of these
Text clips that we're going to play the ones that don't anger me so much
He lets himself slip
But he really shouldn't be talking about
This is another one of them
You like talking specifics about your finances
Security number out there as well
Camo 3549 9999
Thank you for the support
Next year
It's just like we bought this
We don't sell guns that we bought it
You got done
Sporting good stores
Pop out
About 15-20 years ago
Lawsuit
They're blocking your access to the market
Alabama
Oribe
Arkansas
You're saying you're not allowed in this restaurant
No
Your website
You're not allowed to make money
So one thing
That's a hundred percent
In a box if I was going to tell you to go somewhere and die
Boxbox
One thing under ground Maybe
What does it's really important to recognize master of naan
Metaphors
Because you saying that gun shops can't advertise
Wizard ever witch
I support
Cigarette companies
That's the correct he goes to Black kidnapping able to go to school
Blackheads being allowed to go to school causes cancer
We all know that
The
Stuff about
Guns being able to advertise
Is business-related private
Industry
Yes Google not allowing black kids is public
Yeah they're very different
Not for long
Under estimating the quick
Switch everything will be Phyllis a private business
Philosophically and very sincerely
Their differ
Yeah
The day will come when they will be intertwined
Just from
Haha but it doesn't recognize false equivalence
I don't know man I just don't like him
I'm comparing him
Any kind of
Civil rights
Or just playing
So sad
Here we go
If you walk down into the deep
Dark Waters
If you want
Don't
Cuz this next clip
One of the worst things I've ever heard in my life
You have all been
Freed of empathy
For Alex Jones because you need to hear this
Alright
Okay
Great job
I want to
Play
Mmm Yeah
He is promoting that feeling
Play play these games with the with the terms
Pamela basically runs the UN
And they're so scared of getting caught now
Normalize
Weldon
My 357 Magnum
Little girls
Family
Somebody
Little girls don't like seeing quotes
In the shower on my daughters
I will beat your brains out with my bare hands guaranteed
Boy oh boy
Boy oh boy there's so much there
And
The first thing that we need to deal with is the
False comparison
Between
Pedophile
That's number one
Believing
People want to shower with your little daughter
Is
So f****** full of s*** f*** you every person that I know
They're all wonderful people
That I've met
But nothing
Stop immaturity
You know what they are
Hey you know how you don't want to go and f*** a little girl in the shower
Your neighbor today
And you know what else didn't want to shower with anybody a lot of them feel very uncomfortable in their bodies
And they don't want to be around other people
It's not about like throwing your dick around
People are you mother f*****
So he makes
False comparison
Yeah
What if
Which is
Literally
Threatening to murder people
He does that
And then
He did
What is that song
Because he doesn't understand the disconnect between
And someone who wants to hurt
He thinks that they're the exact diagram is a circle
And it's not
Sweet
Catch you in the shower with my daughter I'll kill you
No I agree with him
But if someone was wagging his dick his daughter
He's right to be angry about that
The one thing that I find revealing
Is
Like he was talking about how
Tirol
Does a child can hang out with
Your child
That's what you are Alex Jones
Used
Sound an awful lot like
Child
Your understanding of the world is very childlike year-old
Child not
Like words in his mouth
Play Red
You're right but let's just hope he gets
Buy a truck
No let's hope bore
Financial hardships and truck
F******
Let's let's hope for all the success he thinks
Caesars
I mean
Does Delta
Just genuinely think
Free single prints
They're pulling a scam
Is Joe
Tricka
I think he thinks at least a large enough percent of Mr that
You know
It merits discussion
That can't be real
No reasonable person
Well do use the word reason
That's a good point
Okay
Because
To me that's it
If he's if he's
Misrepresent
This as an arm of trying to defend
Trump's nonsense
He's if he's lying about the
It's Pat
Give Trump
Legitimacy for
Trump's Inn
Sanity the North Carolina repealing of protections for transgender
He's lying
In order to kind of support
Then
Truly
Truly deceptive and miserable
Or
He's telling the truth
About believing this
I don't know
If I'm more or less
Because if he's telling the truth in that kind of suggests that you could convince
You could come up to him and
Hey
Let's talk.
How about you and I go to because you just start yelling
No I'm talkin literally like
He and I
Go to a
Go to a therapy
Just go to a
These are so important they used to be
F****** Underground
This is how important it is
That trans people
Have had to like go into
To f******
Places to talk to other
Because they've been hunted and hated for
You're so f******
Pedophile
Take him to
Listen to those stories
He's a man who
He loves a good narrative
If he actually listened to the stories
Then
He's telling the truth about believing
Sort of redemption
Impossible
Cuz once you find out these are people
Then he'll grow and become a better person
Even that don't never happen
Lying about
Then he already knows
And there's no there's no Redemption
Evil evil man in the middle like I don't think he's fully aware
But I think he knows that what he's saying is oversimplifying things
I'm just trying to rile people up
I think he's aware of that
I don't think him knowing the truth would help
You don't think so
Readily available knowing the truth
You don't even use it is really really available news from his own website
But that's that's what I'm saying
Like
The truth is readily available but it's not
Inform to him
He doesn't know any trance
People he doesn't need any Tran
And people
It's like it's like all of those
All of these neural area
Blacklivesmatter
But if they actually
Went to one of these places
People in
Added them to their community
Instantly
They would suddenly understand something very different
Never do that
You threatening to his financial position
So then you just go from being an
Fuct
Demagogue
Evil
Like how marketable is it to be reason
It's not where we are.
Set of our mouths.
He thinks he's not being hateful
Yeah he is
He thinks he's not saying he wants to
Kilt
With him
Talking a little too much
He's so good that
Myself
Because
But I just said I can't believe it
And now it seems like
Telephone
News for me
Ears
We all look at a 57 Chevy blue and white
And it's the Emmett
Absolutely
He's telling me what to think
Play Martin call which we haven't
Almost
Also
Clean
Like truly clean called 7-Eleven
Either that or electricity cost
Get your narrative straight about why businesses don't want to be here it
The actual companies
I think he's a Starbuck
I think that's maybe our real win here with Alex
Charlie Sheen
Trump was a good guy
The Russian television thing
And then they invited me to give him a little
Baltic
I bet if we're successful and it really huge and we one day or like
Alex Jones
So f****** awesome
He would love it
X
Have we have we considered
The Grinch
Oh my God
Have we considered
Alright
New York time
Does not write a post
It does not write an article
Taking down Alex Jones
Yeah
Deadwood
Is praise His Showman
Ignore the content altogether
Does he suddenly like the New York time
I think you might
Did that
Then
Is that how we
Cure ourselves of Alex are we literally in a world where if
Love conquered all
It doesn't work that way with him
For just a second
On the show he does like a half hour interview with joy Zia
It was that lady who wore a makeamericagreatagain dress
Do the Grammys
Great and her record sales interview with her about how great
Everybody
Biscuits
What are albums
I know idea
What are
He's following us
Are these Infowars
I thought
Never never
Tell me more about that
2 years ago
Where's the phone called on what
The dinosaur
Enemies
Yes very interesting
Annihilating
Little girls
You again
People enemy
So you can keep saying he's going to play that clip throughout the
The three hours I left doing never played even
Even in
And his
Recollection
Greatest moment
Trump is like
Yeah
Store
Interesting I got to go
Does not realize that he's getting blown up
You're telling
Too much hair
Yeah because like if you do talk to Trump a bunch
I imagine he doesn't want you saying
If I were the president I wouldn't like this I would say this guy lacks decor
I'm saying he's getting polonium poisoning this guy is not discreet
So
Attitude
Yeah
So
Maybe these calls happened
If they did
Again I think
Now that I know Trump
No I'm like
Austin on Spotify.
You know I got a man in my little other daughter's bathroom
Are very prompt the man in his own locker room
F******
That guy that you're afraid of being in a
Small girls locker room
The president is that guy
Too good.
So good he actually it's physically
Play solid gold
Alex talks about
Where's all the money in the world going
Almost all the wealth goes to
Building
Because most of the yachts and houses in real estate doesn't add up to
Yes tell me what they're building
Underground bases.
You're so close
World
So you saying that a real building their building is just a metaphor for the metaphorical
Yeah yeah
That's pretty good if that is true
That makes me giggle a little bit I'm on their side if I was going to build a building
It would definitely be a metaphor for another building on building
So f****** stupid
It's insanely stupid
He wasn't
Sing
Immediately so wrong on the thing
He's right
There's so much wealth
And they're not using
The Builder
Just have a computer number
A lot of it is just to secure generational wealth
That is what it is
Dynasty building essentially it's not
It's not that they want to
Build underground bases and get off the planet
Or maybe some do
Most people just want to create
Built like
Set my money on just now doing that are they crazy exactly
Stupid
Alex
You're destroying it Billy
Yeah that's
People trying to
Pretty homophobic
Give them
Magic
We will work give you magic advice for Boone's Farm
Avenue
The next clip is about a media lies and also drift
To homophobia
Infowars is ready to take action
I just I just right now in those the show Legion exist
Scare people they can kill me tomorrow they can come tomorrow
He's getting existential approach
In between
Grown men in the showers with her
How many times
Telling you you're bad you're evil
And you're watching come he's got me going
The frogs are gay in Houston
Play this stuff but my audience knows when I'm being serious I'm being serious
Now it hasn't he spent
So much try
Blurring the lines
Between when he's serious and when he's not
So he can get away with so much b******* introduces a new
Which is this is actually not even that segment
We have another segment history
Is full of s***
When he says
The my audience knows when I'm joking
I have definitive proof
The key
Is a monster
F****** liar
Now consider these
About Michelle
A man actually doing the this is your life situation
Urban Outlet
Old man who is the guy who
With mixer
Is he going to be is he part of
He doesn't
Arguing that Michelle Obama is a man
By the way this is a side issue I've always thought something was wrong with her
Beautiful she has she looks
Christian Lee
Scary and monstrous to me
And her shoulders are
Kids on a male's shoulders
Only another half
That's a well-known
Call an online video that I made
Talk about Michelle Obama
Looking like a man
Only released photos of our weather
Covering your shoulders
Angle
I've been here is it for years and I thought come on
Obama was raised by transvestite Nebraska
Look at photos over an official White House photo
And she looks like an MBA Center
I mean she looks more like Shaquille O'Neal in a black woman
Call Raisa
And then his dad clearly
We saw the documentary
You
With the famous
Pornography
Grandfather's was best buddies with
Famous communists
My husband from Kenya we visited his place of birth and multiple videos into
That's that's a lie but let's let's skip
You know what that's a lie
Tactful
Nothing wrong with me
Communist pornography
I'm going to go on record
Again don't care about that
Prehnite
Islamabad
Go for it also his whole thing about
Communist pornographer of dogs
Not cool with that I've watched
The Dreams of My real father were there any full of s***
Based on a clip of
Michelle saying
Talkin about HIV test
And when they went abroad they publicly took
He's always good to go to the homelander whatever Obama's home
Campbell ship Michelle is
I'm trying to prove a bigger point
The smaller one
Here's another another clip
You
Well Joan Rivers talked about in the last few days and it's a big International
News story
The question is
Who is
Michelle Obama
Is she really a woman is to be a man
No
Michelle or Michael Obama
Everytime I look at them something doesn't look like
She doesn't look like any black woman or any woman I've ever known
She's got shoulders that are wider than a man's which physiologically doesn't happen
Three heads on a man's shoulders and only
Two heads on woman shoulders
Anatomy
Women generally have wider hips
The Mender
She standing on
She looks like no woman
I have ever seen
Except
For people who have had different
Chromosomal disorders
Choose
And I got the statistics of the numbers right here in front of me
We're seeing more and more of these chromosomal disorders is all the toxic waste and GMOs
That's been introduced one of them is they Klinefelter syndrome or the double
Facts why
Where you basically are parks
Yeah can we just stop that
Can we just never
Naruto's seemed very serious
He was making arguments
He was referring to medical condition
He implied that he talked to doctors about this now
Now that was very much
Buried
Now listen to this
I want you to realize I'm not making this stuff up
But that shouldn't even quasi joke around about
Michelle being a tranny that was wrong
And I'm not David attack
End justifies the means I just get real cenacle in a bad mood
Makes it jumps out of things
F*** you
Do you recognize what that is
I was I'm making jokes
Are not joke
What is a I don't know it's like semi-formal wear
Give me anything
Situation where a quasi joke make sense
Or just as a
To say like what is it
Joke
Approximation of Pi
What would that be
It's not that
And then you just stopped talking
That's without jokes
Is Janeane Garofalo of his
He definitely doesn't have notes that he brings up on stage
And the stuff about turning frogs gay
Looks
Nobody there is a clear example of him
I met him claiming later
I was joking
Yeah no you can
That again
Locker rooms
I was joking
Everybody Talks
Whatever that f*** you meant the segment has been called
Amazing everything I just did
You're busted
Yourself
I don't know
Your part
Check your checked baggage
So
We get it
He says horrible horrible things
I meant sometimes when you realize
Jafar
Coward
Power
That was
Racist
Sex
It was rainbow beak transphobic
Those are all very real thing
Anytime
He ever says
Afraid of olives
You are those the
Thanks yep all of those
On the 1st
Dead to rights
So you have no there's no like
Other people you should respect the office
Nope.
None of the
Stan.
He is a racist
Transphobic who like in anyway insults Melania
No way you can say
Respect the first lady she was a man
Is a huge victim
You can't leave that poor woman there are those moments but there was that one video of from the
The inauguration when he was looking at her dad's smiling and then he turned around and Melania immediately
We got like really scared
Horrifying
This first one that I'm going to play
F****** weird
What kind of fun
And a little out there
I'm going to play
Is what made me rage turn off the app
Are we going to live are we going to have to rage quit the episode
Is that how you're going to do this we might but anyway this first one here is about
Serve about parenting
But Alex's childhood that's pretty fun
Seriously do whatever I tell him
Because
Approved
Call back whenever you want. Just don't be a jerk
Yes
Go to stand up for yourself
I'll let you do whatever you want
Keep in mind that his thirteen-year-old son works for him
Seven Hawks his product
13 year olds
And has those values and wants to that school
Yeah I'm told that's a good way to raise your kid
I wish he raped his listeners
He was like
To his listeners
Texas radio show
F****** father cuz he likes
The one that serious
They listened to every word
No it's really like whatever I tell
Please don't say it
In the bushes a couple more thoughts and then some weird s***
Cuz I love you
Oh no I forgot what actually is about to say I want to give a little introduction
Until he talks about the idea
People need
Therapy
Psychological issues
I'm out here working out my psychological issues with you
Young
Ancestral memory
Elegant.
And I do not know what to do
All I got was 80 years older than five
I realize everything the globalist do with the block that
Because whether you were little girl with your wife with your engine with your whatever you are
You have all these instincts
Call Discover.
Okay
Hello
So he's
He had ancestral memory
Physically with that
80 year old man
Yes
That's not him closet
No
A hundred percent
He believes
Young
And the only reason that he doesn't raises
80 year old man
Richard Nixon about 120 now
Yeah he is
What is
What is the weather they think about that now I want to listen to him tell his entire time I would love it
He would be f******
I would love it if one day on the show
Instead of talking about news
He just told his life story for 3 hours ever
Because like this idea of this ant-like ancestral memory
The idea that I was born
If you think of it just as in
Instincts and that we have ingrained things
Like fear of
Animals
And predators in Africa
Absolutely is ingrained into our DNA
Seems to be implying is that he has access
To some sort of wealth of knowledge
People are privy to
They are pretty
Me too
Yes
Now we have to answer the question
Is he right
Know about the globalist
Because
He is now seeing the globulus ACT
Very least
100 120 years
Can we vent that the eight-year-old man who
I felt like as a
The five-year-old
The same thing happened to
I think 100 years
How far back does
Just go I think the more likely Alex
Jones meat
Jesus that's the real question that that you're the person
He does
That the more possible and more likely
Is he
Paranoid delusion
And has since he was a child
Having a strong memory
Is basically an admission of a mental illness that dates back to
His number
He thinks he's the kid from The Sixth Sense
Basically
Okay so
There is whatever whatever psychiatrist
Psychologist
Get together and talk about this
Like there's that
Trump has
Narcissistic
Personality
It's been a rule sensor
We don't publicly diagnose people who aren't our page
It's hard to look at that and not be like oh do that dude
Delusional
Explain why
He has to label everyone to Just Breathe him as having a
Mental illness
Because he is an untreated
He's the only one of him
Yeah and
Everyone used to be like me
Episode
So now we get to the clip that made me turn off the show I will give it this
Lita
He knows what he's saying
I hope are you absolving him do
Are you like
Free
His behavior there in some way
Have to think that he doesn't know what he's saying
Because if he does then we have to end
The show
We're going to cry all the
No
But he is
Really on the cusp of legal
Okay
He is going
To say some things
But I don't think are protected by the first
Oh boy
Let's say that
And can we bring as evidence in his eventual position
Subpoenaed so bad that would make my day so much
Now what
Wanting to put a bullet in the head of trans people
He couch that in such a way that you can't
Say
You act
Sibley assault
Threaten to murder
I think it's
But he is
Slippery enough
It is within the range of what he's allowed to say
Yeah you got
He's got some wiggle room
This is a little bit less
Oh boy
Less than
Identifies with your brain
Last
A little direct okay and I also want to make it totally clear
Still has not played that clip
Chris Cuomo
Still talking about this clip at nauseam
Bring it up over and over again but never playing it
Because he knows if he plays it it doesn't say what he says it says
Get ready
Don't talk over this please
Sorry just because it's baddieville
Chris Como in Brazil
I wonder if she's the problem or her overprotected until her dad teach tolerance
Yeah you want to have a training
With your daughter
You should accept
Maybe not baby
Bro
You're pro-life
Jeffrey Katz
10 year old
So that's why they're the end but I think
Did you catch what I'm talking about
He has kids
Yeah
I think we should tweet Adam and volunteer
Yeah what
Yeah
He's encouraging people
To harass Chris Cuomo
About pulling their dicks out in front of his kids
Literally what he saying
He said that
It was
Now if he was nobody
That would be horrible
But he's someone who has dumb f****** listeners
Who are known to attack people on social media
That is one of the most irresponsible f****** things
I have ever heard in my life
Chris Cuomo about the situation
He was saying
Bet it is intolerant
Do not allow trans people into the bathroom
Of their identity
He was not saying
B A Daughter of some
Hypothetical person
Isn't
That is not what he was saying
That's misrepresenting it
He's calling people to action
Do something
Even though it's only over Twitter
That's still
Probably illegal
He said
Go on Twitter
Offer
Volunteer
And then
He very
Then let it was probably illegal
It is
To say to your audience
Go offer this man sexually harassed his daughters
And the only made that
After he had confirmation that Chris Cuomo had kids
F*** this
S***
Wow
Army fatigue
And then
And then you have
If you're saying that though
Best to believe it
He has to believe it
If you genuinely believe
Genuinely
That the main goal of all of this
Trains except
Get your daughters
Into a bathroom
I'm with a dude
Yeah
That's the only way you can just
Defy
Inside
People to do that
And I don't even think
Is if his
Nightmare hypothetical scenario about trans rights
If that were the truth
What do you think
No
The answer is not it's not it's not it's not if your kid is getting
Pedophile
Pedophile somebody else's kid
But never been there
How that works
He's also sort of implying that his audience would like
To do that cuz he said we should call him and volunteer
In the first place
You f****** filthy Spock
Call him and volunteer
So it's time somebody
He taught you a lesson
Fight hurting your child
Which it really sounds like someone who cares about you
Certainly
It has a grasp on the issues
I just spent over raise my children to not be a jerk
Yeah by being the biggest
F****** jerk in the world
What a f***
Monster
And that's why I turn this off
There's just no way that you can
No
You can
Now
Just make sure we're not we're not
Listen with
Second time around
Okay
Every time that Alex Jones wants to play on your sympathy
A
Play this clip in your head
Chris Como empezar Twitter
I wonder if she's the problem or her overprotected intolerant dad teach tolerance
You want to have a training
With your daughter and you don't like it so you're intolerant
You should
Maybe not baby
Bro
You're pro-life
Jeffrey Katz
This represents a tall guys
Open contacts
Okay
This is what this is
Stephen Colbert talking about
Go ahead
Okay I'm trying I was trying to write down as much shorthanded like
Say the word
Missive
He doesn't
He does it the same way Milo does as if it's taking up her free speech I will not allow myself to be language
Police
F*** you
In the shower with your daughter
How about a guy who poses
Is Johnson out
Part-time employees
Dad said you're pro-life get out
I think that's what Mario Cuomo
How about
Volunteer that
Yeah I think
I think what he
He was saying there
Is
How about we volunteer your daughters
To get
F***** in
In the bathroom
Even if that's The Interpreter
I think that's what he
Because I
I think
Kids in p***
At the age of 12
Which is also
Crazy
Yeah I think I don't know where he pulled back from I think I think what he saying is that
If
Here's what I here's what I think he's saying
I actually I think I might disagree with you on this
Okay
Think what he's saying there is
If we allow these trends
If we allowed transfer
People to go into the bath
That their gender is
That they associate
Their gender
Then
Cuomo's kids should go first
I don't think so
To go in
Strangers can do that by Twitter
Twitter why do we need a volunteer
I know it is a little bit is what exactly
Even if your argument is correct
At least
Harassed harassed
His children
Even the show new
That's like Oscar said it was going to go down I have to assume
Lucas self in the middle of it
You better get him recognizing
He has to go down that road
Ocean
I guarantee
Did some people
Cuidate Chris Cuomo
I guarantee it
Coward Alex Jones
If this ever turns into something
Yep
Now this is unfortunately the sort of thing that
We end up having
Undercover sometimes
It's so much more fun when we can just laugh and goof around but
This is also a reality
This is the thing
About his show and this show
That does put everything I've ever known about him
Before we started doing this
The the same like
Adjustable headlight
Alex Jones has this crazy
At no point
Is anybody really dead
Level oven
Yeah cuz this is 8
Truly cruel person
And that you're not putting up his
Rules
They're putting up the headline generating nonce
As cruel as cruel as Sandy Hook
Sibley tell people to go
Rape
Children
Either
Literally
Right
Yeah I mean
This is the part where were
Like the idea you can say like
Questions about the way he did
Because if you presented as a fake
All of those people are
Write in the same way
Look Chris Cuomo's a f****** monster and I don't want Dixon
Showers
It's okay
You can make that argument
I'm still be on Solid Ground
Yeah once you get into this territory of
He always
That sort of thing you can no longer say that you don't have a part
Is there a paralegal
Is that
Where are we at
I want to know what that is because
Is it it reminds me of
It's not this particular thing
But the thought that I just had was the the woman who tweeted so
Something about
Forgot something about HIV
Honor Flight
Got off the flight and was he had no job and everybody was saying
Destroy them
That was some organic
Weird internet just
Just thing that happened
Great guys we ruined one ladies life on Twitter
Awesome we're all heroes now
But that wasn't anybody
Direct
Is it
Weather outside
Right now it's against the law to
Get up in front of a large group of people and tell them to go burn
Yes
Does that apply to Twitter
I don't know it's it's it's sort of a gray area I know that apparently wasn't illegal him
In Tacoma
Comet Ping Pong Pizza
Right
And when he was inspired by
That's
The same thing is
Not necessarily the same thing but
Lenny told me to kill my
But I'm saying that he literally said that people someone should check out that
Third Bank
You should check out at checkout
If I could check out the pizza place cuz they make great pizza and somebody showed up with a gun saying that I Inspire them to go there
Boys the same thing
But it says the checkout contacts kind of work there
This was very specific
This one's very wrong
I don't like this
I'm not sure like I said I don't know if it's illegal I do think that you
Really on the cusp of what free speech
Protect
Because
Slander
Threats of violence
Those things aren't protect
Under priest
Those are still crimes
And I don't know if
Technically can
Construed as a
The threat
But man it feels
Yeah
You don't then f****** ice
I mean it this
Time
You're starting
Threatening
Good
The Comeback you always forget as much as I could
Stomach February 20
24th
On the Alex Jones program
I can't imagine a better
Hahaha
With him
Apologizing
I'm saying that
We should all be
Tolerance
And he started raising his list
I'm sure of this
Have to be Redemption
This is
Classic Joseph Campbell
Hero's journey away from me I'm so sorry about that
You know sometimes I get
I was joking
This time I was
Sincere and then I
I realized
What my
My beliefs were wrong
Grown
I'm a better person that's one possibility or other possibilities became back
And sold bone
Possibly more likely
Anyway f*** you Alex Jones suck you like this very hard for me to sit through
Underscore
We're on our way we got a couple of nice reviews I really appreciate it thank you
Show with Ludacris
Prince was talking to the logos that people have been making
For us all of this stuff is
Has been very heartening keep them coming the way that we did
It wasn't our choice
You could have left us alone in this world where we believe he's fun and fancy free
Yeah I would not be accurate reporting
Gmail.com
The people been send again we love it thank you all so much
We love you
Can policy walk
Alexandra Thurston color