Alexandra Thurston color
I forgot
We're so out of practice
We have a couple days off and I forgot the pizza
And annoying
Absurdly long
But I'm thrilled
Transaction not appreciate that unfortunately
I got an awesome time frame
25th
Chunk and Alex Jones is broadcasting
Career
There's some stuff
Blow your mind
There's some stuff that blew my mind
There's some stuff that should never have happened
Really quick what you're about to witness what you're about to
Secure is
Evidence
May have been the zenith
Alex Jones is mainstream
Any plays out in some ways that I don't
Any of us could have ever predicted
And I think
He still thinks
He's there
I think in 2018
I'm dancing around just a little bit it'll all make sense I was going to say is this
Whenever kylo Ren murders Harrison
No no
This is a salad.
Looking back
Halcyon Days of Alex Jones being relevant
To a certain extent
I feel like he's more relevant now and less
Even
Alright Jesse's wife
I want people to get excited for
Something really profoundly sucked out something to talk about
It messed up our new donors
What's going on
The gentleman
I'm not sure if I should
Even bring that up
I appreciate it
Means a lot
Thank you so much
Defensive like
Yeah that's right you are going to donate to our show.
Not at all
Absolutely
Appreciate it
This is a new level of
For now we have
Foreign policy global
Technocrat
I don't understand why we have any of these levels
Our next episode
We have a brand new level
They were going to
To be revealing I'm not going to be turning into some Dragon Ball Z
We get somebody all the sudden there's Super Saiyan level 3 word what's going on
Necessitate
And one of those circumstances happened this week
Brian
Posted in our Facebook group
Magazine
On eBay and listener
Jumperoo
Bought them and got them sent to my house so I have an entire collection of info
2013-13
Christy
I've got one of them entirely
Library
I'll be creating about Alex Jones
Which is the
Memorial Library of potion and lies
I have names like Egan
They're excited about that but
I had to say
Terrible writing
It's terrible writing
Buttman the graph
Design work
He's on point I don't know who's doing this graphic design but
Lick man it looks
Good I'm going to post a pictures of it but like
There's some
So
Miles above that really just blew my mind
I'll post a picture of it on our website
Videos of meteor
There's a volcano going off
This is great graphic design work that's pretty good
If I grabbing
Any whites
I appreciate it so much
Thank you all and everybody out there
The new level the Keegan his achieve
Hey we would be doing that right now but I forgot to make the battle happen
Specifically chose as an eerie resemblance to our poster where the volcanoes in the background and I could
Definitely see you're tackling Alex Jones because I'm about
Yeah yeah
For sure
Anyway
Alex Jones
But my love of talk about bulshit his not
Rectifier by Fred
And it's really interesting that if you look at
The history of the Tea Party
Yes one of the things going
This is what we're looking at
As we go
If you look at it it all grew basically out of
Foundation
Freedomworks
Americans for Prosperity
They funded a bunch of
Glenn Beck they basically bolster him today
Irrelevant
Sponsors
So I love it
I love whenever a small amount of billionaires control all the finances
Americans for Prosperity
That were on
Split
A group that was founded by David Koch
Charles Koch
The 1984
Now
Do you know who the first chairperson
Of the
For a sound economy would
When they founded it in 1984 Oliver North
Interesting
Why not
And so at this point in 2009 January 22nd
2 days before
Trevor Leach
Who is the chairman
The Young Americans
For Liberty which was a group
Actually named if he is a young American
Anna young conservative
F****** play easy chairman of the Young Americans for Liberty
What is a group that sprung out of Ron Paul's failed presidential
He organized
Tea party to protest
Bo Beastie taxes
The governor of New York
I put in place
Can't buy large 24
Kickoff
Of what would end up becoming the
These.
Copycat but a lot of it is also a interconnected
To describe these people is
Akin to the serial killer or kidnapper
Meyer's book
I'm not sure if she cleaned it but that book dark money they talk about it is
The code to put the coax
With their
Directions
To put space metaphor for Goldman Sachs
Good luck
Metaphor
Everyone knows visually what an octopus is the word octopus
Work you can put in a lot of
All right we got
Is chicken the same family
You got it
All of these other white
A lot of this is because
Something happened the way it starts out the show on January 22nd
Makes me feel
He's not aware
Of a lot of those forces that are at play
The funding
Adecco card
Is already in the works
And it's getting ready to Bubble over
Is it the end of the formal
The protest
That went like a larger
February
I am in the month after that but not Fox News
Started covering it and all that s***
It is it is like
A little bit under the surface
Even to someone like
Best friends with Ron Paul
The leader of the Liberty
Right it's important because
Listen to this clip
It shows a lack of
Of forces at play
Both parties
Jones
I don't even know what that
I do
But no one is talking or discussing the fact
Pub
Racist
So in the next two to three weeks they're going to collapse
Prediction didn't
New always been right
Even he knows
Is Fox News is talking like that
Even he is aware of that like
They know there's no steak
Also he doesn't
Seem to realize is that like
His rhetoric
Being co-opted for
Specific reason
Because they don't want him involved
But they want
What is to be a piece of this artificial
AstroTurf movement
So
It's tough cuz this is another moment where you can almost sense
Feel left behind
Like he sees his buddy
Ron Paul going on
I'm saying the things that I like to talk about
This is the best movie
Because once again as we've proven and as we William
Every episode
Veronica
You never gave up the game
Give It Up
I don't know much about Glenn Beck
Glenn Beck comes from like his Mormonism and stuff like that
Shock jock
That's really invalidates all of his
Theatricality and fake crying and stuff like that
Cuz at least like there is
I think there's an argument someone could make and I wouldn't hit him
Like Alex really believe the things you say
Yeah I mean like if someone told me that you said Glenn Beck really believe the things he saying I would hit them
Sudbury
Conversation about it
Because
Heathens
There's there's so much
Craft
To Glenn Beck
Career
In terms of like
A
Fake
Low-rent Howard Stern
Prank calls on the morning show
Fox News and then they are
Who is about
The old time
Isn't folks Enos
A little bit of Garrison Keillor a little bit of like Pat Robertson
A little bit of Rush Limbaugh
Is an artificial creation
Very easy to see through
Remember him
About 9:12
He should f****** die
Remember how we felt on 9/12
I want to murder you
Hey you know what I don't like
Think about how you were on 912 I would hit that
Get that s*** out of your
Don't know really fun fun little piece of information
V9 principles and 12
Statements and 12 principles
Publication like about these
Steve informations in 12
Principles or something like that
I was like what our movement stands for America
Buy coke money
Don't deserve this planet
Or whatever
Attributes
Already already
Completely crib
From a book by W Cleon skousen
No that's
His uncle
Joel skousen who's on the show his uncle is W Cleon skousen was a member of the John
Society is mostly responsible from everything I've been able to tell
For a lot of
Active misrepresentation
People live cam
Where can I get more in-depth in the future episode I have a couple
Episodes we're going to do
I'm preparing those right now
So don't need to do that
It's interesting to see the
This lineage of
Montebello
Uncle book that he wrote is
Responsible for Glenn Beck 912
To become more lies
Exactly
Allconnect
Here's another clip I guess
About
Jokes
Tea Party
Does misrepresentation
Presentation of
Becca said
Vanity
Fairly recent
Stop.
What like
The truth
And their CEOs and people
That's
Absurd
Absurd explanation
What's happening
I don't think any Media company has ever accounted for like
Oh well if we don't tell the truth we're going to lose a lot of list
About that
Alright so
Here on the 22nd
You know what you know
You don't want to my favor
Commercials that he had back then never not going to love me some random
You don't have a diamond gusset commercial 2009
Sponsor that I've never heard of before
And it's a scam to help you get better memory
The school of phenomenal memory
Information quickly
And efficiently
You need to exercise
Exercise mental
Improve your memory
The school of phenomenal memory will a
Is your person
One completed
You'll be able to memorize
Information
Guarantee
Hypnotic techniques
Or other tricks that you said
Valerie asked you why you think I don't trust that commercial
Well
School of phenomenal memory already seems a little bit over salad
Also misspelled or mispronouncing demonic
That's what they were to namik
Did you take Manama Cannon there
Different companies that made it to air
He mispronounced mnemonic
Baby did you forget that maybe you need to take the six
E-courses again
Monadic Menomonie yep that's crazy
60 lessons and then you will be able to memorize entire books
I don't know but I think that's a pretty absurd
Some pop psychology bulshit quite like that
I'm so undershirt
Our old buddy
The guy who's
Himself Hellyeah bobcat
Comes back Bobby chaps and I started to really enjoy Bob Chapman
Man voice
And very much unlike Tracy Chapman
Is completely
Absurd fear-mongering
On this episode Alex
Havoc
Pacific point
And bring him on
Use for him
But I think you'll be able to figure out exactly what's up
For Staples the rich guitar Ridge How It Go
Arabic
Retired for two years kennel
Former world
For 30 years
Is there a snow
Explanation
The fact that you
Be able to stay out of
Financial Harm's Way
Come with me if you want to live cuz I also enjoy the title
Alex Jones arguing with song lyrics
No this song is incorrect
How did know
Alpha flight
You can see the game real pretty clearly right there
Baba
Talk about like how the economy is going to collapse
Buy gold
I mean unless you want to survive the coming apocalypse
I know there really isn't the reason but
The table more or less
Right after this clip Ted comes on talk about his British sovereign
Lady Sovereign
Shut up
Anytime I take a shot
Anytime I f****** go for it and just look at me weird or give me naked appointment
Look at you
There's a little weird that was. That was just as I read and I wrote
You say that is not a weird.
Incredulous open already
Fair enough
That's a fun game
Little bit like
Chair sales pitch like
It is incredible and I'll tell you something
Anderson and he's going to tell you about the
Will you come in and have your life
I give you a free
Hard Sell
Playing out there
I don't know what else to say about it but like if you're
But if you're listening you don't understand what they're doing
You poor girl
Is that there's a lot of like old people
The same people who fix
Thumbs up
VC who don't
Understand what's going on
And they're the ones that got ripped off
Anyway your prosperity
Built entirely upon the backs of TT
For sure
August 22nd we're going to days
To Barack Obama's
Does inauguration man-o-man
The stars are out
Haha
Alex Jones on the 22nd
Joe Rogan is
So do we get to hear a little bit of Joe Rogan is like
Joe Freeman
Being sweet and dumb I don't know Eddie Bravo was like a media figure in
In 2009
I don't know their history but I've had him and Joe were friends
I don't know if
Anyone
Cared about how stupid he was
Or how Charming he was
That's what Joe Rogan is in town he's in Austin and so he comes into Infowars Studios
And through it we kind of realize that Alex and Rogan have
Exactly one story together
That makes their French
Ladies and gentlemen
Microphone
Important
Are you
We met in 99
Remember when when when
George W bush Mass
Silhouette
Running around the grounds of the Capitol building
That's the only story they really had it up like twice
On this episode and brought it up on when he was on Rogan podcast
So they wore ex-presidents vast and did not rob
You can find the video of it it's on YouTube it's swelled up
It's just I'm running around in masks and then smoking weed in the bathroom
It's not
Shenanigans Charming on detail of Alex Jones
It would be like if you and I were friends
For 10 years
And the only story that we had was
That time that we did shows in The Burbs
And had a great time
Like if you remember the time that we got on air together it was
That came up
I mean it would be like oh you're trying to really
Reinforce that your friends
Figure.
Well it's kind of spread
You think we're fresh
I know we're not really friends
But
You're so
There's a slight imbalance
Exploded
Music
Use a
In-demand stand-up
Newsradio
Because we talked about it
A little bit about being
And it's because of that now I got to really appreciate like
Craft of creating like a good television show so makes it hard to do another one
Goofy game show in others not really supposed to be a cop
It never happens
Your backups.
So the connection cut out the government
Well I'm a far less threatening than any of those gentlemen
About me I had comedian
Those kind of making fun of Alex
Little little
New World Order imater scary event
Cliffview Resort of making a
They're doing an impression
2 m
You know Rogan not
Totally
Not into
Some of the things that Alex
Shazam 2
She is about Ron Paul
First off
Restructuring of our government
I mean
He's a real conservative
A fiscal conservative a social conservative
The federal government is completely out of control that is
It's a flawed Institution
He believes have to get rid of the Federal Reserve
I mean if you look at the way it is now
This is a honeycomb
Option and
Sure whatever you responding today
I can't even now I can't even remember what
Man just
F*** is he talkin about whatever he's like everybody knows
Good idea to get rid of the IRS2Go
Everybody everybody doesn't know that
It's easy to get seduced into Ron Paul's line of thing
Because he is very sensible.
Foreign entanglements
Stuff like that
Drug policy
I'm so if you're someone like even like private prisons
Here again
To like someone like Joe Rogan
Weed all the time and
Generally inclined towards pacifism
Like
Rich
Yeah except
Travolta be abolished the FED in the IRS cut
One of his biggest bike rally
Comprise the goes around is
Federal Reserve
Check if this is
This is sort of a misconception
Playing on people's
Unawareness of what actually goes on
Yeah cuz you can go to the federal reserve's website
And audit
Does the Federal Reserve ever get audited
Yes
.
The the Board of Governors
The 12 federal reserve banks at the Federal Reserve sis
System as a whole are all subject to several levels of auditing
The government accountability office conducted numerous reviews Federal Reserve activities every
To the board's financial statements and
Compliance with laws and regulations affect
Independent office
Inspector General
The results of this
Independent auditor released
To the Congress and
The boards
The board's office
Inspector-general conduct
Evaluations of criminal
Nations related to programs and operations of the board
As well as those boards delegated to the reserve back
Some of the reserve banks are also audited annually by
Independent outside auditor
Each week the Federal Reserve publishes its balance sheet
Charts of
Recent balance sheet track
It also provides a
Interactive
The balance sheet is
Including the Federal reserve's h-41
Statistic release
Affecting Reserve balances of depository in
Institutions
Statement of the Federal Reserve Bank
Clearly fake
Has just about their balance
Team doing making it up
I don't
White understand where the line is drawn between V like
Rallying cry to audit the Fed
And the reality of what is
You've done
Do you know like what is
Not being done that they want done
Call Oliver
Okay great
What do you want you think the answer is
You bring that stuff another like
Yeah
No matter what do you think isn't being audited
It is unsatisfactory
Same thing that same bulshit from Rogan that stupid
Is always like oh well it's a it's a
The complicated
This was like
Yeah cuz it's a f****** insanely complicated complicated sis
Unlike a one-word
Like with those men in the middle or liquid
Consumer Financial Protection Bureau
Shouldn't be
Because according to the law
It is the outgoing director who can appoint his follower
In the interim or whatever
Right
This is base to The Reason
Challenge is it based on
Law that was written that
Kind of says that that supersedes with
The president appoint
It's the difference between the life
Should or could
Fire log
Actually said was
Could
Like there's no way you can write perfect bulshit on there
Wyatt becomes Hokage
That sort of semantic breakdown
So
What are the other reason
Three sort of frustrated with Joe is that
As we as we saw in the beginning 2017 when Alex was on
Rogan's podcast
Chief complaint
I had was
Rogan Woods
Something
Maybe challenging or like a question per hour
Alex Wood
Yeah that's right
Repeatedly and also Joe talking about
Working
For the u.s.
Collegial interview
Rogan's career need to listen to
Ears Alex saying that Obama is
Going to be worse than Hitler
Bush was bad
I know it
Aaron is just accepted
And now you know he's got the spoiler is that
Behind the scenes
Right now
In January 2009
Alex
Editing
Producing his Obama
Deception docket
He's already
The quick turnaround time South Park episode later on I don't think it's on the episodes of recovering he gives
The release date of it
He's rushing Vistaprint
Okay basically all right
Do you understand
Painting Obama in a really negative dictatorial light only serves your interests
I'm selling this documentary that you're creating
That's what you're doing
Okay
Documentary money
I'm guessing they definitely wouldn't have although I would almost like to live in an alternate his
Street where we get to mccain-palin
Ception
11th hadn't happened I doubt that
Well certainly.
But I bet that Alex wouldn't have made any documentaries that were
Harshly critical of bush
I mean we can't rewrite this
We're going to have to develop a niche
Interdimensional travel
Perhaps contacts
In Vacaville prison
Call call Mark
Abso
Despite Alex
Who knows what his motivation
His motivation maybe Pyar me his motivation
He's trying to
To fix the defect or
What's the time
New World Order
Well do you think a new world order that I mean like a new order to the World hours today
New world cattle-raising starts
What is a set
One World Government
What a good idea
A little bit not pushing back
You should have said what are you talkin about when they say New World Order memes a global government
Ocala Post
Good question
Is it possible they just mean a new
Way that the world will be ordered in the world
Especially considering the fact
Mere moments ago
He was grieving
To get rid of all of this
Old World Order
Premature for me to bring this up but like I've been reading Carol quickly
Tragedy
Misrepresentation
That's not what I was writing about
So much
The focus of people like the author
School of economics
Lamesa Institute which are big parts of Alex Jones's
Philosophical underpinnings
Desire to get back
Gold stand
Desire to go back to
Dupree 1914 economics
Which is when the Federal Reserve
What I remember.
It was wonderful
But what's interesting is
The internal Quickly's book if you look at he does talk about how there's a network of bankers
Some stuff that we're trying to
Manipulate settings after World War 1
What cuz that just makes good Financial
What Alex never takes
Come to a cow and never really disgusted
Is that
Their goal
Stanford
Donuts in my headband
These the protocol herbalist
Yeah it's Alex's is taking
The people that Carol quickly wrote about the beginning of the interconnected
They have the exact same goals as the message
Well yeah but that's cuz we all know they were
Correct right
I don't know what to think about that but
Everyone polish
Evil
Even in the service of
A good idea okay
So these globulus
Their coop.
The get back to the gold standard argument
In order to
Further cement their power
If that word
If we were to go to the gold standard and they would be able to submit
Their power
Standards in order to keep them from doing that.
It's too loud
Thanks so much that's good
So
I remember
Do whatever your enemy.
The right the same thing
Mister Rogan leaves
We don't have Eclipse but it's worth bringing up
Austin Police
Okay yes going every now and again back then
Really
Because already savedo does an impression of Alex to his face also
You hear a kind of thing
Because he believes
She believes in Community Connection
Stuff like that makes it a priority to go around like I looked into him and like
As much as
You can ever like
Stop
Kind of like a lot of
The stuff that he seems
To be about seems like a good dude it seems like
I don't know enough to give him a rubber stamp
Mayor or not
UNLV police chief
Houston came over in like 2016 from Austin to Houston
To work on that department
And during Hurricane Harvey he was f******
Out there with his people
Elderly people from building
Huey like
He had this whole thing where you didn't trust the electronic and automated gauges that would tell him where there was danger zone
You got all the people out
Monitoring particularly
Vulnerable sites for flooding
Where they're old people and disabled people there that would need help
Music
Proactively trying to make sure that the damage would be as low as possible
And that's one of the major reasons that cited for why
The death count wasn't
Is because of his
Really active
Really engaged
Approach
Alright so we did some heroic ass s***
Well yeah I would say so and it falls in line with
The philosophy that he espouses
For policing
With
On Alex's
The show and interviews that I've read with him son
That is like
You're going to make much better work
You get out there murder
There's also has a very strong position of
Keeping his
Officers
Accountable for their actions
Trying to make
Body cameras automatically turn on as opposed to
IOU
Getaround s*** could never imagine get around that
I think he's pretty cool seems pretty on the level
Further review answer the two of them have a fine again
Does jovial conversation with each other and
Alex keeps trying to bring up that lady who got arrested
Spelling of Bloody Mary on an airplane
I don't know that story I've ever you have to send it
It was just that over and over again, I thought I'd no idea
What do you mean you can't comment on something you know.
We move on now
And it's just this on the 25th
August 24th is a Saturday
On the 23rd
We get
My voice went weird.
We get a little glimpse
Intuit Alex Jones's Finance
Does look like back in
So we're going to be
Truck show
Worrying about can I get a microphone can I get a camera
Sodus Point
Concerned about buying a Michael
Yeah
Van Dyke
I mean I don't know
I don't know
Look like a good mic
Couldn't be more than like
Thousand dollars
So the idea that he has to
Concerned about $1,000
It gives you a sense of the operation
But he's running
Now
The same time
Important to get the highest quality for your lowest dollar that make sense
95 bucks
It isn't necessarily the top-of-the-line
Absolutely
You could very easily
He talked about I don't have 500
Snapshot
January 20th
2009 that's where Alex's finances are at
I'm inclined to believe it's the prior though
Well we're not in trouble
Which in Alex Jones pilot who'd never
No I think it but I think I took
Sincere
Lakers
She's asking for money
If he's wanting money
We are in trouble
Is the way to get it
Can you make the situation much more dire
Him saying we're not in trouble means like
We can use your money but you know I'm not going to f****** be manipulative about it
With my gold
So Jordan mysteriously told you at the top of the show
This is the Pinnacle of Alex Jones
Relevant
Interview with with Joe Rogan
Yes celebrity Joe Rogan
Pixel
I could tell I was looking down
Do you also have you also have
An interview with legitimately
Police chief of Austin
Yeah so there's cultural
Write these are in the
The chief is giving him the time of day to come into studio for like
This pretty
That's pretty
But then
On the 23rd
Something happened that I never expected to
Angelina Jolie
Chris krs-1 Parker parkervision
Vicious
Peach Productions Bland
Message
Dexterous
How's asr-10 how's the real is it to hear him read that bio he is reading it
Very uncomfortable
Krs-1 is on the show
Why
Don't know
Is it going to do a couple of tracks know he's not but it does turn out that Kara's one he's very much
Afraid of the New World Order
And the Illuminati
Yeah I guess I don't know
Look if anybody should be afraid of the New World Order
Ckrs
So what I mean
Like
Man
I don't I don't know what I don't know what to
I think about this other than like
If I'm the next episode like Jayru the damages shows up I'm going to be like
What happened
Krs-1
You made it I would say
You know what I bet Master P would go on but I bet Alex wouldn't have
That's what I would guess
That's not
You want to go with Big Daddy Kane you think
Willard
It's just
Super weird to me and I would really love to talk
Gareth one now and ask him what he's
Like
We won't go back on
And I like
You do it is another
When I say his mainstream relevance
He puts out isn't still overt
Someone who is
A smart
Insightful person like krs-1
Could come on Alex's show
And find common ground
What's some of the things of like
Yeah I don't like I don't like violence
And stuff like that
And what have you
I disagree with the way they look at
The New World Order and stuff like that
I understand also
The people have
So it's not like he's in Kara's one is insane.
Killer Mike went on today
The owl
Killer Mike
I couldn't do that
You don't think so
Qpublic
The ship that Alex
There's no way that
Bit someone
Who has a career
Would like an R8
People got all mad about
But I still don't think
That I just
I think you would get
Too much lag
Cuz you got one
And then all of your fans would end up posting all the time she said really
F***** up stuff about black people
Ancient like that and then you be like
LP
Don't go on his show
Even if it is just
Like we see eye-to-eye on Gunn
No way
Well they don't see eye-to-eye
Because Killer Mike would like black
Alex
Saves you would
Like like most gun-control reforms in America
It's going to be once
10 guns all the sudden everybody going to be for
Did you read this story the other day I was going to retweet it
But I don't I don't like to retweet the
The taste of JuJu or about Infowars
Give me the story about Tyree Campbell
Gentleman who got arrested
Because of that
He was labeled a black identity
And predicting his movement
Palantir in the lake and if you read the article here on the garden
Investigators began monitoring baloga
His legal name is Krista
Super Daniels every participated in
Austin Texas
Cuz rally in March to
15 protesting against law enforcement
Especially
Aaron Neely said
Court
BFDI niley said
Learn to the protest from a video on Infowars
The far-right site run by Peter Alex Jones
Fox News
Wait
Infowars in court
Stunned baloga
Quote
They're using a
Conspiracy theorists video to justify their tyranny
Reference Infowars
That's not good
Your are your your lawsuit
Charges indictments
Be tossed immediately
You're at you saying a black person with a gun sparked my
Thought of this
Because there's a picture in this
Article of him
With a gun
State of Maryland with a handgun
Picture of item
Really like I'm not
It's really f***** up
B b
These are the sorts of things
But you got to realize you got understand
But I'm glad they brought it back
Here Comes
Alex
He reads another like minute
AppleCare s1's
Bayou
The same Rover hip-hop stuff and confused by all of these things
Introduction
That this is the good
The Hip Hop
Exactly
ARS one is are Gatsby's
About John how horrible the
90 +
Away from that but he's a pioneering have off
Record
Partner
Anti-war
Pandora
Krs-1 on the show
Hello how are you
Elsa real is at
Types of realism
Just to hear his voice
Alex Alex
Cultural violence
Yeah it's a piece of us
Piece of our history
Biologically we
You seem to have
Rise above it
What have you
Can we
Added to my lexicon
Absolutely
Oh man Cara
There is a reason that you are immediately incredulous
Instincts
So it's it's a what
Does
Need to seriously learn a lesson for telemarketers
I'll tell you this
Quite a while
I can't find it
Infowars.com
For all sorts of word combination
Pentagon study murder-kill
Societal breakdown
15 days
There's no article on Infowars
Where he backs up
But it's just historically true
90% of the human Race's eventually
I would like to hear from an article in slate titled
What really happens after societal collapse
Doggy dog or lions and Lambs
Sun article
Open 2017
61 paper there's unpublished until 1996
Sociologist Charles Fritz laid up a case
For his country
Perspective
The disasters and other majorly stressful events don't necessarily result
Societal breakdown at ROM
Disasters while stationed in Berlin during the Blitz
Gloriously happy people
Enjoying life to the fullest exhibiting a sense of Goethe and love
Of life that was truly remarkable
With Britain
Reaching Beyond class
Sharing supplies
And talking to people who they have never spoken with before
Marshalling sociological and historic 11
Example after example
People pulling together in the midst
Of tragedy
Black and white police militia members
Uniting to maintain order during the yellow fever epidemic in Memphis and 18
Enemies for getting old corals during the German bombing
Krakow in World War II
Community members reporting
Strengthen personal
Relationships with Neighbors after the White County AR
Consol tornadoes night
Are so numerous
Of when the s*** is going on when it hits the fan
But all the chips are down
People are social creatures
And we don't
We don't
Each other
When those things happen
Unless
Echoes
Wait
Kia is the Independence Day Theory of a global coming together
Zombie movie mentality
What was going on there is the people who is that
The only way for the entire Globe to United if we hadn't
Extraterrestrial Force
Like the only way human beings will unite is in the face
Of some larger
Naruto
Exit
Independence Day
My friend okay
Pullman
That's kind of
Fairly
Compatible with that
Biscotti
Majority of
Circumstances
When supplies are low people helping
Which other and
And disasters
Come together
Carrot one
To save us
That's just
I never forget about what is it is it
Interviewing
It's a little bit more of that with Alex line
Sad
In Austin Texas
Krs-1
So much for joining us
Have you studio tomorrow
There's no snow tomorrow
Straight up we don't
I'm right in your left
I hope we win
Not right now
What a bummer
Port Apartments
Hip hop stands with Alex Jones
I feel like
I don't think krs-1 speak
Score Hip Hop
Delightful and wonderful his music
I don't think he has all of hip-hop
Ever
Terrace one
Disappearing more time than this will find out
Haha
Professor Griff
She seems to like Alex Jones quite a bit
Immortal Tech
Those are the rappers that I can pick up who have had any affiliation with Alex
Stanford
Mainstream pop
Who's the king of the soulquarians
Bob Chapman
A comes back
On January 23rd
That's very weird
The economy coming down
ARS Wanda doing it
Forecast
Open right now
Revising your forecast
Chili's
In the forecaster
At the beginning
The forecast
After hours
Or I want to catch people
Attention
I said
This is it
You go all in on gold
Silver because
They're going to take off
Which I've never said but
Never
So go all in on gold and silver
Not surprisingly
Prices
More
Doesn't get any better
Jesus Christ this is so over
What they were yesterday we can't just let this go
This is a limited
Time
Offer
Two days in a row
Alex has Bob Chapman on
To talk to Gloom about the economy so you need to get in gold and silver
Immediately transition to Bob
Time to do his failed pitch on gold and silver
This is what makes me think that you're not necessarily
Reality
Is there pushing this
It's tough to say I don't know
I don't know I don't know if you did this forecast 2 weeks ago
Today be any different than yes
Did he just get some sort of brand-new forecast in the ultimate Saturday forecast
But Alex
And maybe it's just because he had a little bit more decorum back then
And doesn't want to show ass
Maybe that's why you said we're not in trouble
Moana look like
Modern-day giving up
The pretense of not being desperate
Bothering
You know what if we
We don't make a ton of money but we just survive that's okay maybe there was that feeling but now he's
I need a lot of money
I know it's time for me to tell
But I will say
Another guy
On the show
Snow krs-1 it's actually Kool herc
It's not
Guide
He's one of the good ones are the bad ones
He was he was
It's pretty good or bad I suspected this guy does not stand I'm not terribly sure but
Your yours Alex
Report on what's going on worldwide
Problem
My problem
Course
What is
Responder
Sounds like a half-hour with his
Survival food sponsor
He's much like the soap guy but he doesn't say any limericks so I'm not going to listen to him
Alex is going to sell it now it's get the cut
It's just
F****** over
Read a ruler
Three days worth of food
30 Celsius
Pens that have 3 days worth of food
Okay but what if you run out after
Three days you should buy more than three days worth of food
21-day Bend
Just for like Fine Arts
Like maybe
Snow storm that hit New York
Shuffle Bot like
Why everybody is needed all the time
Yours give it a Hard Sell Here
That much different from Blue Apron Plus
A little worse
If Blue Apron was trying to scare you into buying it
And also Blue Apron
Okay
Steelers
Does perishable that you can't keep it in your shelf forever that's the survival food
Totally
Military rations are the only thing to eat
Yeah
So on this show also I don't have any time I do a special episode by myself about this is who I think it is
Merritt's covering butt
We have a limited time your show tonight
I couldn't make this a 3-hour epi
But there's a couple calls that Alex
Square peg
Call him out on
And it's really in
Interesting how we respond
Because he
He's arguing with this one guy cuz this guy calls any talks about how that subsection 51 Barbie baba baba
The subject section you're talking about the next one after it says
You need
Consent
Informed consent
And then he goes to commercialism
Or whatever so on the radio
Commercial plane
Put on the Infowars stream
They're still talk
They're still talking
And key
It's worth equivocates with the guy a little bit
And
Exactly what it is but that brings up something
You exaggerate about this
Completely wrong is like
It wasn't about that subsection video admit
But then you know that
Got got to go got to get back to the shop
I can leave it off the actual episode
Cuz it's far more important things like Heroes one like Joe Rogan
This team is developing of
I've almost Vaudeville
This game that they're playing in order to sell gold
We get to the 25th
The Sunday show
Like I said
One of the big reasons that we're doing this 2019
The receipt
Shocking differences in Alex Jones
Philosophically from 2009
We go to the board
We continue to either anti-police neutrality
He is
Also
Explicitly pro-palestinian
Not Carol
He doesn't talk about Soros the bad guys of the Rockefellers in the Rothschild
Differences in
That day's Alex Jones in present-day Alex down
Here comes another one
Just signed a
Friday weather
Leader of Israel
Minister of Israel
Next year
Buckle
Program
Or two
So
On the waterfront
Obama
Exactly Spanish
Neocon
The Pat Robertson
Coming out
Alex knew in 2009 that are on
Program of nuclear
Is peaceful
The exact
He says that they were trying to make nukes
The entire time
The modern-day with trying to make rationalization
Infer why Trump is cool to get out of Iran
Deal and what-have-you
What he's essentially talking about is
Trump's position now
Which is
You're either going to give those up or we're going to a hundred military options
Where is position was
How about
And we make an arrangement where in
We give you your money back
Chris
You can get your money
Also you will agree to all sorts of testing
Oversight
And the Iran deal did have very specific
Pieces of like
If someone is not in compliance with the deal these are the steps that can be taken
Cuz there wasn't
Because some countries
So when the deal was made there was an expectation
That was a possibility
So they were pieces of
The deal dealt with
So no getting rid of it
Stupidest thing in the world can get the money back we're not going to be able to enforce the same
Iran deal
Why
But everybody is not going to go along with city on a hill.
Like France
Who's chaos
Drunken
Ex husband divorce
That's the way the world treats
Pray that they go for regime-change
Title
Exaggeration
To deal with this guy cuz we need the alimony money but God
This is the worst human being in the world
It's really really f***** up
That Alex
That's his position
Counter
I don't know a hundred percent to turn everything
Don't
Because
All they're doing is playing
Reply
If Trump does anything that Obama does the most brilliant idea
Even if it was a good idea even if they know it
It's a good idea
They have to support Trump
These people don't
Believe in anything this is why
We've touched on something that is why I'm not into
Interested in the current day
Like
The Thursday show from last week it was just
Piles of b*******
But when I watched
People on our Facebook group do want us to talk about the present day
So maybe instead of Project Camelot on Wednesday we'll do it modern
Episode
Just to be like
Here you go or whatever
One of the things that
What really struck me is it first of all it's an incredibly stupid
More so then
In 2009
For sure
Jumping back into watching it after having not watched for liked
Stop shows like
F*** this is stupid
Like I was just like
There's nothing there
And all the things that I could really bring up our like
His guest is a monster
And I could tell right Alondra list of things about this guest
Like and then all of the other stuff is like
He's a hypocrite
And as we talked about over and over again you even brought up there
That doesn't matter
Right
Big version of it in 2009 the hypocrite
Is much more interesting to me
Because
You can look at them in I gave you the hypocrite about xyr seat
Critical
His awareness in 2009 that are on
Nuclear program
Was for domestic use it was for electricity in research and stuff like that it
Hypocrisy
In present day
But in the past
Clue
It's a clue
Because the thing
Change for a wreath
And the specific things that change
Change because
Someone f******
So these are hypocrisy
Many of these people are
Actually motivated more by money than ideology
I mean baby I don't know I haven't started a whole lot of a lot of them
Human Nature
Right
No not
But these guys are still alive
I'm trying to make
But like Impreza
It's pointless hypocrisy
In the past
It's indicative of something
Clue
There will be
You know there is follow-up on
I'm not trying to bust him for hypocrisy
To guide me
Towards like
Who
Would have
The Pacific
Goals
In my
That Alex is rhetoric changed
The shortlist
I bet that really brilliant
Because what we are talking about in 2009
Is a more independent
Alex Jones
Is not quite as beholden to
So many of these
He's independent at Subways but then also of course
Independence
Then you start to see exactly whose motivations
Archangel
Exactly
It's not just like
I don't like
Bisque
I meant Big Biscuit
Comes in Idaho
Weird example
Big lobster bisque
You know like it's not a superficial thing where you change
Better
Name
Big Berkey
Big Biscuit
Big Beth Bath
Water filter you don't want biscuit
To be associated with the filter
You will make it to the Superbowl
Now I can't remember
I thought you're talking about
Bronson's
What like a baby
Who cares
Yeah that's the point I was trying to make is that like these are not superficial pointless things
The change position
Shrek the idea of like
Being cool with what Iran was up to
Position that check
Did you have bean Pro net neutrality
Shifting to anti net neutrality
Is a position that
They aren't they aren't superficial
Preferences
Or something like that
So that's
Very
More revealing thing is that these aren't just
Wide Republic adopting random like a wide swath
Policies
So much as
Why would you change your opinion on
Specific
Stickley netnutri
That is if you thought about it
Clearly against your best in
So
If you're picking something specific
Said something
Add what are the things that don't
You also another
Clue Into
This guy
You know the things that don't change
Like him thinking climate change is about carbon tax
Write those sorts of things that are consistent
He's very pro-russia stamps
Like those sorts of things are things that you know
All of this
6 Clues
And I understand why this isn't like
Maybe as fun as listening to Alex breakdown enough laugh at him
I get that
But this is
Substantially more important
Exactly
Alex Jones
He said that he was going to talk to
The krs-1 tomorrow on Friday show
Okay
Policy change
ARL
Alex who does not like krs-1
Koch brothers
Alex mission of Americans for Prosperity
No Cara
That might be one of those
Terrorist one show
Is his report from it
Krs-1
Barack Obama
Barack Obama's a new world order
Everything
Pizza
The phone last Friday
Saturday
Behind you
And he was telling me
How many people
Professor Griff
Fans of this radio
And the films that what we do
Expanding from there
Yeah I talked to my buddy
Does a major
TV show in Hollywood
Charlie Sheen
He told me you're the whole cap
Michelle
Read Scripts
And
Krs-1
Call me routine
Case you were wondering I know things
Fighting
Like a big guy
Exponential
Pretty crazy
So
Dang
Anything about the
The relative in Telugu
Of all
UFC
Beacon cost
Gentleman
I'm not generalizing
Of course UFC fighters list of salt
I don't begrudge Alex
For thinking that
Maybe Everyone likes him
When he has in the same week
Joe Rogan and krs-1
Making time for her
You know
Now what they probably said work
Something like that
Sit around the dressing room and listen to me
Like you could
You can understand where like
You got to pick up
And maybe like Icarus
It leads him to
The fly too close to the Sun
Because he thinks he's a much bigger deal than he is
At this time
Anyway
Harb recent episode I told you that I thought that Alex wasn't going along with the Obama didn't
Swear in
That didn't do the inauguration correctly clean
Inauguration
We pointed that out to Obama then two days later
Do large parts of it
So right there
Already
Reported on it
That made him redo it has already taken credit for that
Absurd
He then was born in
Cameraperson there but in my cereal
Record it
Any did the Square NY have a camera Facebook
I guarantee you
Debates about Woody swearing on a Bible
Hannah was he really a Muslim almost at work
Alright
So if
Conspiracy
Youtheory map
The way that it is metastasize is now we're past the the
Cinderella midnight theory of global
If you don't do things right
The first time everybody invalidates it
And we're onto
The whole reason
It so people wouldn't
See that Obama
Wasn't going to
I swear it on the
Okay
Because he's
For example Theodore Roosevelt
Didn't use the Bible when he was taking the oath in
1901 John Quincy Adams
When Pierce war in on a book of the law
With the intention
They were swearing
The Constitution
Johnson was born in our Roman Catholic missal on Air Force One
Missile missile
Am is s a l
Cuz if you said missile on Air Force One
Instructions and
Necessary for the celebration
Nevermind
Yeah
Are plenty of bread
In our history
And other things
That are not
Bet bet
Cockamamie
That's not
Anything anything any of the
You can go back
American Pie
Yeah this guy already
Make a big deal out of this
So would you believe
Yes
The Bob Chapman is on it
He's on again
And we learn a little bit more about him
Here on the 25th
That is super duper
When I was 9 krs-1 denied ride
To take down the selves
Okay good good
Lately
Because his track record of protecting
More accurate than most I've seen 95
Receipt
Everyone is 95%
Everyone just like just like every dictator gets the popular vote
Single person that Alex Jones talks to his 95%
So stupid
Nike Huaraches
Retired
Didn't have.
Was the largest private seller
Gold Brokers well
Toys for 45 years
Help Tempe
Producing public. Are called
Conspiracy
Gary Allan
His partner
Work with us on the other leaders
That is big so many other leaders in the
The fight again
But that's big
From 45 years
I didn't know
The bobcat
Was responsible
For financing
And Publishing none dare call it conspiracy
In the
Influence line of Alex Jones's life
That's
Really
William port
And if
Making it so we're going to need to do a full on episode about none dare call it conspiracy
It'll be fun you'll be very mad
But it also led me to be like wait
I need to look into Bob Chapman
Yeah because I was like
He's just a
Stupid gold guy whatever who cares
I'm not really worried about what this guy
Like for the most part
The clown and then I started to look into
And Bob Chapman is
What would I call him
A fast car
He's a blossoming flower of question
It cannot be answered
He's dead he's an onion bloom
Yeah there's layers and layers to a little bit
Stockbroker from 19
Cheetah 1988
During which. He was probably the largest gold and silver broker in the world
According to his
So
But I believe he was a big
I'm sure is a pretty big Square
But that bass
The question
What the f*** happened between that. And now
To reduce him to being the from the top gold broker in the world
And obviously a billionaire
To be independent filled future Act
The setup
No
After 1988
Well it would have been the stock market crash of 87
No
Also there was actually looked into because I thought that 87 was possibly a source
He lost everything but you couldn't
Because golden dip that far
Only took a short
Fairly small dip
It was not something that someone like Bob
Call Chapman
Would have
He's f****** stupid
And just
Babies sold everything during that
Small dip
I'll be at most likely
Be better as help
But I watched outfits for this
It doesn't make sense he's someone who's like
His whole life
Is just about buying gold
And I gold will save you
And the idea that it starts to go down a little bit and he doesn't
Hold on to it
It just us
Track
It would be but it would be very ironic
Do something had to have happened at that point because
If he was a huge billionaire
Maybe he still was I don't know
But if he was
Money
Financial interest
Wouldn't be
Making him do this embarrassing s*** on Alex's show
Somehow then that make sense
But if not then there's some philosophy
That is guiding him towards being this
Trump frolicsome today
I don't think so just married one
Throughout his life
But I looked into it a little bit more
An interesting
419 6
222 1976
Give me pretty much all of his money from
South African culture
What those ears
Where was Apartheid
I was alive and well
He was making
Shootings on South African gold shares
During a time when I was it was that intention
Subclaim after 1976
She started moving to North American golden silver any sites
As the break-in
Interesting Lee many experts view the Soweto riots
Lesbian
And in the open
Which obviously made his gold operation impossible to run
Adult for North American Gold which
Definitely be lower-margin
For him due to overhead expenses don't exist in apartheid
So he's making a killing off this s*** and then pressed black people
Started standing up for themselves
Education
People died
Is horrible
So
What you see then
Isn't having to shift
From this spur exploitative
System of making money off the gold
And the resources of South Africa
Into much less lucrative version
After 90
T76
Should have switched in the canto
What diamonds
Now interesting
Knock knock outfit
From 1970
Cheetah 1973
In those gear
Bob Chapman lived in Johannesburg South Africa
And did Rhodesia
There's literally no champ
So you could live in two of the largest and
Cruelest white nationalist States in Africa
For three years
And not be keenly aware of how racial oppression was in place
And how it works
And his f****** telling
Informed his life and work
At all
The only explanation I can drop him that if he was perfectly fine
With a tons of money
Yeah I would say he's not he wasn't just perfectly fine with it he was overjoyed
Certainly.
Delightful
Troubling
That wasn't already enough
He lived
In Rhodesia in South Africa
From 1970 to 90
Team 73
None dare call it conspiracy was published in 90
30 time to Bob Chapman would have been financing
And helping get none dare call it conspiracy published
He was living in apartheid South Africa and Rhodesia
And making a killing
Stealing and selling natural resources
Apartheid
Great
Stormy Dan
Sorry
Thought it was delightful.
Everybody prison
Entire goddamn life
So I started publishing the Gary Allan report which I can't find any copies of those or anything
Sing about really online
Early newsletter type of thing baby
Like really really early types
He then went on to publish
Claim to fame
Does a newsletter that presents
Investment business
But I found an archive of it
I started reading them
They're the ramblings about the New World Order the Illuminati
Eddie mobile
Any cost
Sentences that people buy gold the newsletter is
A hundred percent of vehicle
For selling gold
Sphere
Fear-based mind
His entire career is based on
Droid nationalist apartheid States gold sphere
Based pimping
On Alex Jones Show
Kind of
Common trajectory
If this is incredibly f***** up stuff
I'm trying to look deeper and find out more
Connections
That could possibly exist but like
I don't think
You get more messed up than the idea that the guy who's financing and helping put out none dare call it conspiracy was
South
Skin apartheid
Getting gold and getting rich off it
Black women complain
I don't think white nationalists are good people.
Here's another interesting wrinkle
And the international
In one of the issues that he put out
Very literally
He said that
If Ron Paul doesn't get elected president
We're all doomed
He's a big Ron Paul guy
Has connections
Society
He's dead
Pancreatic cancer
Couple years back
Let's go Khalid
Let's get him again
Probably living in some new Rhodesia somewhere
F****** a****** New Berlin
That's a real bummer
But this appearance
Why is he on
Well I would hope
To sell gold
For the schuckmann
The owner of
Call brokerage
It's right there I just want to be totally clear cuz we have to be super fair Dallas
This is the only time that I've heard him
Correctly
Site hoot at Anderson
Yeah he will say he's a sponsor or something like that but this is the only time that I think he's above board
In terms of like FTC rules
About you have to say
That this person
Run your f****** Network and owns it
I don't think most people listening
I would have heard it
Chad
Bought gold
He hasn't it
Score
He also won
I'm Your lady
Hard copy
Cam
I wanted to briefly bring
So they could call
And find out about that
Midnight tonight
Because then he's got
Going to have to put clock on it
Higher price
Technics sl 1200
Would it be smart
Physically
Have partner
Well
Recommend gold and silver related assets
Hooters
Very strong
Because
Can say
After all my years
Experience
This is the only place
And he's selling it
That price
Purchase
Pay $45 he was selling them at that level
$15
Please
Alright talk to you like
That is so
Over
If so
So Bob has said then all is like the only thing that then makes
Tattoos that Bob has a vested interest in
Genesis communication
Invited
I can't I can't find
At press time I can't find a specific connection
Between the two past
Philosophical connections the Ted Anderson is a big booster for Ron Paul
And I also
Has
Leaning towards
John Birch
Both have that leaving without having basically I'm just saying that that's the only
Firm connect
I can find between the two of them outside appearances on the show
It's late because Bob Chapman was a player in the game he's just going to stay on the sidelines
Fell for somebody else National forecaster is a sponsor on Alex's show and it appears that they're also again
Communications van
So they buy add time
That's one connection but it doesn't
Rationalize this
It doesn't it doesn't make would be
Like
In many ways
Sticking his neck out
Credibility as a Wonder
What's the world's largest
Golden silver brokers in tubing like
Right right
But Midas resources is like these deals are amazing
And I don't I don't want to read like
The pages of rip-off reports
About Midas resources if you Google
It's very easy to find
Pages and pages of
People who got ripped off
Bite my tongue
Market
Constant Market
Horse tears
Constant weird like hidden
Charges in
Speed
People who bought gold at like
A certain amount and then trying to re
Resell it later
I can't find a buyer for you
Constant with with
Ted Anderson
It was a reason that he lost his truck
Cabuyao NYC
Cuz this s*** caught up
I'm trying to reinforce the point that you are making
Is it like
He has to have some sort of skin
In this game
It doesn't make sense for him to but I think you probably also knows
Enough
He has decades in the gold business
Noah's potato
So he knows that I want to get on board with this Camp it says
Where is
Alex just
Later
Wrinkle of his career
Oppressed minority
So I don't know man I don't know what conclusions week
You can draw but
There's something
Really really major
Really really f***** up
What the f*** is
Chapman Do It
How old is he
Like 12 or something along those lines so he's
You got to be late seventies right now
Let me see
So
Died 76
Oh s*** too he's in his early 70
He died in 2012 so that's
3 years after the Escape 7373
Not a big player in the game anymore obviously since he's on
Infowars
Still got something going on
International forecast
I'm just being a
Magazine
Gold propaganda
I don't know I mean
Yeah probably
I have to
He's also doing like insult
Chipettes up like that giving Financial advice to people on
I would assume
I don't know man it's really weird
Easy racket
Refuse
Like if you're hiring him you should really already know what advice is about
That defect unless they give you
Read the amazing advice Everett what's your what's your ossicle
What would we need to look at is
This
3 days
Is an Alex Jones history
Open up
A number of questions that I think are running
Expected
The first
Is what happen
Like because
Or what didn't
You know cuz like
They're like I said there's a decent chance
You still a billionaire and coming on and chill
Like if you shilling
And not in financial disaster
Then what is
His motivation
What's the final of the philosophical reason
If you could just be he's old and nobody else is paying attention
Certainly we all know that the show is the
One-Stop shop for old weirdos talk to anymore
The flipside is if he doing it for money
Then what happened
Where did he lose his billions of dollars
Because he had to have had billions of dollars
If you was
Raping South Africa
Yeah
Second question
What was going on in 1970 19 71 when he was living in Rhodesia and apartheid South Africa
And helping Gary Allan Get none dare call it
Conspiracy palette
What the f*** was going on there
And is there a connection
Is there some sort of
Is that cool
So there's that
And then third thing is I guess I don't know
Do they keep doing this
I don't know if we can a batter that from these these
I believe it was in the 90s
In the 90
I believe so it's possible
Responsible
You know like it like
Where else are you going to admit maybe maybe
Chapman
Acolyte
Maybe Ted was like all
Too late for me to rape
Country so I'll talk to this guy and see what happen
Let me see if I can
Can get a star chart North America
I'll try and fleece
I don't know if I can find
Start date
For Midas
Function
Negative
Harshly negative reviews
Now that not a solid BBB rating
Check out piss
Consumer.
I like that I don't know I can't
He was his mentor
Is that Darth Vader
You welcome
Also that is another piece of it.
Needs to come into question
Another big
Clearly
Bob Chapman
There's an indication of someone who
Who is fine with or
Sports bike
Right
You can't live without you can't have the career that he had
Without
Pretty well
So
How much of that is relevant
I don't know
When you get there
Most of these
Most of these people who are
So
Violent towards
The rights of
Any kind of Labor
There are also
Violently White
Naturalist
Let's talk about the Koch brothers
Whether or not race is their stated
The Bugaboo
So to speak
They're all of their he added
Bugaboo
Kabul
All of the Bugaboo
All of the
Things that they are for
Did they are advocating
If you if you start talking about
Getting rid of
You know when you start doing them
That is mainly
Racial bias
Well that didn't last a racial violence together
Together but what's the highest percent
You know all of these
Sings all of the
These policies put these conservative fuckfaces
Want to divorce from
From there
White nationalist
If not entirely
Affecting
American Idol
I would just bring in
Conversation I guess
Is
Violence
Is the app
But is it
Intentional violence or is it just a
Lack of regard as lack of
You know what I mean
Yeah I don't know but it does for the conversation
It doesn't matter in terms of it being wrong both are wrong but it does matter in some ways because you have people who are like
You know daily Stormer
And stuff like that who I like know I get hard thinking about
Destroying my door and then you have people who I would say probably isn't like
And out now Tracy
He's just like
This system that really
Viciously oppressed minority group
The non-white
This system was really lucrative
Ton of money
So I'm not that I don't notice
The violence or something like that
But it's different
In terms of what you want to keep your eyes open
The clues
And the point
Don't find too much
Particularly it whether or not there is a
Distinction
I don't give a fuk
It's academic weather
Bothers me far less than
I understand
And I agree
But I'm just saying
The keeping things straight
In terms of what we're looking at another one
Totally feel like in terms of like not getting off track and being like Bob having the racist
Something like that it's important important
It could lead us down a stupid road
But whether or not that is is it different
Fun
All except that only because you got to get out of here you got a show tonight
So
Let's do it so this brings us to the end of January 22nd
25th and 2009 I think
Is a lot of Revelations
A forested
There is one
Infowars
Yep we're
Nobody asks Alex follow-up question is unfortunate
Nobody ever asks
Follow-up question
Alex
Tell Anderson to Bob chapek
Under clearly running at the
Three man three-card Monte Styles scam on the radio
Alex
Do do some rest in about fear
And then bring in the closer
Exactly like you soft
Metaforas Park
So
The f*** is wrong with you guys or what we're going to end up learning
Because that Saturday
The 24th
Is when that first tea party thing happen first
Little protest
Is growing
My suspicion is
Alex is going to be
Against
To start with
He's going to he's going to be like
Petty and bitching about how it's not
But I don't think he's going to he's going to be against but I agree that he's going to be
I think he's going to be like
Call me Ernie Crusher 2
That this was so I think there's going to be some of that but I think he's going to get with
Program free
Suck my that's my theory but we'll see
We'll see how it plays out
Cuz you and I are both just
Bowling alley have no idea
I think from the 25th
From the 25th
To whatever it will be I give it two weeks
Before he is
He is right there saying that these guys
A little bit more than
Two and a half hours
Cuz we've seen this trend it that goes through so he keeps getting left
Behind by stuff
Like we see it already was Ron Paul going on Glenn Beck in this episode modern-day with qanon
Buc-ee's
He waffles back
Come forth with PICC line for being like
I don't trust it to being like
The only thing to trust he doesn't do that
Does
Momentary like
Hacker got really rich
Berlin to Max Keiser
But
That's why I think
It's going to be longer
If there's one thing that is through-line throughout his career Beyond just being in favor of Russia
It's Vicky
He is a late adopter
He is someone who comes to the party late and then is like
He was here the whole time
He started it
Start
So I think it's going to take him longer cuz you didn't know
Understand
Reality
Jerome corsi and Alex Jones
Turned on Cuba
Sure Riley from their articles though
Qanon
An overbite
The globalist took over Cuba
When did they get there
What happened to sveta qanon
Making fun of Jerome corsi
Sort of like
Javis Petty idiot
So stupid
So f******
I thank you Jordan for taking time out of your busy day to come in and do this is much more fun than
I'm here with the plants
Sticker Cthulhu Bank
Remember who it was but someone
The figurine
I'm sorry
Sorry about my active,
If you want more of the show you can check us out. Com
You were there
You know you weren't here for the last
Episode
Someone
It's obviously go fuckyourself Reagan but literally
But f*** yourself
Thanks for holding
Alexandra First Time coloring