Alexandra Thurston color
Novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
What up what up playboy
Like we did not do on our last episode
Situation with Chicago's weather
Started perfect nailed it
We would have gone something like
Doremi Faso Lottie yellow leather yellow leather
I know a lot of
Completely caught up with doing that
Today's episode forgot again to make the sound drop
For arguing on the next episode
Seriously
We made it through one round of the bracket
Okay Bubba
You're just hoping I would never bring it up
Garlic
Pizza
Deep reference
Alright alright
Maybe one person listening to this will get that belt
Back labor
Alright alright
I don't know
No let's just let it go
I wish I could
I do wish you would have brought him
Wish
But we have to get
To it
Also has been around
And we're thrilled to have her on board
Susanna
I'm a policy wonk
I guess I'm out Shanna welcome
Call swanky
We would appreciate it
Everything is
Appreciate it I could use I work more if you'd like
Alright
Something I don't know your attitude
Second of all
What time we're leaving was the best
I don't appreciate that we're not doing Project Camelot episode
Sound off that we aren't talking enough about modern-day Alex Jones alright
And so at is
Schmidt
What
Yu-Gi-Oh
Yo
It's not a punishment
The people who demanded this
Right and also enjoy it it's more a
It's more of a
Beware what you wish for
Careful
You're keeping track
Over 50 people were gunned down
And Israel I didn't hear that
Which makes for an episode of The Alex Jones Show
50 dead in protest
Violet
As opposed to
Military murders unarmed people what other way
Tubi
Not all that song
I have two pretty fun out of context drops
We're about to turn your lights on
But that's something that Alex should say if he's like
Starting a rock concert at North Korea
Write that like I like buffer did with
Something money on the
Which unfortunately
The today's episode will also feature
As if Alex talking about Israel was not bad enough
It also involves an hour of goddamn Milo yiannopoulos
Dammit
Yes yes Dad
Nice dynamic
Applications that I don't I don't want to think about that at all
And I wish you hadn't said
We're going to jump in here and we'll get to get to Alex
The show but again
It's important that we remember that we're also concurrently doing an investigation
I wanted 2009 Alex was
Full throated Lee
Supportive of the Palestinian
He was against
Bu violence and atrocities that were being perpetrated by Israel
Upon Palestinian population
Fairly obvious position not to shoot on our people
Thousand
People
Sniper fire
That's probably a lot of that stuff
Some of the problems Alex's rhetoric as we go along but let's let the nice to know that
Actually
They just they stopped with the whole thing they're like
United States
Barry Iraq
Perhaps really perhaps the best way to fully destroy the Jews
Is tricking them into starting a war with
Is the Middle East
Project
Gentleman's draw
Asbury
Germany Lost World War
The Nazis didn't
That's really hard to argue
Like Alexa
Lost
Your baby
They're not wrong
Just
Try to yell as little as possible cuz you're going to be so mad
Good Start good start
Good starch
You and me both
Political system
No
Israel
Is not expanding
And telling me I can't have a church on my street
Israel is not telling me that my children have to submit to Allah
Israel is not
You're almost
George Soros
Brothers country
Oh boy
How many newspapers Publications
Please
And they basically told me
Yours
It's wrong but that's like him that's like humans
Expressing is there like in the lawsuit
They also say
Alex routine
Background information
It's really all about
To know that the powerful backing
Is that we living in a spy movie that's only in his head
Just clip up for Wii
Conduit
Technically true
I just kept that last so in there just to illustrate how long of a pause there is there
Going to be a lot of pauses as he tries to navigate the worst
Close to him
Israel
Is it explained
Now if they were those how would you feel
You wouldn't feel great
Might be against that right
Imagine yourself in the position of somebody who was
Unless they perhaps
The people who work
Actually
Murdered by the government would then be on this you literally just a loose
Sedated
This project
This thought experiment that you're proposing is flawed
Requires a modicum of empathy is not on the table
Find abstract probably problem
Side effects
So this is going to be pretty much
Be going
Theme throughout all of it
But I'm just going to talk about hating
Israel
Here's the issue
Alex believes
Nefarious powers that
Play
In the world right now
Support Israel because the alternative
It's something
Real scary
Smoke shop
That's a great work
Program
Subaru
Man
Alicia
Adulation
Avalon High
And the false prophet in control of Jerusalem
Color
Jerusalem dollar for everytime Alex declares of Babylon
Default
We were living because everybody
God dammit
Obama
Obama's advisers who by the way really funny I've been listen to 2009 we're never going to listen to clips
Sunstein wants animals to be able to
Alright
For like that
You know what
I think I might as well just because that would be the
Hello Doug are legally allowed to confront
I want to take over Israel and Jerusalem
Yep
Yeah together
In concert
That's true
HBO
I would I would call this this arrowsic. He's just like this is high levels of bulshit
Fat like
It's hot
You need to prove anything you're saying
You know it's just it's tax
Stacks of b******* images
Anyway anytime
Perfect Christian
Commentator talks about Israel
Sooner or later you're going to go to sleep in a
Really what everybody likes about Israel is just like the
We definitely have to have it
Cuz then
Israel
Is that what they think
Rid of Israel they be like
The Bible isn't real
Or if you get rid of Israel that means they were already in it
Or something like that I don't know
I don't know ask about Rapture cuz it's always
Hard pass on this bike that I don't care to know like once I hear like Alex in a caller arguing free in
Post-trib rapture
That I like
Spectrum
So anyway the Rapture is never mentioned
Here is some interesting
Islam bashing
Some boots touring
And Alex do something very interesting
Not involved
Wow they're lumped in with Christy
Really interesting research talking about Christianity
Islam Coronavirus
And you'll see that Islam is expanding
Islam is not
Contract
Christianity is Contracting
Capitalism is Contracting
Prosperity is
Remember during Barack Obama's inauguration
Beach break down when he was talking about how I brought up
I were at War
Economic troubles and Alex
Vector them together Alex just
Vectored Christianity capitalism and prosperity all together
I'm only doing this to Alex Jones
The vectoring but I'm only doing this because it's
He called out in
Bring it up every time
Which I would say that the only thing
Capitalism
Christianity
Common throughout their
History has been
Exploitation of
Minorities
People that
Professed to help
Expand as far across the globe
Is it possibly could
Does Deadpool look like
Two other lands they're spreading this
What's the First Nations
So much
Emily Islam takes over your country
Continue
Tubi free
Is expand
There are countries that are currently Islamic countries that are currently
Islamic
Could work there is a house of Islam
There is the house of War
House of Windsor
Pre-sex Gosa Gosa
I want to pause there for a second really quick
Because all Alex is doing is taking this from a guy that he
He talked to during the inauguration of Donald Trump talking to a guy and the guy screamed
About the house of Islam in the house of War outside of the house
Islam is the house of the world
How houses work
Well separate houses
Only have the house of
Islam
And then everything else
Say what about the house of bugging
LL Cool J was on it I think
Issue is that Alex
Just took this from this guy that he talk to you during the inauguration it didn't look at
To the concept at all
Right there is the door of Islam are all hard
Which are the two distinctions
Countries that are ruled
Play Muslim
Without
And you could you could
The darul harb is the house of
Saphir translation
To some extent
Not not a literal translation
From the Arabic
And also dar-al-islam
Doesn't mean the house of Islam
Necessarily
It mostly meme
House of peace
Is what
The word Islam
Look at it in the Arabic
What it comes from is
Come together like salon
Salaam alaikum
Islam General
Accepted to be translated as
To enter into a state of peace
Surrender or
Submission
And that's not exact not a good
Translation
It's those who have entered in
State of peace
So if you look at the darul Islam
You have
The house
Of those who have entered into
And those who have
Interstate
Nonky
Raccoon translated as War also a different language all I heard was the sound of
Dirty monsters out
Speak American
Say gesundheit
There's also
Which is the house of
Call Richard
Yeah it's like
Between two countries that country would be said to
There's calm.
Which is like hey you're cool
Yeah there's there's other distinctions that are made if you actually
The most but not all of that
Do you like
Just alyx
From somebody he was talking to on the street because it
Fit into his world view of
Muslims want
To kill everybody who's not them
And he has incorporated
Into
His rhetoric and his narrative
That's really f******
Stupid
Very bad
I'm going to say this over and over again
You are a f****** big italics
Leaving like a big
It's also it's also interesting insofar as
It reveals how terrible his stories
Really are interred supplies
Is because something really happens like
I met a guy on the street who said this
And I realized instantly that this was something that is so important
Learning about dancing
He does not tell a story about that
That just gets a simile
Where is everything
Isabel
Which by the way
Exact end of this episode
Instituted real time
I'm just completely making up a lot
Islam is already in control of most European countries
Commentary
With more than
Poor country
What
Block
You have Checkmate control
35% of white people have a lot of
F****** power understand that ladies and gentlemen
I do
Not all countries in Europe
Parliamentary government
Not all of it
That doesn't mean that they all get
10% of the Coalition or whatever like
You have eight
That groups combined to 2% of whatever MN
Absolutely
That's okay that's all that's awesome hot bulshit
Like if you if you look at the elections that are currently happening in Iraq
It is
The guy who is the guy who's winning is a fierce nationalist
Like they're so the
Consomme correct
Weirdly
Strange mixture of what's going on at like the more you look into it the more fascinating it be
Because
What everybody kind of predicted
Was the
The pro Iran
To get in there
I think was a pro-american guy or whatever
And he is not doing well
Well
The pro Iran guy
Not doing well
The pro Iraq guy
Who doesn't trust America or Iran
Also
Their governments
So the way that it set up
You got like 30%
Of the phone
I meant they have to figure out how to deal with everybody else like a like a
Parliamentary
Democracy
Like that today it's the same thing that happens when you get a
Labour and liberal Democrats
Coalition going on to serve
Nobody agrees on any
It's no different than any other system
So
Jump
Cuz we got a lot of clothes
Last night as we recording this
OurTime
Israeli snipers
Shot
And killed
It's over 50 at this point
Absolutely
Footages come out of
Tear gas being dropped from like drones
And stuff like that
The Seas of people
A t-shirt
It's interesting cuz Alex
Actually takes issue with that
But not for the reason
Is a l
Yahoo said that it's absolutely true
That's not good
This is called leadership
Trump was sticking Isis up his dirty a******
What happened
Alright
Sister called not doing the same thing
In a failed piecemeal
Across the fence
Having six kids
Why do Turbo
As a weapon system
What do you think his problem
Amazon didn't have a stake in it
No he would hate to accept Visa
Alright thanks
Alright alright mr.
Because
And didn't fire it directly out of another human being whom he was
Injured miserably now you're not thinking like as a booster
With the psychology of the individual right you got to think about how f****** Petty
Himself involved
I remember seeing that
Removing criticize 10 years ago
There's no use drones to surveil
Real property search
Over 1,000 newspaper
Who was the first
Disinformation pitch
If you're so funny fight Jade helm
Defensive posture about the
These articles that have come out that I have shown that Russia
Control account
We're promoting
Yeah
Really f****** defensive about that but I don't give a s***
Really
The Palestinians how is
Against
Before that I only kept that part in at the end
To demonstrate
The he does not
Say
It's wrong
This crowd of people
Years ago they made fun of me
Updated bypass
But he said it was bad at the
The time
Back then
Yeah
Nothing means anything
Dammit
Market
Curfew Manatee about himself
The aftermath
Cuz I forgot what this
This is about it's just marked Alex seriously hate
So let's enjoy
Situation
That does not mean he doesn't get out of hand and
Anime
Understand
It's disgusting
But I want to address that really fast
He's complaining the
The other story
The day with Palace
Look up suicide bomber
Yeah that's the one he's anywhere they were using
Children
Suicide
Absolutely related
Is that all
Palestinian
That's right
Haven't you seen the that's right there everywhere
But that's his problem
The same mentality that leads into the stupid idea that
The globalist are all one big group that are against him and like Mexican dances
Focused
Idea about his enemies
And it's just
It's caca
Recently I don't know
Disconnected or not but I want to say
There's something that is
Profoundly unsatisfying about doing the show
Because at the end of the day what we're doing is kind of a
Describe it
Like you know who gets laid at a party
The guy who's like everything you know is wrong
Even if he's full of s*** that's really appealing if people are really turned on by that
Where is the guy who's like
Actually
Most of the stuff you know
Kind of accurate you just got this morning Watts than you think but most of the broad strokes and stuff
Is pretty close to what you're told
Alright that's not right
I'm going to stop you right there
I'm going to say
What was the last party
It's been awhile
Because the answer to that question is
Neither of those guys they're both creepy and weird
Those guys are in the corner talking to each other and everybody else is like but the guy who's
Okay baby I'm basing this off like when I was in college
Open your eyes
It's still more appealing and intriguing to be both I like your eyes are open just read a little more
Littlemore's you understand
Some of the
Pieces of the school is usually not the best
Are are like
I'm not going to make
These feathers gorgeous
I'm going to write
The 97th
Be able to like
Gin up his base and get everyone excited by saying
All these Muslims across the world are suicide bombing
If somehow
Conflating it with this
Is real
Massacre
For lack of a better word
Conflating those two things is going to get him a lot of
Attention
Is base is going to love it
Where is us saying like no that's a completely different situation that it has no correlation
It's bad yes absolutely we certainly aren't
In favor that right
Making things up and inspector exam red.
Yeah Alex has the coat from and loves it right thing that's going on now
They're doing everything that you think about America in Red Dawn
That's what's happening to Palestine right now there's got a better
I like metaphorical
It's a direct
189 it's not an allegory
Wonder Woman
They don't have cool Jack
I don't have cool bomber jackets
Palestinians we should go with Wolverine
Has Palestine okay letters alphabet on
Alex said a choice has to be made
I think that there's one thing that could happen
To get him on board
Turn them white
It would help
Probably wouldn't hurt
Turn the flashlight
Didn't he can come out with a really good
Concessions by the Israelis they've never done
Wendish
North Korea
Really wants to try to fix the problem
Is there women wearing hoods over their heads
Girl jungle Dawson
That's gross
That's really really gross pets
That's profound leave
Disgusting into
Painting
Entire culture
With a broad brush
What I hear there's really nothing else to say
Like we shouldn't even respond
Quite frankly
I'm I'm at the point where like listening to modern-day Alex Jones
He doesn't deserve a response
Like that sort of rhetoric has no place in
Decent Society
Here is why that rhetoric is
Something that I
Immediately like latch
That is
My eyebrows are raped
Oh that his viewpoint
Is 100% correct
No problem I mean it look if they fall
Those people are
All of our The Munsters you imagine them to be
So if you
Really dive into that world view it make
Clearly
Stupid
Clearly doesn't believe it
Because if you really believe that
Then you would f****** do something you would have killed those two girls at the pool shop
Choice
What is that
But that same concept
The high-end respecting people who think
Abortion
Is murder
Brave
What is the look
If you believe that abortion is murdering a child of course your world
That's you should be doing
But you don't really believe
If you believe that you would do something you're not
So f****** Brit stop pretending
Stupid
So much what
Constantly comes back to you is like
We could have like a conversation probably about
Conclusions
The people come to
But people seem really reticent
The debate
Discuss the premise
And the premises are the one part or the parts that are
Profoundly flawed
Because in order to make that argument that Alex Jones
Is premises in his argument
Is it all or both
Muslims
Are just their identity is putting their women in bags
And cutting off their children
And I putting their bombs on their children
Moral
It's our moral imperative
Right stop.
But that promise is not something else would ever want to discuss
Because it's Pat
It's absolutely
He doesn't believe
Who cares whether he believes it or not
It doesn't matter
Level up
At the very least respect
Lego
Pimply
Weirdly
People who say they believe it
I meant like
Again
It comes back to like you've accepted this argument without looking
Bring it what it's built on you don't know what
Is
Supporting
You come to your example abortion is murder is the
Looking at
Alex's argument Muslims evil
They don't
Have any bearing in reality
Anyway even when the even when you
Which like
Yes
This is an issue
Ed we're on board
Genital mutilation
Guess what
There's a bunch of
Liberal organization
That work
Young women
But there's a bunch of atoms
MC organization
Computer on the ground working trying to help people trying to change the way
No young women are brought up
Open for in contact with trying to evolve population
Right
Alex is doing any of that s***
Okies injecting
Squeezing into the national conversation
Slightly
The Muslims are going to take over
And what have you heard
Alarm
So this leads us to a new segment on the show
Set alarm
Sound the alarm
Alright
It is extremely important to introduce geopolitical disorder into the internal American activity
Encouraging separatism and ethnic social and racial conflict
Actively supporting all dissident
Extremist
Sectarian groups destabilizing
Political processes in the United States
Guy
Did not sound the alarm he's heading on the show multiple times
Is from page 367
Facebook Foundation
Games of GTA
He heard him
Well but I mean like
He's literally sitting sweetie to
Destabilize and completely crippled the United States we can bring the Soviet Union back together
Way to stop the globe
It's apocracy but who gives a
So here's out
Abundantly
Liquid Esports
It just comes down to that I'm not labeled a radical Islam and
Fights for Israel
Israel
Works
I don't see how that works
I do not see how that works
Alex got a hotline to be read
What is that
So if I if I come on my radio show and I say
People who died Israel has right to kill him
I get a seat at the
The table where I can try and help things from within
What makes
Perfect
What
It's a long time
It's a long day
Have we considered that perhaps Alex is eventually going to the
Progressive Revolution from the inside
That's right
I can see it
Are the are the turn has been all the other
It has been
Rationality
Put flawed
From
Hilarious
Florida Humanity
I would say probably in 2009
To outright
Completely
Irredeemable
Monstrous
Estimate
Cultural
Bigot
Violence and
Agonistic
Buck Lake
Is nothing
I guess you could have a Jonah in the whale kind of moment
But you expect that to been when
Said the Trump show prices of Dark Knight where you sitting there alone
What have I become
It's not
He's worse smell
He wrestled with
And came out the wrong
He's like I like it in the whale
Well you know what I wanted
And let me tell you something
Feels good
This particular show
I'm sure that I will feel much better
Thomas episode
So supportive of Israel
Seems foolish
Yeah but that's
Okay
This is going to be a
Not like not as well researched
But
At this point supporting Israel's government
Is maybe the most anti-Semitic
To some extent and nobody is working harder to destroy the Jewish
The government of the Jewish state
Yeah
But
Up to this point Alex is not really dealt with what the actual news
Rod coming out of Israel
It's murder
Not the whodunit
Like murder on the Orient Express
The story in
Next clip
Turns out to be a
Palestinians in 1400
Other way to take that I'll tell you this
Take that headlight without being like
Oh
The bad guy is the murderer
At least
At least you didn't say
Israel kills
Just saying
Free 5,000 protesters rally against the US Embassy opening in Jerusalem
Overseen by trumps
Middle East
Ivanka
Is it
Drones
But you see
Route
Hourly suicide bombings
The only way you know about it is because of people
Because if it was islamists doing it they would they would not say
Muslims or Islam
Fun semantic point you have no evidence at all
Like that
Think of a
Terrorist
Attacked
Attack
That has
Killed more than
50 and wounded more than 1,000
Out of it that's a
All that really means is
These terrorists just want to
No no. Kill
No I think a couple of
I could be complaining it with all the other
Everyone's confused why I'm not telling you I have neighbors
Catchphrase
I don't get really worried that like 9:30 or so
God damn it took another phone
Las Vegas
Ohio
Spell it doesn't
It doesn't matter
$50
I don't
Understand I'm just driving how you can
Any
But to be fair
Murders 50 people and wounds 2000
Does that are
Just people
They're not people
They're just there
People Are People
At the other side of it
I think it's a dumb idea you like
Complete
Complete vacuum
Dumb idea
To be mad that there's a US Embassy in Jerusalem
It's all just made up
Your religions are lies
I'd like if you want to get down to the fundamental underpinnings of all of it I agree
None of this means anything human beings are weird f*****-up creatures and there just creating reasons
I hate each other
What happened for fun
What 4000 goddamn years now like what and what else do we need on this ship I have neighbors
If you're interested.
Can you just see the encroaching
Monster
The US Embassy
Did you recently
Is just a signal that the United States is going to watch
Everybody you know
Murder
Moving that Embassy to Jerusalem is them saying
Specifically
We don't care how many.
This is Ben
The second statement on the show Jordan
Shut up
And I have no response
Let's go to next clip
I mean it's not interesting in terms of
Content
About
Muslim
Wake your f****** say you're staying
This isn't Trump's this isn't
U.s. Embassy to Jerusalem has been around since
Rake
How to divide
Who plays of kushners
Even Lakes
The point is that like many presidents
Going to do it the reason I do it is because they were like
If we do this that the United States to everybody
We will watch message resonates
Throughout much larger territory than Palestine
It does
Absolutely send
Now
Suicides horrible message Jesus
Make me feel by
Clearly you think I am no I appreciate it but I don't know how to respond to it
I could have responded to two points earlier but now I'm out
Anyway Alex
Hear Rance a little bit about Islam but
It's important to listen
Because what he says at the end
Is
Particularly glaring
And I don't think you means at the way I
I think
Everyone
What is real Flash
Christian
Killing little girls
It's almost a little girls getting raped
Hottest
Constantly
Yes
That's why I play that
You see how my brain works
Clearly
Beach
3 what is it that there was just a BBC article about
Girls
Being raped and then lit on fire in ND
Like this is a thing that everybody
Like
Viola, he talked about
Dude
Like if you want to be a conformist gender concept guy
If you if you want to just be so
Reductive
Then look at the world weigh Alex does
More common through line is
Testosterone
Alex cell
Crepe
Great great
So at this point we're done
He has real stuff for now
But we will get back to it
That are
Particularly
Goodnight Moon
Jumps off any good
Get back to another narrative
We talked about the past
Development
But what's more important about
Is that weird
The point where
It 2018
Alex is just really trying to get a tan
Really desperately
And you can hear it at the beginning of this
Clip when he's even trying to introduce the
The story is about to talk about
Really more concerned at the idea of like we need this go viral
Call Alex Jones about 10 minutes ago
I really want to have this go viral because this illustrates everything
That this was going to end up happening
We not
Los Angeles
Exposing others in California
Misdemeanor
Give blood
The Thriller
Virtue signaling
It was racism or something insured up
LA County
Are skyrocketing officials racism and stigma
And he starts laughing
I want to really bring into sharp Focus
Chris is the reason the California made it not a felony anymore
Because part of that law special
Is that him
If you
Don't know your status
And you give it to somebody
Then you can't be held accountable in a court of law cuz you didn't know your status
And people would probably be more scared to find out
Because then the test would be on record
It would prove that they did know that they had it or something like that
Instances where like even if you use protect
Condom
There are situations like that
People have done studies and they figured out that
The end result of criminalizing
Having HIV in pipe
Somebody
Is the people don't get
And so in order to try and work against
Decriminalize
It is one of those situations
Are the
A practical solution
Runs counter to your idea of
Like that's a that's a ferret of well just like
Just like with
Cocaine or whatever it is you want to do
The Practical reality of
Cocaine trafficking
Is that because it's illegal
It's far more profit
About to be a murderous cartel
The kind of situation
Solution
Is legalizing
This truck that you have been trained
Since you were
3 year old
To think is the most heinous crime
So that doesn't make that doesn't drive with people's natural scent of
Like
Of punishment should
Equal the crime
Right right
I can kind of understand
And that because if you recall when are first
Our first reactor maybe my first
Action was like
I don't know if this is a good idea
You know like it should be a crime to
Give somebody a chive
Yeah it should be
If you don't know
But it's the same
Breakfast
That seems
That seems counterintuitive to take your sense of no that you can't be held
Responsible for the crime if you don't know
That
Will only lead to this morning
Read this new LA Times article cuz these are
Completely different
Stories
No idea what this
About
In LA county half of chlamydia cases in a third of
Is diagnosed that each year among the people
15 + 24
Miles for my point
These are not people who are getting blood transfusions on a map scale so that idea of being able to donate blood is
Out the window
About how
Quote absent only works
One boy said he had known
STDs from anal sex
So that's not
Yeah but that's just
So also this article.
Is that there's a few gone to read the entire article it makes it very clear that this
Is not a specific
And unique experience for California
Quote
Nationwide STD rates
I've been climbing for the past 5 years
More people are diagnosed with syphilis chlamydia and gonorrhea 20
16 that ever before
Some blame underfunding of Esther
TD prevention programs as well as failing
Falling condom usage
There's also speculation the people are having sex with more partners because of hookup
And the reason that they bring up race
In this article as a possible
Contributor is
Statistics
Those are dangerous the picture is more complicated when it comes to the high STD rate among minorities
Gay bisexual men make up the vest
Majority of Nucynta
Pinellas County
Syphilis rates among a
African American women are
Times higher than white women
Three times higher than Latina with
Center for Health Equity director Heather northover
So that officials need to evaluate what's called
Structural or systemic racism
The way housing or education policies May negatively affect people and their
Studies have found for example the people with HIV have low levels of literacy
Outside people with HIV who had low levels of literacy were less likely to follow the treatment
And that poor Americans
Time to work
We're bored like
Did engage in Risky sexual behavior increasing
Do all of this
To go back to the club of Rome is a problematic
There are so many
Pieces that come into it when you look at one problem
Another problem
All you're doing is ensuring that none of them ever
It is completely stupid
Alex Jones
Okay
Fruition
I let myself down.
But I thought why not have some of the diasco Malek's
I think cost
So we're going to see if I could be a good boy today
Good boy today
Certainly haven't so far
I want to give
Like
Is already back talk about his return
I'm just not of the coal cost of living for Palestine
But I'm also not
For the people over there
They got tons of nuclear weapons
Anywhere
Samsung watch
So couple things really quick
Not knowing how to speak
Samsonov
Hey Alex
You know what that is
That's a plan that Israel has
If we plan that the global is running Israel have
Must be a
Destroying everybody
By the way Iran if you're listening
Israel has hundreds of nuclear weapons
So they're not going anywhere
Maybe
Do things have a lot in
Via the other the thing is that like
Legitimate
Four years was that Israel play
About whether or not they had poops because of Alexa
Schrodinger's nuke
Wrecking all that ideas like maybe
Adoption is
Taking everything down being like yep we're going to f****** attack you in this
Brett complete destruction
That's a plan of theirs it's not a plan a saurus
Implying it
No also Soros does not want to destroy as really doesn't want to blow it off the map
All the stuff that Alex is
Referring to is like there's some WikiLeaks
Square
Females
The discus
Cirrhosis views on Israel
And it's just that
The regime that
Empower is
The racist
Awful
Yeah you should be out should not be
It's not destroying Israel
It's not that he's not anti-israel
Anti
This
United States
I am not a literal Nazis running Israel
Looking dice
Keep dreaming Soros
Keep dreaming devil Pope
Bring in Israel
Because
Israel
You haven't
Also
Ochsner
I've been
Attacked
Coming after my funding
My pigtails
I can
Give you an explanation
Why your enemies of the same as Israel's enemies
But you're not going to like my answer
Not these
Philosophically
Behavior of
Israel
Either
It's almost as though we have a ideological fruit
1 witches knot
Depended upon
Definitely not
Anyway Alex gets office
Alex gets off Israel for a moment
Because he wants to chime in on the Stormy Daniels situation
I only get this in because it's
5000 horsepower
What
Right there right
We got up there and talk about family values all day long
Never do that
I'd like to direct Alex's attention to every time he denied all of these honors
Literally every time
He did that
Every sport
He talked about
Freedom Christian f****** Gathering
Childtime
He literally does this is just equivocating
Imagine if like I don't know
Cedar America
Yeah
If he was just like
Michelle Obama looks like
And f***
Yeah that's bad
Sugru
It's so gross
Say that I haven't had
View
Stop it I think it's so gross
Alex is like
Cheese looks like
She's got five
Horsepower
Is it dead
Wolf that there's so many layers to how disgusting that it is but grass
A pornstar
His wife is hotter
In my mind in my mind
There we go which apparently dropped
Does not agree with me
Does he have to keep sucking all these other people
We are now back to
God I wish we were
We're now back now
2009 Revolt 2
Call Greg
The media never covers
But they want a bunch of wires
Trying to break
Into is
But you trying to
Kubrick
Israel
Houston ulcers make
Can fun of their death
Which is real real gross
For this article from
New Yorker today
A nervous Frisian ran through the crowded
Push towards the fence
Gaza and Israel on
Sunday evening holding 75t
The Wire
I traveled the gods of
From Cairo ahead of what we expected the enormous demonstrations
The Border fence
I want the first
I want the first see the site of the protest on what I thought would be an uneventful evening
It did not turn out that
Has clusters of Gaza
Milled about
Israeli snipers watch
From the other side barely visible in their fortified purse
I watched it
A group of young Palestinian women step forward in dark cloaks
Colorful snake
Gesticulating wildly
Quote This Is Our Land not yours yelled one
Then
Suddenly
Two bullets slammed into the ground in front of
I'm picking up
Pops up.
The crowd jolted in the women's retreat
About 50
But minutes later they were moving forward again taunt
Sing the soldiers
Another shot rang out
And this time one of the women fell to the ground
Clutching her stomach
BaByliss raced along the bumpy ground
An emergency workers scoop the woman up
And raced off
Trail bike riding with
My colleague and I gave three of them a lift to the hospital
Did it not seem too.
Did not seem sure who the woman was
Only the cheapest standing alongside them
I finally learned the woman's name
Housewife earrings
When I found her mother in the hospital Corridor cheek smeared with tears clutching her daughter SilverSneakers in
In a plastic bag
Miss Liz Oswald
I was watching Yuri 26
Was born it with a with a mental disabilities that her brother
Muhammad
She learned embroidery at a school for people with disability
Letter to the protest
She wanted to show off the embroidered bags
Cell phone covers
Not know how she ended up in the front of
The crowd
She was not behaving in a violin
He said
She was not holding a stone
So what's the excuse for shooting her
So that's one of the victims
She's actually didn't die they thought you
She was dead but she's just ended up in critical condition
I don't know maybe she's dead
She wasn't
Set the oppressed
So
Really wish I didn't have
Nuremberg
Well don't forget the Nuremberg trials LOL
Jurisdiction
Come up when you when you talked about that for a child and laws
Fiction is my issue
When Alex comes on air inbox
The people who died
We're murdered
And then beyond that murdered
Paints the picture that these people who were shot were all aggressors or
Trying to climb the wall and stormed the barricades
Patata
Whatever
Alex impression
A lot of them or not
A lot of people were shot
Humans
So anyway now we get to Milo yiannopoulos
On the show
As if it couldn't get worse
Comes on
Pickle dick
Starts off his appearance
He's got a theory about sjw
We talked about how I
He got kicked out of that New York Bar
Remember those I recalled
Why is everything about bullying
I just never ends
Alright might
Bi-State Justice Warriors
I understand where you're coming from but I promise there's a reason I'm playing it
I was about that
Trust
Trust my technique
Please
Visit other people's behavior because they're unhappy with their own people's psychology because they
Have something defective about their arms make everybody else miserable because they themselves are suffering
Is that bar in New York
And I was I just went for brunch
Also
When you talk about people suffering
Have you ever
They don't want other people
Nope
By the way from the gay magazine he worked for for writing a profile
Looks looks at me now
We just went in there for brunch can you drive
Previous Mission between
38 - 14
And purple
PS2 monstrosity
Neighbors neighbors
I also this lady was fat
Sabaton
You f****** ass
Reacted at least use multiple sentences to be a f****** a******
Reacting sorry this is the reason that I'm putting this on the show
Is because
We need to really look at that
Trolling
They they think they are
What they're doing is just
Being horrible and like
Dish TV and thinking they're funny
But they're doing it
Specifically because there
Desperate
Yeah that's true
They know Alex knows on sublevel
That I have Milo on the show
And we say a bunch of f****** horrible stuff right
It's true game absolutely and the more everybody else gets mad then
More the people
Support them are like well obviously if it makes them mad
This game is so easy to see through
Lame I watch this and I like
I get it I see what you doing guys
Then you even pointed out that even a block away and all of them
So lame
But I do want to listen to a little bit of it just to drive home the point that like they're doing the stuff on purpose
Here's them talk about lesbians
Before this
They've been talking about how the bars at
But he got kicked out of or got yelled at
It's called The Churchill
And accidentally
Heavy air quotes
Accidentally
Stumbled into a meeting of the New York socialist
I bet that's not an act
I bet that wasn't
Great thanks my love
I love women
I just asked you why they all have
Smolich go out
I mean this is just like
He's hacked fan
That's really you like me to host the rest of the hours of witches
Limit a nice resort
We're all afraid of
Commercial Alex plays that video of
The girl in a Sailor Moon costume
Yeah
He claims he didn't delete from the internet but that
She posted on Twitter
Because
If you don't know what I'm talking about you can go look it up on
Dog YouTube now
Infowars reporter who I don't even know who she is
Between Zetas
Really low on the totem pole she comes up to this girl is drinking iced coffee
And on her phone
The different Millie Weaver character
No it's not Billy Weaver it's like Eddie Murphy
Coming to America Whiteface
Full transformation
Okay no I'm not going
Go over the entire video
They end up playing the entire thing
It's basically this reporter just trying to ask got your questions and the girls been like really different
Twisted
It's pretty hilarious if you if you are a
Sailor Jupiter and Sailor Saturn
That was edited out of
Cuz they are
Maybe
Funny point is
She's like you guys have a
Sasa Sushi
Hilarious
Very funny video and I Alex they play it and they're just like
She is so stupid
She can't even talk
It it's not worth it I was going to play the entire thing
Just to see they're like
Just watch their breakdown of it
At this point
Alex and
Milo
Start shooting on max
Sweetwater's
It's for a reason
There's a reason
What
Panda
It's disgraceful
Exactly
The same thing that I got Bill O'Reilly
A lot of hot water
Flying Saucer
What is up with the left cuz they really are it was a part of crazy people
What is a rising on this planet
Sushi cover for Galaxy
Call Ray
Add dog
You just showed too many cars there Alex
You just showed too many cards
I love that everyone's talking about how much
In front of her
Let's do more of it
America
Bill is Bill Gates
Walmart.com
Hahaha he's a guy who's running again
Maxine water
Gotcha
Understand
Conservative comedian
Caught
Funny so funny
To the cross
It's a bit
You know man like
Old man the turns
The sleight of hand
Things never do the obvious
I want to talk to you a little bit about Omar Navarro because Alex Jones said I'm not going to get into his background
So I'm going to do it I should tell you one thing fits they don't say it any point
And that is that Rodger stone is one of Navarro's Bank campaign advisor
And I think that's probably a federal elections
Pretty violation
By appealing to the district's growing Latino population
Opposition to Waters at centerpiece of his campaign
Alex Jones
If people really want to take a jab at Maxine Waters and everything she say against President Trump donate to my campaign
Navarro said on Infowars shortly after he announced his candidacy in late May
Also if you look at it made like
30 Grand in donations the last time you tried to do this cuz he runs
Augusta Road Vet
This time he's made 100,000
Interesting
Does General Flynn has come out in the doors Tim
There's a really funny joke
That quote that Donald the offensive firing back at the GOP
Candidate looking to unseat her following his endorsement from former Trump adviser Michael Flynn
Slim's endorsement of Omar Navarro at the
The 43rd district
And the 43rd district candidates event
Friday was the first time
He spoke publicly since pleaded guilty last year to Lions pfbi conversations with a Russian diplomat
He broke his silence to be like this guy
He's good
Whatever you think about Omar Navarro
Whatever you think about him
You can't take away that he is a
Motherfuker
Mary Jo Club
Controversial former Sheriff Joe Arpaio
I don't want to hear his name
Obituary
Who is convicted of a crime related to alleged racial racial profiling of Latinos and pardoned by Trump
125 ticket fundraiser for National Golf Club
Palos Verde
Last month
The event ended with a skit in which
Impersonator who is wearing a wig
Pretended to attack conservative musician Joy Villa
Navarro intervened and pull off the waters wig as a dozen or so attendees applauded
You can find the video of it
It's disgraceful
Also
Vista
It must have happened after
The time the joyful celebration party
It was sexually assaulted by Corey Lewandowski
I guess you was not out there
What are we
Navarro
What's this
Wherever it is Burn It Down
The Daily Breeze about Omar Navarro
Navarro of GOP activists in the South Bay make me a second bid to unseat
Trench representative Maxine Waters
Is on probation until March for criminal conviction stemming from his use
Have an electronic tracking device attached to his estranged wife
Play Breathe
Course
Of course
Navarro a 28-year old Torrance resident who welcomed former Arizona Sheriff Joe Arpaio at a fundraiser Thursday night
Misdemeanor charge in Orange County
He was
Instant September 2016 to a day in jail and 18 months probation
In order to take an anger management course
Orange County
Attorney's office
Confirm
Navarro who resigned from his volunteer post on the Torrance
Traffic commission earlier this year when faced with Central removal for his political activities
Did various Los Angeles County cities
This article was fake so I wanted to look into it
What were these various
Political activities that he was forced to step down with Valen
A post
Italy tours
Traffic Commission
What is even
That
From the LA Times quote
He resigned as a Torrance traffic commissioner
Pepper spraying a child
What
Aries political
Tri-Cities event in
And subsidiary
Videos of the incident show Navarro in the backseat of a car while driver in another pass
Spray rally
So people expressing their right
To congregate
Free Speech pepper-sprayed them out of
Car
So that's why he had to resign from his post
In the torrent
I Baba blah
Traffic committee
I don't think this guy's a good
Congress vice-president of the Rogue
Beach cities Republican Club until July
Alright
Pretty well.
Is just an adjective
Party Road Beach City Republicans
The County's GOP leadership revoke the charter
Publican
The County's GOP leadership revoke the charter of the club earlier this year for attacking members of its executive committee
Violating its bylaws
I tried to look into that and
All the articles I could find who like this is an internal matter they wouldn't talk about what they actually did
I've got a really
Just hitting the Rogue Beast
Sound like a biker Club
Convicted
Putting a tracer on his wife's car
Help
Navarro reached for comment Wednesday morning was about his criminal conviction
He initially said they're quote a lot of Omar Navarro's implying the hold on
Strong
Strongfirst Vale
First stop
There are a lot of Hobart
So you can't prove it
Are there alot of Omar Navarro
Implying the perhaps
They was convicted of the charge
Then he said the incident that led to the criminal charge occurred years ago rather than life
Last year
Totally different
Finally a lot of universes where Omar Navarro
Finally he acknowledged the misdemeanor
Conviction but at first blamed the Orange County District Attorney's Office in the media for quotes fake news
Admitting it was his own doing
Highlights
I wish it was just one interview of them being like
Come on man
I think it would be
Alright I did it
I'm bad
So one of his initial quotes was the district attorney refused to dismiss the case it was filed under false pretenses
The Daily Breeze is biased news
Then a little bit later
The afternoon
I got what I deserved everybody makes mistakes
At least you can own up to
Trapped in a quarter
Child
This guy is a
You seems to be deeply entrenched
Sheriff music
And then also
It really is
Important the Rodger stone is one of his
Manager campaign advisors
Okay I do think it's
Against
Aren't there laws against Rodger Stone being involved in politics at all anymore
Do we just write a no more Rogers don't be good
He's allowed to give advice and be an advisor but I really think it is a strong concert
Interest when he's essentially part-owner of Infowars
He uses that as a platform
The fundraiser
For his candidate
Think of that would probably qualify as contribution
In kind
Now
Thought
Perhaps we should
Okay
You and I
Send a petition who's our who's our local representative
Some random ass
Send a bill to them like those those
Sinus you don't like American Heritage Foundation and all those boxes
Okay
That just says
No more Rodger
With a list of Rodger Stone Behavior
And if you get
3 or more
No more you
You're out you know
Just adjusted General no more Rodger Stone
I love that you're saying this cuz you're going to fall in love with Rodger Stone all over
Here's the first clip of the Rodger Stone Saga
And I
Alex Jones
Scott McCall from
He's very talented
I want to have the phone tomorrow
So Rodger Stones freaking out
You got big news for Alex
Now how to say this
Play music
But you just heard about our know Rodger Stones belt
He's not he's not a
Is it a precog
Dude dude
Do way Rodger Stone starts out this clip
Is like
This guy gif
Undisclosed location in the back room of a cigar store somewhere in South Florida
Today's date
Cerveza
I'm freaking out the door
Morton Florida
Drinking Scotch smoking a Cuban
Weirdo
South Florida
Alright that's almost like a boomerang
Lacrosse
You know I have always praised Facebook for their sophistication in the Commandments
Target
Effectively
Crusading toe Trump state senator
Who is Michael Douglas
Call Georgia
And his campaign
When they do their pay promotion on Facebook
Supporters of Infowars or Alex Jones
Subscribers can no longer be accessed
I immediately shut down my own paid
Supporters
For Alex
I have the screen grab
On all of them
So funny story
I also have a page
Acknowledged
Can you access Alex Jones followers
I did everything but give them actual money until the are you sure
Post
Anything come up its
And I'm not saying that Rodger Stone isn't getting that message
Yeah it's I mean like I don't know
I don't I don't
Is it true
Calling in for me
The humidor
Hi hats
That's such a great way to open it and
I'm calling from an undisclosed undisclosed location
In the back of a cigar store
Subway
So Milo's appearance on the show and I saved you from a lot of
They keep saying they're going to do an act
Because they're trying
A parody of
B language
Liberals liberals
Lever action but they don't mention what it is
And then after the show
Alex Winter
On periscope
Him
And Milo yiannopoulos
No
Now Google
Okay
I guess I'm fine with
Why
F*** Google
Embarrassing pile of s***
Vent for a second
I'm here
Google is no longer at like a as bad as Facebook is Google is even
Is it least as bad as
As
Implicit in all of this b******* they were
Pissed off at face
The fuk Google
I hope Infowars shows up at Google's offices every f******
I hope Alex Jones just opened up a f****** office across the
The street and just walked in and knocks on there I'm sure
Pristine glass doors
And there's the building.
Did though is
You lucky I we're not going to
Super Big Sam's
Google
A storefront
It's just like you they went to the Apple Store
Google office
Like Google Fiber office in Austin and I mean that's it weird
Local Comcast
We're going to get them to give us a router
So I can't I have some clips
From their very embarrassing trackdown
Google enjoy
Not
Hilarious
Milos
Showmanship
Google
Does he does go to
The Google Fiber store Front
And
Aboard employees time
Galaxy
You can hear the stomach
That's really what's more about my love
The bell I get paid $11 an hour
$11 an hour
50 years old
You guys are drunk
Alex is
F*** it like for me to judge
He has red face
He is like
Who watched him out and about is just like
Like I don't know if it's cuz he's out in
Amazon or something like that
Like
Manatee
You could call the white Apes could call the cops on white
People the same way you do on black people they would be
They would have been murdered by
Ears it's really fun
Before he does
This is
True comedy
He's a famous band
The audio shifted their head to Adonai
But it starts with
Who's your friend who's your friend
Leave me alone
Who's this
About
Ideas Google Fiber store
They said
Walls
He gets distracted from his whole talk about his lies about Elon Musk
Plants is just like some Ivy growing on it
Like a fuking idiot
Google
About YouTube
Google Fiber about YouTube to grind and is he
You can go harass mother
Like they have to have the aliens
You got to have a second
Who's the dude
What's happening is go harass some low-level employees at the storefront
Going to get them for publicity
Because they're obviously going to get thrown out and they're going to be able to make a big deal out of
Restart this but it's so poorly executed
It's there's absolutely nothing here
Generally speaking when you're trying to get kicked out of a place
Saying I like
Friend
Is a bobber
That whole thing is a bummer
I promise
It's pretty funny
Alex
Suggest what Google is really up to
Nefarious plans
By the way
He's talking to a low-level employee at a store
$11 an hour to work
Is colored
Nanotech
Alright
We're at our local Comcast office
Is secretly trying to create destroying lasers or something
Do you want a bundle
And we're like
Looking today
Have you seen Stars
Embarrassing
A real cool oh s*** the cops are here let's leave
Cops coming through the glass
Let's Be Cops
Heartfelt
Badger shows up
The manager of Eric front
She has no time for Alex's bulshit
Customer service
The correct about it.
Beautiful
Yeah f*** off
So here is the the last two clips that we have
It is Alex Jones in the
Shop
He talks to the
He says to the cops twice
He's patronizing
Panders to
In 2009
That's the only interaction
Somebody has a cop
What's the female cop did say how are you doing mister
George Jones
And the reason I said that nine times in the back
But the reason she said that is
Because everyone f****** knows who our
She lives in Austin
Yes kicked out of Google frequently you've done this before
He's done the same set up Google Fiber but there was a Google open house in thrown out of
The only interaction that he has with a cop
Here's the chaser
After they've left in her walking down the street now it's Jones looks like a goddamn Lobster he's so red in the face
This is what he said to Rob.
Exactly who you are
Hahaha
The cops were all listeners
You just making that up out of whole cloth
So every time
Listeners response to you Alex
Hey Alex
Hey mr. Jones
You got to go we are doing this again
Hey
Oru harassing low-level employees
Never seen that before
So
George Jones
This isn't a Wendy's at 3 a.m. sir please leave this calls into question
I mean not that there was a question
Not at all
Really should
Paint every time he says
Some people said their listeners
Every time he's like I go out in public and everyone loves me
You went up there and you were like a guy who works at Google Fiber I'm harassing
But I think that's probably how you treat people and then
Indicates a slight awareness of who you are like
Yeah I got her listeners
This is pathetic and all of it is
This publicity stunt mentality
You having Milo on
The troll by saying that Maxine Waters is a dog
And I also
He's doing all this like lesbians are f****** stupid and have dumb haircuts
All of it just to rile people up so they'll give him Free Press
Because he's in a fuk
Nothing bad play
We recognized
Is it a bad place
Come to it
The better
We can do
At this point although it is fun to learn about Omar Navarro
Certainly
For me but like
Hey
Grotesque
There are a lot of
Only one other Jordan Bonet is in this planet
Like for us
Come on this show
And save that I'll expect
Disgusting things
About the state of Israel murdering Palestinian protesters
Not
I would say almost all of them on arm
That doesn't help
Obviously that's
Everyone knows
That's not helping
And then beyond that all this other s*** is
Trolling all this other s*** is Judge
It's stupid
Okay you're welcome Italy Ollie's
The entire time
Is
Blaming
The victim
You put that you punch down in protection got punched
I have one more thing I wanted to read about the the protest in Israel really quick
Dino that a list of all the crimes all over Navarro's across the country have committed
No
This Omar Navarro
Also did I read another article in the New York Times by I feel really bad about this but I forgot the
The guy is
Name byline
Someone who helped to organize the protest
The big March is happening
I think right now we're recording
The 15th
Preamble to the big
March 9th
I read this article you wrote about what it meant to him and why he was organizing these protests
I think it's really important
Thought disorder thing
Feed
Mention
Discuss
A couple years ago people here would have dismissed the idea the peaceful demonstrations could have tea of anything
After all every other form of resistance
Is producing nothing
Concrete
What amazes me is the transformation
We're seeing in the way we resist
Our struggle previously with
Green arm Palestinian Fighters
An Israeli sniper tanks
Now it's a struggle between
The occupation and
Protesters
Men women
Young and old
Still
Despite the response from Israeli snipers
I continue to be committed to nonviolence
As are all the other people quote coordinating this March
I use quotation marks because when a movement becomes this large
Estimate to be as many as 200,000 people on Friday
We cannot be completely controlled
We can discourage the burning of Israeli Flags
And the attachment of Molotov cocktails
The kite we walk peaceful equal coexistence
BR message
We've also tried to
Discourage protesters from attempting to cross into Israel
However
We can't stop them
It's the action of
Imprison people yearning
For freedom
Sue
That's the voice of output that's the voice of literally one of the main people coordinating
Bob these marches
Well-put
Alex
Go fuc yourself
You're a piece of s***
I go seriously
Read
Read any
Look in your heart
You Grinch
The racial Grinch
Anyway
Libertarian
Was actually correct an acting within his capital
Absolutely
So if you like to show what more you can check us out at knowledge buy.com
Arachnology iTune
Just go there
Will eventually lead you to
Ask enough random questions will eventually be like
Jesus do you want to go to knowledge
And then six years later will create a city destroying the microorganism
But conservative businesses
I want to know
This is everything
You know what I like my daddy
Call Birdman
So I am stopping Like My Daddy
Anyway
Solid as a good anyway
I like the yeti way there I want to enlist people if you have a fever if you want
He does make a big difference
Leave a review on iTunes
A rating and review
I would go a long way
Your turn buddy
It is and I know exactly
Play who I
You know what
Okay.
Alright
I'm interested
Part of me wants to save state of Israel to go f*** himself
And everybody knows it
I think that leaves me with one option
And that is the many
The many of them Omar Navarro
Good tomorrow
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work