Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Beverages and talk a little bit
What up what up
I don't I don't even know what you would call is there a Blues Traveler
Spell other people
Know what number we're at no clue
Like twice
No
The Shack song no hooks featuring The
The Riza
Start my disagree
Rated
Very competent as a rapper
I think the people need to remember that there is a joke
No it wasn't all right
Platinum has a song with biggie
Dazn on a track with Method Man and the Rizzo
Wichita
I've known him for a long time I have to live with this
Alex Jones put out on 2018
I don't know it sucks to be in the present
Cancel this and then wait for you to do another 30 hours of research we can just
Play the entire 40 minutes
Debate that I found between Lee and McAdoo
And Owen Shroyer know
Other side of the debate
Eddie Bravo
All right well now I'm debating Flat Earth
It's not about the shooting it's very weird
The Earth is flat
Very f*****-up
As I got the light
Santa Fe Texas shooting
Second Amendment people would allow me to give thoughts and prayers to Ted Cruz's
You know what those look
That's horrible
I'm fine with it
Define
Sacrificed a separate myself from that sentiment
You say that if you live in other than what the president said I understand
But that doesn't mean that it's okay for us
Just because it's open
Portable heated but anyway
Did Elisabeth
I watched the press conference that they advertised
The other day
Fire went out to the memorial of the shooting
The night of they were having a vigil
Type thing and like Ted Cruz showed up and
Governor Abbott Texas governor showed up
And I'm just thinking wouldn't it be better if you
I would think that the best thing that could happen to me is for me to just
Go away
2 oz
Preferable
Horrible
Should I watch that
Actually all that terrible
Like
Antagonizing people really
There were a number of
Some of the interviews he did were really messed up but it was just at the people he was talking
You're stupid
He ran into a couple people who were like you know this is all about
You weren't being
Disrespectful to the proceedings
And so like I'm not saying
I tip my cap to your reporting or anything like that it's not really all that interesting
I think it's really negative in the sense that it's
Kind of normalizing
Because if they did go out to this thing and everyone was fine with them being there
For the most part
And they just behaved like a normal news organization
It kind of gives them cover in some ways to be like this reporting at that scares me a little bit
I think what we should have learned
From the Grinch
Not to gather hands
But to grab pitchforks and torches and murder the Grinch
The real lesson
Broccoli
But look so we're covering that and out really pretty
Particularly care cuz every time we have one of these shootings
You know dude story is
Misogyny
The story is angry white men
Feel like they're entitled stories come out about one of the victims of the shooting
Rejected his advances
Domestic
Another story came out just the other day about the Sutherland Springs shooting with a guy went to the church kill 20-something people and
The story that just came out about how she'd waterboarded his wife in the past
And over and over again in any conversation that does not taking that into account
Is really conversation worth having
Okay let's table gun control
Alright
And instead let's just put every single f****** white man in jail
I will stay there in jail
Because I'm f****** done
Look
Mass shooting
Names of the last couple years and I did a article on
Or website you can find
That's register almost everything
The conclusion that I came to and I believe this
This is like
You going to have to
Choose one problem to solve
It's either got to be the guns or the dudes
I don't think Alex wants to talk about either of them than most people
Who are in positions of power don't really want to talk about either
What you're talking about
Like the idea of adding more doors to a school or taking away drawers
That's what I'm saying all this stuff is like
Each each successive
Shooting that happened
Be like the answer gif
Weaker
Like you know last time it was we need to arm teachers
Free week what are you what are you talkin to hold on
Pretty
And people did not enjoy that idea
So time goes on we have another school shooting and they know they can't just toss that back into the ring
This time it's
Let's doors
Even weaker than arming teachers
That's stupid
You know that's going to cause a bottleneck of people trying to get out of the school
Lendup
Do you understand what your next time it's going to be
Even weaker f****** argument in order to not talk about the gun issue or the male entitlement issue one of it
There is no
It doesn't matter how weak there are
Is because the argument that they're always make
We will watch your children die
That's the argument
We don't f****** care
I want
Look at the statistics and everybody's put out has more children have died in full
Shootings Bend service
This year
That is absolutely accurate because what it really is is
In the war against the rest of us
We haven't been part of that war we've just been the f****** Victor
These people need to go
.
I can't say
I want
To give people my thoughts and prayers Dan
The thing
Instead I'm thinking
Because there's no other way we have to if this is a civil war Scituate
Civil War
Behind the scenes Civil War get election behind the curtain of Illusion
Unfortunately but we can't lump ourselves into that group
We're not in school
You never anything like that we are just
We rise external to it as
You're not a lot of people it's just
We respect
The Voice
People who are part of it
Anyway I know about that now 10 minutes later
How do you f******
How do you avoid having the only accurate
Murder.
Movies
In a post-apocalyptic nuclear Wasteland in America people have more hope than that f****** girl
Great
Progressive
Comforting for everybody to hear maybe can't change our can't change our listeners opinion of Alex
Going to be talking about around the internet
We're out at the they went to the Google Fiber store
Afterwards
Accidentally
Showed up because he was watching the livestream it was like I can go find them
As always shows up and tries to get Alex to like
Help him launch
Infowars music.com
Spider-Man on 6th Street
As soon as he recognizes it is one of his listeners who's crazy
He immediately slams his drink
Hey brother I got to go
He just tries to get away from him as quick as possible it's really funny but there's no way for us to really cover that
Yeah well he's
He's aware of danger
Alex's own ideas to start
The listener he did not recognize this
Scooby-Doo or whatever the f****** guy's name was his name
Goddamnit Sylvester
Daffy Duck it was Daffy Duck
That was it
Tails nicely into this article out of the Guardian
That also came out
The reason we're not going to cover that is good at the video and it's really not fun just as audio and it's too difficult for us to play
Play a video that you have to watch
We all have a text documentary
The guardian
How to find the
The date on
This is from Saturday shooter was conspiracy theory
First what do we
Reno
So turns out that bunch of documents got released
About
About Stephen Paddock the guy who shot up the concert country concert in LA
Las Vegas
And that they're bunch of people who had run into him
And bunch of people I gave statements
There was this one
Lady days before the shooting at with her son
She said she heard him and continue discussing the 25th anniversary of Ruby Ridge
And the Waco Siege
She said she heard him and His companion saying the courtroom Flags they got a courtroom with me
The beliefs of gold frame
Jurisdiction or admiralty Flags
Is characteristic of the so-called Sovereign citizen
Believer
The current u.s. government and its laws are illegitimate
A bunch of other stuff they found about him being afraid of FEMA camps
And stuff like that and what it really goes to show I think
Is important is that
This guy who
Bum-rushed Alex
At that far away from him
I hate people who believe the same stuff I believe but aren't millionaires are crazy
I have to get away from that information coming out
About Patek
And we see
Oh he believes a lot of the same stuff Alex does
Which is why he has to spend the narratives about him being a lefty
Big antifa being God
So if you're going to if you're going to get caught in the conspiracy web you try and put it towards the guy who's there
In the
The left
Right right
Audio segments
I talked about not this episode for the first 13 14 minutes of the episode
This is Special Report on Saturday cuz
What happened
Amboy
Alex is really worried
And he should be
No I did see this one
Gorgeous
Oh yeah so years that out of context drops
From today's episode
Special Report
May
Is this
It is pretty crazy Rogers.
It's not crazy
As much as
We have been saying this for a long time that Rodger Stone was going to go down.
This is news
Sounds good as Alex
A reasonably good chance
What's
Come at me
Stone Stones age
Have been called Africa
Social media
I have been brought in to Mueller in the investigation
That's what Alex has really freaked out about because
Fit this is the right
Thread to pull if you're investigating us
Does the Social Media stuff
Is really where you know you get
You get to figure out exactly where was intention
You know like what was an accident in terms of box elevator your traffic and what was intentional
Is really important to nail down if you're trying
The track the actual
Story
Colleges on Russia's payroll
Before we go
I was looking into Rodger Stone a little bit just for fun I read an article
About him from The New Yorker
Also that must have been the shortest FBI
Could you say on tape that you are a Rodger
Mediaite
No you have to say
Oh yeah he did it
Whatever it is you're going to ask
So I read this article about Rodger Stone from The New Yorker in 2000
Vaguely Swingers Bars brings his own bottles of vodka
Good time but he hears a couple passages that I found particularly interest
Over the years relationship with colleagues and clients have been so combustible as a messenger has been copper
Stone work for Donald Trump as an occasional lobbyist in advisor when Trump considered running for president in 2000
Quote Rodger is a stone-cold loser Trump told me credit for things he never did
That's good
Call Ed Rollins who served as President Reagan first political director said quote Rodger was a fringe player around town
It was a reputation of being a guy who exaggerated things
Rodger was never on Nixon staff was never on the White House staff
I don't think you'll find anyone in the business who trust him Rodger always has been a little rat
So that's that's why I believe he's in the center of things more
It doesn't matter
Nixon Administration to tell me the truth about anybody about Rodger Stone from Buffalo
He got involved
What people thought about it before all this
I just like the idea that somebody in the Nixon Administration is like
That guy is not credible
Thanks Google
Emergency Special Report on
Saturday cuz he's got a call from Rodger saying
Start
Try to promote Americana
25 years ago
That album by
America
Give me the capital of
Get rid of
The First Amendment
I thought well I'll get
25 years later
I look back and
The effect we've had it America
The world
Chet Baker
Nationalism
So shouldn't be
Capitalism
Americana
Your name is probably in an utterly disappointed
I am one of the most prominent people in the world
Doing this
And women
Who are super smart
Very Charming
Very hard-working
Chosen
To go along with the establishment because
So the things I'm going to say to hear the breaking news you're going to see
Saturday
19th of May
2000 +
Vital
My sister's getting married
That's a breaking news
Because this is so important
Farley's
Weather alerts
He doesn't break that up Alex
You're going to miss that weather
Just left the report
You weren't invited that wedding where you at the end of it spoiler alert shows up just wandering around the studios like
Miles for a little while
Your Africa
Korean adopted sister's wedding
I got the Special Report is over an hour long so if she's getting married in an hour
She's getting married at Infowars Studios
Possibly like two drinks
South
You know that's just a nice standard Preamble for Alex
You've got you know globalist on the mind
What have you been
Busy so you know it's important that he's doing this
Are you mad
But he also has received
Now I got a message for Robert Mueller
I got a message for Hillary Clinton
Got a message for call me in 40 C
Allyu Spa
I got a message
Crowley ice
Egos running outfit
Long pauses in the bathtub
I thought I was going to talk a big news on the breakdown
You're not
The mainstream media was going to push this to me about it
Who happened to be on infowars.com
Newswars.com or on our Twitter on our Facebook
Are you
On the pages
Notifications go out to
Anybody they don't
Very small percentage
That's not true I don't even subscribed channels and I randomly will get updates that their chant
I get push notifications on my phone
You got to disable your cookies
We are
Ahead of the biggest
And Sawmill layouts
Some exhibit
Think I'll just make these claims
Sorbonne
Eve
Preserved in Amber would you like some more exempt
Yeah you got that Mr X to the Z
What is rideout's Outback
Exhibit
One of the great one of the great rappers that never got the respect they deserve
Feel like you're wrong I don't even I don't even listen I haven't listened to exhibit in 20 years and I'm still like
Great song you did with Talib Kweli
Talk with my sound
Yeah you're right he's not one of the greats but he was better he was better than to be remembered as the guy who
Who was on Pimp My Ride
Well you need any money man that job
Are we there yet
So you can write talk tweet
Mikey
What about Friday
Maybe next Friday or Friday After Next going with the ghetto Grinch
Start with the
If you're 14 and you're watching Friday After Next
No leave it no movie series is transformed themselves
More than the Friday.
Serious with some Goofy's out of comedic relief
Very much absurd comedy
I think Friday is an amazing movie
A long time but you also
Hulk Hogan
I did not know that became a wrestler the WCW
Tony Tiny Lister
Alex's got receipt
You've got exhibits
That's how we got caught off
True true
It's an interesting thing I think Alex is actually really worried cuz it keeps saying he's not worried
And he's very restrained
Like if you're not going to see much freaked out from Alex you just going to
Which you're going to see it attempted really liar
Okay
If it's you trying to be very serious and actually he's acting like he's bringing forth real information
No it's not
Baby as far as him drunkenly screaming feel your hand
Or something like that but
There's a lot
You can dig into I think you're going to try to find some
Real bulshit
Restart
First off
Here's a McClatchy
Last year
Pull it up
By then
FBI Dash lead investigator
That's from
12 months ago
Who played the club from Patty
Shaka Shaka
There's one at Reuters last night
Warriors last night
Special counsel subpoenas another stone age in Russia probe
Sexy six
Grab 50
About the street
This week
What was Mueller asked
Of the five we talked
One won't talk
Good call
Smart very smart
Ambassador cigar shop
Cuz it's all coming to a head old russiagate
But why
Wait till you hear her
Play me the Russian Mastermind
There's more
Wamego at Soros Alex
That's the strawman
Even the most
Paranoid person is still like
Two-bit player come on man spent hundreds of hours going over his rizin 20
15 into the Trump campaign
Like we never thought
Smart know we always thought
The obvious thing is he's being f***** with by people over and over again it Rodger stone is
F*** with him
Like 2nd degree
Delightful
He also is running a scam operation that
Is easily manipulated
Pendragon type situation with Rodger Stone in jail
The better part of three decades
If there is a secret space program
But that would make more sense than most
This is big news
Big news coming out of the Trump
World
Yes right now that isn't there was a mole
And his operation
Other exhibits
We broke this last Sunday Rodger
Now that your times broken
FBI Spy Optics posed Trump campaign
CIA
Cambridge Professor Stefan
Helper
Is a zerohedge hadlyme you claiming that it's like mainstream news and
New York Times
The other headlines are about it that I found our
Trump says
Don't
Doesn't the FBI and the CIA have planted most white nationalist organizations yeah
Hey baby that's just a reasonable thing to do
I'll tell you what
If you want to like say that our government had infiltrated Trump's campaign
That opens the door wide open for
Who else was in there infiltrating about that out
Have another exam
Sure
Cuz I'm like I'm not going to just sit around
Tell you what
Show you what
Okay
Another headline here real quick
Bruce Edward Ivan
Comey & Mueller hope you forget
And Sean P O'Neill
We're going to get into this until a little bit later I know is that his name is probably don't ring a bell necessarily
I will get into it as Alex gets into it surgically decipher right
And then Michael R Caputo
Robert Mueller is an amoral legal
Will do his job
That's a headline from the Lyndon larouche political action committee not going to take that one all that seriously
The the Lyndon larouche political action committee
I don't
We don't have time we'll get it to another day
Piece of s***
That's just some of the research
Call
Hit midnight last night
Three headlines with some of the research he did
Rodger Stone
Give you directions to go off in
So whatever is being
Just being filtered through Rodger to Alec
So it's already third-hand information even if any of it is real
But then the research that he did
McClatchy article which will get back into the past
Does Alex gets into it
An article from zerohedge
Political action committee
This is not good research this is this is Shawty
They're not either
Headlines that sound
Like maybe they built to something
Straw
How do I
Most of the Special Report
Is really Alex Black
He's really just trying to be like
Punk he should talk to me a little bit
So I'm going to lay this out right now
For the average solace
Corporate climber
Having Robert Mueller breathing down your neck
Would be a really scary
Can you find out how you
You'll bend over
Chatting with you
Chords
Chords the timer
Because it's emission I chose
You're going to do the spikes
Self-preservation
Fight people
America is about men
I smell anachronism
Was about men
Fighting
Strongman
Congrats
I know it's
Do you know what
Cuz my soul
My spirit my gut feels aligned
The only master
God your God. Dockside.
Fake hypocrite herb ivory
No you are
I just I got my own
Personal relationship
My rock
Republic Service
Sounds unhealthy
That's an unhealthy relationship
Relationship
And we need to get him away from you
Yeah like Jesus has someone that Alex
We talkin about it being a relationship
Like I I don't want to put too fine a point on this but like
If Alex has a personal other people
Spirituality or anything
Define then I'll do a little bit of it if Alex has a personal relationship with his conception of God
And God is fine with him getting drunk and screaming at women on the street
For example
All the time
He's fine with any of the other thing
Documented over the last
Year-and-a-half
That God does
That is not that is not a god
In the vein of any
Except for baby just hard Old Testament but even then the Commandments are very specific
Hard
They are breaking them if I recall correctly
It's f****** guy I was allowed me
To be a white match
He allowed me to drink on air
He
Pushed
Frankly
Pushed me
To be mean and cruel to people
Talking about is Jesus Christ
I'm not afraid of Mueller but he is afraid of God
Right is another person is not afraid of
My message
Mueller
John McCain
I don't like that Alex is like he calls them walking brain tumors cuz like
Look whatever whatever
You say about John McCain and not liking him yet
Point taken
I agree with
I think it's a really f******
Fuckedupshit anything to make fun of him having a brain tumor
I'm sure you are I'm not I don't I don't like that and we are duty calls
Hillary
And I are walking
It's a cheap
The chi
F****** ugly attack
Yeah
Okay
Recite
Book them
I don't give a s***
I don't look
The real power
Let me
Try to walk
Through this
Another. That's what Star Wars.
New Age Star Wars
Sorry I don't want to I don't want to discuss
Any more of your
Like I'm not your ideas but like I don't want to talk about it's okay to make fun of someone having a brain tumor
Doesn't make that fine for me
Your position is your position mine is mine good enough
A person to share it
But
I'm not
Philosophy philosophy is
Million so go f*** yourself I hope
I hope
I hope John McCain's brain tumor gets a brain tumor that kills his brain tumor as the brain tumor kill
I don't give a fuk
I honestly I don't
I agree I agree with you in terms of like
There are a lot of really awful people
Often masquerading as Beason
Some people
And it's okay
Do not really care
When bad things happen to them
I also don't like engaging in schadenfreude
To a certain extent
Like I'm enjoying it in an ironic way I'm not enjoying
Bad person tripping
False I am enjoying the universe providing some small semblance of cosmic
He should die
In the most
Painful possible f****** way that he can
You just described schadenfreude
Anyway, another person just because it
Just because you view it as some sort of cosmic Justice doesn't take away that that's what
Ice cream
Finally gets to that McClatchy article in a
Little bit of us to discuss what he's talkin
Let me go to
The first
Document
That I
McClatchy
About 10
This is the speed at which she read the book
Bed bath
It says house
Intelligence
Services
Nmd
Committees involved with elections
The big entertainment
And I said
We want
Breitbart
Executive
Where
I would have
Board of Governor members of the FCC
AutoZone
Infowars is a Russian intelligence
Snow they said
And we want to shut down
Peace
Mueller
If you in the McClatchy article
In the first place
You weren't about
Cambridge analytica
They want
Breitbart
They won
Rodger Stone investigated
And they want to know
About 4
9 months
You didn't hear about Alex
You didn't
First couple months of 2018
So I want to reach you a couple of choice clips
From this McClatchy article that Alex is talking about
He saying is
Declaring him a Russian agent and all this s***
Operatives to Russia appear to strategically with links to
Pro Trump stories
At times when the billionaire businessman was on the defensive and is racing
Democrat Hillary
These sources
Investigators examining the body attacks or exploring whether the far-right news operations took any actions to assist Russia
Their participation however wasn't necessary for the box to amplify their news through Twitter and Facebook
They're even in the article making clear that this doesn't mean at all that they were involved
Question that's being that needs to be answered
They're not saying
They did that
Also
The article goes on to say
The investigation of the bot engineer traffic which appears to be in its early stages is being driven by the FBI's counterintelligence
Division inquiries rarely result in criminal charges and whose main task is to reconstruct the nature of the
The Kremlin Cyber attack
And determine ways to
Prevent another
It's not even like
Well it's it's a very simple question that you need to ask in order to
Get the negative you need
If
Targeting V story
Specifically
In response to specific time
Well
Are they working together
What are the bus
Doing it on their own and Tibet the timeline is if this difficult like it if it does come
Like a stereotypical
Lawyer buddy comes to
Like it does come down to that and that is not immediately apparent that's one of the things that we have difficulty with
Like in terms of
Nailing down specific
He really is he meaning to do this is very like when we when we uncovered in the end of 2015
Alex talking about how he's traffic headed doubled
His sales Wright-Patterson
Risen at all
Is there a cognizant there of why that happened but it's all automated
Or is he
Completely in the dark
And just confused about all fit
We can't know for sure
So we can save
This is what Alex is describing
Right and we know
Pretty clearly
That Insight is being artificially inflated at that time frame don't know
And if you were investigating and you just assumed that there is no connection between
You're not doing your job that's not an investigation now even if the answer even if the answer is no
Likely no possibly no
If you don't ask that question and just assume
Because I have to go back to be like
We should look at that
Think about all the questions that seem so obvious in retrospect that just were
Assumed
8 +
Like it seems like the simplest question to be like hey were you working with the Russian
End
The answer is no but
If you look at the Russia if you look at Mueller's investigation it's like
Are you guys working the birds with the Russians
What do you mean
More than three questions if you're a better liar
Yeah for sure
I'm so that's that's what article is really a bad like
It's just about like the questions that are coming up
In terms of
The social media site
Because that's where a lot of it
Took place you know like
Hey there's even a quote on this McClatchy article at the end here that is really
Towing
In terms of where that the mindset
The folks work
Here's a quote
Someone official made in February twenty
It is speech in Moscow Andre
Fruit
Kreutz Creek told a conference of Russian computer security officials that the Putin government would be unleashing a cyber
A nuclear attack reminiscent of Russia's 1949 development of the atom bomb
Trolled whose speech was first reported by Washington Post columnist David Ignatius
And independently confirmed by McClatchy also reportedly said that
The gain respect for Russia cyber
So the idea that like
This information space
And social media being such a
A wide-open area
That's a very obvious place where investigations would be happy
Listen to like just because he's mentioned
In the article
They don't say like
He's doing this or he's a Russian age
Did they bring him up in terms of like
He posted Lotto
Add Breitbart Infowars are like the two main
Places where
Like stupidly Pro Trump s*** with
Especially in terms of
Very visible voices
I very clearly
And weird
2 with
With no
Pushback not with no flashback
It would be it would be way less suspicious it's at that time they had even one article that was
You know like any one of those people be like well maybe there was a
Maybe there is a difference between the two but if it that right before
Before he switched with 90
Eighty-seven percent you're like
That's suspicious and it's obviously
Brightright 100%
That's suspicious cuz you're not a human being if you're a hundred percent protein
Throw anything
Also Imagine like another election in another country where you have a very prominent
Conspiracy theorist propagandist
Clearly gun-for-hire
Who is like I don't trust this guy he's mobbed-up all this Papa dupa do
I made it
One of that guys close Associates becomes
A major player at his news organizations propaganda outfit
Ryan seemingly all of a suddenly starts
Shifting everything to this guy is the only person who can save us
You not look like if you take it outside of the American context
And put it as just an abstract thing you like I see what's going on personalized it a little
Bit and take it away from the context that we know it in
The picture becomes very
Suspicious
At 1 and 111
Power system analysis
Lenny said something really f***** up about Rodger Stone
Okay
They think you're stupid
Let me know that I think you don't wash long videos he walks like 2 minutes ago the Mavericks
Do you think that and we also do
Because
That elevation for
They want to have the fake investigation go forward just have me arrested her
Shut Up and Dance like that trailer
You know he's going to jail
Program as well
I'm aware of what they're doing I mean
I've got the
Bird's eye view
Nope
Please
This is an article
From almost a year
40 months
Where you got the Democratic Party
We want Alex Jones shutdown
And there is an FBI investigation
Espionage
What's happening now
Lot of people getting indicted
In the last 4 days
Styx
People associate with Rodger
Plays up
Cooperative OSHA
He was involved in Watergate
What do you mean I've never seen you do anything
He works with you
Nonsense
Crazy music
Wow that's amazing
Everything everything
Everything
Bright
This is the new strategy no problem
A mugshot of an appointment with Ferdinand Marcos
Consultancy firm with Lee Atwater and Palmetto
Official said and said he was just a rat who's always on the edges
Politically correct
That to me is a tell pathetic self
Other times we talked about Rodger he's been like he'd been involved in the deepest levels of
Reddit when you introduced him on Infowars
This guy
Is involved
Cesar ratfucker
Yeah I mean
That's hilarious
So good
Do you mean he pushes on us
And so
Grab Michael R Caputo orbitron
They grabbed a bunch of other
People
For 8 hours 6 hours
3 hours
They just keep going back to Alex Jones so Alex
What like
Alex Jones
Kumon
Rodger Stone
Commentator
Just lucky
Houses
Keep saying racist s*** on the aircraft that
About like
Probably like you use in charge of everything in for there's not another guy they running things by
There is no robbed who's actually there the power player by the Puppet Master
I'm sure that that's more of the questions are asked
I would say any investigation repair Alexa
Do you know if they talk to the Russian
The podcast run out of my bedroom between two dudes
Who are busy in other aspects of their life
If I were
Why ask people questions
Just listen to Alex's show he tells you all the answers if I were working for law enforcement
What I would do is I would make Alex
I do an interview on her own
Never spoken to Russian intelligence
And then you would say no
I mean I would bring up that clip
And be like would you like to discuss what you were talking about there
Either have him admit
That you made up the entire story or federal investigators
81 you do the other nobigdyl
For himself
Did you talk to Russian intelligence
Where you have spoken to
You have had Alexander Dugan on yourself multiple times
Right after the election you were on his show and he told you that you were
Greatest example of an American that he's ever seeing it anti-americanism is over in Russia because of you
And here's how you would get Alex to tell the truth you be like
And we agree and I was like okay sweet
Let me tell you all this s*** for the Russian Film might be better angles
Esbi but secretly were on both drop
Hey for real
Tell everybody about this interview
What you said
Look tell them what we told you
You're the greatest for the BET Alex
Too easy
So Alex
At this point
Presents
Theory that he has
But he is a victim of grbl style propaganda
Clearly
Here's the king
This is being done
Politically and culturally
Assassinate
My character
And make me a bad guy
Show that people believe
Something
Credible
Joseph Goebbels the cheese nachos
Whom I ever admired in the past
Just for fun
Gerbils was largely inspired by Edward Bernays
His work ahead of an A-frame Jerome corsi
Who works for Infowars Six Degrees of girdles
Big Lots
Done the propaganda but also
Go over-the-top with Allah
That perfectly describes Infowars
It's very stupid stuff it's very dumb
The point where it's accessible if you dropped out of third grade and you are just angry
And I don't know anything about the world
It's accessible by the way
Wesley Snipes
Was in Major League
Alex Jones
Has Jerome corsi working for him
6 degrees away from
Grbl I could go quicker
I was trying to go as far away in the weirdest possible way Wesley Snipes
Fat white gerbils
Wesley Snipes didn't pay his taxes
Right
Irwin Schiff says you shouldn't pay your taxes and Son Peter Schiff was on Alex's show
Jerome corsi Jerome corsi bearnaise bearnaise grbl
Ducks
None of those were movie
The victim of a big lie style like it
It's just so big that they would lie like that
You
Your globalist thing is the biggest lie of all like that's
It says that they drink children's blood in Lake the thing
Say they're demonic and they're possessed by a force outside of our Dimension or whatever like
Big Lot
Tiger
It's the biggest lie
Is a lot
Starts complaining about property
It becomes like this weird Ouroboros
I didn't know you could do
Thrilled that your audience is that dumb that they don't
See-through like
When you
Talk about propaganda
It accurately describes your show and it's just a treat
The people don't see
See through
Anyways
Yeah your only response to that if you're propagandist
Legitimately should be like
Game recognize game man I don't know what to tell you that guy is
Russian
Don't know what is really all about
I do it's all about the
Destroying
The family real media has
They are demonized
The president
Troy realmedia
Asthma statue
Touche that they can free up please shut down
Shutdown info
Maintenance brother
A new score
Three months
In the Wall Street Journal
We're going to Alex Jones and Isis
Weird real everybody
I kind of put them all together though I'm I'm down
I'm done with that platform. Then it'll just be 100 Corporation
So that's what I'll be allowed on Twitter face
New Supermarket Sweep 100 corporations are less
Support
Debt
Once they get me
They're going to get you
Howard
The guy that was a long time ago
I'm following this course
To the end
I'm just ashamed that
When push comes to shove down
This is not the time or place
2000's rock
Debatably
The opposite
Is proven to be true
For you
I agree with her
I don't like those idiots should be backing out
Cuz if they do get Alex Jones
They can go for what it what is brightburn the daily color but Alex Jones
Bradford Exchange considerably
Alex Jones for the time. Where he was the b**** that
There's a great
Here's the ears the real issue cuz I proposed that thought experiment where we live
Looked at Alex Jones his pivot outside of America for a second there
I want to take this to another
What we need to do is we need to take politics
Actual rhetoric kind of out of it is a bunch of people who are running
Stamps the running various caught collar Breitbart
Infowars all running cons of different
Description
Most of it is about clickbait most of it is about driving traffic with Alex for a long time is about selling gold for 10 a.m.
And then it became selling
Weirdo supplements
For Breitbart
Very high
In terms of ads they could sell
Same thing with Daily Caller there a lot of Publications aren't really interested in
Publishing realshit there about
Like a scam
They're running a scam
They all do it
They should
And so when one of them gets put in the hopper
Plano
That the other person knows
That they're running a scam
You and I were both guys were running online scam
Because of your behavior
You were getting investigated for something
I would also back off
From you
Because I don't want my scam to blow up
And it's not going to
This isn't going to spill over into all of conservative media you're buying another slippery slope argument that
Believe in America and that is
Scammers all hang together or they all hang separately
Not true at all they're going to survive
The f*** away from the Heat
Yeah it's just too much to it there's too much.
Get into this
There's a investigations of these people
Resources
You know in terms of
Yeah it's a necessary one that would improve the lives of everyone
Certain extent we're not
I think I'm doing that with Alex
It's realistic results in 2009 but you f****** don't want to hear it.
Give me your 14 months all day
Anyway
Alex manly
Do you want to talk about in the
That makes sense now is the right time to say that
Very weird that I think
Indicates that he's stupid
The globalist are
That I'm one of their biggest threats
And that
I'm
The focus
Dedicated
Watch Northstar
Rock
Remember growing up
They were the biggest bullies
White Chicks
I just noticed
Cowboy Hamdi ulukaya would disagree
Because out of what we do here just like the Alamo
Will come example.
They were the bad guys
That was like
Is incredibly strong person with the old young black white male feet
But it's all the so-called smart
Still pausing
Pausing
The globalist
There we go
Used modern society
Lexi
You know what the globalist couldn't Ricky with you or like
You have a potato I have a peach let's trade
They couldn't I couldn't talk.
Everything was
Resource-based barter
I understand what you saying but what he's kind of saying
Is
They're doing what I'm doing
No
I don't think I don't think that's the case because I don't think anyone's manipulating
Because of complexity Alex's saying
Man
I can't figure out the world
Well that's
That's actually a good that's a really good point because what I'm hearing it throughout this entire thing
Is that Alex is
People walk
You said all of these long pauses are hippie and like
I really can't figure out this game
And usually
I can figure out
Against
I think there's a piece of that and I think that's because
Back to the wall he doesn't have any
You don't like in terms of his worldview In-N-Out
He can rattle off subsections that article headlines and stuff
If Alex had to prove his case like let's say in a quart
He knows he can't do it
Probably because you had to do some dark soul searching lately
But
So there's a piece of that where he's like
My-oh-my flowery languages
All for naught
There's there's a part of that I think it's a
I know there's another part that I think
I have a I have a thesis
And I think
I think Alex is about
Sellout
How so
Well
Which which direction are we going
I want to wait till a little bit later to explain my theory that will help make my point
Teasing
Bullshiter are the Galaxy's getting ready to jump off the
Maybe you can cash out quite frankly
Oh like for real well
I will call it a f****** night I'm not entirely sure and we've made so many stupid predictions in the past
Just going by
I'm kind of a natural
Conclusion of where this is going to go
I can keep saying the Trump is rolling up had a file on that works
Destroying
The globalist
He can keep saying he's a global at the internationalist I do want to take the guns early
You can keep attacking people when I say that I it's no big deal that he doesn't
You either
I can't push this much further I've kind of come to the end of it
And so I think
I think there's a bit of it in this in this special report because
Right now his bullheadedness suggest that he's going to he's going to flame out the way that he's supposed to which is
Pile of ignominy
But for now Alex explains
That's not quite happy
Super Auto
Because they're scum
Real quick I want to save it
This also feeds into my theory
He keeps talking about how he is the last
Man
He's honorable and all that stuff part of me like the build-up to The Prestige
Do certain extent
He's got to go John Wayne in the Searchers and just like
Walk away from the building and sacrifice
They're the only people that will
Corruption
That zone of corruption
People
He's able to siphon off of the largesse of humanity
Build
Strata
Also if this doesn't make sense don't worry it doesn't
Really bad
Sociopathic
Sadistic people
Who's in
Shark
Control
Honorable strong
Truthful
Feel
Defeated
Always trying to extinguish freedom
Turn off the Great
Extinguish the light because it reminds them of what
Horribly Fallen cowardly
Checks out
I chose my
Chose
That's not how Destiny work
Strong truthful
Let me know
Many
Right
Heat-seeking missile
Because
.
I'm going to blow his ass up
What's up
Defeated man kind of presenting himself
Be good I chose my dad
I chose to be honorable
GameStop
But like that's why they sent me is a villain
He knows very well on some level that once they start really releasing information that they have on Rodger Stone
It All Leads
In Cahoots with Russia or anything like that but really problematic
Difficult questions to answer
About
What were you doing
Didn't worry
How could you
A very short FBI deposition
How could you up to
I did all that s*** I was asking you just a very simple question whatever it is
Totally did a plausible kind of reality were you unaware of what was going on
Back when it was like
Rodger Stone got taken in for questioning that like
Wasn't on the record and wasn't under oath
Like you can
Spin mat and be like
You can play top with that but like
This Thread is getting pulled sweater is coming undone
You know like it's going
EXO
Again the fact that stone is still in this country boggles my mind
I guess I got a deal
But either way
At whatever rate which is going to try and say instead of from now on
Alex
This whole time has been saying that he's going to get to his message to Mueller
He's going to give him a WWE imagine
What he's going to accuse Mueller of doing
In this next clip
BFDI
Bestiality
Trying to set me up
Overtime
Working on trying to find
Something wrong
Cointelpro
I'm not afraid
I'm not the game Life
I'm not trying to join the system
The threats
Stronger
My message is this
Robert
Mueller
I know what you did
And I know
Real quick because you said was up over it I Know What You Did in Vietnam
Clarify
What Robert Mueller Vietnam I think this is corsi's influence cuz you know he did the Swift boat s*** I think he's probably like
Okay I guess what everyone in the mirror
In America
The soldiers that were there at doing bad
Things but the mission was bad
Did a lot of really f***** up stuff
So
The blame goes a lot of Direction
Also let's be
Super clear
You can't just say that
PewDiePie it's probably a smart idea like when I say I didn't want to half
The director of the CIA I'm going to say that because
She tortured people personally
What happens beyond that
People should qualify
No
No the answer is no
The answer is no
And I will tell you why because of the equivalent for Alex
Should be like
I don't like her cuz but you did in the war
What do you mean
I Know What You Did in Vietnam Robert Mueller
And I also know
Recruited by
John P O'Neill was recruited by the CIA
I understand O'Neal
Okay
Alright
Before he dies that's pretty
I know
You were involved in the group sabatini's
Destroyed the World Trade
I know you're a killer
I know you were
Killed
Okay so now
That Bruce
Edwards Ivan
Want it down
The other not third noun
I remember
Wait what
You'll kill an army scientist
Avocet
Let me see what happens
They had a counter-terrorism tfbi
I know you're cold-blooded
Worship the dark Ultra people
But I don't worship
Cool
Which one there's a lot of
John O'Neill expert
Before we go any further
Mueller did 9/11
That's what he says 23 on release pages
Mueller did that
Clean bill of health
Help put the explosives
That's what he said
That
Saudi Arabia was working with the government
If it
Saudi Arabia was also part of the plot
To put explosive
I thought it was Bush's idea
John P O'Neill is a guy who was a counterterrorism expert
And he was in line for some
Some jobs
In the early 2001 he was recommended to be the national coordinator for security infrastructure protection account
Terrorism
After Richard A Clark
I was going to move on and he recommended John P O'Neill to that position
John.
Because the salary wasn't to his liking
Bobcat around the same time it became
We became known that the New York Times head on him about how a little
Glover year earlier he had a briefcase stolen and caused 911 know
Include like classified documents and stuff like that
And what appears to be is that like he just
He was a victim of theft
But
The story doesn't look good in terms
The View keeping
Record
And India border line classified
It may be we don't trust you anymore
In the Fallout of the story was going to come out he decided to retire
And take a lucrative position
It may or may not have been hooked up
For him by Rudy Giuliani
Security
He became head of security at the World Trade Center on August 23rd 2001
The salary is like $300,000
That was the
That's what he thought is like what I've done with the counterterrorism
I'm here then course 9/11 happened then he died and
But ivy
The conspiracy world
Is weaved all kinds of
Compelling narratives about I
Because he did
He did research the initial 1993 bombing
Of the World Trade Center
But he he was someone who did
Have expertise to a certain extent
He was the inside man who knew how to blow up the
World Trade
No
What was the guy who wasn't on board
And so they put him in the tower
What doesn't make sense you work there for a month
But you three weeks before then why would he go to work
But it's not as big as not that it's not
Is Bruce Edward
Ivan's
Bruce Edwards Ivan
Is actually Robert Mueller
Do you know who that is at all
He's the guy who was the anthrax Mailer in 2001
What's a week after 9/11 a bunch of people including Tom Brokaw Salzburg castle and Patrick Lake
Remember they got letters that had Anthrax spores in them
It is the Department of Justice
But I
Long 90-page
Document
Explain why him
Boy it's
Compare it with him it's convinced it's probably about this
The anthrax
Mahler killed five people and injured 17
Can't pay that started a week after 9/11 ended
Couple months later
Some of the notes that were sent that had Anthrax in them
Tom Brokaw said
In all capital letters
This is next
You always know it's important
What are you got all cap
This is next
Take penicillin now death to America death to Israel Allah is great
Emma letters that you sent to Tom daschle and Patrick Leahy they said
You cannot stop us
We have a ax
You die now are you afraid death to America Desta Israel Allah is great
So initially
Bruce Edwards Ivins was involved in the investigation because he was one of the world's foremost experts on cultivating and produce
Using anthrax
He actually was
He was
Brought in to investigate the letters of anthrax
Then he said
Dexter s*** right there since Vic
He had did he had done it
Well it seems like now it's an obvious ticket retrospect wait wait
In a way such that he was and that would kill his other people in the lab
Using using and there's other people in the lab there's a lot there there's a certain amount of plausible deniability that got
Worn-down much like an old brake pad
To the point where eventually in 2008
He couldn't keep up the ruse anymore and that's what I'm done blowing up in his face but there was enough
Committed suicide
I'll explain why
So he was a senior researcher in bio-defense
Fort Detrick
The US Army medical research has
Sudan infectious disease what I always say is the best biodefense
Is the Best Buy Owasso
There's no doubt about it
At the time in four years the FBI's investigation focused on Stephen Hatfield another researcher at USAA
Mrid
Who they have decided with a good stuff
The FBI surveilled him and raided his home in hazmat suits multiple times
Do the whole 9 yd investigation after years of coming up with nothing solid Hatchell was exonerated and he sued the government
The case was settled in 2008 with Hatfield being awarded 4.6 $1000000
Etihad Bruce Edward Ivins right next to him and he was wearing a shirt that said
The murderer in 2008 exonerated Ivan started demonstrating some erratic
Suspicious Behavior
On March 28th
2008 police were dispatched to Ivans home where they found him unconscious
And took him to the hospital
In June of that year he was involuntarily committed to a psychiatric hospital haven't showed a pattern of suicidal ideation
In July it was informed that he would be prosecuted for the anthrax attack
And according to his report
No one
I couldn't find this from any government Source but he had told other people that he was facing the death by
Penalty for it
In July to July 29th you found unconscious in his home haven't taken two bottles of Tylenol PM
Which they have receipts
Swore that he had bought
Bright before
Are you taken to the hospital where he would die from liver and kidney failure before it's after
His family decided not to put him on a train
The family decided
Amtrak murderer
Go to be honest
Two bottles of Tylenol PM murder
Aw
Bottle of Tylenol PM never went into the equation throwing up man
You good at that too many will die from liver and kidney failure
Then that's what it is
Quick enough right but there is forever odds of it being successful or better
Let's read a lot of other
Methods other than like
Straight up gun to the Head
You know what he's probably researched it more than I did probably
For God's sake
Professor
Drift Away
Really convincing
So I took all of this from the Department of Justice report you can find it it's online
The spores that were sent in the mail were of a strain called RMR 1029
Do the frame that he wasn't exclusive control over in his usamriid
Other people
Our people had access to it
Haha
They have all been excluded
Many of the people interviewed were like
There's no way we could have gotten access to it without him
By being involved
Not even more damning in the months where the mailings were happening
Ivan started to work suspiciously high amount of overtime
Specifically in time but he'll be alone in the lab
From January 2001 to July 2001 he worked a total of 8 hours and 48 minutes in the lab after hour
On August in August
York 11 hours and 15 minutes
In September 31 hours and 28 minutes
16 hours and 13 minutes 6 hours and 20
The pattern is of
Increase time alone in the lab when the attack were happening
Dental scaling back to normal after
Now keep in mind you would have had to sign into the lab there electronic
Access
Stamps of when he was in there
Hate to get into a lab that's dealing with anthrax
You have to take off your clothes and put on a special suit to go inside rather than afterwards take a shower and get into your
Normal clothes
Cumbersome Affair after hours
Is insane
Ivan said no explanation for why he was working so much after hours
There was no special project that there's no special project happening that could explain it
He was just
Is that in order to make Anthrax usable it has to be dry
This is from the doj report as one of the problems with such a complicated way of murdering people
People that limit the suspect
You and like eight other guys
From the doj report spores likely would have attracted attention unless the perpetrator a access the equipment
At night
Anthrax spores requires either a sophisticated drying machine call Delilah Pfizer
Zach or a great deal of time and Faith to let the spores airdrop to allow the water to evaporate in the leg
Because drying Anthrax is expressly forbidden by various treaties
Overuse of overuse of any of these methods if noticed would raise considerable alarm and security
Of course you have to do it after hours and guess what they happen to have a Lyle phaser the equipment that you
You need to dry and 4x at that lab it was requisitioned by Ivan in the paperwork says
Property of Bruce
But such a dude waiting like it's that old joke about men always
Cheating on their spouses with like the girl next door like on the road cuz they're not stupid
Like he was like it well I want to murder a lot of people but I also want to make sure it's the only person that you can look
To go get to have you tried to throw people off the trail later
So it's believed that his motive as funding and approval for his wife's work that is complicated
And then scare children away from his lab females got left behind today
His life's work was the development of an Anthrax attack
And just funding and approval for this was in Jeopardy at the only exactly
Origin story
The only way to change things
Nothing to scare people about anthrax
Interesting late this is exactly what happened after the anthrax attacks
They got approval and funding
This is a Spider-Man villain
But he's also a lunatic
Obviously
So I become 98% anthrax
Terrorist and in the vein
There's a very strong history of
Not too much domestic violence in this case but domestic
Harassment
Okay
So Ivan was obsessed with two female college
At the point when this report was written
Two former colleagues
Leading up to the anthrax attacks you sent two of them disturbing emails about his mental health struggles
He admitted to stealing one of their email passwords and reading their emails
He also said
Wants to get caught
He also sent this poem that appears to be an admission of schizophrenic Tendencies 21
I'm going to read this poem to you
I made up some poems about having two people in one me and the person in my dream
Hazleton
That's not a good time for your phone I'm a Little Dream self short and stout
That's also not a good start for your Paula he lets me out
When I get all steamed up I don't pout I push Bruce aside that I'm free to run about
Hickory Dickory Dock Bruce. Bruce ran up the clock
But something happened did a very strange Rhythm his other self went to exchange places with him
So now please guess who is conversing with you
Hickory Dickory Dock
Bruce in this other guy sitting by some trees
Exchanging personalities
It's like having two in one
Actually it's rather fun
!
Well that was the worst
B Andrew Dice ever did
That was the worst the clay is ever done
So he's sending all these harassing really kind of scary emails and there's a lot there's a lot
There's a lot more we trying to play the two against each other and like
Telling them that they're the only people who really know him there's like it's really f***** up stuff
Also
When he was hospitalized I ended up in group therapy
And in that time he said some really f***** up things ranging from threat
Two other people to basic admissions of guilt
For I haven't gotten the address mailing
With the rest of the group
Not until I Anthrax all of you
Visiting from the doj report
As described in detail in the mental health section Supra Etta group
Therapy session in July 9th 2008 statements regarding the anthrax investigation
Detailed plan
Involving a gun from his son at a bulletproof vest
Kill quote
Co-workers and others who had wronged
What other members of the group was what he was concerned about if he was innocent
He reportedly just smiled
Statements that he made also indicated that he had lost
Time
The only reason I remember some of this stuff it's because there's like a clue the neck
Today like there's an email or you know when you're when you're in bed and you're like
You're like this you know that's
That's not really fun it's like oh s*** did I drive somewhere last night
She has a bunch of things about waking up in his clothes
But not knowing what he did the night before 6
So cute
Just really f***** up high intelligence do
If there's a part of me that now is like I
Baby if you work was Anthrax everyday of your life your
Your brains going to go f*****-up
The rest of the people in his life
That's a good point nevermind so although he was working overtime and they were
Weren't though
He was murdering people concurrently yes in November 2017 sent himself along 12.9
Milo trying to craft an explanation for how the two former female co-workers he was obsessed with we're probably the ones who did the a
Direct attack
Hey Bruce
April
How you been
It's good to talk to you
So they had said stop working with him and he felt that abandoned
Went with Hatfield being cleared of charges
You knew you needed to shift the narrative it makes someone else look suspicious to keep eyes off him
Add to complete
Did you read those 12 points
They do not amount
Finally
Bruce Ivins had a rich tradition of taking on aliases to send people things through the mail
That's the winner right there his female co-workers a package ostensibly from Mia Hamm
Which contained a soccer jersey
He also
Set one of them
Gabriella's
Shoot your shot dude
At least ghost
Lovett they also sent one of them boxes
The Yankees memorabilia and a package marked from Derek Jeter
So alright alright alright cuz it's going on this guy I mean
Women's forces while this is a Title Nine supporter my friend if you look at the big picture when you come away with very clearly is
A guy who committed suicide because the jig was up
He was a tortured mentally ill person and that
There's a tragedy there but you know you crossed the border line and you start sending
News organizations and
Politicians Amtrak
Kind of
They are you kind of cross the Rubicon at work
First of all did 9/11
I killed John P I P O'Neill
Bruce Ivins
In order to cover up that he was the one who did all the answer
All of it is
Bulshit
Oh yeah
Such b*******
This is exactly like when we were talking about the madam
All those people that Alex said were murdered
In the episode we did about Andrew Breitbart is all just like
And he's just hoping that no one actually reads stuff and be like
Focus
It is really about how Hillary is ugly
And a Hilary thumbscrew
You are so demonically ugly
You're so twisted
You are such a
Picture of a witch
Praise for God's justice to come down on Mueller
And what have you or whatever
Alex says something a Time
Long enough to have committed all the crimes
I'm fine with that whatever
Galaxy something I'm pretty excited about
And so
I'm all in
I think
But that is an announcement that Alex Jones is going to be wrestling at the bullet Club in Chicago
Alex is all very excited this card is stacked
Rey Mysterio
Oh my God what a man I don't think you will
I don't think it's going to happen I don't think I'd like to see Alex get super kick
I would
How to spell eyeball
I just trust God
I'm almost guilty
I don't even pray to God
Kids are on drugs
He's all in
There's no
Call Ann
Jesus Christ
And you know that's why Hillary
Alex Jones vs Rey Mysterio in a Soros
Alright alright
Because folks
Slump God
Don't think you do
Little puppy
Except not
Stars
I love happy
And that's why I walk
Watch a bunch of
Murderous monster
Shifter
Watch the Earth
Get back to the stars at night Europe
Alright cellular
Scared about
Tottenham
I love the stars at night
I'm like I'm like you human
Human level
I take
I take her leave
The stars at night whatever
I've seen Stars
So I mean you know Alex is always in whatever
Episode
Are you saying nothing
Because all stuff you said before like I will go to The Bitter End by whatever
But in this next clip we get to what my theory that I was saying before that I think Alex gives an indication in this Mexico
But he's getting ready to
Completely change himself
I'm damn proud
Rihanna
I'm willing to
Whatever Lexi
Electroshock
Romeo
Gibbering idiot
I think that's preemptive
I don't think he's going to come out like sucking McMurtry
And One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest
Packages himself
Again much like pro wrestling
I shift the narratives
Or whatever
He convened be like
You can salvage something
People will forget this
I'm just imagining robbed his nurse ratchet wearing that
That nurse
I can see that that's all I can think of right now
Siri stupid
Define something
That's a weird better dialogue that's a weird piece of rhetoric
I think
This idea of like if I Trot out and I'm completely different
Don't let them ever demoralize you
Liar
I'm not real I'm an actor
Your lawyer Robert Mueller
What state
So he's ahead of the deep State now
Bright
Alex like don't let anyone ever tell you that I turned my back on you if I come out
Right in some way his
Launching a possibility for him to like
Get a job at Fox News or something like that
But I Justified floating it as a possibility
Something to keep me interested in this Saturday is just a mess
Lady that maybe you like
Uno
Foreshadowing
Microphone
It was okay
What
Andrew Soros
Bruce Ohr
Except
Sure
But you
Will the
Destroyed
You know what
You are going to be destroyed
Your crimes
You have gone across that line
You have crossed that Rubicon
UF
Crossover
Sure
Did your old man now
When you die
Your family buries you
Failure
Penetrator
Anime
If I was you
I'd be getting you
Shelves
You know 1000
Percent
And the cottage Chinese year old
Again Alex admitted on are these talk to Russia
Intelligence
Asia
What's that subliminal
You die without honor I believe
I mean this is
By the way
I don't know
You've ever read the Bible Alex
But too late for you to accept Christ is very much
Not what Christ said
Christ was very much on the side of like it's never too late for that guy who I was
Committed all of the worst crimes and I was like
You're cool dude remember how it wasn't too late for that f****** guy guess what
That's my whole gig
Yeah but the Alex does Italy say I do
I don't know if you gone
But that doesn't apply to the physical diagrams to like
Robert Mueller did 9/11
Uno's
Alex accuses about something else here this next clip
And then the end of this
Is pretty why you did 9/11
Your grandma live
Explosive
Peligro Matt Daley.
Oklahoma City
Is the cops ever
Help
Transmission
Oklahoma City
Live streams
Yukon 911
I'm going to see you
Hell you also did Oklahoma City
Vietnam
In Oklahoma City
When you killed those cops
Are there any 9/11 when you got John O'Neill
Well that's about my time so I'm going to get out of here later alright
Alright G looks like we made a little bit of product
Anymore cuz he's pretty much done but
Little bit more and then Owen Shroyer walks by
Just gets really boring so that I can listen to that special report I think that we've learned
But Alex is probably
Reasonably afraid of the revelations that are coming with them looking at Rodger Stone
I think it'll be interesting to see what happens with
Beyond that I think
Did Alex
I mean what we have to do is be if that you know
Really look
Everything is
All of these stories are such lies
Bruce Ivins was murdered and they forced tylenol.is mouth
Uo8 order to believe that you have to believe that every other thing that Bruce
Did isn't real
And that
Baxter's document
Chrysler's everything is document email gave to these other coworkers
The timestamps of him signing in and out of the lab during suspicious hours
You know what that sounds like Neil is doing
But it itches everything comes back to
Everything is alive but it's a
Capitola July
That's why people fall for it
Anyway
They were the present I don't know how much longer we're going to be doing present stuff but
Enjoy it
God just watching
Watching Stone
So nonchalantly be like
Oh I'm going to be indicted
I'd like any even had that ratfucker smile I was just like I'm just like
I can't wait to tell you all about that
From
2016 on he's known that there will be is this
Does he have cancer something does he have some kind of like
You'll never catch me motherfukers last ace-in-the-hole like he's got to have something I think some part of him knows
You can sell some people out
Okay
I think that's probably
I think that's probably the
What you're replying
Is it still in him
Is probably an awareness that he has another fish
That he can throw in
Cell
Given his history given who he is as a person
I think that
I think that he knows he's safe because he's not the most important
Primary
So f****** insane
Knowledge underscore
You can do that and go to our Facebook group also sorry I forgot to put that to clip together again will do it on the next
You're the worst
I am
A busy man anyway also we're on iTunes please
Describe All That Glitters.
It is my turn and I think there's only one
One person
Tutela to go fuc
And that
Every single conservative in this f****** country can go f****** kill themselves
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work