Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Little bit about Alex Jones
Everything was coming up to
And just came up you on the street and said you sir
You look like you have
Perhaps the only podcast
That's about one subject I could imagine
No other people could have this podcast
Describe
To whom you know
Everything is coming up to
I would say leave me alone
I want to talk
Before we get to ourselves
About something you all in all you
Inside stuff
Alright I would think of that Isaiah Rashad
All day
The way I love our relationship
Because
YouTube
Cuties
Life stories
Before the show you're like I can't tell you about this
Antidote for my regular life until we're on the show
It's it's relevant
Okay until today it would kind of a little bit up in the air how the f*** I was going to get to Austin
I'm show in Austin on June 15th
A lamp
Ashley Judd
Probably okay
Because I had an expired ID and I realize I can't get on a plane with expired ID
Secretary of State's office over and over again
This isn't good enough
Whatever piece of information that I have about myself is not good enough
I'd approve my date of birth approve my address
Like
I had to get them my lease
And I couldn't get my lease
Until after my birthday
And after my birthday my ID was then over a year expired and now I can't use my old id
Approve my birthday anymore
So they tell me that I leave either my birth certificate or my
School transcript right in order to get my ID
Together as everyone knows those are the only two ways to really identify
Freaking out the last time I went there and then
Tell you
Start
Alright
And she's like
Stupid
Scuse me
Is your name Dan
Please stop.
I wasn't crying but I was not happy
And they'll give you one of my
How does that work
California images
I think you have a password
Mechanics expired by now
It's not right there like maybe School transcript
Those looking through my apartment
Top to bottom
Couldn't find my birth certificate
But I did find my school transcript
And Jordan I have a little bit of a reveal for you here is my high school equivalent
Degree
Cancel my social security number on
I would just like
To congratulate David a freezin for graduating from the Department of Elementary
Secondary Edge
State of Missouri
That's my Jeep the camera
Congratulation
My brother's name on it
And my middle initial
Perfect completely fuk sound like
There's no way they're going to accept a problem
And that does not have your name
You might be off
The group
I thought you even have
Text
I thought for sure I'm going to go in there and I'm
Nah that's doesn't work
This morning
7:30 in the morning
To get there right when they open today sweating bullets
As I put this transcript down on the table just like
No fart
They're going to catch
I'm the guy who has like a balloon of cocaine up his a******* going through customs
At the Secretary of State's office
I'm like
God this is
The disaster
They accepted and I got my ID we will be in Austin that's my long way of saying that
But in going through weird and stupid that they're like
That's wrong name
Because your ID expired 4 days ago so that means clearly
You could be any
School transcript without your name on it
How can we not trust
Navigation so what's fun is the in going through all of my stuff to try and find my birth
I found a couple of
Cool
Remnants from my path
Very sentimental
I want it I want to elevate our friendship
And expose myself to the audience a little bit with v
I like it when you get real.
The first one here is equipping
From a newspaper in Missouri
Where I'm protesting the Iraq War
In 2000
Whatever Whenever Bush's second inauguration was
Nice so 2004
Maybe
Looking for the newspaper
I'm the guy in that picture
You're this guy real
No I didn't have a beard all the time I can't imagine that just most of the time I figured you didn't have a beard all the time
Swear to God I thought you were a baby with just 99% of the time
Kind of realize that I was in the paper protesting
That's a makes me feel good make me remember my cat
Eli's Raiders I found this picture from my first apartment
Rich Forever
Is
I'll show this to you and then I'll describe what it is
There's a guy by first apartment at 18
Turn flashlight to the camera cycle people
I'm looking at this and it concerns me this young man needs help there's no doubt about it so
Clip-on the screen gear I'd like to describe what that is that is me with a beard without a mustache
Amish beard
I was living in a shity basement apartment and if you look at what you'll see is a
Later that the only thing it is to dogs
Yep that malt liquor and carefully
You'll see a picture
Of myself
On the fridge
Only thing that's on the fridge is passed out on a lawn
Is malt liquor
Life is good
God
That no-man's land where I didn't
Didn't look like it was going to get my equivalent
Times are bad
Anyway Two Hearted Ale from Bells
To the chat room and now let's get down to business
Okay first things first
Requested that I talk about my past a little bit and that's why I did that that's not that's not true.
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much Tim for joining up
With the crowd
I ran out of the bed okay
A few times and you're just now noticed I haven't noticed
Brinkley
Wasn't worth
New drop and I haven't
I have got it
I appreciate it for our new level of
Play new level of support
There is a course
Policy wonk
Yes there is foreign policy walkthrough
There's technocrat
Couldn't get any higher than that there is a new level we have three people who are at that level currently that I've been waiting
To give a shout out and I told one of them
Before already and that is Keegan
Keegan who so kindly got us all these back issues of Infowars magazine
But I've been reading
The crazy
There is also a little part of me that's like you're an able
A little bit he he got the honor of naming the knocked Memorial Library
And also I would like to
To congratulate him on being the first
Raptor princess
Northstar
Amanat Ali Aprilia
Someone someone sodomites
Jesus Christ
How to read
Control my life
Abused by white people
Joseph Stalin
Thank you so much
Guitar
What's the weather
45 second floor
Thank you so much we got a couple more folks coming along
Remembered and said that he had praised Hitler in the
The past
Forgot I forgot that he had called him and Stalin
What a weird thing to say very strange
Episode
May 7th through 29
All right there's a reason for it I was going to do a project Camelot show today but
It was tough
My original plan
What are the reasons what are the reasons that my day was so ha
It was I was trying to prepare Project Camelot episode
Cuz what I intended to cover was
Courtney Brown
The remote viewer who I inadvertently
You know
Basically like pleasure Heaven's Gate
You were both interviewed an object UFO behind
He was on Project Camelot again and eat remote viewed Moses
And the Ten Commandment
Right and I was like
Which one was the favor
I didn't watch it cuz it was so boring
Like 25 minutes
Half an hour
None of this was entertaining
It's just a really annoying dude
So I started looking through more of his s***
And I found
But he is doing right now and investigation using remote viewing
To talk about
Future of Bitcoin
But
But because of his financial advice
He has to give a disclaimer that is like this is for entertainment purposes only cuz he doesn't want to get f******
What's really undercuts his own belief in his remote viewing capabilities
Does watching that and like this is a disaster
This sucks so much
Hilarious
He did a remote viewing into Alex Jones
Amazing
You just played Rises are episodes entirely that we made tattoo
Alright
Kody Brown's new episode sucks
Let's go back to Mark Richards
Watch the first episode
Just
The time the Kerry Cassidy
And Mark Richard Matt
And I realize
You've been lying to her the exact same way the entire time
It's all the same ship in the first person
Jesus shoes she's like
In her car after she got out of Vacaville prison and cheeses like
He's friends with the Raptors or like
Alright we can do this again I love Mark Richards but like I said it's the same thing right
So then I was like all right you were hoping for the story
Evolved over time it said of almost being
Yeah pretty much
You know what the fun of Project Camelot is
It's us finding
New crazy
I'm so I found this other guy
Because he was so terrible
But he was on talking about how Mormonism was created by a lie
Battlegrounds
Right
This could be juicy
Fat
What you talking about new crazy
First reasonable person that's ever been on
Project Camelot
Imes
I wrote a book
Signs for
He wrote a book
Called
Deception of the ages
Mormons Freemasons in extraterrestrials
It's always watching
Great
Great books
Title
Terry is arguing with him
She's like she's like that doesn't make sense
What like Battlestar
Jessica was based on Mormon beliefs or something like the ten tribes of Israel or out in space
Carrie was like that doesn't make sense
It was just
It wasn't good
Is really fun
This guy who wrote a book about
Terrestrials in Boardman
I found
Hugh page
Egg salad
Which
If you are not a stand-up comedian you don't know that is a place where really shity Comics Go corporate gig
His bio on dick
Normally I do stand-up comedy but until next December when I win the race for US Senate District 1
I'll be campaigning
If you need if you'd like me to speak to your event about politics or tell jokes or both
That is fine
So
Falling in love with him
So here it is what
Delusion of the
Grin disorder and I love it
He has a what to expect sex
A highly professional comedian author or MC that doesn't use
Nauseate your client
With 20 years of teaching experience around the world at high school college military level
I don't work a crowd bullet point
It's about like why he's a good comic the first
Material I can write jokes
Any crowd
He could only write jokes for the crowd
It doesn't
Education
I told him after
Three education in a bachelor's and master's degree in education
Yes sir
Apparel
Does not equal
But okay
So there's
Experience location
Most watched Comics that I know
Probably didn't even graduate
High School
Forget this number 5
Yeah physical presence
Absolutely important I lift weights and swim three miles every week and it does
Lots of stamina
Richmond Craigslist edit video
Number 6
Loyalty at this stage of my career I will remember those businesses that help me get started I will be at your beckon call to do everything I can
Fulfill your request now calls me home
This is the guy who's coming out and talking about Mormonism and Aliens is amazing how much does he charge on a book
I looked
At least they have the booking fees
Free
This is great but is this whole episode if it's just like
Nonsense and him being like
I don't like okay
I don't want to do this
How is his physical presence with with Carrie
Not good
Not not great
You probably somewhere around Washington state is great location awareness
Although at the same time I got to tell you
Local jokes means local work
Project Camelot Road
And they all
I had some 2009 that I've been looking into
One of these episodes that we're going to cover in this December or January 27th to 29th
He's my second favorite episode of Alex Jones I've ever listened
The first my number one favorite of course is that time that he
Rhetorically jump the shark
By suggesting that we kick all Muslims out of United States
Bobby with kind of making that argument
That's that's my favorite episode
Second favorite is going to be the 28th
Get to that here in a minute
First
There's not a context drop for
Alex Jones
Cool Daddio
He-Man still laughing
You guys are you guys still smoking the reefer you guys still the the cool guy you want to go shoot some
You guys like
The 27th alligator going to take me down
Alex 27
My man
He is
Seven days in Obama's presidency giving him a chance
Not great
No
No he is not having a good time
What were the first 7 days
You setting up a all sorts of negative things
Can come grab was running around battle guns
Is that like one of those hand extension things that old people use to pick up a robotic arm
Leprechaun
And it only
Took it to the chat room
We will call Larry Nichols again sometime
But not tonight
Too late for the old man
Alex
Discusses
This
Very very ironic position
That he has on what's going to happen after Obama
That's a quote
You say they're going to
Man
Physician's basic Elementary psychology
Interesting
2016 the person who is destroying Obama
Although there was
No reasonable reason
Have some harsh criticism
You mean he was probably a little bit more than fair
22 Obama on his way out
I didn't know way
Trump look like
Soul job pretty much
2009 Global is they're going to do want Obama is out
We have in 20
Exactly what he predicted the global in 2009
Learn from your enemies
You learn their tactics and you deploy them against
Yeah
Thinking
I do agree
You fight fire with fire
It was like crap I just have the time just to re-establish that Alex
If it's not a flipping state
For him he does believe that a run
Nuclear program
Very deceptive business for peaceful purposes
Spectrum
For them to do that
I don't know what I don't know how you make it more clear than these
He's not
Repro Ron
At least
As far as this this angle
I mean I know we already established that we already talked about it but he's not considering
A huge backer of
Right right
But that makes me furthers my theory
But I don't think he's actually
Bike
Beholding to Russia necessarily or on the hook
Jax off to Putin
He's like I love you but I don't know if I like your friend
I don't know about that
Well
Alex
I'm I am digging you
Advocate
RockAuto
Ice cream socials
God dammit
The deterioration of
The family
Dating
I don't know
So
I regret that you were not around for that episode that I did with Marty where we talked a lot about libertarianism and
The Von mises Institute
If you were here we would have done a lot more
Who screamed a lot more about all the stuff I've researched about how heartless these f****** are
At its core the Austrian
School AMV
Institute version of libertarianism
Is like
Real harsh
F*** you and your needs
It doesn't matter
Cowboy news
They're straight-up making an argument for why you don't have an obligation to
2 ft or close your child because that would be a negative obligation on yourself right as opposed to
Positive faith is a huge mass
You can read their articles about it
I'm not making any of this up
So that's the school of libertarianism to Alex come from and a lot of
The John Birch Society stuff is
And so on this episode here on the 27th of January
Alex is talking about a story where an old man freezes to death
In his home
He's angle on it.
Does not make sense
With his
Philosophical
They turn people's power off during the winter
I got some of the
Local news
This is what's going on
Turn
Power off
When they're living in freezing temperatures
Dollars
Scores
So a couple things this guy owed $1,000 to the utility company with says a lot of back bills
I'm not saying he deserved to f****** die or anything like that power off in the winter
But you know how you do that
Suck a government
Regulating business
Message literally the
Literally the office
Fair enough
The old Liberty
The only way for that like Alex's desired outcome to come is against his philosophical position
Because this guy was an old white World War
What's happening in this economy that's Obama's fault
Or whatever
But that's what libertarian is
Libertarianism is entirely
I believe myself to be a god
And if everything isn't going right for me
F***
Real
Doesn't matter which direction
It could be if you're in the lower powers that you know
I tried to buy this with currency that I wrote on my hand that said
All the money
And you would let me that's anti-libertarian
But you didn't
You turn it off cuz I didn't business it morally wrong user
Are immoral businesses should be able to exclude gays are black people if they want to because the market
Take care of that in their freedom to segregate
Then whenever anything goes against me oh my God this is
Yeah there's a breach of
Very fabric of American society
It's all this this horseshit
But I like that because libertarianism is just
Amman
Staying
Well it shouldn't happen to me
Whatever
But I think that this is a moment we're like Alex Jones
He's like
I think it's a little bit of a towel and I don't want to say it
Just because he's an old white World War 1 veteran died WWII veteran I use that as like a
You know I get a little bit of a
Big but at the same time I think that this is a moment where like is Humanity's waiting out over his
Like
Bulshit
I don't mean to say that makes him
Good or anything like that really believes in his beliefs
Like I don't think these libertarian beliefs that describes to really go much deeper than
Leave me the f*** alone I hate gay people I don't want to be forced to talk to black people they scare me Muslims are weird
And I want my gun
I think that's probably like
The rest of its kind of scattershot intake really really an ideology
Really and ideology that falls under the banner of any larger thing other than
I want to be
Quietly racist
Please
Well it's kind of say the n-word if I never saw any Edwards
It's a process 20th century
Masturbate
Be like Ike
I'm so
Episode
We get
Probably other than old man house phone
We get one of my favorite colors
I miss old man house phone
But you got calling a lot
No
This caller is in
Credibly inside
Also my phone is in the shape of a
Golfer
Yes
A really pointed question cuz I was complaining about the transit
The quarter that never got built
Figueroa
Take over the United States through a road
District
Suspiciously very similar to the timezones this is all stuff we got over in endgame
Game coverage going to learn more about to go listen to those episodes
I'm not going to break it down again as an amazing question but Alex
Another question go ahead
Yeah I'm up
What
With the depopulation agenda
Why do you think they would need a
Superhighway of 90% of people going to be dead you know and other all the
And other things it seems like you're doing
Are really don't seem like they would be necessary in it
With 90% of people gone
Mopeds
The issue
More preamble preamble before you get to onions
First I got to talk to you about this one thing but then I think I'm going to analyze
I am going to synthesize
I am going to buy also I am going to dance like Giorgio moroder
I will be able to tell you why,
You sir are obviously incontrovertibly wrong sir
Another word for we have to go to break
I'm going to Vamp talk about how smart my answer is
That's just to show you there's no Cuts here
Official
The world's population
Baytown
Go with Vivian GameStop week
Internet
Encarta
University
This is
Control grid
Rambles about how like they need to put this road in and
Poison the water so they can do a slow kill
Tammy Heaton the road
So you can incrementally.
The population
Super Highway if it's taken over by the US and then
Sovereignty blah blah blah
Maybe what the globalist are really against
Traffic
Yeah I need a bigger Road
And then I need to get rid of a super highway
That's just for
Cargo
I think
To use that if everybody's dead there's a there's a diamond lane
A global cash card
And then you get to go through
The carpool lane
But I will give Alex credit and maybe I hear peep
People's criticisms that I'm being too positive about him in 2009 I think they're missing the f****** point
But I will take my cat
Take captive because he
For so long about nothing
He did manage to come up with an answer
Very least answer the question
But the whole time you talk in here
OK Google, can you look at your B if you're like where you from
How do you do a little bit of crowd work while you're trying to figure out what was like that
Was that going that's what he's doing the autopilot is like April
So this guy
Then
Comes in with an amazing follow-up the follow-up question 6 amazing
Yeah alright
What one of the things
What you thought
Why do you think that
Alma Hollywood
People that you know and
Big big
Time people and wealthy
People rich
What why you think nobody's ever just giving you a million dollars or
No half-a-million
So you would
Spend so much time advertises
You're called
That is another
Really important complex question
But but first
But I want to go back to your first wife
Lookout little biscuit
Alex Jones
That's a state
Questioningly don't do it
So how do I answer this question where it is very clear
Keep pretending
With millionaire support man
Billionaire support me in multi-millionaires and Kardashian gave me his coat
Why won't they just give me the money I need to run this operation instead of me having to sell
F****** dumbass didn't have his guys soap guy come do limericks on myself but I look like an a******
I just look back
Why wouldn't I
Alex Hester like Rude Boy
Promenade sometime today
Hollywood first question that I've already
So he mumbles around a bit and then he finally lands on this as his answer with his like
Alright
I got a reputation in Hollywood baby
Cuz it would be gauche exactly it would be
Notice it is simply
Done sir
You you notice
The caller didn't ask why haven't you asked them for a million dollars
There's why haven't they given you a million dollars
You know they would do if they supported and believed his dumbass b******* about the globalist
You are doing the most important
Call Alex
What he presents things
They know even more than him that he's right because we are apart of the system
Charlie Sheen's pedophile party
Bitcoin worth
But if you actually
It's controlled up
You can't allow him to get
Too powerful
Getting all these million-dollar checks
From Charlie
Charlie Sheen in
Yeah
Probably like that
Get my knowledge fights approval for today is the s***
A caller who is the exact opposite
Okay
Complaints for the election Halloween Obama
I took his daughter out
The corpse Queen
Are all the major media was reporting that and that's when I knew we were in
First century bullet this guy
It was
Halloween
That tracks
Tracks that is when the spirits and the devil's come out to play
Yep buddy dresser like a death Queen
I think possibly yes I don't know what movies came out in 2009
Yeah I would assume
Some pop culture bulshit
A visit from Gerald Celente
Harrold
Right intercourse
Everything's going to s***
So he's at the DMV
So they don't they don't do the same game
Is Bob
We get to the same point to man
Con coming out Vaudeville training
So the other person videos episode
Is investigative reporter Wayne mad
Those words are true including go f*** yourself you don't remember
Who told the story about the White House Chef who got murdered with button
He is a mess
He appeared briefly in r2000
GameStop
DePere anymore
If you f****** hate
He hates them
He thinks that he is a fuckboy
Spell out for Israel
He is here I'm not going to side with him on this except for the Hayden Alex parts
Your reasons are wrong
Probably
But he at some point
I'm not sure exactly when we're going to have to figure that out as we go along
Now is like heat
Brutal s*** about alley
But he hates
He's one of the you like
Laundry list
Of dudes were involved in Infowars who now or like
F*** this dick
Play Madison pellegrin enemy of my enemy is not my friend
F*** Alex Jones I'm with you
Smirk at the enemy of my enemy but I will not go
Consider them a friend
Hard-hitting reporting bro
He wants to come in
And talk about Rahm Emanuel
Good because
Reasons they don't make
So many worse things than just being they don't make it that it's not about that but it's it's
It kind of about
The singular focus and how weak this f****** reporting is it feels like you're pointing finger for a reason
Don't make this up text textbook how f****** week this story is the
Would you say it's fair to say that Obama
High-powered
Honeymoon
Is this honeymoon was over before they checked into the
Motel room
Real quick I also wish that really a honeymoon
A whole bunch about how like Obama
What
It's crazy
It's crazy these try I don't know if he did or did not support Obama or vote for him
But if he did
Wow
What is
I voted for him to bring back hope and change
Write clearly
I need that
This was never a honeymoon because
Oyc doesn't like Emmanuel Emmanuel
I don't know if you know about this but the other days
Report a New York time
There was a cabinet meeting
And Emanuel was sitting there at the cabinet meeting cracking his knuckles that Obama was to him he said
Where am I wish you would
Stop that I find that annoying
Emmanuel gets up and cracked his knuckles right in Obama's here
Discussing with him
That's this respectful to the office
The presidential debate
Okay
So
The story is that he cracked his knuckles at Obama
What a delightfully Pettibone
First of all
Who cares I don't know I care
Can you imagine be like
President of the United States you're annoyed by my knuckle cracking well
But one that is to try and President Obama
I think every part of it
A week after
2016 election
The twittersphere that is the propaganda against Donald Trump
Let's say
The shity stupid dick do dick holes
If there
Propaganda line
Steve Bannon cracked his knuckles at Trump
What the f*** are you doing
That's your story
That's all we need
Boy you got to try harder
Real bad
They don't
If everybody is a Fox news story for two days they do not have to try at all
They don't give a
Jet the glom onto anything
And if you already hate Obama you're going to join in
They talk about knuckle gay
On this side is episode they come back to it a couple times unacceptable
Crazy
But
Only thing I will accept
Being called knuckle gate is a Jean-Claude Van Damme
Whoever becomes the president but I also had to fight B Underground
This would be great
What even great
Is that in 2009
Wayne Madsen comes on Alex Jones Show
He says
A bunch of positive things
About John podesta
Maui
In present day
No problem
With John podesta at all I'll tell you what
If if
Alex had an idea of what he would become king
Wayne Mattson play positive things about John podesta
Now Alex Jones
To be the center of a pedophile Network that kills
I'm in order to get into the blood
But you know what Andrew Breitbart
Wait he's not dead yet
Who cares
Going to get back to it real Emanuel and visit
You keep your mic down for this
If you need to hear house
Walking hard Alex laughs fake Lee
It's something about Rob
And and even John podesta was ahead of
The transition team interesting
He was Clinton's chief
Stampy at the same job.
Emanuel has under Obama
Baby found in
Administration
Political ways and his mannerism
180 outfit
From this guy Emmanuel Emmanuel
I just a nasty guy
Anna and you know
Obama talked about bringing change to watch
Well this is it suck I am on you I was a former ballet.
You're not to impugn ballet dance
But anyway
I did listen
This is like this guy's like at call rauf I wearing a tutu
What is not very good
What a goddamn fake laugh
Hahaha all right. We got to get back in
Some serious issues
Oh boy he does even more
Come back to the well on me the ballet dancer
It's because like
Comedy comes from
Largely surprised and
Familiarity being Blended together
They don't understand how do I get that
That symphysis together I'm not entirely sure why but
He was a ballet
Gay
Hilarious right
What why isn't everybody
Everybody laughing
No you
Because Isabelle
Get off the stereo
Supposed to be
I'm looking over by my clips
I realize that I labeled some of them accidentally
December
I don't know what I was doing when I was cutting clips
I got the dates wrong
Interesting John podesta
So
Adesa is the exact opposite of Rahm Emanuel Rahm Emanuel was in nasty
A piece of work
Therefore
But I could also
Pajama Tessa is not
That's the logical
A conclusion
Hilarious
Hahaha
So a little bit later in the show Alex Jones going to take some more collars
And you get a call from a guy who is
Sounds black
And I said some bad things about Obama
Okay I meant he's like cuz it's literally the show
And the end music is starting to play is like
The musical playing so call in tomorrow
Do that
Yeah they did Obama they need a black person to be president cuz they're vampires so they can
Chicken takeover
The Africa because there's a black face on it and then they can steal their gold and like
That's what Bob chat
Batman dead
Isn't you already have
A friend boots
Africa
It's not important OB
Because January 28th
Yes
It will go down in Waterbury
I'm forgetting about but this is
So what it wanted apology box
I'm going to message you later just be like
You and your second favorite episodes
Touche
This
Should give you a sin
Of why
The documents are still killing
Americans
Is it real quick
I just want talk about this really quick
Interview with Kevin
At the end of the show
And I do want to get into
Cuz it's really long
I thought I forgot
Specific
But Kevin is a guy who is a lunatic
And
A minister for the United Church of Canada
I got excommunicated by them and
And told
They stripped like on their roles
Get the f*** out
He had a series of Sony
Not allowed to be buried in a United churches
Camden
Knows he's a freeman-on-the-land kind of guy which is
Some s*** great he's a monster is transphobic
Montrell guy
He's a complete mess
But he's claimed
If you talkin about
A genocide
It's going on against natives
Canada
And
It's about
Like a school building
Kind of complicated to get into and I don't really want to
Except to say that Native American
Can tribes have written him season 2
Assist leaders
Like the people that he's claiming to stand up for
Have written him inside
Please do not
Username
You don't speak for us
Because they are in
Concert with the United Church of Canada
Which was the organization that had
School setup
Where he's claiming that there were like genocide
It's being done sure and
Excommunicated from even
Talkin about
First Nations
Communicated from the church
Keep our name out your mouth
Right by the native
He keeps trying to
Use
Attachment
To Native folks
In order to
Raise money
International tribunal into crimes
Church and state
Which is basically just a Blog he has that he acts like they can
Put out warrants
Some stuff like Asher
Complete Luna
And it's one of those things that like
You kind of get a scent like you get a feeling immediately of like
And I kind of empathize and I bet there was some really bad things done today to people in Canada to assume there
Knowing OK Google
Even in Canada the white man came and that means horrible shape
You get you get like empathic to the argument that he's making
Until you look more into Mineola
F****** con man
It is like you look into it in your leg
This guy is also part of the white man destroying Native American maybe horse
Yeah maybe some Subway
Broadcast ever done
He want
You mean! My nuts and I never do
I think! Or terrible but it's if it's this next clip is an audio exclamation
Call your friends and family
Right now
Infowars
Salomon stores
Right now
Primitive
Mammalian response to something
Immobilization
Mobilize
Coming out
It's just no other way
Red light in their car
Go knock on neighbor's door call everyone you know cuz this is the s***
What's going on
What are they making a c
Sequel to Ferris Bueller's Day Off
Sir that is not
That is not what
Flights
Such incongruous music
The most important announcement
Music to play Vine
Being played
During The Towers falling on 9/11 you don't know what the most important news in the world
Did Alex
Choirs who to stop people at red lights
No I don't
Man that's that's a bummer
Well I'm not going to tell you what it is either
5-minute story
News report
Good
Injustice
Peace of a puzzle
Precisely
Tire infrastructure of what they're setting up
Course we have been completely historical research and government documents
Hundred percent as we said that
This is it
Is this it
Air raid sirens in the background
Make no mistake what you're doing is
Don't f****** pretend you're taking a Highway 6 is going on
Theatrical
But it's so serious
You just
Told everybody
Park
Call your neighbors your friend your boss
Right now
Information
Calmly
Okay
So he wants you to get in the middle of traffic
Block people off Patrick hallway
To write a sternly worded
To the glow
Global global
In traffic
Begin handing it out politely if someone were to say no
You say of course not
And you continue going
Can I ask you
Close
Yukata calmly go over
Did you know that
Right
Well I'm still not going to tell you but he has another story wasn't no
Amazing
Real quick marketwatch's not the wallpaper
Both owned by the same company
What are they going
This isn't the big story
Jabberjaw
Now that's Street Journal
Nope MarketWatch
He told you
So I looked at that article I found it
And there's some interesting things in this article
Man this article doesn't say anything like what he saying
First of all
I got red flags all over MarketWatch
Because this guy was right it's in the opinion
And
Was it Kissinger no I just saw that you wrote Atlantic and that's why I
I didn't recognize this guy's name
But he was like
He starts out with like now that we're in the grip of the New World Order
Yeah
I should have been in the letters to the editor section and the very back of vanity
Let me read to you from this article about is a North American currency realist
Know if this Dynamic plays out and I've got no Insight that it will
The global balance of powers with fragment
Primary read
North America Europe Asia and the Middle East
Time zone
Play I don't know about that
The breakdown
In such a scenario ramifications of manifest through social unrest
Geopolitical console
This particular path isn't something one would wish for but the cumulative imbalances
Steadily built
In our finance based economy must be resolved one way or another
Therein lies the critical Crossroads weed together face
SeaWorld
To find its way
Scary
Yeah
Probable
Not so much
At least for the time being
Possible certainly
All again offer before the pieces of his prickly puzzle fall into place
Have I said anything
No effective money management dictate swaying the entire probability Spectrum
Potential outcome
In factoring that into our decision-making process
Right so this guy literally saying
This is likely
He has written
That does not
Express in Topanga
No just not it's wishy-washy
Does not use
Information
That is all just
Pure speculation
I have no insight into this
So that's the main story
Continues
I have no idea what I'm talking about
And I'm making this b*******.
So this is not the main
Story
On any other day
It would be
That's true it is weak enough to be the main story absolutely
And it's got a good enough headline for Alex to have not read the entire article is a North American currency
Impossible
Shrug that no one's into it but I guess
We still don't know what the
Pistorius the main story
But I have called my friend
Britain this next clip
Alex is not one
For theatrics
But perhaps does
One of the most embarrassing Lee theatrical things I've ever seen on this.
This
Like this is my town
When I was listening to this episode
Like I blurt laugh
Sitting alone in my apartment
This made me laugh harder than maybe anything I've heard on Alex's show alright in the past who are playing this up
To call your friends your family your neighbors Wiener House
A huge responsibility
Proper analysis
Establishment
With their spin on it
Has a chance to understand
Right now before I go into
Campbell report
Door open
22nd
Confirmation
Profile
Understand
Julian's epitome
Still long
Fuel relay
Jet.com
Last night's Top story
Stop
That to me is biggest news
That requires
Not just a moment of silence
But frankly
Bye-bye account between 14 and 60 moments of Silence
Is an article that was written yesterday
Take me to go
Super-mega viral because they already made it viral
Fairway
Like this
Clip
Episode
Keys this b******* is like
Stop traffic
Call your mom
Burn It Down
She still needs to know this is the most important thing
70 TV store in stand and stare at the TVs in the window as if
You imagine the experience
Me listening to all that buildup
What's going on here
What's this what's this
But something exciting is going on at Disney's commercial breaks I still have to listen to he's selling gold
Dip roses
You selling tchotchkes on the show
Rose's dipped in gold that sounds sexy easy also the memory scam commercials
Absolutely don't need it
Comes back on air Republic
There's a story by Paul Joseph
The fuc
Bird
I should have known
Isn't saying what this bill is
The death of the Republic
What it is
Man
This is one of those
If this it is this description that Alex is about to
To give was real
Infrastructure and architecture
It's going to be shut up under the superhighway
Grinch
Everything
Coronavirus Boston
Secretly recruiting preachers
So
He still hasn't said what
Ezekiel
Chapter 11
He hasn't give up your guns
To inoculations
Even those haven't been invented yet we heard from Daniel and accusations or table
Daniel Daniel got that one done
I also
You know what
Why not there's going to be a road
What the bill is yet
So we're not going to talk about
But I will say it's really important
So goddamn afraid
A FEMA camp
I like
Heath
I I legitimately think I haven't listened to too much after this
But I suspected might be what is brain bro
Like I think the word list like this episode I think it's all downhill from here I think
Starcrest
To begin the decrescendo might believe his b*******
Actually I don't like I don't fully believe that
But I think that this is a very useful
Like way for him to descend it away
I don't know what episode
Yes but
16 moment
Infinitive silent that is not adopted
We need to be clear 2009
We talk about what's going on 2018
We have a situation where ice
Is separating families
Inputting
Children into like military warehouses
Right
That sort of thing
They would prefer to be in
FEMA camps
Any any conversation of Alex Jones
Like all this
Pedaling
Fear about white people being put into FEMA camps of the time for the Patriots
White people stuff like that but the rest of my
If you believe
If you believe that you think it's
So goddamn
Human and disgusting
And you aren't offended by what I see
Is doing right now Trump is
The presiding over
Yourself
Not separate whiteness is rightness and we are witnessing
Now granted
At this point
Where We Are
Present day in 2018
We are not witnessing
But we are
We're witnessing
Terrifyingly absolutely edit something that is so
Solutely
Buy antithetical today
Is stated
Bring it up ever
Just bring it up ever is so f****** crazy
When I listen to this imp
Present date September 2009 Warriors doing this
20 minutes
20 to 20 seconds of Silence
For the Republic I'm like
You son of a b****
The clergy response team
You heard about this
No but I would watch that show
So this all goes back to Mansfield
He's a guy who likes
Call himself Pastor Revere
I heard that no
No no
Stupid warning about the imminent end wa2000
It's not that a bunch of the interview
All of them link back
To an interview
About him
On Prison Planet from May 24th 2006
Written by Paul Joseph Watson
All of it traces back to Alex Jones
Great
All this is based on paranoia about the Bible verse Romans
Which says that all power on earth is
Bestowed its power through God
So that is
Is the give to Caesar what is Caesar's
Side effects of the reversal
Can we get some of the reverse of the versus River
Is can we get some of the verses like removed
Just to like
Indian new Council of Nicea
Just a couple of verses removed
Things change why is it the 14 words
Sentence
People's horrific world.
Well here's the thing
Anti-government crank they were tough time with that scripture because it does
Seem like you should submit to the authorities of the world or whatever
I've been bestowed with through God
Scripture they created an entire
Conspiracy around the government using the scripture
10 list
To pacify their congregation
And get them to accept the New World Order
I can find no concrete evidence of this program
Tell all of the links
The documentary evidence of Paul Joseph Watson article is just
Substantiated rumors this has to do with religion
Stop
And start searching Within
You and your relays
I've got anything searching my heart through a glass Darkly
Everything
Is completely vague and based on Infowars history
Paul Joseph Watson
Weaver's
Confirmation from other preachers and pastors that this program is Nationwide initiative and
A literal Soviet model
Where in the churches are being systematically infiltrated by government volunteers and uses conduits for martial law training and conditioning
The pastor was told that over 13
100 counties are already on board
So that's where Alex gets
Is 13 hundred a number
Mansfield AKA Pastor Revere are assigned by
You didn't know that but it's
It was in the Protestant Reformation
Martin Luther himself set
We will assign passers-by County
If you gerrymander your county line
You will not get
It's all it's all
Oh yeah
And I didn't I didn't know any of that cuz I've always just been like
A bomb
Whatever I just took
What it's like to love I love the name clergy response team though it rolls off my back like water off a duck
Action
I imagine just a series of just like
40 preachers in Convent or something along those lines but with like the Giants
Fire station doors
Like just sitting out there the way firemen do it at 11 p.m. all smoking cigarettes and then to get the call
Clergy I'll put on there
Fireproof mask
Destiny jump into the
Clergy mobile
Sucking response
Alex
Suck this bill is called
McLaren
Response
Checkpoint
Tricks on the street corner control grid
With millions of Americans forced labor camps
Authorizes us
Still not saying the name of the goddamn failed
Alex is not what you to find it
We're going to play a new game on the podcast
Bluetooth
Name the episode that this clip reminds you of
Very very good actually nail this one
North Austin
Real quick that's not the end of the clip holder answer
I think he's snapping at David Knight
I think David nights around but he's not on camera yet the other day
There's so many other day
I just want to follow people's origin stories
Goodnight is old enough
At this point where he wouldn't just accept Alex Jones
David David are you kidding
In my
Headcanon
There's
Barton Creek
Alamo
Call your friend
So Jordan I know ask you
What episode of our podcast
Does that remind you of
It's some it's some number but it's a number that can be
Expressed through letters
It's one of those days
They're taking him to the airport
Shackle
Shackles
Space command is probably involved
The grand prize
Which is a microwave oven we are at 7
Here at lady would have been washing machine
These microphones that are eight
Yeah
Enough money to travel around as a headliner
With only one of those my
Has recycling
2 hours
10 minutes
After you called your
Andrew Pham
Yes
Yeah
At listen to Alex
Discuss
Directions
Street names
Snapit David Knight
What year was the place off of Martin Luther King Junior Drive
Neuropathy
I'm not scared
Anyway Alex finally says the name of the goddamn sucking build
Apologize
Amazon other article here
Legislation authorizing age
HR 645
The name of the Bell
House resolution
This is also known as the National Emergency
Dissenters establishment act we've already gone over this
About 4
Yep and we've read over all of this and it doesn't it doesn't say any of the stuff that Alex
Really thought about it
Need to remind people that
Libertarian
This guy have to die in his home cuz it's cold
Like that sort of Disconnect would apply with a situation like this where in there setting up
Places where in
The terms of a
Large-scale disaster people could be
House
People could be taken care of there could be emerge
Duty services available to them
He's so mad about the idea of it but if that desire New Orleans
Disaster happens and services are available
Huey like
How dare this government. Take care of evil
You know he plays both sides of this
And the only thing that's really important
Consider these roads are a lot
Okay so this episode of Alex Jones Show is
December 8th January 28th
What is a.
6 days after this bill was introduced
HR
645 by representative Hastings
Florida
And you know what
It died in committee
It never got out of committee
Cuz of course it
No of course it didn't because Pastor Revere got the word out
Issue is that
If you scroll down far enough
You find the the amount of money it would cost
And that was
Not all bad
No it's not that bad but people don't want to prioritize that s*** about the name Pastor Rivera
It's not that bad Pinterest
Interesting pivot for you to make
This is
All of this
Is Been A build-up for
This is Alex Jones does he ride a horse
Paul Revere
Anyway
This is
Crazy
We are crazy
This bill
What suggested
Hypnosis
Didn't get out of committee
Didn't even get voted
This is the end of the Republic
Let's have a 22nd
Pause
It hasn't hasn't happened
Consent
It's not like it's happen
Nope
Alex
This is still part of his career
To present day
He still talks about the
Dissenters established
This is a pivotal
In his career
This January 28th to get one of his big
Pieces of propaganda
This might as well be Waco
For him because he's like oh
I got this
Give me the ball coach I'm going to run
I'm going to f****** run like a Forrest Gump
Touchdown keep running
Oh yeah
So
I don't know anyway
Done with Alex
His breakdown
Of this is a bunch of like really
Scary stuff
About the Bell
Here's tries to make everyone really afraid
And then he has an interview with a lawyer
Is he still also spinning like he's the kind of music I would like to the keep
Plate spinning
It was one of those guys look like 45 plates Shopkin plates to the county fair
It so he has one that one from earlier about the lady who spilled her her Bloody Mary on the play
Are kids field 1
To talk about grass
They talk about it
Before eventually become his lawyer
0 there is a zero in the middle of it
In the middle of it Alex Jones
Kind of slips up
Accidentally said something
Did I don't think most people would recognize
Lesbian
Super f***** up
It was not a privilege
Travel
Does that mean anything
Nope
That's because you have not studied
Sovereign
Alex Jones is espousing
Literally a sovereign citizen
Whatever you watch any videos
Getting arrested for not having a f****** driver's license while they're driving
I'm traveling
Did the Constitution guarantees the right to travel
And in quarts
They've decided that what that mean
You have the right
To go between
You're the right to wander about as you see fit
The Sovereign citizen
Believe that if you're not carrying cargo
You're not driving
You're traveling
In an automobile
So therefore you don't need the government
To certify you to be able to
I don't need a license I'm traveling
So there's all these videos I'm driving as I was traveling
How fast do you think you're traveling
I love it
Has like little like
I guess what
We got this loophole
You guys don't have any jurisdiction
Gold actually around flag there's no power in the land of the local sheriff
Play why
The Constitution
Whitley said that
Everybody
Constitution was written when they were cars
And also
Go fuc
But it's it's crazy because Alex like
To pretend that he use
Oliberte
All that stuff
The more we look at it it does seem like
There's more
Similarities of Hammond
These guys who end up
Bucking chute
Yep also from the 28th Alex Jones
Hip hop a little bit
Great
I am
Trouble
Who do you think that is
Is it Terminator X
Is it
Flavor Flav
Check the
4 is a pentagram
Flavor Flav
Spoiler alert
It's a problem for all the
He got kicked out
I'm really sorry about that
Not great not great
You don't like to remember that part of Public Enemy fast
Anyway
It's really interesting is
Overlook
That is the differences and similarities
And I found a
Probably expected
Similarity
Between Alex Jones smoothies
9 years of history and that is
Try to steal fetishizes
Truckers
So
There is little Alex sing along a little bit
You know it is just his like
His eyes
Loving violin
The masturbation to the idea of Justified Violence
I
Can only think
Is
Precursor to
Unjustified
Hours of really wanting
But I know I can't just kill a man
Dreaming of the day where a man gives me a reason
How to kill a man
That's what it is
Like maybe he could sublimate his No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No
He would be way on the side of the Nazi zombies in Call of Duty or was it also one of his big things is
Is that the use of video games
In professional football
Are taking a wave
Warlike Tendencies of
The man
Write in order to like make it so they can't
Fight against the New World Order
Mountain Laurel today
Could we do that
Do that
I would love it
Because
In this next clip
Another similarity to live in Grand Theft Auto
Around La in god mode
Never bother you wants the plot to be
Similar to The Fugitive
But with the game functionality of
Grand Theft Auto
Justly being accused of a crime
And everyone more like more like death wish
He's going for
No
No cousin
3D makes friends with an old Jew that's true that would never
I watch all of them
So glad I could pull that
DoubleTree 3 is the best of that person
I will not stand for anyone arguing.
Enjoyment when it comes to your your pop culture
Trivia gifts probably in the chat room still we watched all five movies back-to-back
That's too they were on I don't know what channel it was on but we had a case of beer
I just got
F***** up
Rock salt
Made a pyramid out of the empty candy that was the best time ever
Time for us to really get into the weeds
Commentary tracks on death wish
Anyway for the 28th year
And if this is again another similarity
Between modern
Alex Jones
Thick f******
That he has
This
This is disturbing on a whole bunch of levels
Levels is
There is a girl a woman
On the phone caller
Who keeps we like
Okay
Oh no she seems a little bit scared of the things that are coming out of Alex's mouth
And rightfully so
Yeah
Bob Hill
Sprouts
Argue with any of them
20 years in prison
What
They're getting shots
Just trying to do our jobs
I know
Torturing people
Thank you Allah
Thank you
That's so f***** up
If if Alex was just doing that alone
That would be really f***** up but the fact that he had someone else on the line
I know
Right
Threat like that is
Profoundly f***** up
That was a that was a college where it was going well until like 11 whenever he started
Doing a lot of cocaine
Senior Life
Oh s*** I'm not going to get
What are anything out of this
From here to hang up
Shitol out
Oh I'm sorry I'm sorry you broke your hand getting really mad about nothing about a bill that doesn't even make it out of committee
But thank you thank you Alex for fighting
To be that
To be Alex
To be both
Fragile
So
We are now onto the 29th
And I want to say one thing real quick
Real clearly
Real public
Yeah
I have received criticism
From the chair
The group
So sensitive
I know I'm not defensive cuz I actually think it's fairly accurate
That we indulge a little too much
And how much
Italics
Business
Criticism
F****** sing-alongs from now and there's an argument to be made like we're dealing with a harsh
Awful propagandists
We're being suckered in by like
This
Right there is an argument to be made to that
My response to that
Is on the 29th
Alex Jones sings the entire song
I Was a Highwayman
I want to be really clear all of it specific reason but also
I want to say this
Like
It's the same song over and over again
Not that like
He keeps singing over other song
Eastbound & Down Silver Stallion
80% of 9
He just has to single-a it's like a guy who goes to
Karaoke every week and does the same song turning me into like
Biking Sasha Banks new theme song
Eventually you just start getting
Inured to it takes on a different context
Here's how I don't work for 3 minutes
Back to it
Wake Forest
Galaxy
Nardis is my grandfather
Okay
3 + minutes of his f****** show that he dedicated
Exit
He did a 22nd
Moment of silence for the death of the Republic
What is there to do
That the end of the Republic
Highway
And I promise you
I'm not being petty being a dick about people saying we played s*** like that too much
I promise there's a Reaper a little bit
I'm going to play later
There's a method to my madness when you things that twice
Yeah just go to break at the end of that just
Alright we're back from break
If he'd heard episodes where he doesn't entire break just doing a
Like he goes from commercial to commercial commercial if he did
Victor singing
Stairway to Heaven
Through weather radio Bryce over the
Where's my book I mean script run Infowars better than we would
We bringing like a professional wrestling sensibility online
Anger on your side
This is why we're not just
For Success Dan we're not know exactly
Interested with reasonable people and just goofin on clown
Clarendon food
Oh God yeah Rev
Freebird would take a break.
That would that would
Hotel California
Clip Alex realizes
Vet like
How long is Hotel California
It is still being recorded
Jetimat draft
Alex realizes he needs backup
The fight is coming and he needs backup
What is coming in
Coronavirus
Saudia
Anything by Michael
McDonald's
Great for Alex's range grapefruit great like Yacht Rock
A varied career boobies
Regulators
Outlook
Alex needs backup
And up to this point
In 2009 what was
I'm seeing is a very anti-cop mentality
Auto Parts
But because cops are a representation of the government overreach
So but on this episode here on January
29th
He realizes
I might need
To get them on my side
And I don't think this
The successful
But
I think the people who manipulate
Can probably heard
This sort of rhetoric coming out of him and used it be like
Love you
And maybe twisted
Because this
This is gray
Your pension fund
Love you
And honor you
The Daughters of Liberty
Republic
Choose
A pressure
Join the republik
Join
Truth
Everything
He does this for another like you might be awhile
Ecos
Disco
Music
Stop baby
Love power
I'm maybe they are not
Ready to get on board
Have good Hearts all man
Snakes and sometimes
I go out by my house that I have to kill a snake
Butt snakes want to bite my family
It goes on for
F****** ever I want to play it all but I'm like
As I was turning the clip sound like
This is a six minute clip of him a rambling trying to be like
Please cops
Because we live in
Cops respond to that by saying
Nah
How about you come over to our side
I love killing black people to
I think if we want to really parsed
Like
Things
That are happening
Wait we can't
Not
Chicken eyes that like
As this is all happening
Initial
Tea Party
First Salvo is already here
And things are are moving
I think I think within the next couple episodes this is my big prediction
We're going to see a lot of these narratives
That we have seen
That surprises
Support for a Ron
The net neutrality
The cop f*** you cops
Kind of stuff go by the wayside
We're going to see it as we get more into
We're going to see that stuff sort of shift
Into a much more familiar Alex Jones
And I think that one of the things
Things that we have to take
Consideration
This clip gives us a little bit of a glimpse into
Is that like
That hr6
That's nothing it's literally
Don't like the idea that he made a mountain out of that molehill to me
Memes
Either like
He is just
Desperate
Latch onto which
Or he needs
A big
And you need an excuse to make a big bow
And I suspect
That this
Is
He uses
2 launcher
Okay
I think that we're going to see that HRC
Even as
You know time goes on
Text couple episodes that we do
Will be
When
It's dying in committee
Wreck it out
It will be what he uses
In order to change
Track a little bit
From this
Support of Palestinian
Support of net neutrality
Support of
Ron
Into
Just being
Straighten line with
What you would
Respect of
I think I'm not entirely sure but that's that's my that's my operating
Thesis right now
I'm ready to be proved wrong
Hypothesis
I'm ready to be wrong
If I ever
Thrilled
Is that vegan
Weirder
Spell generally speaking we have always been
Like there are always two tracks that we
Confirm.
White nationalism Alex is going to Veer towards that
If you had guns Alex we're going to be rude towards that but everything else
It's on like the margins
We always wind up getting it wrong and goes in such a
Estranged
Stupid Direct
There's no way to predict it
Rite-Way
In 2009 and 2010 and you said he would get more
I would give you
You know 100%
In terms of guns
With white National
Little bit
Just because I have listened
Forever
Bike
Our of this podcast we do there's
20 hours
I get a
Sent from Lyft
To him
Villa
Very late racing
You know like even back then
It's not like he's not
A cool dude
But he doesn't
Have the same
Tality that he does now
Or even in 2015 2014 some of the episodes of
We listen to like
There is there is
That happen
I don't know what it is
I hope it's soon
Cuz
Much more interesting
Then
We do three years
We happened sometime in
Weird
So
I know I told you about those old people with their little robotic arm
Handguns
But I
Alright
Left and right
Gun grab Jordan I got to show you this map
I have right here right right right
Are there begun Grabbers in hippogriffs
Hippogriff
So anyway Alex's claims that he has tons of bills
That are being pushed
In order to take
And this is the coverage of the gives for it
Seminole
Record
Firearms owners also required to report all gun transfers even those other phone number
Titles
He never mentions any of the other night
We now know
Also we do that
Because of how Amanda
Let's work
House resolution on
Additional
Because everytime a bell go through
Through the elaborate process of undoing an event language
Parts of the state
Why do we still have those
Alex pretends that like
Hey if you get us on a technicality with a bill this amendments done
It's so stupid gives no understanding of civics
Now hr45
From 2000
I hear from factcheck.org
If elected it would require a federal license
To own any handgun or any semiahmoo
Automatic firearms
Except
Any detachable ammunition feeding
It has a single sponsor
Representative Bobby Rush
Chicago
It was introduced on the first day of the new car
And on February 9th it was referred
Is a routine matter
As of February 20th
Still sitting
With no action sketch
So
Also real quick
Bobby Rush introduced the same legislation
June
HR 2666
Yeah it wasn't wrong
It was Bobby Rush
Quietly in the house
Committee on crime terrorism and Homeland Security
Like all day
Subcommittee where hr45
Now reside
The people who need gun control die loudly in gun control bills.
Subcommittee
Pretty f****** screams bad and yells back
It's just random ass politicians right to build
Get some sort of
Like that
I don't know Bobby Rush I don't know his career
But there's a
These impossibility that he was like
Someone's got to do it
The bill out and if it fails it fails but I did what I could write
I don't know if that's what I'm going to
Did I when I leave Congress
I'm going to atleast be able to stay I f****** gave it a go
I put a lot of calls they were f****** dicks because America
Could be like like you say
Jaded
Like
I know that what Alex is saying
A decent number of congressmen
Every every year they're like
And now I'm repping this bill and throwing this back out there like it could just be one of
What happens all the time is that
I don't know if you was in
Before
So it might have been his
Rodeo
But
Yeah that does have
What happens if
Any idea that Alex
Presenting this is why
This is a scary thing
This exact same
If it's the same thing
If you said that I respected more
In his worldview like a globalist
Control Barack Obama
And George W bush so
He doesn't see a difference
Only in terms
The blackface
Jordan I know I told you earlier
That
We listen to that entire Highwaymen
Windsong for a reason
And that reason
He tries to sing along with the rest of hurt
He doesn't realize how long
That's right.
Okay cuz he's waiting like
You tries to sing along with it
And he's never
It's the right Mark at all
But it just goes on and on and then at the end of the
Great
Alex you know that was a nine inch nails song
First right
IMEI Maybe eunos
Cover
Spectacular
I'm really emotional it's coming from Johnny Cash late in his career like he was
Intex
That is the definitive version of
The song
I don't think that Reznor's version
Is better than
Video music
Covers are much more
Like residence
But All Along the Watchtower
Write with plenty of I-40 Bruce Springsteen
Acoustic
Nirvana cover of the meat puppet
Sure yeah that one was a big deal
Show up
This the rest of the episodes of three more clips
And the rest of them are like
What I would describe as like
Liquors
Alex Jones is salesman
Ship from the
The present
Starting to manifest
And it's really interesting because it
Alex likes
The cell survival
Speedvault
I think this what we're seeing is a survivalist camp
This is a seed
Cuz they come up every year without you having
Listen to this phone
Can clip
And tell me that this
Is not
What will grow into the
The plant of Infowars sales
Nice metaphor
He's just gotten out of like AIDS other letter
Efoodsdirect food.com
Yeah but like he's gotten out of like a two-minute about how great they are
3-day survival pack weather
Seafood
Melago
Special
Sounds right
What the fuk was that
Yes of course they are telling us that they're not going to give her if you were willing to fire on Americans
You get a promotion if you're not you're going overseas they're putting it on the front to die because you're not waiting
By the way
Wow there is no need spectacular no need to book with another plug for your
Sponsor
Unless you're doing it
In order to make people scared
Let's get to the spot
Have they started
I haven't
This is this is a month
In
To what I've been listen
In 2000
29th
Listen to a full month
And I've not really seen that mentality
Am I saying it didn't exist before
He may have you met only employee.
Something like that that's entirely possible
But
It's
F***** up
To see it cuz it
Clumsy
Back that you know what's interesting
He's much better now
Anybody ever considered calling their Bluff
On what
The gun thing
Letgo
I think we should not give them quarter
I think they've actually been telling us this whole time that the only way for us to get rid of gun
Call their Bluff on this dumb bulshit
And just do what they say and then they'll find out throat
So in this next
Anderson
He's run out of everybody else me literally
Literally Alex is saying
The Ted is selling
For what he
Bought it for
Am I
That's not a business
I don't know where the barge
If you're just selling it for what you bought it for and you're telling people like
Oh it's amazing it's worth much more now but I can sell it to you for this cuz I bought it for
You don't
You make any
And
Is it
It's a promotional cost
Is it promote you bring out the promotion
It's a buy-one-get-one
I will give you one of these gold for 8:30
Whatever whatever that is
Going to have to get it
Whatever what is the price I don't know I don't know
Matter because
Research
Turn off of there like
Customer reviews to know that like
All of the prices that they say
Huge Market
Fees
And s*** like that
You couldn't buy it
Yourself Sarah Middleman
We've had a lot of fun here we've heard Alex Jones
Sing along with Ian's
Tire highway
Stop singing There's a delay
We've heard him freak out
Tire show about a bill
It's a bill that died
MIDI
This
To me is one of the funniest thing
He
He's screaming about the New World Order
In about
But
Watch
This
This pivot
It's not like our tartar normal add pivots
To where it's like
Smoking stupid
Briefly
Is it the Proto version
Listen to this
Incremental
Total land
Well I'm still offering the stuff from 8:30 I got that around still do pranks I have a
I'll give you an idea right
Is the whiplash
What the f***
What's your deal
What is it gold
I'd like the I like the Ted catches it
We got but we got to run through this let's go let's go it's 8:30 on the goldfrank's his ain't there it's 240 on the Dutch
That's fair
It's okay
Crazy cuz like
Did the reality of this is like we go back 2019
We see like
Disgusting
Well s*** going on receive the scam happy
I just I
I don't know
Cash4Gold started
The guy on the Grapevine
Works for Ted Anderson
From what I understand
Midas resources and a lot of other businesses like
Get what they would do if they would think they would sell you
You gold but you didn't get the
The gold
Unless you wanted to hold on
Unless you want to take it out of their V
You would pay them if they would store the gold
And he would have it
Like if you if you call
It from what I understand
From what I understand
Hold on there's a lot of businesses that
Work
There were a ton of
Most of them
But a lot of
But there's a lot of precious metals businesses that had like
We have it all involved will send you pictures of it
This is a and if you call but also if you if you
You want
Withdraw
We will send you your booyah
Well then yeah
But a lot of people
Ozone
To some extent
Kind of like the wave it like
Banks
Filoli
10% deposit on hand
I don't know
That's true at all I was just trying to be cool
I like it I like it
Breakdown
Do you have a code
Not been great for me in terms of like May
Making great point on the wrong side
A couple times
But do that
Either I've been right pretty much this whole weapons
Especially when I said we should kill everybody who owns guns
Fairing
Hey
This has been a lot of fun I love I love
The 28th
So much
The terms of life
Alex panda
2 hours
Building up
The reveal The Prestige
Article by Paul Jose
Joseph Watson
Oh by the way in post do you want to go back
Can put in it as saying we're going to hold 20 seconds
The silence before the 22nd
Kings Island
Now you know what I had that
Way2go
I would like to give out our website
For that
20 seconds of Silence
Yeah
Play
Dismount when it comes to pot
If possible we're also on Twitter
That's correct. We are on
That's where we are going to go to
You can download you can leave a review
Can tell your family if you want your friend if you are at a stoplight and you throw your phone and somebody else
State is playing knowledge fight and it connects to their Bluetooth
And then begin playing are podcasts
That's that's
If you would like to
I'm also
Like a like us on Facebook
Good on you
Join our Facebook
Cuz I don't post all that much
In the Facebook page
You replied everything it's all about the group
Really
That's where that's where everything happens
Go home and tell your mother you're broiling it does really where the action happens
Here's what I mean
I mean like
There's not many side
Characters
Along the way
Get to the gone go f*** yourself award
Themselves
I'm at Snapchat Kevin and that guy who is gotten season
Desist letters from
First nations in Canada
And still try to make money off.
You're stuck
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work