Alexandra Thurston color
Drones
Dan
Very aggressively
Play today
Damn
Okay alright
You can't make noise when we're playing charades
Going to try and do this.
Very visual media podcast
I'd like I can respond to you like
Yes and noises but I can't
And you don't know anything about Alex Jones
No exceptions
Probably
Messages
I've ever gotten from anybody
Squeeze covers
Okay
Needed to send us a message with Alex Jones
Turned on Trump
Ben said that he shows Isis up his dirty a******* that was going to be an emergency
We're going to be going over Friday May 25th 2018
Zimos
People gotten
Give a thank you out to hit something happen
Yeah it's
Sunday recording this is completely out of
With my schedule
It did it get better
Emails about button
Is there a coming
Emails
Some stuff this month along with your
Being busy with the club nightclub
EXO
A terrible about correspondence
This the first I don't have
I will just give a shout out
First person who did
Dakota
Pointing this out policy walk Dakota
We appreciate Saki
Keep your eyes and ears open
I will withhold my fix
To new donor
Someone who just signed up
Connor
Thank you so much
The Highlander reference my friend the B comes back
Something is much better than
Highland
Highlander 2 is one of the weirdest
15 years I've seen it so I cannot answer a question
The different movie and they were like
The Highlander
Another said I would like to give
Is someone who
Quickest way to work
Episode
She's wonderful
She's been around for
So supportive
Send some really nice emails and
What's the best
Out there
Maria you're now a Raptor Ford
Kelly Aprilia
Has a Caribbean
Control
Abused by white people
Where Joseph Stalin
Welcome to McDonalds may I help you I'm baby Saunders
Thank you so much Maria
We really appreciate
And if you
They're listening and you like sport to show you don't know exactly how you can check out our website
Sports Chalet
Anyway
It's not a complicated process not at all
And I would like to say
For the listeners
I need your help about this thank you
I've been getting criticism
From people who watch the live stream
Thing to you and because you they were saying it to you you're like
I agree with you I think it would be nice
Mean criticism it away
Okay
A literary criticism
You and I having a conversation
Could be an argument that we're not fighting
Connotations that it might otherwise
And I would like to let you know
Yes I am
When is episode comes out
7 days
No cigarettes
Congratulate
Thank you
So
Number people who suggested
I'm really criticism that's like let me translate it
We love you
Nobody is
Sent me that message so I think everybody don't know
Baby keep going
I think the messages on the chat room during the live show
Combined
I would like to
People who sent two messages that have been encouraging that direction.
Is it a moment where I'm like
I don't need to
Tool anymore
I don't want to
That's that's some self-actualization
Thank you a lot of messages
Couple
Since your urges
D'smoke
In that recording is 6 days
The worst friend
My schedule
Able to talk this week because of your shows and
Terrible
I've been working
1820 hour days on
Some research
I'm in
It's so
But yeah it's it's
It's it's
I don't know what else to say
No no no
Here's what it was
The issues that I'm
I'm realizing that
About a week ago or so
Is it I have an opportunity that's unlike
An opportunity that will ever come up in my life ever again
It's an opportunity that most
People don't
Have ever
Going to Austin on June 15th
Already
It's terrible
Alright
It's not that although that is a piece
It's that we've created a thing and people have responded to it in such a way that they've been very supportive
And I'm able to make my job
Doing this
I get to live
The life that I desire to live
I don't have to have a ball
Anything like that other than
You know
Stopping smoking when The Listener say you should stop now
Jeff
Really want
Live up to the
I'm starting to record
Recognize and
Appreciate that
The situation that I'm in
And made a lot of excuses
In the past don't fly
The idea of it like
Oh I don't have time to meditate
You know what the fuc why do you don't have to sit on
2 hours of the train to get to and from work at straddle have that can
Oh I don't have time
Record my dreams what I wake up in the morning and ordered it
Advanced dream recalls so I can get back to the days when I
Used to be able to lucid dream
Alright. Making
I don't have the time to
Stop smoking
Aldi's
All these things
Aspired to whether it's
Take time or effort
I have the ability to do those things
It'll be disrespectful to myself
Everybody
We're all watching you grow as a person
Beautiful
I'm lighting two cigarettes for you
Heroin
I got to go
Dewberry Cooper
Jordan let's get this started out of
Text dropped from
Today's episode
Alright alright
Alright
Amp
Alright alright of us for this episode
Oh man
This is
Comment on the our Facebook group
Go home
Brilliant
I've listened to hundreds of episodes of Alex Jones
The show I've never heard any
Notion
There's something that happens on this episode
That is
The real on the level that
Is not to be believed
And once I explain why it makes sense
It does make
What he says
No he's crazy
Black fox
Looks like it's just take a snap
Shot of what happens on this episode
You'd be like
Well I'll be damned
You be very confused
Put on closer analysis
Baymax totals
Alright
We have a bit of rhetoric.
Get through before we leave
More lies
You take the bag
What do you have last year
Spoiler alert
Involved
Krs-1 is back
It's not okay
It's about
Very different
First ever going to listen to
But Alex says which is
Yo it's fun to
Check in on that a little bit
Here's the first one he's rambling about how
The globalist world for robots
The future that's being built
Robot
Shut up
Where is a post
Human
Global
Compaq
The Fortune 100
Has warned you about nope
Nope
It's what the Unabomber it was in the MKUltra
Mind control programs volunteer
FedEx
Call the revolution against
Technology
Emily closet
There's
Reclassification
Of the CIA rondomedia
Asian
Conspiracy theory
I thought we should show all this for people
Right now
He was making all this
I was going to say that seems a little redundant
The plan
Eteri
If you know and bold plan
Verbally
But on the page get it
This is something
I'm talking about being like this
Just been to class
Trump didn't release most
The JFK
He did
Involve this
Set all like
And we've already had the planetary plan for a long time
Interplanetary plan
This is the reason
So this is a common argument
Conspiracy theorist
CIA either created or popularized or redefined
I'm confused
There are a lot of whores there I got to be literally anything
Probably
Where each of those
School of thought there's this school of thought whatever
Aluminum foil
This was all in the wake of the jfkfc
The reason
In order to discredit anyone
Disagree with the findings
Almost uniformly they point to CIA document
Dispatch 1035 Dash 960
Which is released as part of the question
Made by the New York Times
It does include the work
It does suggest ways
The folks
Conspiracies
About Oswald
But a close reading
Not reveal that it says that we should quote
Make the
Conspiracy theorist popular in order to discredit critics
Which is the allegation
Child are called Atkins
So this
It's just something that people are taken out of a tax
Cleon Warren
This is
Could you read the dispatch
It's very clearly a document
I meant for non-domestic
Accused
Which is with the CIA
And based on what is in this document
You'd really
Have to be
Kind of dumb or intentionally obtuse to not recognize that this is about 4 in
Guess what like that
That's where we live
Acknowledge
Are we are really important
Quotes from that should be
Pretty illuminate
What this is about
Of such seriousness
Affects only the individual concerned
But also the whole reputation of the American gov
American government
Being reflect
In the eyes of foreign
Where possible
Counter speculation by encouraging referee
Conditions report
Itself
Where possible
Counter speculation by encouraging reference
The commission's report
Open-minded foreign readers
Should still be impressed by the care thoroughness
Objectivity of speed with which
Mission work
Put it in a manual possible
.2 proof
Yeah exactly what we have.
Speculation
Point
Primary sources
Some attempt to
Did the u.s. government
In foreign country
Which falls under the
CIA perv
Whether you disagree with them existing
In the first place or not
I think there's an interesting argument
You could have
They're in there
Realm
What's important the scope of practice
The nearest it existed in its current form
Something absurd like 880 or something like that would be great
Under that lease right now
Oxford English Dictionary
The earliest reference
Can Liars earliest reference listed in there is 18
Okay
The CIA was formed in 1947 so that makes
The idea that they created
Popularized
Again seems impossible
I'm going back to the late 1800s
I've been using such diverse settings
Theosophical journals
Brother talking about Helena blavatsky
Is that being a
Conspiracy
The popularly known widely used term for over
It was the same
Used whatever the rich people try to assassinate
Yeah I prefer
Alex
At this point if I ever had an argument
Operation Mockingbird
Alright
Let's Get It On operation Mockingbird
I understand
You believe that operation Mockingbird is about to
CIA taking over the midianite
But unfortunately that is not what it was
A 2007 report called Family Jewels
Was decline
Yeah
The CIA had done that would probably be considered illegal
In the report there was mention of
Project Mockingbird which was described as.
Project Mockingbird a telephone intercept activity was conducted
Queen 12th of March
And 15th of June 19th
Hampton Bays newsman who at the time had been publishing news articles based on
And frequently quoted classified materials of this agency
And others
Top secret and special intelligence
Trying to answer
How they had top-secret Intel
This makes the name of the operation
Mockingbirds are primarily known for
Just at the CIA
Reason to believe
These journalists
And information
So
Alex was actually talking about
Horrible expose on that
That just Monster attic
Emporium
Give a smoke
F****** stupid of me
Figurin say
The CIA doesn't have relationships
All I'm saying is
Yelling
Project Mockingbird and s***
That doesn't match up with reality
So
The CIA has him repeating something before that without actually knowing what he's talking about
Perfectly committee
Laid out most
They maintain the network of several hundred foreigners who they used to
Of foreign countries
Which again I'm not into
But it is what they are for
I don't know
So in this in this situation it's less like the crafted more like they're running PR
Propaganda
Foreign propaganda
Respectful to the people of those countries but whatever
Iowa
They also found
Approximately
The agency
These assets are individual American journalists or employees
The US media organization
But it's important
Consider the context
Comes later
In the document
Bring up is that about half of those people are actually employees
Media companies are freelance
Alright
Article 2 hours
But also this is
Is super important
More than a dozen United States news organizations
And Commercial
Publishing houses
Formerly provided cover for CIA agent
Abroad
A few of these organizations were unaware that they provided
Discover
A lot of the intersection
To the CIA and the media is this
CIA using me
Media organization
His unwitting cover stories for their ages
Either way this is far more complicated than sayings
Took over
Operating
Plain Sight music
Protect themselves
Hip
Overlapping
The CIA trying to
Infiltrate the media in order to
Put stories
Through that serves their
Domestically
Or it could be
I get a job I worked with
CIA I get a job with Time Magazine
In order for it to make sense
For me to be overseas
Navigation no one
Gets really
Suspicious about it because I work
Overtime
This doesn't bother me so much because I would prefer
There are still spot
Lego
With no States like nobody is going to win or lose it's just
Ocean's 11 spy craft fair
The world is more fun place
Rifling through
Through trash trying to find Denny's ism
Documents or whatever
A smash-and-grab job
Is no fun
Nautilus
Create or popularize or telemedia to use
That's all load of horseshit
Dispatch document to use
To say that it means anything
It's all its I hate
Torture as
The director
That would be like not appointed Oliver North
To be the head of the NRA
Meet I have to sit here and explain like
You're not bad on this one
You're wrong about that
Yeah I am pretty pretentious
The things because
The CIA does
To dislike me CIA because they can't be like
We love the CIA
That's a good point
Ime Nelson talked about it lately
But he has been
Pretty consistent generally over
He's also dumb
Real dumb
But make no mistake
Being indicted for multiple felony counts of rape
Sexual abuse
Torture basically
That's all because of
Hollywood to the bully
Donald John Trump
From CIA MI6
Army
After
Sex trafficking
He just talked about this earlier
I Hold On
Not just the gardener ride
Weinstein on the plane
Express
What has been convicted of trafficking young girls to his
She's trying to come up with the name Jeffrey Epstein
But he can't come up
Because you just
Why isn't why isn't pulling Allison Mack
He does bring it up later but he says like I know you absolute
Lilly did not son-of-a-b****
Based on this clip and the insane
Insane thing that you just said
Way he might be correct
No yes no yes
Alright
So
By electing Donald Trump
Women realize
F****** no one's come
So we might as well have two
Do this s*** ourselves
It's not like Trump helped it is but he's caused it
With his evil evil evil
We have a lot to get
I find a lot of that
Be pretty on taste
Compelling of but also
I think that you know there are people who
Tried to speak up about it before and were threatened by Mossad agent
Victor your Weinstein and hired a chick like that
Yeah so there's like
View spying on people and stalking them and s*** like that
Bring up heavy always talks about how Clinton was on
With Epstein body
I realize we never actually really disgusting
The details of it
Went and looked it up
I looked into it I researched this
Little bit about the friendship
Donald Trump
And Jeffrey Epstein
The Lolita Express that Alex talks about
All the time
Like a phone back over Bill Clinton's head
This is from the New York Magazine article called Jeffrey Epstein International Money Man of Mystery
The came out in 2002
6 years before it was revealed that he was a guy who like to lure underage girls to his mansion
Quote
Steve likes to tell people that he's a loner
Americans never touched alcohol or drugs
It's far from energetic
And yet if you talk to Donald Trump
A different apps
Christina merges
Quote for 15 years
Terrific guy
Trump booms from a speakerphone
He likes beautiful women as much as I do
It's even said that he likes beautiful women as much as I do and many of them are on the younger side
No doubt about it
Jeffrey enjoys his social life
He's a pedophile
I am not going to say something incriminating right now
And I'm always there while he's there with young women
Come over me
I am a pedophile too
So this is from 2000 to curious before it was public knowledge that he was a pedophile
Play no
I mean who knows all the specifics
@donaldtrump
You know that he knows
So
From November 29th
In a previously unreported comment to the now-defunct maximum Golf Magazine Donald Trump singled out
Imagine why that way
Nothing in the world likes
First-rate p****
Okay
Alright the remark never made its way to print as a top
Ain't nothing maximum golfer
Maximum golf hitting brakes
Multi-story
A top editor of the magazine forbade the reporter from putting it in the public
The former journalist who wrote the article Michael Corcoran and another editor both confirm that it was said by Trump is Corcoran followed
Autumn around
It is Florida golf club for a profile
A 2000 Corcoran with a guest on Trump 727 that
That weekend
He wasn't the only one
The article published in maximum golf
Magazine notes Trump had to wait at the Marine
Terminal 4
Disgrace pedophile billionaire Jeffrey Epstein
Any society gal pal Miss Maxwell
Who is Ice Cube
Doesn't abide
Slavery
Corcoran know the parrot the time remembers Trump standing in the doorway of the plane yelling to them
You broke the cardinal rule Jeffrey never be late for someone else's playing
Do not mentioned in the article
Do not mention
Not mentioned in the article Corcoran now recalls a young woman boarding with
Quote
I honestly couldn't guess her age but she was
Young made to look up a bit older
He says untoward happened during the
Safelite
Friendship with Epstein isn't news
Before the mysterious financier was jailed for operating a sexual pyramids
Steam were allegedly paid minors around $200 for sex
Massages
That included groping and rape
Epstein was a regular at Mar-A-Lago and had to a sworn deposition
Confirm Epstein's brother
Fairy the future president at least once on his plane
Is never been reported that Trump return
A favor
Now here is from a New York daily news article that came out on March
21st
17 headline
Labor nominee reportedly made Court deal with notorious billionaire sex offender Jeffrey Epstein
Epstein a billionaire money manager
What's in prison after pleading guilty to one count
Soliciting an underage girl for prostitution in 2008
Court papers show
The relatively light
Prompted widespread outrage
Federal prosecutors
Had alleged
64 year old Epstein sexually abused at least 40 girls some of them who are apparently as young as 13
Epstein's brief was a result of
13 month
For that
For what he was well interesting it was
Not okay
Sentence there my man his brief prison stick was the result of a non-prosecution agreement drawn up by Trump's labor pic
Alexander Acosta
Put the time served
Does the US attorney in Miami The Washington Post first reported on Tuesday
Trump's first labor secretary nominee Andrew puzder
Pulled his name from consideration last month
I've been accused of domestic
Violence by his ex-wife
He has the best people
The best people
Can't we actually like
With this
Isn't it
Illegal for the cops
To seize all of their property
Like if you can steal somebody's house because somebody had some weed in there
If
Epstein was at Mar-A-Lago
Running a sex ring guess what
We get Mar-A-Lago now
Are you
It's there is no billionaire billionaire
Through of file
And you don't find some horrifying crime
Billionaire you're already a criminal
If if that
It's real bad
Dammit
Physically now I want to
Chew on Donald Trump
F****** like we're clearly
Pretty good friends
Years
Girl clearly as far back as 2000
To he was aware that
You'd like an 15 years before that
Yep
Flying by yourself
And that didn't stop him from being friends with him
They had that he was a regular at Mar-A-Lago we're actually one of the people who worked at Mar-A-Lago
Has accused
Miss Maxwell
Of trying
To recruit her
Movie sex operation
Great while she worked at Mar-A-Lago
So there's all this and then you have the guy who cut a deal for everything to not have to do much
Prison time
Mysteriously getting picked
SB labor secretary
Coincidence bright absolutely a coincidence
Present
You're into
Little bit
Help me out you home
This is the most blatantly
I think we've ever had
R s r s
The Teapot Dome scandal like what it was
Talking about this is the most
Blatantly criminal organization that ever run
Yeah that's not good
Some stuff it's just about
I can't skip it though
I'll just not get into it as
This is important
Cuz Alex reveals who won of the
The sources
Of information is
Cast of child traffickers pedophiles
All over the country
Who did I tell you
No don't say it
Don't say it
That Erik Prince
What's quarterback
This move the front window
Guess the former founder Blackwater
Criminal
So just for fun Alex
You know
Blackwater
If you go back to 2009
Keep f****** hates them
He calls them
Murdering scum bags
He's right into the other night goes on and on about how they're committed war crimes
Sounds much like your muttering a second ago
Yeah it's insane
F*** you
You mean
I just want anybody just actually f****** believe everything
Why can't he at least still believe that
Can't you give me one f****** thing that you actually f****** believe in no I just everything every
Something happened
God dammit as we go through the Pam don't worry about
Don't worry about it I've got you covered all right
I looked at it as I search the entirety breitbart's back catalog can only find one article
It's relevant at all to the
The topic today
Talking about
That involves Erik Prince
The came out in November
It's from November 4th
Not 2017
Funny wieners laugh
Revealing maybe there are inside forces
Involved
2 / dramaticized
In order to force
Applications that article and read
Slimy piece of s*** he is he's a f******
Garbage man
Kind of sound
True like listen to this
Weiner and Huma Aberdeen his wife the closest adviser of Hillary Clinton for 20 years have both
Flipped
Like you saying s*** like that that didn't happen
He's lying he's creating a false reality
Anyway he is a man who never was never born with a heart and where his brain is supposed
To be there is a garbage bag filled with
Also in other news
Donald Trump got played like a pro by North Korea
You didn't understand that
The new Clear Eyes
Unilateral disarmament
Current never have currently there's a better chance of North Korea becoming
A better Ally to South Korea than us
Entirely possible
South Korea's in like 2 seconds
Maybe the reason that we've been fighting this long is because America's f****** garbage
Are they the ones
Maybe we should be more like
That's really the only way for them to stay safe
Is Sturgis
Bail on America and be like
Better
So drunk that really Patty and decided
Cancel
Himself and Kim Jeong Hoon hilarious
Summit
Do the John Bolton
That's interesting I mean blow up the pump
Nuclear testing site
Look and confirm whether or not that destroyed their nuclear
But here's the thing
Where's that reason and others
It's absurd to say that this is a victory
To you from an article in the independent
From an article that came out on November 2nd
In 2070
A report that North Korea's nuclear testing
Spheres of the major radiation
At least 100 workers at the Geary
Nuclear site are feared to have died in the accident that happened around
10th of September
Following tourism 6
Atomic test
Earlier that
Japanese broadcaster TV
Asahi reported
Then go a little bit further into the future
A visit from CNN
North Korea announced on April 20th that the country had quote realize nuclear weaponization
I would no longer need to test nuclear weapons
To demonstrate its commitment it said it would destroy the nuclear test
No weapons inspectors or nonproliferation experts were invited to witness the event of the
Destruction that happened a couple of days ago
Here in present day
It was unclear whether the explosion
Brenda tunnel inoperable or only cause limited damage
Before Thursday's explosions experts had warned that the total Destruction
Destroy valuable evidence
The state of North Korea
Programs
Examples
As well as radiation counters to assess the levels in the atmosphere
Turn off two attempted to take radiation measuring equipment to North Korea said it was
Also
We have no idea if that was their only nuclear test
We don't have any really solid until the
Since about what they're up to
So celebrate
Foolish
I think I think maybe we're only at put up a banner that says mission accomplished levels it could
Birmingham
I'm sorry I'm rushing through
Some of the stuff because
I do think it's important to deal with the narratives that he has
But we do also need a good chunk
Go time to go over
Most important part which is the interview that we're about to get to but for now we have to listen to this
And this is Alex lying about
Democratically
15 months ago
Point of order
Don't think about it
He said quote
Alex
Clearly
He didn't say that
Responded to Trump's threats to impose heavily
Tariffs on steel and aluminum
Imported
This would have been
Majorly
Disruptive dominions
Streets after the German auto manufacturing industry represents about a fifth of the country's export
What Yonkers said was
Quote
We will continue our negotiations
The United States but we refused to negotiate under
So in response to Trump's proposal some people in the EU started preparing for a trade War
From the Chicago Tribune
Quotes
EU trade commissioner Cecilia Malmstrom
Perfect man
Great names for the Maelstrom
Malmstrom
I like cheese I like to f*** Lowe's whirlpool
Like yeah
You are the right person for this
Really close to maelstrom
Said Wednesday that the EU is circulating among
Hmong member states
The list of u.s. goods to Target
So they can respond as quickly as possible
The state of trade War
Is another quote is also
From yogurt
This is stupid process
The fact that we have to do this
But we have to do it
We can also do stupid
Little bit of a difference
What would Alex
You're just saying
Countries
Threatened
Okay well I guess we have to trade for then so we might as well be prepared you guys are
F****** stupid so
Zombie I got a response time cuz otherwise
Economy
I know I am is next Clippers have done at the way you called America children
America
Wet
Play this clip in
Is
Shocking
Supposed to get there but
Hereditary grandson are the most powerful
I don't care I made so is the store Yonkers
A part of New York
Yonkers
I don't I don't
I don't care anymore about these your descending
Promenade
Stuff I don't really care anymore
Yeah cuz you're not
Alex and you are
Confederate royalty rights
So I mean like
Don't care I don't care who
The sins of the father don't fall to the sun unless the
The sun carries up the work of the father
That's how I recorded I just don't care anymore
Stupid
Can you put this in Limerick format
Spell check
We've been completely sold out.
What
A crush
What was that you could have just not done it
Legitimately think that's probably a Freudian slip normally would say is weird
Public is going to defeat you
Whatever it is
It's about time
Central Time Zone
Russia will defeat you
Just doesn't feel good doesn't feel good
Problems with us
Stupid these people
Colluding with other foreign powers
People are employed with foreign governments
Man do I love this one that seems to hate our country
Also by the way
I understand why all the
This is happening now piece of information
From 2009 that I think that we have
We got a Smoking Gun
I don't think Alex is into America
That's
I don't think Alex likes America
At least we agree on something and I think that's why you likes Rush
I don't like America either
Everything is
REI
But I don't know how to I don't know how to say this
Things it's very consistent
He's a bigot
And I hear you
Being thrown out of movie quote
It might not be working
Allied with a 1.1.3
Years ago
It's insane
Most important
Smooth
Smooth smooth smooth
Muslims are
Increasing by 500% every 3 years or 100
1.8 + 500 million
Yeah
Wait no
I'm profoundly unmoved by these demographic
At that rate
In only 30 years
Everyone on the planet will be abuzz
I don't care
I learned something that you should care
Wanted like you know
Let's say there's climate change and then there's
A lot of Isla
Those are the two things
Worry about right now
Not going to lie
The entire planet
That's too much must I agree with you that's the one time I will admit
There's too many
I agree with you on that but I would also say that like
A lot of the versions of Christianity that are around right now I don't want
I want any more of them are already
I don't want more of the Christianity that existed let's play
Hundred years ago whatever you do like I don't
I don't think that's great
I think we all have a long ways to go in terms of becoming the ideal people that we want to be whether Christian Muslim
Atheistic
Secluded
I believe it's 75 or 80 per-cent of Evangelical
Do Christians really support what Isis doing right now so
So I don't like I don't like Christianity
Not great
The other thing Tuesday like as well although I will admit Christ did say in Matthew 10
Get them f****** out of here
I grew up my dad's a religious studies professor and as such I grew up around
People of different faiths and different
Cultural heritage is in like right
Globalist
You sure I go to the mosque
In town from time to time
I knew Muslim kids
Growing up
I don't know if we had any in Columbia
I really had to of but I was unaware of them
They must have they didn't tell me about it
It's where the Muslim
The reason I bring this up is but like
Childhood and throughout my formative years I could very
Easily imagine myself
Dating
Someone
From like a muzzle
I could see myself marrying that person
See myself having kids with them
Event
What
Vismai
Kid any less my identity
Culture
Natural disaster demographic shifting or so
Something like that
Is
Zoe's
Because it's the exact opposite of America the entire history
America is
Doesn't matter where you come from
You get folded into our culture and our culture
Becomes better Ford and
F****** like our culture gif
In-country culture doesn't go anywhere all culture only get
Bigger and more beautiful
It's a trade that we do it's like you come here and we all absorb into America
And then what you get
Play The Promise
From that is that we will also celebrate your culture
Book value whatever you have
And you've brought to the table
And that's just that's something that to demographic
Cliff numbers and all this b*******
Stupid it's a part of the
The social contract that I think America has lost its way on
A little bit
Islamic culture
He's also been built
America's garbage
America created Erik Prince
We're back
There's old like you
There's
Cultures that we just have
Left
Hanging
Finish the high-five with
I would probably save the very first one that was in America
Closer you are or further away you are from
Visual eBay
The last chance you have of America
Celebrating your culture in a
Right because I guess
I got I mean like
People do celebrate Cinco de Mayo
Wrongly
Autocorrect
Not go any further with this thought just to save it
This is stupid
I hate I hate the idea that Alex
Muslims and I also hate that
That is somehow
Game over
That's
America has backup of
Against the wall
How's the talk about it
But alright
Now we are facing
As American
Socialist
Muslim
Hollywood
Famous country
They're up against
Everything
They are winning
They're making all this
Ridiculous
You don't want to miss
I'm greasy
And believe me
This individual was one of the biggest news stories this week
I think I'll tell you at
Start
Of the next hour
He will then be in studio
Very
Excited
About this
Attracted
The guy
She's not from Austin
Any idea who he's talking about
Flying down here
Not from Austin
Not for me
Heroes who protected the teacher
3 bullets
Protecting students
In our other mass shooting
It's not that it's not
No he actually does pay the color Kaepernick's a little loser on this episode
You know who is that
Alex's death
He's the fella who got
Evicted
Videos
Discussion
Free Speech lawyers in country
Jaundice
Is happening
I seriously I've ever read the headline of the story 30 times and I was like
Nah not clicking Miss no no
Don't need to know it
Doesn't matter
All right so why did he get evicted
To leave
Kennywood
He's 30
They gave him notice
A bunch of times and try to get
I did not realize that
Where my parents are my friends are like you got to go I'd be like s*** I guess I have
To go I didn't realize you could just be like
Still living together while they were
Stick it up
Turn this country to the Gravel Pit look here's the thing
Fixing media I think is being derelict
Give its Duty there's a couple places that I've seen that reported this well
Other people have not
A lot of people are reporting this as like
This guy is a representation of the Millennials and they're entitled and pick they deserve
Is crazy
Crazy cuz if somehow like did he doesn't belong
Conservative in his own reporting
But she doesn't belong
Sadie's crazy cuz that's like judging mental illness and what have you put
He is mentally ill
He is someone who and also is a
Buckhead
Much bigger issues to deal with him like he's some sort of a Healer
Serious look at this f****** loser what is doing a disservice to
To the truth it's doing a disservice to this
It's really insulting to this guy's parents
Who we don't really know what their position on it is
Because they've been trying to stay out of the
Spotlight
They don't want to deal with
This being a media Zoo
They probably don't want their
Kid to have to
To deal with that either
Although he's courting the Press
Yeah and
Until like the various aspects
But this story really really
Really trouble
And the idea that Alex
Has him on
And behaves the way he does
God dammit
This is the weirdest thing I've ever seen in my life
This is one of the weirdest things I've ever seen on Alex's show
F****** with
If this turns out to be a weird dad pivot for
Bunker's what you can hide from your parents while living under these their basement I'm going to f****** lose my mind
That would be
Pivot of all time
But
Before we get there we got to listen to
This guy Marquan.
Who's a lawyer
C'Mon mostly just to talk about all the lawsuits against
Free legal advice
Like reassurance but you're right
I guess
At the end actually I was like
I'm thinking about countersuing
Let me know if you want to
Explorer slapback provisions
I never tell people.
You have to understand what
He's doing is like
I was like
Should I
Hook family members for suing me
Yep
Google be good rate
But it turns out that is also a
Buckhead
The second guy in
2 minutes
Hookah
This guy belongs
This isn't a conversation
About one of the top free speech lawyers out there
I mean is right to say whatever you want but
Buckhead
This guy
This is a conversation about
Philip Morgan
Look hitting on ladies
When's enough
When what number of
Hugely powerful men do we need to get confirmation where monsters before were like
I think we can trust the me-too
Book for the
Rich old p
Next next
It's this
Contingent of a very
Small group of people
Really
Women
I need comes from mental illness from what from women who just don't like their dads
Kentucky just stated this Paradigm analysis
Out of society
Convene
Absolutely no Mass
A crisis
Sorry if it hasn't already
We got to be
Worried about this
Hotels downtown
What alpha male
Stop
CenturyLink
P****** if you're going to
Fifty Shades of Grey is wife sure
The reason I played that is like
This guy sounds like everybody on Infowars
He's a f****** lawyer
Top free speech
Snot
A slouch
It look
Sure
Physically
I just I just want to illustrate
Kathyzworld
Look at it
They don't just exist in these hallowed Halls of Infowars Studio
Anyway
Randazzo's
Randazzo
Say something else
BookIt
Everything is about power and domination
The other way around
One card
And your automatic
Likely a disadvantage
You know this is a good way to Target
Anyone and everyone
It's it's the if the victim
The First Amendment
Pink
In the future
I want to just be
Be clear
Listen very carefully to what he's about to say and what Alex's respond
Uber victims
It will be one victim
Every single possible
It's Disco
It really is like this
This race
Sissy
Strong through victimization
And lazy and stupid
Week
And lazy and stupid are the wise
Define exist
40s responding to is Mark
Grimm Doza
Talking about aspiring to
To be victims
Status
What you described as
Black
Lesbian female in the wheelchair
Well he's also acting as if though
Those are stealth
Appointed
Things
Cinemagic
You go into a room and play a game when you pull a car
Know what that means actually that makes perfect
Perfect randomization of birth
And how it f*** you over pull a card that says
I was born black in America
Succeed by Lake somehow that makes it easier
Whatever
The only people who would ever subscribe to that is people who are on
Highest level
Abuse of social hierarchy
The victim Olympics
And you are
Calling yourself a victim
Somewhat yeah
Because you're not
Victim
I don't get to taste like I get everything and you guys are joking
Cards
All have negative values on it and you're mad you don't get the pole card
Lockhome down
Left to get through
You're going to enjoy every minute of this I think
The first clip is the longest one
But it's
It's worth it
This might be a Mite downpipe as we meet
330 year old
Whose parents still waiting for this
Name is Michael Rotondo
Michael Rotondo not March
30 year old put on a wig
How's it going to be clear
Can you put ear keep your ears open to see if you can tell what Alex realizes
This is a bad idea
It's exciting it stop
I was just too
What I asked for what
Believe
Justice to be
I didn't really want
To have
How to turn into a media thing
It's fine I understand
30 year old man
A crazy person
I think you're
But everybody's a little quirky ways
Get you on here and be mean to you know that
Because
Welfare and
Abortion
Search engine
Level above
Are they
California
The conservative media
I called you a bomb and I'm going to add a joke
A slob and a delusional
Which
That makes all of us
But all these other people are entitled
Real quick
Listen
Rotondo response
And listen to Alex's response to his response has made
Then all the s*** that he just said
Everyone's saying that you suck if you're a piece of s*** someone else
Yeah but everybody
But at least you're not one of these welfare Queen's Right
He's pissed off that we have to pay for illegal immigrant abortions in at the same time is pissed off that illegal immigrants are have
Anchor baby
Also you don't get both
He has a child who he is not allowed
Be in contact with Progressive something
Right
He claims it's because he's
Stupor
Right
I don't think
It happens a lot
I halfway believe it in this
In the stupid f******
Country
Nothing else I don't I don't believe it
It made his
His baby's mother
Say hey we got to go to court you can't be around your son
Trust women
And you know what do you think that's vert not on
Some sort of welfare
Because
He doesn't have a job and won't work
She has to take her baby she has to support a child by voice off without
The father of the child
Being able to contribute anything their moms
I don't think he I don't look I don't I don't like the idea of throwing stones and what have you but I will say that
If someone is that you know
That's what I say
Alex's said it least you're not one of these bum
Right
Willy's bombs on welfare
And here is Rotondo
Response
Would you crazy
I think that
You shouldn't have people who need things like
And shelter
And
Your own communities I don't think it's something that you want
I'm sorry
Even
Even if it cost more
Get these people food and housing I don't think
It's something that you
Would wish to forego because
And you have hungry people and asking friends and go up
The Nugget
That's one of the
What the f***
So Alex
Alex
It's the only way to combat a lot of that need base crime
Is by
Taking care of those
Now there's
No way possible to take care of those meats
Everybody knows that's an impossibility
What just happened there you have him being like
You're not a bum cuz you're not on welfare
Clearly
Situation where someone
Needs to be on welfare
Then he comes
How does responses like
I think that if people need food or shelter than even if it cost
More in taxes we need to support that because the alternative
Is there another probably race
Time with people not being able to
Sign the Bottom Rung of Maslow's hierarchy of needs
Alix Bailey
Historically but you are absolutely correct before I left
I will murder anyone who attempts to help
Have a professor
He could have a senator
Look up liberal Progressive Senator on who would make it
StubHub
Sorry this week why is he allowing him to make
He doesn't know what's going on
This is out of the gate, we have no clue what's going on
So he's 18 what do you think Alex
Was going to happen
That
The twists and turns show you a picture of the
The two of them
I'll post this on our Facebook group
But I just this really well
Thumbs up
How the mood was
It's Alex with his hands clasped almost praying position
Up and into the middle distance
Well the other dude is staring bullets into his ear
Alex
To being
Servient
Ended usually goes through
Through your parents why is this
And say you're the worst person
Natural ways
People
Irani
I would f****** know
I used to use one of the buildings that he owned as my studio and now
We have no expertise in the field
Department
I think you know a little bit about Pastor dependents
I would call him
6 level bump
Clearly
Becomes clear that Alex
You could judge
But you I would never call you a wishlist
Please pizzas yet I would never call you that
Alyssa
I'm not saying it's true
Send a text
Viral
Alright
I've been trying to leave the home
4 years
That
I felt as though I would
Which was that
Chase
Okay tomatoes for 6 months
Because that was what I don't want to make
And take care of me
No
What did you have that handy
Don't freak out using her phone
I don't I don't
Particularly care I love the way that Alex is so disarmed by this guy
Weird that he's like
The thing that I claimed isn't true then I will accept it
Somehow I'm cool with it
Did you see that need like
Particularly
Care
About the specifics
Cuz I'm in the same camp as you that like
If my parents told me to leave
I would leave
My parents
Like if I were
19 yeah you're right
He write sorry
Alright here I go
It wouldn't take
Put my little bindal on my shoulder and start walking
Especially
If my parents were as
Gracious and nice as his parents
Clearly were
That I don't think it would
I don't think it would ever
Isaac
I think that this state of affairs that we're in
In terms of this even being something
Disgust
These tragic
I don't think it's
Funny I don't think it's fun
A finger in
I think this is absolutely tragedy
To baa
No
Astoria public
Clickbait
Stories
His parents offered him
Him $1,100 to find his own place
In February
They just gave him 1100
Hundred dollars
He took the money but he used it for quote various other expenses
End up moving out of the house
He claims on Alex Jones the show that he wants to move out and he would have given him
Six months notice
But that is action
Don't really seem to it
Indicate that
But again
You don't give a s*** for a number of reasons
One of them
Is that
Is
He seems like a dangerous guy
Oh yeah
Sorry to hear from the
An article here
From
What year
From the future
Years back
Over the past week was arrested outside her window Thursday night
Police say Michael Rotondo 22 years old sent a woman several threatening text messages
Earlier this week before finally showing up outside her home on Wednesday
The victim called 911 but Rotondo fled before police arrived
He returned Thursday night however if police caught him
Walking around the women's residence
At about 7:15 p.m.
Counts each of third-degree stalking trespassing and one count of second-degree menacing
Police say Rotondo was arraigned and sent to county jail on 45
Hundred dollar cash
Bail or
An order of protection was filed
And
Police say Rotondo was ordered to surrender his firearms
He had guns
Grapes
Temporarily
Got his guns back
God you're not allowed
Mom was trying to encourage him to move out of the house
She sent him a note
We're really speaking
To each other
Not at all
IG suggested that he quotes sell other things
Things that have significant value
Cheerios
Some tools Etc
She also says quote
Is especially true for any weapons you may have
You need the money and we'll have no place for the
Your compound bow
What uses recreational
Lever action 30-30 rifle
She says use
So this is a guy who has a small child that he's not taking care of it is not allowed to be in contact with
For a mysterious case that happened in 2017 we don't have the details on not entirely sure about
He's been arrested for stalking a woman he was caught outside or f****** window
Igear's ago
This is a this is a dangerously Disturbed person
If you
If you even
If you even get a sexual harassment
Complaint filed against you at an office
You should have your guns remote
You should not be
You should not be able to have
That's just a anywhere near every time there is any kind of b*******
There's also a history of domestic violence
Or violent towards women always f****** there
It's always
Beer that
You don't get done
In this case
Especially we have a situation where this guy is being
Thrust into
The spotlight way more emotionally able to handle
His parents house
The place
Seemed at least like a safe haven for him he's not allowed to contact his child he has a history of stalking women
How's it going
All of it if anything happens in the near future where he kills somebody no one should be surprised
That's not to say he will
I'm not saying that
Boy those signs are all there
And everybody in the media
Part of the problem
Can carbon illustrate even further a pattern of sort of resentment
Towards women
I would like to play
Switch to the fact that in May 2017
Best Buy
Because he fired him for not coming into work when he was scheduled for the weekend
He claims that he had an agreement with management that he could spend
Time with his kids have to work on weekends
And that female employees were given more latitude
BestBuy completely disagrees
Himself in court pro se
And I've looked into some of that
I'm fine
Anyway
That's why
Is just to say
That's why it makes sense he's on Infowars
He has the cutout in the profile of a domestic terrorist
I'm waiting for the storm front
Reddit page or whatever it is
His handle on Stormfront
I need to move out like
F******
We're not nearly done
I did this all one-dimensional
Exhaustion
Did your face you're just being honest
Because I want to have a man-to-man talk with you
Okay
Deschutes and do the report
How to say it
We could turn you into a
Iceborne DLC my son
You're not allowed to
Is Alex secretly his dad
Black Alex is secretly his dad touched on
What I'm trying to flesh out as this goes along
Alex wants
To be his dad
Wow
This is weird now this is really weird weirdest thing I've ever
Never heard on this now here's going to build a lot of credit for you
Set up in your own place you're going to have to
To take on some responsibilities that you're not used to take a note
I think I should have called you son I didn't mean to call you son put on I think this is a good idea that's going to make your life
A lot better
Oh my God this is so weird spiritual father of all the Wayward this effect
So why wouldn't he actually put himself in the position
He doesn't need a dad
He does
He has a dad
He is mentally ill
She needs to go to a hospital
He's someone who's clearly showed the signs of like
Being a risk
He should be in a hospital
Not in the news
Not on Infowars especially
To be fair
This next
If you don't go out
That's right
Ensure
Do you think Alex would save us to a black guy
A black thirty-year-old who didn't want to move out of his parents house
Do you think that conversation would ever happen
Criminal
But you're not
Completely
Productive
It's a spirit it's a program
Very little
What is happening
Swing video game side like to announce that I just got married
Stardew Valley
I try to watch television because I
I need to stop
Working
So that I can
Sleep I need
What all day everyday almost
I want
Like I do business
Questions for you and come back
Discuss this
Cam
We got it
Redial
Xclusive that everybody has been waiting to get we're the ones who grabbed him
What is happening
Find out
His businesses
He's running
Business
The other stuff to eat what do you working on all the time
That could be that isn't it like
Law that's him defending
Himself
Jesus Best Buy
His son back with the judges said
You cannot see your child right
In this next clip
Again
This is not something that you would ever do any other Circle
Stance
So f***** up
I will pay you
Set reminder.
Before
I love that frustration
The white box
Statistics
He's kind of resent that he had to correct him
I was never married I just haven't
Here's $3,000 my friend
What is capitalism
Capitalism capitalism my friend
Thousand dollars to come on by 2000
For no reason because I feel you
Here's what you need
You need
To have a home
And you don't have one right now
You need to have food
And you don't have food right now
Now
I'm not saying that they should be afforded to non-white
I have a strong suspicion that he's going
Various other expenses
Show that tell you can hopefully get on your own
I-10 and
This means a lot to me and you're
Street
Appreciate it
I can't sit here
Just just just putting down call you next
The social engineers
Culture
System
That is trying to arrest our development
Cell phone radiation is causing heart problems damage
Aaron judge you want to be with your parents
Waredaca
This won't go well for you down the road
But it's not a psychological
This is not a situation where he wants to be around his parents
He said quote the deaf people who don't know sign language
That's how he described the relationship with his parents
He continues to live under their roof
Parents and son
Strangers lineup for food you said
He waits until they're out of the kitchen
Before cooking himself
Then
He goes into the dining room or up to his bedroom
So it's not
To be around his kids
Arrested
Situation
Hostel
Bucked up
To be in a f******
King Hospital
Actually living a life
Anyway
Question
Bestowing upon this viral star
I'm going to have to trim down some of this cuz you got to get out of here to go to your show
But we're also going to have to move or have two trucks alright
There's some clips cannot be skip one where
Just forgive my use of this
Turn but Alex just kind of things
But this guy the p****
Really, you're not
What we're discussing here is super
Jiraiya gets the twin
Most people
Gross.
Well you are
Alright
I a millennial
What is it with millennial
You got to pay close attention to this next part
I was
Okay bet it a bunch of
Syndicated
Suggest
Just to be clear
Vig of having penetrative sex
With someone at 11 or 12
Is what's considered
Inappropriate sexual behavior
Based on developer
That's not something that you're so
Supposed to be doing I've heard of that before 11 like 10 11 12 that range psychologist
Diet wrist
They
Interested in nudity
You're supposed to be like
Chords
People
But the idea of actually f******
That means something has gone to
Terribly wrong in your life
That means
Something
Very very serious
I'm not 12
Psychoanalyze somebody over the radio
But that is
Severely f*****
Dude
That's f***** up
He's using that as a way to be like
You're Wicked how great I am
Crazy
Continues in that thread of like
You don't like
Matt
Is it like right after Alex
Talks about how great his dad and Grandpa were
Rotondo has a little rejoinder
They were raised to be capable
Not play today
Okay so how are you
I wouldn't really characterize myself as having been raised necessarily
Whatever
I don't care
Explain
So this is
Liquid Alex
Didn't
Go outside
More like
Continue Alex
That's why this is so weird
It leads to
Worst at Vivid I've ever heard of my life
When are you going to get out
And considering that
I cannot pull depends on how many hands I have to help me cuz I've had some people offer to help me
Stuff to 3000
And put them another $1,000
Myself
Mercedes
I haven't January 1st
June 1st
44.com
I need your support
I need this part cuz I'm in the middle of
An awful interview
This is weird
That little that little bit of like
We can't be more than three or four hundred dollars is like
I can't do that
Myself
That is a man
With
Genuine
Mental illness
Compulsive disorder perhaps
Nothing
No absolutely not
Up until this point
It was like
Listening to that conversation is such
Listening to a conversation between
A dad who has
Never met his son and the son who is
Breathing in pain
Yeah it is
Very much
Struggling
Come to its natural conclusion
Next one cuz it's trying to give
Career count
I like to watch
Videos of machines
What do you look like
Very reminiscent of my dad telling me to go to
You learn something very sad
Any friends
Sort of
Go out get out the house yes
Alright
Computers are allowing people to plug into virtual reality
Flash
Lowering
You're in a mesmerized
Come on
There's a new season of Arrested Development
You understand
Around the mountain
I don't do things like that
Exactly
But the point is that
You need to do
I need to
Run around
Yes
I got it
I'm crazy
This is weird
Really f***** up because Alex is
This is because Alex has checked out he's like
He offered him a job
Out the gate right and he was like
I don't know
I'm not good at Grand
I'm not going to use that I'll do that myself
Videos of machines
Yeah I don't think I want to do that too monotonous and then
Pizza place offered a job
Jubilate to that someone told me about it I didn't see it
18 ft so weird because I
Guarantee
This is the exact same conversation this guy's head with his real dad
Undoubtedly
The only way to get what it's about 30
That's what I do for fun
Hangout in my Mansion watching Netflix
Netflix
Great so famously
About Netflix and
Euphemism
Blown up in my face a little bit
I smell the internet making fun of
Breath
He realizes like
I'm not doing a great job here
Maybe I should bring in my other surrogates on Owen Shroyer
This happened to help me insult this kid
Immediately after
Next to you
This guy is the future right here
Serious
What you got to do
It sounds like a
That
Another Star Wars
No
Okay
I don't know what that is
Other wife
Okay actress hilarious
A Pepsi with a comic genius
You know that
Best you can be out there and we're going to leave that hang
That's one of the worst
I've ever seen
Like
That's a two-man Act
Will never have night too
He's like
Palpatine is my spirit animal
I don't know what that mean
I thought you weren't awake
It's a joke
This is this is
But no instead of Yes Man
There's no but you can
Just you can not really Star Wars
Alex's misery
Keeps trying to be like
What
Why don't you want to leave your parents house like I do
I want move out right I want
Little more time
I don't believe
That argument on his part
Hugh
I believe I believe he wants to leave
Absolutely fundamentally cannot because
If you had six months you would be able to
Course he's not he's probably thought that for 6
But all that stuff is like you're never going to penetrate into that mindset
Do you want to stay at home
Easy question for him to answer
It's almost like there should be some sort of
Profession
That trains and studies about how to break
Through the type of
Mental illness never
It should be one that
Is readily available to anybody with his mental illness that would allow
Tell them to at the very least find some
Part of life that they can function
Happily
Stupid
Sounds stupid now you just need you just need somebody to be like
You should do that
And then they shove iodine
Surprises burger burger
So
Brings in a Cavalcade of Infowars males
Navigate to Zolman doesn't make any Headway these other two.
Hey bro
Motivated
Where is your motivation
Adizus like
Whatever just sort of like a lackadaisical response one guy comes in
What have you done that you're proud of what's your
Singer most proud of
Other than your kid
Eddie doesn't have anything
Can come up with 15 minutes later he's like how I thought of an answer question what I'm most proud of
Is my kid
I said
I don't want to play any clips of it cuz it
Really sad
Yeah it's watching this guy
They're not
I think they mean to humiliate him but it's humiliating for the people asking the questions
And for Mike
And I feel very bad about it
Everything that you say to him if everything you say to a person is
Why aren't you like me
DIY f*** you b****
Why are why are you different
Disgraceful and I'm saying that about a guy who I think
The danger
That's a big part of big part of why is it dangerous because
Never
Got help but that's why this is a really difficult thing to talk about because we have
On the one hand I think it's awful to Alex's behaving at all the other hand
I find it very difficult to be
We fully empathetic towards Michael Rotondo
Cuz I think
He's only only wear them because of something that is 100%
Mental Health
Funny parting shot they do that round-robin
Hey you suck bro
No
There's a
They have the
They have this weird like video camera with just a microphone in front of it in a backdrop of
That's what people come up in
They come up like a spelling bee
Some questions you like
Pictures of my face
So Alex
Then you'll eat
I think this begins with good advice
Okay alright
Goes off the rails
Werewolf
Box
I think they're being athletic or at least like
Getting some sort of regular exercise is it is a good thing for your mental health
It did have there been studies that have been done that it's absolutely
It's beneficial
Restarts with kickboxing isn't a crazy idea because
Martial arts are really good way to enforce discipline that's her thing
As well as buildup comfort
I think there's a lot of positive
4 shirts
I I like the
Bicycle
Flexi-Rod my bicycle
Is it
How would you like
Tubi
Bernie Sanders
Probably wouldn't like that
Someone else
Maleficent
I don't remember
What's
The fuc
Call
Or your breastfed
That might be a little too personal hours
So
Ultimately I think Alex had no idea what the story was with this guy had no idea what
Expect when he came into Studio
I'm going to offer this guy a job
I love your operate
Surprising with 2000x
$2 which is going to be enough for him to move into a place in New York
Or
Subway near enough maybe Hoboken yeah
Regular real reports
Open up the New York Bureau with this guy who already has a lake
Cuz he went viral
He's a crazy
Which would be started welfare
Important Alex nested like not argue with him because he
Don't know how to deal with this guy at that point
Thrown on his back
Foot by the like I think I might want to give you a job and then be like
And then becomes dad joke
Yep that's correct
It's not very very awful
And then reinforces all the mistakes
I just I don't even I don't know
I don't know what to say about what I was watching this I was like
This is
Supremely f*****-up
Cuz it's more about Alex about Alex
Alex
Do you know that geysers there is a prompt
I mean even like
Supposedly benevolent attention of like I want to give this guy a job and give him to get out
Really just to suck off a little bit of that side
Virality
Eastside viral
The same
It's going to go even more viral with Alex
The life of the thirty-year-old who was evicted from his parents home
Every Millennial and Sarah
Prove that everyone who is willing to work
Will be, success in Trump's America
Absolutely
Yeah that what that's happened
Wild
I think that still doesn't ridiculous this show is
You said that and I wanted to be surprised and then I kind of like
Yeah why not what would me have the random ass thirty-year-old who was evicted on his show
Plays out at 12
Recognizing
You're an hour-and-a-half your show.
You're saying the globalists are attacking you and Trump under attack
Do you know what else is under attack Dan was at the traditional family
Texas trying to recreate here
Owen Shroyer is the older brother
Diarrhea is the absent mother which is how Alex prefers it Battalion for the absent mother
Uses to let him sit on his lap or whatever sure she's
Exactly that's the way to go through the ritual
Ritual number one
Have a really f***** up childhood relationship
Ritual number to have a really f***** up childhood relationship
Ritual number 3
Around 38 Raptor Kobo
At 50
Worthless now
Anything higher than worthless
Chris your nipples got2breal heart
It's all about the
It's got to be the level of cold where when you
When you breathe in through your nose you can kind of feel it
Little little
You got to get out of here so let's shut this down alright love website
I do
I barely use iTunes on
Business
I barely ever download
Only ours
Podcast know there's other ways on Android
Although we're not on Stitcher
Technology isn't
Is almost over and I scheduled
Except it's been very difficult we appreciate so much
Back to normalcy
Even for that
Panda
Also my schedule
But I will tell you
Right now
Absolutely should go f*** himself
And that is
Shutting down and closing so many Mental Health Services
In his term as president
Pissed off but
Because this is affected not just my life but your life this is added to the homeless population
This is increase the amount of violent incidents in our f****** country Reagan also is
If you f****** remember that we didn't have this kind of
And f****** co-pay versus all of this s***
He also destroyed the f****** unions
System in this goddamn country
What he broke the strike of the airport
If Reagan is out there
Butt f***** in heaven
Go fuc
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with your Japan I love your work