Alexandra Thurston color
Hey everybody
A little bit about Alex
Text Jones
Dan what up
It was summers day
I'm here in the Atlanta area
Chicago guy the guy leaves his house
Wearing a button up short sleeve
Classic guy around 1 p.m.
Leaves the bar around 6
Begins walking
Notices there's a nice breeze
Unbutton his shirt entirely and then walk around
With his got hanging out drinking
Hi to your gut
Okay
Sister like the guy who I saw the other day
I told him everybody
For good luck
Memorial Day
Designed as a pet
Sure but it's like a
Lovecraft shirt
My brother
Every every birthday or Christmas
He tends to give me a Cthulhu themed gif
My wardrobe cuz I never buy clothes
So I end up having a couple of shirts and that's why
More hipster
The Hipster one of the Elder ones
Who episode to go over
But I'd like to do donor
The clown for a while
Freedom Pointe
The world
What's going on out there Scrump
I could join up with the team
Calm down
Jordan
Don't Laugh at My Voice from
Anyways
Okay
Because Move Along
Name entitled
Format
This title we are giving out together next
Denis Raptor princess
There's a big help I really appreciate
Everything does
Congratulation
You're now a raptor princess
Until you're brilliant someone sodomites
IHOP
Abused by white people
Joseph Stalin
Welcome to McDonalds may I help you I barely find her
Yeah hell yeah
Doubt
Maybe now
Corporate another level
Apple podcast app just hit the
The 15th
I can't about six times and then you're done with that club
First order of business
Coronavirus live stream but ended up cutting it out of
The episode
Because I thought that the way I framed it was for
Alright so you had some time to think about it
You've written in your dreams
Propose
I knew
Thank you
Stardew Valley
They cannot marry you
I'd like to
Couple months back we had a little bit of a drive
Towards that
Raising a certain amount of donations
Launcher game game coverage
Which ended up
Lobbying 9 hours long and
Defeating
Describing a kind of
I would like to do a similar thing
With Alex Jones is Spiritual Bible
The book that woke him up
None dare call it
Conspiracy right I've been going through it and I realize we can't do it as podcast
It would be 30 hours
Gun
Especially writing a book
About
Why this book
Okay
Cuz I'm going line-by-line through this f****** thing
Constructing
So much of why it's wrong
All of the context that getting off
How many let's say
Nazi apologist propagandist
Star quoted as primary sources
Mysteriously
Things like that
Understand correctly
You're next
Marathon reward
Given out as we reached some sort of
Is going to not
Feature me at all
Must work for you
Just let me go don't let me run over with a red pen
This is going to come out
Probably
As we get to the end of it
It'll be up on knowledge buy.com it'll be a series of blog posts that all
Just be deconstructing all of this
And I will begin to release at what the incentive that I am going to propose
And maybe people think this is stupid but I don't want
People who already donate to
To the show to feel like they need to get more
Baby feel like they have to like
Maybe you donate more than they're comfortable with originality.
Any kind of
Because people would want this to be
Released
I don't want
I think some people would and I don't want them to feel like I'm a
Going to give more money and make this happen so what I'm going to propose
Are things that are positive
Right
Punish you with a book report
I propose
15 new donors
New donor
From the time they were recording this which is Memorial Day 2018
Until the end of June
Throughout the month of June we can get 50 and new donors
We will have our Easter
Easter sale
Percent off releasing the post
About what's wrong
With none dare call it conspiracy and why only a stupid person would ever fall for the b*******
It's listed with it
Alright
And I've anybody would like
Independence Day
The lizard
No
Raptors
Batman
Whatever
I am nothing if not
The desire to correct
I needed to I need to call myself out about this on the last episode I ended up cutting out something at the
The beginning after we released
Diversion
This diversion
And just because I'm
I like to smoke myself
Operating on a little bit of lack of information
About 1,500 children who
I've gone missing from
The
Immigrant children
I completed a couple things and I
I spoke of that in an irresponsible way bad about that so I cut it out of the episode and I would like to
Call myself out
Before I head to
Taking it out and about that
Splitting up families and the children who are unaccounted for are completely different
Stories
Conflating them
Possibly not the right thing
I don't I don't know enough about it
Stupid
On the other hand
Both are
Well I mean
66 + 1
Kind of situation either of those f****** things happen
1500 children thing I read Ninja
Perspective on it where
A lot of the people who were reported in town hall
Do we like it
It's not that it's that they're released from custody to
To people like you might be family members or might be
A friend of the family or something like that
When they're checked up on their whereabouts are
It's possible that they're like
The person who
Care of them it is their Guardian doesn't want to
To answer questions
Necessarily mean they're in a negative situation they might just be
With guardians
You don't want to
Deal with the government considering what they're up to now 100 years
From now if we found a
A thriving civilization in a forest somewhere
Then their Legend was like
Well then the white man came to take us away
My bad for creating a whole secret society
I just felt like a bit of a dumbass
What I looked more into it as I I feel like we should have
Be completely aboveboard and apologize
A little bit too
Flippantly
No granted
Some of those people could be a negative situation
I hope that's not the case
But we don't know I don't know enough
I don't think we know enough
Pretty sure horrific government
Changing the rules on you at any given moment and destroying your life
Even if you're with a good home that's usually a f*****-up
Anyway the other thing is I need I need to give another correct
On our last episode we talked about Michael Rotondo the thirty-year-old guy who's getting evicted from his parents house
Yeah
The show
I need to issue a correct
They did another epic
Here's another context drop probably going to be going over today
They are closing
I don't think you're a loser
Wait
They kept going I thought we figured out how to be a surrogate father pretty quick
Is Bailey got it miserable
So this is correct his own mistakes
Part 2
The NeverEnding Story
Yeah they talked for a good hour and a half for employee roulette
Reverence
Then the War Room comes on or whatever
Why Alex
Michael Rotondo the thirty-year-old whose parents took him to court to kick him out of the house
Who also has a conviction for stalking
They sit down across the table from each other
And have a bull session
Because Alex realizes
He realized he couldn't be in this guy
Wait till he goes on a different show
I think it's recorded wow that show is happening but it's in a side like you
Yeah yeah
Giving the wall with a broom
I normally would say
Alright we talked we f***** up man we talked about the episode already we can't go back to the well
Really done this necessarily
Okay here part 2 of death
I don't think we've done that a lot
Listen to this
There's so much more
Oh no no no no no
Alex
Weird from themselves
Take
Zach weird guy completely out of the equation
This is all about Alice
I understand that
Goes
So esoteric
He gets
He's talking in riddles
Lightly diet
Closed to vehicular
There's two of me one over tell the truth what kid only lie
What's good
This goes so far off the rails there's no way around
We have to go over but the other thing is there's one more correction I need to make before
We get out of the shop I meant to say
On the last episode and I didn't make it clear enough
And I really regret it
I was thinking about editing into the episode just a little bit of my voice being like
A pretend that you just didn't
Respond
Make
Clear enough
Is that
And then he went back to his home planet
Michael Rotondo is 30 years old
Right
How long how long did you say you've been living with his parents
Leeson's Elian Gonzalez 8 years
You've been living with his parents
How old was Michael Rotondo
When he got arrested for stalking a woman
The reason he probably moved back in with his parents
Was because he got arrested for stalking a lady
Is not really
Argument
Oh hey also get this but he has a different address
When he was clearly living on his own
Right
So
Got arrested for stalking a lady
Yeah and then some point a little bit later that year he moved back in with his parents
Coincidence
Can happen
F*** you
Now baby
That was Judas
Jordan
What are we doing
This is so f***** up
If I let me let me make a
Prediction
Allen I love
Alex Alex is going to
Channel
The ghost of his father's
Parenting
Through this child
And speak
2 it's in the
The past as though it is something that he wishes
Had been happy
My friend there will be ghosts
Anyway
Episode starts the video start the livestream is an hour long
Start
With I don't know at least
Like 10 seconds
It's not fair
Mike rotundo sitting at a table
Fiddling with the mic
But there's an innocent
Who's awful Alex walks into frame
Some bottles
Superman
Which
Hold on
Cuz it comes in at the beginning
Superman the whole time you're like
Yeah you got supplements on the table
Nope
It was just
He's bothering them up
So this is almost just recapping the
At least
Yeah
Bright light.
Demon in the world
Pushes
Disagree
This whole millennial
You are very very complex
Well
But I think that I just am doing the best I can read been sitting for the reasonable effort
But I don't think it's really anything
Wrong with the things that I've done some wrong things
By the things that I've done
Yeah like what
Like earlier episode he say that he
Can't think of anything he's proud of his daddy's brother smarter than him
Is what he said the kids 8 years old
Yeah well that's probably
Panfish bait
Flying around here
His son was born in the same year
What is the person who I don't know who he was talking was cuz
Whose names are confidential
Please mother
That would also explain why he's not allowed to
But he had visitation rights
For some of the time
I believe
Made it so he couldn't talk
To the kid anymore
Yeah he's not allowed to have
If you was stalking her back that I would assume
No contact from
The jump right
Yeah but they're all those f*****-up Lowe's in America where it's like you're rapist
Can still have visitation
Yeah like that kind of thing I don't know like America's a f*****-up place
I don't know if your
Ques laws are like
It also introduces the idea
Wasn't her 8 years ago he has a baby with one lady
He's talking to another lady gets arrested
His baby's mom is like f*** off get out of here but that would still leave him in
Situation where I like it's not enough to not have rights
Missy your child
I think it should be I'm not
Probably like
I don't know how to parse it other than to say I'm not for any other
But I don't think we have a hero in any of this this episode
The hero
But he's not a hero either
Just swoop in and put them on a backpack and then he died
Climbed up Mount Everest
Together and he's like
I am giving you all I know and then he becomes
When's the next the next
See everybody settling into their new roles
Are the new Rodger
Training them
That's why I take you
Got it
Everything
So he was unable to
To deal with
The question what's your greatest
Achievement
The show yesterday
Alex
Does not have such a
Although
A little bit of humility
Starved Rock
But sometimes
What would you say your
Earlier
The world
Americana
I have
You kept was around about 15 years before I ever had
You sent forth
Achievement
Is
Creating a movement
That would help stoop
Ruining multiple countries
Redheads
History when I was nine so that
Now I've toppled f****** Britain
Normalcy
Brittany
Book when I was 12 an hour
Johnny Appleseed founding father of fascist movement around the United
Around the world
Global
Boner
What's my proudest
Achievement
Firstbeat
Being super confident
Mixture has led to a lot of good things
Attribute
This amazing ability
Even though he doesn't need to be
No but listen to this
Name-dropping
Show me some of the notes
No idea
Alright
Hold on
And
The weirdest want to talk to me
He is both Hank Hill
And the other guy
King of the Hill
Everyone who's ever talked to Mike ever about
King of the Hill to the copious numbers of interviews he's done
Involved in the show is a one-man operation okay
Just just Alex
The entire show is based on his show
Now also Access TV
I would say that that show
I don't I don't know if my dates are totally right here but I
Probably Premier 20 years ago 22 years ago
Alex Jones
Is 44 right now 9:40 he was King of the Hill
King of the Hill
Everybody knows that that balding
Two-year-old father-of-two
Twenty-two-year-old lunatic got into Public Access TV
Dumb conservative
Pretending to be libertarian radio
So stupid
Alright so he spends a long time
The neighborhood I had to drive
Redbad was Iowa
Someone was dead on the street
I don't know about that
F*** you I'll let you have it
All done that doing stand-up
At any rate
Talked about how
He made
His first film
America
Destroyed by
Design
And he did it on
Badcock
Auntie ended up flipping it
The Macon
Cool half mil off
Billion dollars
And then he turned it around and put it back into the business
Annette something Millennials could never get over
So here is him talk about this when he accidentally slips and talk a little bit
But too much about the money
My cousin
Question for
Dollars
Car
All that money
Sheriff
Yes that's the weather manipulated
I'm not doing this to me
Okay
This is this is a logical
I bet he just does that and what's the temp
Pacifically
You acting weird
Dragon very suspicious about something
This is how I would talk to you if we were on camera
I'm starting to tell about all these accomplishments
I made
Livelook
Half a million dollars
Bridgeport
Now it's 40
I mean we are a shoestring operation
If he's like legitimately he's ever brought in 40 million dollars through his sales in a year last year
You went on record
Is that the cost 13 million.
Billion dollars in operation
That is a prophet
27 million dollars
Right where is that money going if not to Alex Jones
Buckley
And the HR department
Lakeview I'm sure it's at 8
Exaggerated
Target once
Expensive
You buy one of those little runs out immediately
So he just goes on and on here about how like
Just because he's trying to deflect
I'm talking about his own
He's just talking about
Go do it
He's trying to present itself like
Used some sort of elevate
It's not that important
Trust me where we're going
We don't need to
Texas
Alright
That is a
Nicotine
My son work
Mike Rotunda
Talk to you I wish I would have got her legs
I just want you to know that
They're the ones promoting
Millions of sex changes in the country
I don't think so
So he's really containing
He's confused by this but
It's really fun
To like
To look at like the reality of what insurance does cover
Because if you get rhinoplasty you can convince doctors that it's
Cosmetic medically Medical Group
So there are a lot of nose jobs that do end up getting
Conned into being covered by by Healthcare
Now if he wants to talk about her one for yourself you know what I mean, right there
Maurice Chevalier
The other thing to do is like gender correcting surgeries
Mariana
Diamond Millions
Formed in the
United States
Take taxes from
I mean I mean
Right I don't know I don't know millions of these perform
. no
The the number
Specific numbers are kind of iffy
I was reading this one article about how
Gender confirmation surgery
Percent in 20
Steam which makes
It seemed like that is a lie
Fight
Tiny amount but if you read the article less than
5% of us
Procedures involved any kind of
Genital
Surgery
There are no large numbers of you know chest
Surgeries that satar down weathering
Increasing or decreasing
This article here in Denbigh
BBC News
I will
I will concede that the beginning of this article
It does say that
The Bubba Bubba Bubba
The American Society of plastic
Exergen
I haven't
Some questions about the data
Or the data was supplied by them
And there are some questions about it suits not
The best
The data button terms
The specifics about
What is able to fly
Didn't delete it
Then delete the articles that mean something
Thanks anyway
It's only 15 total operation
In 2016
Genital
Correction
Millions of them
If you have no idea if those 15 were paid for by out-of-pocket
Or any of that
No clue
I was just making s*** up to be mad at
Cuz he hates marginalized
Myscripps
We're not done with no jobs though cuz I was going to talk more about that
Roshes
I like it
Exercise
That's how that works
My wife will sweetheart
You want to spread what you're
You want to
Make some change you want to
Pinochet cop some things you want to
Witches human empowerment
Cancel
I would say an encouragement
Talkington
You fighting for his life against them sort of vicious
Demon against the wall
Happening in between this
Pools of the whiskey
Yelling at a wall about problem
Trying to
The same time walk this guy down a path
Cuz he's trying to indoctrinate him
To certain extent
Why do you got to go in
Playlist Kelly this is ex-wife
Okay talked about that before the past
How can I say has material to the wall he's just like doing Vapes he's checked out
The rest of it is him just being like
You know what what is it what is human empowerment
Don't ask a question like that
But it's much more
F*** you
He's trying
Sing 2
I don't think
It's a question that has an answer
Ask her the question
Can possibly know
And you will never get that question right
Because the answer is whatever it is you didn't say
Wait until this plays out
I'm telling you
This is the beginning of him attempting to be like
Now what do you think about this
It's in trying to butter him up at
Is it like the book
There's two things that play Beyond him
Complaining about his wife's nose to the wall
Which is one piece of this that
Definitely present
The other parts
Made him cuz he thinks it would be a good gift
He'll be a big get
Infowars
For publicity sake
If they get this guy
And fix him up get him a haircut get him on
Workout routine you know like this would be huge for him alright
Propaganda
But then the other side of it Infowars version of The Biggest Loser
Play
The wall cuz Alex
As he's trying
To do this dialectical thing where he's like
What is human power
There's more
There is
Working for it
He gets lost in thought
This is again presentation to go along with his writing down ideas
He has like what you're good at Electronics
If it was because it's just so base
African crafts
It seemed just trying to steal a little bit of this guy's shine
Famous right now in rap heavy
Can you stealth the whole time
Business hours
I want start Deadpool
Looks like
You got to believe
Wheelbarrow
President
Didn't care
We can all pretty much get something
That was your point that was your point
That was your point
Which is greater
Cuz I
That's a mean
This is great
This is
Alcoholic divorce
We didn't get a good run
That
By ear course I mean
Bucking when I was 11
Job selling memberships
So those are two jobs that are pretty appropriate for Alex
No they're very
Usually train track you in contract
Formally very KT
Distant
How did not allow blacks
Irish or women
Very open-minded Country Club
Golf courses part-time Sullivan
Golf Course
Store
Wasn't
Platform
Right
Make a film
And the lister's responded
So do it
Doing a production for doing that ideology
Here is where I think
As much of a
But s*******
Michael Rotondo is in the fact that he stalked a woman
Is unforgivable and he's not an empathetic figure
Still not an idiot
Because he has
Some sort of
Presents on the Spectrum to understand the social cues
Good way to be a portal into things Alex said all fair that he doesn't realize he's not supposed to
Bushman ideology Center
If you called him
Whatever
Redondo is saying that it's clearly like
The way you phrase
What's the Miami like
That's a problem
Means that the things
Do you say probably
Through a filter
Here's where things turn
I don't mean to say that a couple times
But here's where one of them
Comes
Text Alex trying to be like
Save you
You came off
Okay
Tell me the court May when they took your son away from you
Brood
That looks very reasonable characterization what happened
Do you mean they said that
Actually go out
Have a mission
Ecology
Thinking
Cuz you're smart
Miserable have this was
Amazing
This
Here's a Alex's prescription
Become a completely different person
Stop being that person
Everybody else's
Describing as a pile of s*** everybody's
You're incompetent everybody else did legally
I would
David what makes this
Funny is
Alex
But what makes it not funny is the reality that like
16 or fail Alex is hurting this country
You're not dealing with the underlying issue that he's
He has a mental illness
She needs to be
You need to help Village to raise a thirty-year-old as long as
Yeah from the chat room
Predict that there this is
Jordan Peterson
InStyle
Advice
Too much with Peterson so I don't I don't know a lot of his
Is pretty
Particular quirk
He's but it does it does that sound right
From what I have what I've heard
Stop Jordan
On the last episode
We learned that Mike Rotondo
Cuz we're buddies now
How we learned that he's
Running a business
We never knew you had
We don't know what that other business
We don't know what that
This is he never made it clear
And luckily I'm this episode
And I don't want to connect the two things that I want to bring
Yeah I don't have the infrastructure to support
Did I mention
You can always go
Can I be clear I didn't
Cut there
But he said
I think what he's trying to say is if this is your passion project
Their business
To pay for this passion
I think that's what he
If that's what you trying to say I get it but these nuts
No he's not doing that well
Let's see where this goes
Brightness
What is the
What is the weather
Information technology
Okay
It's not really an idea
Let the stuff
Are you get for me works
CERN
Whatever it Whatever It Is
We go through with it
This is a bad business
This model
This is bad
Is it the business
Maybe
Worn down enough to like be like
There's nothing
I just I just whatever it is I'm doing I'll do it well
Yeah
I'll help you with technology
And I'll do it well
I think that's what he saying
Does the it stuff is like I'll fix
Stuff I'll fix your machines
Your Tech issue
Use but I'll do this
I don't know but whatever it is it like if I were on Shark Tank
I'd be like bro
Go
I'm not buying in
What are you going to do
It's not so much and it's an ideology
Haha
If you get it from me it's going to work
What do you think
User
Are dead.
Department of dreams and wishes
What's your Five-Year Plan to give people what they want
This is no good
Alex
Metaphor that
You got to play with the
That's not what that metaphor means
Poker
The expression you have to play with the cards you're dealt means that you have to accept the situation in front of
Have you as it is
So if you don't like out 26
Or something like that that's
Field much off that
Super Lucky
36 is pop out on the board then you've got the best hand ever but you can't control that
So what you doing
Play with the cards you're dealt
For a better opportunity
Or you going to block it and pretend you have
Pocket aces
You know what I'm saying that's what the metaphor means
You got to play with that cards then do well in you'll get Aces
No
He's framing poker
Classic American Dream
It's about pulling yourself up
If they see that you got bad cards and you win there like hold on we got to get you out of
We got to get you into the car to the car.
They're all locked.
I know that's a little tiny thing
Understand or use
Stop using that
Blows my mind
Most of this episode is largely going to be us listening
To Mike Rotondo and it being confused
Right like not understanding what Alex is trying to sit down on the table
The hold on there's a bunch of Alex's in the wrong
So
Hellboy
Here's a here's where everything turns
I just cuz you mean
Right
Black person
Will not discuss racism
People who are not black
Can understand it NetSpend it's fine if
People who are black can't understand it
But not sharing it
Is the wrong approach
Real
Did like the media or just
Kill a billion
Tell me how the goddamn racism is it
Wow
Pictures of
Supportive conversation with Alex Jones
Because we have
Listen to Alex Jones
For the past year-and-a-half I understand what
You say right
Did not if I had no contacts
I know this guy is a
You f******
Batman
Yeah
I also
Even then at like
If you were around
There's eight of you around black races I had black friends and then
I am better than everybody else who thinks about white race
And I can't possibly be one of them
We're also sad what
F****** idiot
He's bats
Really believes is true even though it doesn't make a goddamn bit upset
No and so I looked into it cuz I wanted to
I don't understand exactly where it says billions of people who are going to be killed by 5G
3 billion
Important
Things that I found that were particularly interesting to
One of them is that whatever he talks about this story
Dimensions
An article
Screen
Article from Wired Magazine
Haha and the headline from this Wired Magazine article
That they always Flash
Have you never read
Right never go over much
Is
Are big bold letters
5G smartphones cause cancer big Wireless doesn't want you to know
If you read the actual article it starts
I've been waiting and waiting for this particular form of popular fear to surface again
Okay
Already done
Yep from the first sentence does everybody who think this is
F****** stupid
You seen this before it happens every time every time we got our first one we got a little
Mark on the board
So then there's another there's a stud a study in the LA Times
About
Slight increase in Cancers and
Rap
There were supposed
T5g
Future
And it's a very slight
I don't think it's
It's clear that there are helpers
But it's clear that there are no hell
Leslie can I keep it
An epidemiology professor at UCLA Fielding School of Public Health
The health effects
Cell phone
So I don't
Noted expert says
Truck
Who cares about racism
We could be cancer
Bright
Dirt bike
There might be slight increases
Alex
BBQ
Get rid of them
Get rid of every barbecue in America
Carson
Energetic how
Dairy burning charcoal briquettes is carcinogenic
Like regulate on that level if you want
They could bring the Callback job you don't understand like what
Is really like
Steak
Could be had with
Strip steak
With 5G
Cuz it's not just things getting much faster in like being a
Vina Wi-Fi speeds increasing what have you
Processing
Speeds would go up to
Any ability to do all these
These things are impossible to do now with battery live
And s*** like that it wouldn't strain your devices
So heavily
There's all kinds of
Applications
The ability to work anywhere
And stuff like that
And that's already given you
Can't even with like my small-minded approach to it I don't even understand all the applications
But these few that I can come up with
Super exciting
I don't know
Maybe they're studying
Is the truth lighting
Grieving cancer
I think they're also need to do more studies
I'm fine with that
Anyway
At this point if it said maybe or maybe not
Good enough for me
Cancel the whole thing
I mean like what we're doing on racism
All right we can't have 5G
Racism dad
I was just would love any
He's not
Blerdcon racism
Because he's
Because he has on both sides
Better than everybody else
Scared like a little bit
Really funny cuz my cousin
That worried about 5.
A billion people
Because
But the globalist
Right
Scientific consciousness
It is completely cold-blooded
Presidents of the racism
More important than z5g thing because
If we die sooner from cancer
Does it matter
If the queen
Patron
Spiritualism talking about
This is The Scrambled spiritual
Fired for a humanistic exist
What's the rating of
Alex
His son in the bathroom
1 timer
Taking it all out on this kid right here
I don't know I don't know if you can
Of course it does but like I want it I want to say exact whip right there
A little bit of a
Like a moose Bouche
It's a little taste
Of like some of the stuff that Alex is going to
To try and drop on him
Cuz he's not here
He's not buying into this
Probably doesn't want a job
But he doesn't understand Alex's worldview and he's like
Yeah I don't know
I don't know but I don't think that's all that
Steven says like I don't think
Going to kill people
I don't I don't believe that
Alex
Really getting mad because it's already established it like either I'm
Going to save you or the globalists are going to write
60 that the globalist to win in Alex's
So
This is the worst Scientology auditing session
Like they're like
It's not a big deal because otherwise
Do you understand
Sorry about that
I do I did not know that
Cuz it's
Trio level human cloning
I did not understand that
Asians killing Asians is not like Oprah Winfrey
Witcher features a dump black guy with a bullwhip
Also did you know that there's
What
Really admired could come up with
Leave them together in a basket
Tacular skill
Any other come out
None
Amazing poetry reading
His parents house at 30
No s*** no s***
I just thought I didn't want to make it to clear but
I f***** up
Play I blew our own game
I'm so in this next clip we should get back
Talking still in the same conversation little bit more about 5
Problem
Buddy of 5G is killing us
Instead of saying what does it matter
Frozen girl
He's already
Kill doesn't matter as long as we're loving
You can say
What I'm saying bye
The 5G cuz realistically the infection we have
Available to us
What do you eat
Okay alright
Change this
Bike
Isn't there any like
Tequilas
Would you believe you eaten
Would you believe
Does that question
Really not so much
Much about finding out what he eats
Also
Real quick
By the way
5G is killing
Right and we should ban
Cigarettes gun
Alcohol
Hyundai cars
Necessarily
Royal shirt
Fracking all of the everything they're doing in Flint
Chemicals
Call right now
No I know Alex
Black is killing us then blank know that's a fundamental problem
Of his philosophy
Because it's a counterexample to everything
If if
The standard
Tube and something is that it kills people
I mean do you would probably make the argument
This is going to
Kill everybody like you have a choice
Engaged
Where is width
It's just going to be in the air and again there's climate change also there is just air pollution
No standards that should be in place in terms of breathable air
Yeah
Does accidentally arguing for regulate
What's know about
Accidentally
He is for regulation so long as it isn't real
If it doesn't help
He doesn't really care about Mike
Regret
Inform you
I eat
Gay
I I don't I try to eat vegetables
And I do
Is it
Is it a witch
Booster
That we come up with cycling
Hard Rock Cafe
So politely
My office
Okay
Okay good
So he gives him a half-used bottle of X2 cuz they couldn't find any more around the office
It's one of those with liquid that comes with a dropper and Alex has on many occasions on his show just
Dropped it
You know that's kind of his behavior
He's given this dude
Lick that goddamn thing
Crazy
Is gross
Is really gross Schrute
There's so many gross things happening right now
Now they're physically gross things I think it's the last physically gross thing
Although X
Accidentally Alex admits
He's denied a whole bunch of
The past
Minnesota
Might make your hair fall out
But did you catch what he said there at the end
That's what testosterone does
Testosterone
Or at least it's up if it's synthetic Lee designed in order to make you release more testosterone
Which is the same thing as being testosterone
That's great
That is great employee new product
You want meatballs
Also probably
Small dick
How do balls
He's getting supplements
Push
In the form of like this will help you
Boy I'll tell you what
I don't know if it's right or wrong but he treats his dude like a child
Natural conclusion of that is he has to assign him a book report
Okay
Rodney Howard Browne
So you know.
Okay
How long do I delete a
Are you actually
Will you read this
I will read it at you would even have time to read it
How long does it take
Pain three weeks
Absolutely
Belle I want to say I know this is already way too late
In terms of Art
Discussion in our episode
I am going to allow a possibility that this is all trolling
Woodworking
And how they would be a eight-year-old stocking conviction
But like I'm allowing some possibility that this guy is just deep
F****** Alex
F****** with him so hard
Because the way you can use like
How long do I have to read it
Brillion community
The reality probably
High regard that
Gorgeous
Do I have to read it
All of it
Deflated
Who wrote This Book Rodney Howard Browne
Killing of Uncle Sam
This guy
He's a hero
So you're the doctor in Ministry
Correspondence school called
Religious correspondent
Score of the diploma Mill
Adonica were top-ranked Distributors for it
Berry juice multi-level marketing scam
Call Demond RV
Until they went belly-up in 2014
He was still involved in but Avi
He was named
What's the company for fraudulently claiming their project
Product
Contains proprietary fatty acid called celadrin
Oprah and dr. Oz
For fraudulently claiming that they endorse their acai products
They got sued a whole bunch
Then ended up going out of business
In 2014 what date
I defaulted on a 100
82 million-dollar loan note
That was to secure their ass
Which is pretty much how most pyramid schemes in multi-level Market
Getting scams go belly-up
Everyone down on the ground floor gets nothing and one of the top has already secured
Whatever they've stolen somewhere else
Swiss bank
Countersunk
So that's what happen
He was a top-level
Distributor probably using his
Religious
Could be could be
In June 2017
Rodney was one of the preachers
Who visited the White House
To pray and lay hands
To pray and Lambs on Trump what did you just say
You got really crazy about this
Like you went nuts what did you just say trade on Trump and they hit that picture that
Came out there's a bunch of ministers laying hands on him
Bi-level marketing
They're all related
Involved in just one
Alex Jones has its political continents
So you went to the
You prayed over Trump
Sure
That I watch this video I watch the video of him talking about it
There is a planned attack on our president
All I can tell you about right now I know what I'm talking about I've spoken to high-ranking people in the government and if this is being
Playing by people that hate God hate America hate our president and we have to stop this in Jesus name
Some of you might not
Some of you might not understand that you might think we're crazy but I'll tell you if you knew what I knew that you'd understand the urgent
50 hour
There's a fight for the soul of the Republic
And God had raised President Donald Trump to be the trumpet that's going to sound in this hour
It sounds like Alex
Something exactly like that
This guy is Reverend Alex
A very tolerant
People
Deal with it
Things that I find abhorrent
Samantha
Some sort of
Actual democratic
Republic in the United States
Sometime in the future
Perhaps
Has not had
Before we do that like right before can we behead
People like this dude
Like4like After the revolution
To set up the government
We take a break to take like a 6 months
Let's clear the
You break I can't just get everybody along that that
You know just Jordan Longline away
Just a long lighter why people now we know so far
Is lying about something if I can see again strawberry
Vicki was going to be a long one
He also believes in blood libel
From a sermon that he delivered on October 15th 2017
They sacrifice children at the highest levels in Hollywood they drink blood of young kids this is a fact
You remember when all the spirit cooking thing came out
That's commonplace ladies and gentlemen
Most of the Hollywood actors you go see onscreen what
You don't know
They bring a witch
The getaway
Personal which for like computer wish for
And they allow Devil's to come into them before they take the part of what they're going to act
It's a fact
It's a fact it's a fact what I'm telling you
Got the quote
Now I'm reading this and it's hilarious
But what I should tell you is I watched the sermon this is from a sermon
He's walking around in front of a congregational granted it's like
Get out of some sort of Nuvo
It's more than you
Hello dollar
It's big
But like it's
Crazy like
This is
You said
In the context
Of a Sunday sermon
Makes me very uncomfortable
Like I don't I don't
I hate this rhetoric wherever it exists
My enemies drink children
That's f******
I hate I hate hearing it
Boogeyman
It's jarring
Church
It's f***** up not great it's really a place where that s***
To not be happening
Like what
To the call this is Africa
Gravitate towards other f*****-up places
Who's better Braden.
Weird ship sorry wait let me get through the rest of this by Howard Brower Rodney Brown
Do you know Alex is like weird paranoid fantasies where he's like
They take it down
Mainline
What's that makes sense why you can put up with
Rodney Howard Browne has also been an Infowars guest
Now you was on on March 19th 2018 and when he was on he described his
A globalist Gremlins
Alliteration
Also
That's it let's get some dirty.
Rodney's from South Africa
White
America in 1987
South Africa without meat
When you're a white person fishes running away from seeing is around 1986
To the tune of like
200 400
And those two years
There's massive Global support growing for the three and Nelson Mandela movement
Like
Is taking over the country around 87
A little bit later in the wind that is not going to work for these white people and apartheid was on its way out
This guy
Who's clearly a con man thinking is I saw you and religion related behaviors was a
Preacher in South Africa who's left
In 1987 with his family
To flee to America
Makes me think
I can't see any reason makes me think you was up
You keep doing that
Alex Theatre
So that's one of the books that Alice wanted time here's the other one
It's not God
What is a three-week no no no
This this this book
This is a very important
I don't want to come back and not have done my
Homework
You're not coming back
Uncle Sam
Type the names familiar
Doughboy
Alex Bowman
Personally offended you don't know who Rodger stone is
You don't know
Rolling my life away for this guy
Have you don't even know who he is a b****
So Alex has to explain who Rodger stone is
If this explanation
He's not
Good
Ibanez familiar
Transformer wingman
Kind of like
Has your pets like a
No I haven't
Okay
Okay but
Rodger Stone
It what you already described as having a
Wow that was so uncomfortable
Donald Trump is a gay
What's a wingman
Say it say it say he's not gay
Stagette you son-of-a-b****
You say it
You know what those
Rodger Stone
His wingman there wasn't anything to do with Russia
He was just having extramarital Affairs all the time that Rodger
To cheat on your wife
Really
Rodger Zapp
He's a swinger
Yeah
Other alternative is cheating on his wife
Is like super tense
To be with Rodger make sense why he's hanging out with Rodger
Hang out with this woman
And it's also clear that Rogers
Explain to Alex because Alex
What's keeps bringing up the
Did not make that another correlation about
You know what appeared
Bright
To really make clear
Is that
When we started
There were two people
In this room
Not you and I is that room
Is a mentally ill person who stalked a lady
It was on the show as a novel
Rather guy wants to be his daddy
Hey Mel got through it
I still can't believe it this isn't like a terrible as Adele.
As we've gotten to this point now
I think that clip represents the point at which
Who's Crazy in this room
Chef
Michael Rotondo
In trouble
But now Alex is more crazy than
For the rest
How is it still going on
What are you talkin about we're more than halfway.
I will say this
Don't get scared
The last clip
I couldn't make a cut in it
It's 5 minutes long
Bryce dad
Alex
Disgusting
More wingman
Stuff
He gets a little conflicted about whether or not he cares about
Rodger
I would say that
Common interests
Can come and go as
As the concerns coming out
So but I mean
That you can you can have a long-lasting
Support from people who have come in person you and just frustrated
Everybody knows
For the Rogers
Don't talk about Everybody's Talkin
Rodger Stone
The book should read
What
Roblox.com
Amazon
Rodger
I need to know what the f*** the deal is
I think there's a little bit of weird conflicted anger that Rodger isn't selling the book exclusive
Second person there
He's clearly in a conversation with this guy was sitting across the table from him
A copy of the book is probably going to go buy it on Amazon
Go fuc yourself
It's a simultaneous plug in love
So Alex is like
If you want to know what the point
Seems like there's not one
There's not much of a
Kind of moving whenever he reject this dude is staying right here in the pocket
And Alex
Just trying to find a weakness like
Okay
Mike has
It's very clearly taken
But
What's your take
Weezer
Personally I
To have
The ideology that you and I both have
Define
Grassroots
Here's what you need to know
Here is where as what I hear is where everything turns
Here is what you need to know is the sentence
You f****** wish Alex never want to hear him say
You never want to be a woman around him that's one thing you never wanted
Caveat
But you you want to hear him say this is what you need to know cuz you know things are about to
To get f***** up
Course they do
Your greatest accomplishment
Is the fact
Emmett you
Are there check expression
You are your ancestors
Is an Ultraman
Miss Universe
Greatest thing that ever happened
Oh my God is the greatest thing you've ever done
Do you know what the name of this clip is on my computer
White breeding for Generations has led to you
That is exactly what he think
And the talk of the like you know your ancestors are
Through you and stuff like that
But trust me
He spells it out more here
It deeply Disturbed
Okay
Other universes
Measurements
Googleplex
Sure
In the entire vortex
The Dominion
Existence
Hey Alex
Everybody
That's literally true of everybody
Except black people
I mean he wouldn't say this
Two black guy
Pure wipes
It does feel that way
Feels very much like breeding and the ancestry that he's calling back to and stuff like that
Oh yeah it really really feels like
This is this is definitely
He was raised to believe that white people are chosen
He was raised to believe that white people are superior which makes it
So f***** up
In Subway the Amy that he's trying to raise a thirty-year-old
But he's obsessed with
Both versions of eugenic
Look
Yeah your grace what this is about your greatest
Success
But also there's more to it
This is Mike Down Club
I think this is one of the most profoundly f*****-up things I've ever heard Alex Jones say
For a while
What he's about to start talking about
Is like
This is why we're talking about Mike Rotondo
Alright
She says this Chicago
Procreator
You and I
Relationship
Electrochemical
Manifestation
Teleportation
What
Dartmouth University
Show this is this is Jess
Call lavash next level
A lot of people
We're all from each other
They're good people
Is like in my mother's womb
Come out
Boy
Do you think about that
Is that
Human
Existence
The very concept of
Recognize that eventually a threat would come
And so it
Putting forth a plan of action
Time to defeat
V4
Against Earth
You're thinking of this a little kid from The Fifth Element
Undoubtedly like
Savior complex
This is Jesus
Roast
This
He's
Severe mental illness
Is
She needs to be off the streets brother needs to go to a hospital but like
Remain in the hospital forever from like the 50
That idea when I was in my mother's womb
Maybe he's a ghost maybe this is an asylum story where he was killed in an 1800 The Mentalist
Silo and now we've come back to haunt us now through the radio
That like you were looking at it too broad
You're talking about there was going to be a threat
Jacques lineage now granted
That would be most of the people
Related to The Tudors
He's Confederate royalty
Holyshit
In the womb
He was downloaded
Through the mitochondria
Like in the movie move on
And the mitochondrial DNA is Eddie Murphy as Mushu
I don't understand
There's trouble
Shookbang
Globalist
The guy they got a foot
You know thank God Alex
We're on the job globalism
Globalism
It's a lot of the Hot Load Anon
And it also
What's fiddle the visits make you angry
Black people shirt off
Which is also about your life
Genetics
Weaponized
Also
Like a lot of this
Is
Crib from various
Message Board post
About the Illuminati
So this is right this is all stuff
Really important
This is
Like you know how Kerry Cassidy we'll talk to a murderer
Do you know stuff about
Secret space program
It's becoming very clear to me especially as I look into 2009 stuff
Readouts primary source
Stuff like that
He's the exact same in terms of not being
Like
Not caring about where he's getting
Mason from
As if you didn't talk to Mark Richards
He just reads box
He read the blogs and message boards and then
Pretends that they are like
This is the truth
S*** like that
It's insane
Now I've just titled I'm deeply concerned about Alex's well-being
That's a good thing to be
Ancestors had will it existed and were amazing
I want to be clear
He's talkin gobbledygook
Understand everything you say
You know it's not like he's talking above my head
I just he's using unnecessarily stupid words
Right
The function of me is what you're saying
All of that
Is physically
Powerline
Went through
Alexander stand-up
That's amazing
You had a child
Doesn't mean perfect
What
More powerful individuals
Jump
Which is going to be
Kill this experiment
Experiment
This is all
Message boards. My bread basket
There's flickers of Harrison Bergeron
Like a lot of this stuff about the idea
You know
Humanity
I read on like above
Top secret
Aldi's
Jackhole blogs
That I used to read when I was younger it smokes a lot of weed
He's just relaying all kinds of
Feel like you should know better than I would come down
That was fun
What is like watching a scary movie
Alex
Come on now
Just fix it at
It's just online immersive fix
And that's all that you're engaging in
Space
It's real because his ancestors
Diversification
Traffic
So
Again
This next clip is just labeled
Deeply upset
But I know that it's accurate
You have to build
The Stairway To The Rock
You gotta
Pillars of Fire
Future
Slow build
To the next level
People that decided
Secret
The door
You don't ask
For the trapdoor
Adore
What do you think
But first of all
I love
No
Demi Lovato
What it is deeply upsetting
Metaphysical stuff
Concrete terms
Like they're standing at a physical door
And they don't know there's a trapdoor if you're trying to stop people from going through the door
It's a sad physically really sad
The sudden appearance of a trapdoor
Trapdoor
Crocodile
But they're really chill crocodiles
Roy's Auto Campground
Saudi
Thing is to like a lot of this is really it in Harkins
Is Harkins to again
Themes that are
Like these these ideas are discussed on
He's nwl Illuminati message boards online
That horseshit
Where do you buy
You got a building
Not the movie
Does the Moneytree
What what what is that
Roosevelt Island
Talk about this
Universe and couldn't
The trick
Call real quick
Yeah is the idea that Alex is going on this long
About like
Isadora
My favorite things
Because you wants to know
What is it
Or is not in here
About the origin of these other things that are not
Stop
Where's the
Perfect
Numbers words
But in the knowledge of evil
His knowledge of distortion
Okay
Because we operate
With a knowledgeable
Are you following this
Yes he's saying because we know good and evil it's okay for us to manipulate and distort things
Well because if you don't use the knowledge of evil than yours right because these other people are manipulating and distorting things so why shouldn't I
Do what I need to be able to golf because I'm so good
To be a sheep like
That's like what there was an a****** who's like you should be
Because it's so seductive interview
Portuguese chose not to be
You shouldn't try when in the cinema
Just got to stop
Further
Cuz I just basically said on-air is it because I'm so good
Google
He's getting so into that
Space
Where he's like I want to talk so big I wanted to try and use my flowery language
Don't you want to be like me
Rodger Stone has been Trump's wingman for 30 years
Deliberately choose not to use the knowledge of evil rat totally this is a funny moment where we've gotten out of
Esoteric stuff now
There's a couple of
Funny things that happen
And then there's this last
Clip where they're having to differ
Free conversations with each other
And it's so f****** my black but before we get to that Mike comes in
It seems like it's going to be a critique
Trump
And then it turns red
Very weird
Do you ruined Donald Trump
His personal doctor
Yes
She didn't it seem like it's going to end up being like
Why would he do that
Yeah it doesn't matter
Turn down because you didn't experience running the VA
Yeah that was why
President
Wrightwood CA
Based on that person
I think Mike started this question
In a critical way
Pushback on his eye
Oh yeah yeah
He's trying to make
Alex
Yeah a little bit
I think I think there's a decent
From everything I can
Tell her I would understand
Cuz I don't have to sit in
It's just that
It also by the way it wasn't just the Trump try dewpoint is the personal presidential doctor
Didn't fire the other guy too
So are you
Put in his own and also his personal doctor may have committed
Possible possible
The ones that he denied was just the one and it was like I was driving like that
So now Alex
Decides
I got to fix this kid
Was going to work
Didn't do it
I can't be around him
He's miserable miserable talking to this guy he's like
I got to find a new way and here's his first
Vale
You should want me to call you at 1.
Dollars
To show you not because
Global Solutions
Million people most of them are retarded
This is been dead bodies
Right now
Alex is pretending to like
His hand over the mic
It's almost like he's talking
Hey
You know the cameras it's not really on right now
There's 7 billion people in the world most of them a retard
Not like you and me buddy
It's like
That moment when the knife salesman breaks
Character
This is
Crazy
But also I do like the idea of like
Hey
Charged $1,000 for 20 interviews and got 20 grand
Go back to the part where he's Whispering because
You need to experience this
As a whole this is
So f***** up
There's 7 billion people most of them are retarded
This is been dead by Design
This is Alex Jones
He's in the bathroom
There's 7 billion people most of them are retarded
This is
Call everybody
I really don't be part of this process
I've been offered to be part of it
I don't want you to
Good
But you repeating it back seat
I'm talking to Standard Operating procedure at sizewell
Okay
Oh there
Caught a lullaby cotton to transfer the computers
Choices is not a
Great thanks
Haggai
Alex
What you're saying
Easy
Brainiac conscience
What do you think isn't
Smart
He's just using words that he knows
Don't make sense to most people
Will confuse people
Exactly
Space War exactly
The cosmic
It's a googolplex
Yeah
A decimal point
Sub something
Section
Globes
Just like
It's not I'm not confused by what he saying I'm parsing his ideas
And pudding like
Things that are unrelated together comfortable with
But when he's like
This is how
People at the talk talk
Manifesting does Brainiac consciousness
He's trying to impress him
Easter saying
Hey
Send everybody home
Stupid
Yeah I'm not you and I aren't like that and look they
Pacific fire weapons and kill everybody with
Drew you know it I don't want
That's the guy being like I wouldn't screw you up to kill you
Girl
I wouldn't know where to be able to devolve anyway you're not going to die
It's totally fine I'm a brainiac
Alex is playing out
His own
Sitting here
No
Alex
Severe mental illness
This is like
I mean I know we're not Professionals in the Goldwater
Rule does exist but
This dude's crazy
Does Mexico have Alex asks about drugs
Everybody with that no
Whatever
Federal
What they call
Autism sisteron term for it
Buick Century
So he is trying to
No no no
No no no no
We doing what are you doing
He is trying to find something to pin autism
What oil
You know people would say you're something called
You ever been around
He is trying to find a way
To blame this guy's
Autism
On the globalist
I bet he'll be able to stay
Jordan Jordan you're right on a bunch of
These things with oil paint
You are not
Here's the next clip
This is one of the
That level of thought
Because it does seem like that's what Alex would be
It turns out what he saying
Is it complete non sequitur question that leads to one of
Razius
Suggestions I've ever heard a human being make for another human being
I bet when that suggestion is
Alex gets really mad and rejected
He feels very very sad
You would make a little
$3,000
Right up until the point
Berkeley
Check 83094
Cancel
And that was a mess
That was a mess
Suggestion is because he doesn't want him to work there anymore
We got the first suggestion which is charged the media thousand dollars to go on their shows which
She's probably too late for that
Probably
If you had a website you could just sell oil paintings and get paid to make statements
I could come up with 50 different things for you to do
So you wouldn't listen to any of them listen to me say you should sell oil painting
With your
Stupid response that I'm not an artist
Social media influencer
Holy created by millennials
So
Yeah okay that's right
Beautiful
Time traveling Powerline
I don't think it's someone being not willing to do it and put in effort when you say you should do something you can't do
Did they say
I think that would be scamming people by selling them
The con
You know how you don't make things
Yeah now that you're famous people want those things
And you can just sell it
Open communication earlier in the day about giving him a job
You know how lame this guy would be around
Hey Rob do like to sexually harass people
It's fun
No one complains except for that time that I accidentally hired a black girl
Then I'm going to hire a disc
Kill
My dad is going to have to deal with HR complaints without on a boat is not even at the office ever
What are we going to do
He's a pissed-off mood like
Used LOL
What was he was he thinking about
Hey Jorge whe was a war criminal
The next
Alex asked
For his final thoughts
And this is where I think Mike thinks he already has
Okay
It demeans
Doing with each other in working together for
Taking steps
Forgetting yours going up the steps
Stefan the second step
I get it which is
Out the f****** door
Jordan
We've hit the last clip
Yeah
I apologize in advance
This is 5 minutes long
You got to give me a high sign when you want me to posit or something like that
Is two men
Having
Conversation with each other
Neither of them understand what the other is saying
What is in a high-status position
In this case is Alex
It doesn't want to put up with the other guy's bulshit
God dammit this is so crazy
And also rest
Okay
Labrador retriever German Shepherd mix and match when I was busted years old
Highway
The sweet dog every time we try to go
Eyebrows like timers old
Pictures old man
Heart attack
It was murder
We thought the point
Everytime I turn the volume up my truck or my dad's Land Cruiser
He will get scared
Put ya
Promise
So real quick
Just because
It's very obvious
What he's talking about
Superjeweler that
Lord I'm trying to help you
Call you dog
He couldn't get over that trauma
I never beat the dog
I love that dog
I buried that. Myself
Childhood
But he couldn't pass the drama
He couldn't trust me to get in the car
Feeling this about Mike
What are you talkin about himself
There is no doubt in my mind
It is
Using Mike as a surrogate to get it out
And deal with it
Hated that
I have been hurt
I have pain from the past that I'm unable to get over
Putting that on Mike
Very clearly because my
Hasn't said anything to indicate any of this
I was whoever it was got to be 5.7
My I grew up with a
And shoot my friend for years
And I remind
We're just different.
Video
Came into my bedroom one day and
He brought her to the pound and there's enough
Will he was asleep
Really
What
Real quick
The day before on the early on the show Alex said that his mom kicked him out of the house
Because he was dating a woman who like to yell at his mom
So the idea that his dog died and you realize that it's time to get out of the house child
That doesn't match
An hour earlier
Also
This dog story
Competition
Surround
I don't want to hear it and then later it died
From this
From this point forward to conversations that are happening
Very easy
You don't want to go along with me trying to help you
Now trying to be like
Why did you take my dad thought I couldn't handle that
The flavor for the next couple minutes
Is that
People get trauma and drama
Because the dog
The dog
Pissed itself
Even though we took it on
This is
The beginning of the clip he said I don't want to call you a dog
I'm about to
Give a metaphor and allegory
What is it you're speculating that
Father.
How you where you're getting information
That particular people was good.
It was traumatizing
Not go to the vet
Bright
Mama horse
That was always different
Like a dog
The story is about
Walk the dog
Traumatized
Time to pick it up on
Because of whoever it was taken away from
But every time I took it somewhere
Metaphysical
The prowl the dogs
You are
Patient zero
I figured the same thing over and over again
It's a whole new world
Will talk to you soon
John Doe
Lesbian
That's the f****** bad end
That's awful
Maybe we should have said this at the beginning
What is occurring in that Dynamic there was
Him
Almost
Existing within the
Trauma that Alex
Saying that the dog was in
Like Mike sitting there going like
So you're saying that my father didn't think I was emotionally strong enough
Did you get that information
About this in advance
Right there looking for
The Smoking Gun
Alex Jones
Is Iraq
I'm saying something
Welt.de traumatized and now is an incapable of moving beyond
While at the same time the traumatized
Moving on past the traumas that he's looking at two separate pieces
I do not understand
One word
Tracking
This conversation that Alex is having with him about
The inability to get over the trauma is what made the dog piss on him and not be able to go along with stuff
Rotondo is Mike
Where to
He latched onto Alex thought you were too weak
That could fill the gap of
Explaining
Metaphorical getting thrown out of a car was and that's why he as opposed to
With just being like
About
Yeah that makes a lot more sense that makes that makes
Dual conversations not as
Curious
And I mean if I were in his shoes
And someone knows not
Has Alex pretty quirky
I would still be like
What's your problem
Why did you say that to me
Hope the interview
Himself gives the Freudian slip whenever he's like
You're you're you're also the Alex
You are a broken person
And you're not good at you're trying to fix
6u time you're trying to push you away
Disneyland
Play
You would watches me like
The dumbest f******
And s*** I've ever heard
The dumbest f****** s*** I've ever heard before my life
Yeah but especially because it's like we cover the Infowars world there's only like
Six varieties of episodes or things
And usually happen
Cool boy alex trying to
To fix himself through Daddy's interesting late motif
But the idea that we're doing a show about
A crazy person
You fixed his own life
Probably trying to distract from the fact like
He's not going to prison but he's got to be worried that like
I got answers
Question
Like there's going to be a come-to-jesus moment whether I like it or not
He's probably pretty stressed out about that
Now I want I want to say that I tried to jump into this right at the end
Episode
F*** us for not kind of
Michael Rotondo is someone
Who has
History
Westside
Him
Stocking a lady
Now
I don't know enough of the details of that to save it maybe his mental illness
Contributed to that
Most likely probably did
Excuse the behavior
What is
The reason that this is funny
And the reason we're laughing at it is not because Mike
Whatever mental illness he has
We're laughing
Because of Alex's stupidity and complete obliviousness
Do the situation
Every complete
That's what's funny
It's not laughing at Mike
Although
Certainly not letting him off the hook
Like this reminds you so much
70s movies
Where the kid is growing up in the seventies and his dad was a raised in the fifties and he's doing the whole distance
Parenting thing
Getting drunk and yelling at this kid
Not able to understand why he likes the rock music or whatever why it was Italian
Use the whole f****** thing
Breaking away
But there's no
At the same time there's no third act where the dad comes around and realizes for my Sunday doesn't work
Do stuff but he's really cool
Or whatever you know
Bike race
None of that
No grown men with daddy issues being daddy issue Daddy
Each other difficult troubling part is that like
You do some
Sometimes as you listen to this
Forget like that's a thirty-year-old
Yeah I know right
Was being done completely differently
I think it might be able to handle himself
Quite Pizza
Like you made a couple points that were counter two things that Alex believe
The last episode when he said
I don't think that it's great to have people not having food
Right trying to raise taxes
Going to get rid of crime
Do the 5G isn't really that scary
Like he's not
Idiots out there a word he's unable to understand what's appropriate to a certain degree
But I don't know if it's
To a clinical level
Stupid if someone wasn't
Screaming at him right
Complete brat
I'm trying to be like
My pills with fruit giving a confession to all that bull
If it wasn't for 5
Street hours
Yeah if Alex was there
You said it was a good idea or whatever it is
It still might have done it
Injustice it look
Do you know what 5 years coming through gives a s*** about the justice
5G stands for 5 jump
There's
This brings us to
BBQ back to even
Ivar Michael Rotondo Saga
Unless
3 weeks from now
To do it I feel like we don't I think we got to the phone no
It's not about him
What kind of headspace
And so are we wish everyone
Reconcile with your father's actually Alex does say that
In the section where he's talking about how like
Genetically it's a power line goes down
He's like whatever your dad did you just going right
Zion Pelicans
Thank you for being late
You don't know what is that I don't know either but like
You know where bucilla I don't I don't want no part of that.
Episode
This is only funny because Alex
Yeah absolutely
Website.com
Right now it's not
Becomes apparent
It will be and I will have to race memory
The parrot
A white background so we're good, great
There's a lot of fun stuff to enjoy on there
Flow
We're on Facebook
Beerland
Okay
The show is starting at 10
Do you have
I'm cool with it
I'm just hoping anybody shows
Night okay
I believe it's you
I guess it is
Well the really the only choice he certainly not going to tell Mike rotundo to f*** himself
Alex is a bad choice I will go with Reverend Brown
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work