Alex
About Alex
Dan Dan
If you had never heard this
Ever
10 Page Long review about Kanye
Never speaks about the music at all it was at all
Podcast
Superfluous
Pitchfork reviews
Maybe is never actually heard me
Carroll County West Virginia
I know a lot about Alex Jones
Pitchfork reviews
Serviceable about 30 years
Now what everybody reevaluate
Back in the past we're going over 2,000
The business
He was on again
Rotondo
The beach in California
Mike rotundo
He was on again
Facebook group
I watched his third appearance
He is there with guy who is mysteriously come out of the woodwork
And found out that he is a distant cousin
Of Mike
Who is
I decided to let Mike live with him
Okay so they're going to tag team
Remote
Negotiation
Cuz Mike doesn't want
Infowars reporter
Does
To do it
Really clearly like I want Mike be
Cookies
Stored up same as something with him not as good
Talking about
I'm your distant cousin Tony is in the thing that somebody says before they rob
Mother's grandmother's
Father said they were Skyping in from Tony's sisters
Child's bedroom
I've good stuff
Is
Which is right
Alex
Interview by saying
Well Mike dollars to come down here and tell
Billions of dollars of free press
You understand
You are straight-up on are saying to this guy's face
I explore a little bit I use you as a prop
Do you understand how Imo
Vulcans of late capitalism myself need to be taken down
Because I
Do you understand about whether or not you ever see your kid again
I don't give a s*** that you're homeless made
So much free
I'm a sociopath
So we're not going to cover that cover anything else
Visa Vie Mike Rotondo unless there's
Major break in the story
Rainbows
That's a character
Dude the other thing I want to say is that
People's responses
My immediate reaction
Whenever someone
Criticism
Like I said
They just reflect upon things
People say
And I process
There is a fair criticism
Episode
Clear enough
About
The difference
Pieces of the story that we were talking
Think about
We kind of were coming from a perspective of we believe that Mike is on the spec
Right
Mentally ill
Not simultaneous unrelated
Clear in our language
Like they were connected and I apologize for that
Perception I don't think that's fair
Probably the best reason that you can take it that we don't mean that is
We didn't consider it in the Moana
Because it's so obvious
Distance to things are unrelated
The previous 700 episodes or however many weeks done should give you some sense of where we're at
Like the most Progressive most equal rights
You still got exclude somebody and it turns out
Asperger's people got a gun.
Because I've been reflecting on this a little bit
I don't believe either of those two things
Been having a great week
I've been walking I've been getting up in the morning and taking walks there's a short super nice
Taking these walk
Taking a walk
Thirty in the morning
Early Morning Rain
Wrong
Early morning walk
Having a great time with
Mistreat my business
What do I see out of the side of my eye I see a moped with a sidecar
How does that not set your day off in the right direction
Is awesome
A moped with a sidecar
5 blocks
Alright miracles do happen
I heard a squirrel hit the ground from a tree
Terrifying
Was like
Sit drop
Embarrassed
And then you see and there's one guy in the eye
You and you and me die with a secret
You and me to Watkins out cutter yesterday
There's some reflection involved
Sorry we weren't more precise in our language
Better
Sorry
Sometimes you just don't realize that there are people listen
It's kind of like
It's shocking that anybody listen to me
Appreciate
The transition I was waiting for
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
I'm not doing it
Highlander
Look the first name that came to mind
Not the one that I want to say
Becomes themselves a Raptor
Princess
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Control
I bet you money
Abused
Joseph Stalin
So I guess you know what's crazy about that.
Progressively darker
Papaya papaya papaya
Real hard
We know that at least is consistent because
Does not mention Maui hate such icons
It's been around a long time
We appreciate it
Thank you so much thank you
Put out the I will be breaking down
None dare call it conspiracy if we have 250 owners
I'm having a great time
I've written about
25 pages about the first 10 pages right
How long is this
It's like
I've ridden so much and it started with a really clinical town where I'm at
I about pissed off
Graduated to do in Las Vegas somebody actually meant
That's what you're here for real.
It's very fun
Sportsman's Warehouse
You can go to our website knowledge will be
Coming out
If we can talk to you by June 1st
Start July 1st
I guess whenever we get to 15
Today
When I asked
I think so
Stop
Save-A-Lot
Makeup
Out of
So we're going over February 2nd and 3rd
Three Days Grace
It's I just wasn't
Things are but next week
We start with
Stuff is weird
Paydirt
Some of the unified field theory of Alex
Much sharper Focus really soon
Cuz if we recall
February 27th
Tea party rally at the first major
What we're seeing right now is
Is the building
Towards
Whether or not Alex has any awareness of
The amount of coke money
Oregon today's episode
I have chemical lobotomy
Okay
Threat or first moment of silence
So Jordan last
Disgust
I believe we left off on
January 29th
If that's
Correctly let me confirm that
Acknowledge
Yes we are
Of January is where we left off last time
September 9th
On the 30th
Here's another Austin
Weirdo
He does
Speak with a gentleman
A country twang
Deerfield Inn
Luna Lovegood
Southern February 1st
Someday
Alex
Text Justin Reed
Either replaces interview with David Icke
This is super weird
February 2nd
Alex
So I went to Ultimate Fighting Championship
Joe Rogan
He doesn't matter
But
Big news
Las Vegas last night
Play Runaway
Craze looks in their eyes
Important
10th Planet jiu jitsu
Nope
Even laugh
What do the books
February 2nd
UFC event
Alex Jones Eddie Bravo zworld intersected
Play jobs because they don't get paid enough
Even though that f****** a****** billionaire or whatever f****** s*** like
All right now
Location of UFC fighters as
Employees
The woman
Fighter who
I've literally just read an article about it
Is article about the implication
Pro wrestling
These workers is
Unbelievable
And then they die
Two years later because of the high amount they make
The work that they do not considering that like
The training is work
Right
WWE
Travel is
You have to
You have to have somebody who trains with Sprite
Like you have to you're running a small business need a body man
Bentley
Is better
Employees
We all got a national Union
Tea Party
Gear
We will
The effects of that
Might be real
Flashlight we're down here in Austin Texas and
Revolutionary development
RadioShack
And more
Revolutionary changes are afoot at Infowars Alex Jones LLC
Right around the time
Giant
Cash influx
In two organizations like
Organization
Like
Sean Hannity
Yeah it's curious
Allergist in timing
We just had a
Huge
And there's something's going to happen in the next couple weeks or whatever.
Negotiate my contract Obama
About this episode about how he's going to hire more people and but how we're going to push through
And expand even though the economy is getting worse
Pretty amazing
To me some sort of
Now will you match that with the fact that
He's been saying that a money bomb is
Coming up
To get a sense
A couple times throughout history
Convenient
Weird point in 2015 it happened
Couple months before he joined
Maybe a couple weeks after 10
Anderson
Who is what he was talking about the headwaters in Minnesota
License to sell gold bullion
Byford
Midas resources
A couple weeks later Alex Jones does a money bomb
Right now
Pimpin the money Bob right around the beginning of the
It's very interesting these timing
The timing Things Are
Super Bazaar
Free car washes
Bookkeeping can't make a
Are Cason Court office
But I think as time goes on it's
These date
The circumstantial case is going
To be damned
It already is it
When we started this podcast ahead
But I used to have a pet
Pretty clear that he's full of s***
Yep pretty clear that
Sold out
4 years
Eddie Bravo
Sweet
This guy used to be present
Guy get a peanut song
Read about impropriety and perhaps
People with
View it as a way for him to be corrupt
The office of the presidency must be above the appearance
Even the appearance
Of corruption Dan alone actually being f***
Whatever
Most corrupt
Seat belts
To believe
The Jimmy Carter
Reasonable ass cat
But
Bisquick
That story is kevon
As well
Believe it
At this point in time isn't he in another country building homes for people
Just because what
Is a guy from weed
Which is an organization that we're going to have to talk about a lot
Future
Sarah a bunch of weirdos
Vaguely related to Ron
Paul
Cordingly related to 9/11
Vaguely related to Alex Jones
SMS
Little bit never even die
Weird world 2009
And has formed
What out
Cornered
Costco
Learning books at a Costco
Here's the audio
During our
Thank you
Clearly a 9-11 truther right there
Light to someone who wants
Was
Yeah sure I'm even to do with it
It's not me but I think it'd be nice if they wanted their victims
One of the only thing about that
Given what this all the ship that went down during Jimmy Carter's presidency
I could totally see him being a little bit on the side of like
We had another bush in there so who knows
He might've done it
Personally
Anything
Not going to say that at Costco
Conditions
Amendment to the Constitution
So at this point Alex
Takes a piss
On the show on the 2nd
Here's one guest
Dan Hamburgers
Stateside
Members
Disease
Really short.
Yeah
State representative
Alright in the legislature
Isn't using for like one term and then he laughed
Got involved with
The Green Party
And also a guru
OK Google swap meet
I don't know I don't look into it much past affected
He started hanging out with a swamp
Hey man
How dare you have you ever read the autobiography of a yogi
Those dudes
Whitlow
Charismatic spiritual leader
Unlike
Speaking of which
I want to give a preamp to go fuc yourself
Listen to podcasts out on me
Howl app
It's about time
Scott
The camera in like a
Youth speaks in a lilting voice using neuro-linguistic
Programming safe little trick
Tell you about like your
Your path lies and your soul and stuff like that
She's been around forever used to watch videos of her back when I was
F****** stupid
Smoke weed all the time
Credibly gorgeous
Now
Here's why I say f***
I know already
The dispatch
It's just going to be another one in the long line of these buckets
Cereal knock-off podcast
Did end up covering a topic
Interesting
And then I don't know
Look at that was that one about Sarah Franklin that cult leader guy
Maybe
F****** crazy dude
And then in the last episode you like you know what they might have felt like they belong
Maybe there's Heaven's Gate and all of us
Aldi's
Maybe she's just like an MSR ASMR
No it's out there's a crew called
He watched some of her videos
Thursday
They're absolutely
I get the impulse
To make those episode
Like those shows like that
Oh
Maybe
Where can I buy like 20 episodes
And we're going to do roughly all the episodes up until the point where climate change
Destroyed
And then we'll be like
But you know what Alex Jones did make a lot of info Warriors very happy
He made
Computer security
Fear
It's just like horror movies
How dare you
Are you
Do a podcast where you invest
Navigate some subject in the entire thing is about how like
Here's the evidence that they're f****** with people just like double back to be like
Nothing
Oh I hate it
I will to listen to
By the score
But just because I
Great write-up at the end of that podcast
So
I'll expect a call for
Citizen watch
Disturbance
But he wants to talk to Alex
About
About his free speech
Oh I was hoping to frosting
Royal XO
You know every time the
Sofrito
Bead store
Kobe gives his right
To travel with all the lights
Every time
The
Covington
Idiot
The right
Stud through the courts
And what beasts
Yeah
Esports
They have
Deborah
Neighborhood
Together
A route that is
Individual
File a waiver of
Tort
The judge
Adult judges
File against them
And they will back on
Because communities
The Super Bowl
First we need to file a waiver of tort which
If enough judges get it
Misters benches ideas
Idea is that if enough
Judges get these they're going to be like
Everyone knows
A waiver of tort whenever my neighbor is not allowed to
Travel without a license
How dare they
Amazing
For Alex
These waivers
BBQs anymore
I do not want to talk.
We are just
Text the song
They're trying to pick me up
Break up
Remember to fight this battle
B b b b
Well I have a
Do boarded by front yard
Smoke with me
1 ft long
Is anyone warming
The Waco that lays it all out
As what
These sources
Or getting the doctor
Imitation of what I'm saying
Hey buddy
Hey buddy if I got to trim my f****** head
Property value
Airport
Delivery
I have a billboard
There's clearly not a real billboard
61p
It's 865
Also
Forklift
I mean I understand
I get it
I do I really do get it
I get it I don't
To this billboard
Billboard
You're not thinking the right
I think you got it 60 ft teams billboard
60 ft I feel like he's I may have I may have heard maybe a 12 x 6
10 of May
Dicks basketball
Brookstone
How many yards
That is one
One-fifth of a football field
Get a holding penalty
Then you have person 22 go
You got it you got a penalty
No you got to have to Pedal
The size of the Billboards
In terms of free speech
I don't
Don't
No empathy situation
I get it
The reason is because of
Like neighborhood association
Agreements with you
Because like is your pudding if you're living in a place where you
Can put up a billboard
Conceivably the
People will
Also we're in a residential neighborhood on their houses
You're not going to get
How many new people seeing that billboard
Seems like it would be
Super effective
Guys just let me
Let me tell you some
You have no idea
The kind of Morning Sun
You are going to get out
Now your evening sunlight
It's going to be blocked by a giant
One that says
Take your morning
The windows good luck
So in this next clip Alex
I have a
Will take you to
So if Alex talks about how
Trilateral Commission
Involved
Week-old
The presidency
This is evolve very quickly
Lakeside Mall
American Union
I'm watching Davos Switzerland
Real big
Extemporaneously to reading something
She's quoting a source
Therealeisha
87 members
Obama's appointments
Entire
U.s. membership
There's a real
People
I mean I don't know I
I think
There are simpler explanation
Cabals
Yeah
Collateral
You sure
Where is the trilateral commission
Sing sovereignty
Federal Commission
Usurping Sovereign yeah
Write something about
Papers
He's trying to Anchor in your brain
Call a few papers and
Trilateral commission usurping sovereignty
Call you cervix prison
Weather like
You and your house
Trilateral Commission
Patrick wood called trilateral Commission
Nailed it the sequel
Literally reading
He just. He spent that he was no real analysis other and
You just reads off verbatim
From this
Post
Originally on website
Dot-com I like
We're going to get the news
No it's still there
Call technocracy.com ibloom
Becoming technocracy
50 red pill Expo that I desperately want to go to coming up in
Spokane
User what are the headlines
The other speaker
This is terrible
The other speakers
It's not a meritocracy
G Edward Griffin
Who's the guy who wrote the beach
Jekyll Island Federal Reserve
What about
The climate changed
Denial
Yuba
Larry Pratt gun owners for America
Alex Jones
If you don't know
More extreme version of
NRA
Jesse Lee Peterson
Who's the guy who I recommend
No one Google
Alright
He is a guy who is what he's a preacher
Maybe former conservative radio hosts
Really don't like that
You someone who we will never talk about probably
On the show
Worried vide Stoppers
Cognition
I've listened to a couple of interviews that he's done he's got some
I don't know if I don't know if it's Alzheimer
But there's something
Aspiring
In his head
There's an inability to
I don't know how to describe
Watching him interview
I want you to interview with David
Progressive
YouTube talk show host
Do way his brain
Worked in
Responses
Atwood Terrace
I hated him
But I also was like
It was like one of those I don't know how you
Oh boy
I feel like there might be
Might be
No
For real genuine
It made me
Parasite
Shutter also Twila brace
Countertop Shelf
That's nice
Works for a number of coke fundoodata organizations
That's right
LaVoy finicum
The Oregon standoff
People who got murdered by the police
Alright
Is she still calling for a sheriff investigate that
Appears to be entirely sponsored by Freedom Force
International
So I was looking
The news
Cuz I'm like I don't know
It's a great f***
Name and I don't know the organization editorial
You just know they got news
They got views
I can sense
From Patrick Wood
Yeah I don't know if maybe this is
Okay
Patrick Wood views on the news no
Because he doesn't run
Published
Okay
Couple days
Headlines
British government jail
Wait today
It's still like the last couple of days in like 20 years
Dial rim
Is the story about Tommy Robert
Headlines
You got arrested for
Couple months ago you got arrested
For disturbing the peace
Precipitating
Agitating and trying to start a riot Courthouse where a Muslim was on trial
We got arrested for that weirdo in the 1700
So he got arrested for that and then
The judge said
But you're a badge
But I'm going to give you a sin
If you get arrested
You're going to jail for that
How long was it
I don't know
Don't care
Particular interest in following Robinson news
I feel like there should be
It look if there is mandatory minimum sentences
Feel like there should be mandatory life
Just like
I just let you know I'm not even not even like
Prison that is
Tough just like a
You're over there in this little like a playground playground
Okay I don't know how
Play grandma got to go to Europe
The other dealer headline that I was attracted
Trailer brakes
Whatever
If... All right.
That's gold right there that's the most clickbait
This is by a guy named
Wooldridge
You draw stages throughout the body
In the last 48 hours
Pic, DeRozan
Media jobs
Displacement
By the show star Roseanne Barr
Comparison of Valerie Jarrett a Muslim
Who's singing Obama to a character
Put the Hussain in there
And doesn't even say former president because
Former Barack Obama
Then starts another
Which as you know equipped biggest oxymoron on this planet
Muslim
Prove themselves
Who's to be the most racist religious economic political organization
Former President George W bush to a monkey with a
Another word of racism from the CNN and like-minded media Outlet yeah
On Facebook
Black women
You can read it
I ready
Quartz as like you know but I'm still up still got on the page
It's a black women
Ite
Because of the color of their white skin
Is white a color
If the apps
I always got that confused
The combination of all colors black
Is the absence of color
It seems like it should be but it's not looking alright alright
Black rappers use the n-word in their songs with such vulgarities
They hate themselves
Just trust themselves
And totally negate themselves as human beings
Never a word from the mainstream media
!
You only get one! Uses it as a writer
You don't support Miss Black America
System itself
True for Black Entertainment Television their Futures only black actor
!
If you don't support the United Negro College Fund which supports
With blacks only never a word from the races
Remedia!
You would be racist if you don't support the TV sitcom
Which produces and features only black
If America the mainstream media
Free with all white national basketball league for television
Hawaii colleges
Malaysian America and those
Editorial note
That was cold the past
Almost
Look if you had a
70 years
And you wouldn't allow black layers to do it and you had an all-black leaks
Boat it was the black lady that was racist
Old Satchel Paige
He was just a
Racist
Hey bro
What are you doing what is this article really
Salerno's on this is the end of this
Is Brett
Look at the racism of Muslims in America
Alright
It's horrible dirty barbaric and growing
Weezy Muslims pushing
A Sharia law which presents the most racist organization in the world
Muslim Conquest in America charges to a fraction of our current problem
Mainstream media
In the end
Races don't naturally get along with one another
Traffic
Men
America should be one for whites and African people black
That is
No that's not even
All right races don't naturally get along with one another
Who prefer to be among their own
On a personal level all I can do is
Respect all Races colors and ethnic groups
Every person to make down the road of life
Alright
Frosty
UNLV
So that's crazy and very racist
That's the publication
News with you
I got you all right I was just reading from that blog
Great
Is there publisher that
Seriously calls into question like what else
What else are they called
How do I
White America for whites black
Africa
Oh yeah
My biggest issue with him
As a representative of the white race apparel
Figure out what the f****** oxymoron
Figure out what irony is
Other figure out your f****** talking about
Cuz you're goddamn
Embedded satire
That's true
It's so poor
Call Michelle
Episode
Answer question
The first two questions are unimportant
Has to do it
The people who are responsible for what we're in
When considering the history of bolshevism and cotton
The Communist Manifesto
When considering the protocols of
Elders of Zion
Considering her
Harold rosenthal's interview and many other
What do you think for life
Zionism in the world
And the New World Order is
Do you think Zionism is a genuine racing
And really that's about all I have
So you girls want
The question
The first to question
Stumbles around a little bit
Third question
Here's an
The white supremacist
Orland
Japan
And
Animal
It's a harbor
Type system
Who is this
Jordan
Straight up Alex Jones
Call Israel
System of apartheid system
Yeah cuz that's what it is
Weird
And they just
Liberally murdered
Israel
I don't know man it's I mean we've already encountered this
In terms of
15 something
The different about him in the past
It's good to like I just remind
I've come to a point where I believe earlier the episode I told you that
Questions
Letter answer
Yeah
And
The wannabe
At least more like a lot of
Pointing directly
Me to Bugs Bunny's rap
And one of them
Is here in this eclipse today
I would say in 2009 has been a really shock
Surprising
Blue
About
Pretty sizable like
Look here
Local currencies
The market is a separation of powers
Within the entire monetary
Are the symbols of credit
That's really dumb
Wow
That's like
I understand
Thought comes
Was only one currency in the world
Control control all stereo
Smaller level it's like if is one currency in our country
Controls
Country
Exactly you have that sort of mentality
But
Boy we done this experiment
Like we have
No
Simple about it
I don't I don't remember exactly how he felt about it
He had competing
The thing is like it in the early 1900s
We had
And late 1800s
We had States
It just had their own currency
What put out their own currency
Tons and tons
I want you run into that with is
Interstate
Acceptance of other currencies
They work in Missouri
Sometimes
Disney
Competing with Six Flags
Disney bucks competing with dollars
Because Disney books
And dollars both work in Disney
Buck's don't work outside
Unless
We allow for the
Free and Fair competition between current and the only way for all of that to really
Ever been in any meaningful way
First of all you need coordination between all of these people who put out these various currency
I made all need to be tied to a commodity or something
Call Tanner
We're basically pretty much could be silver or copper or whatever
Roman coins from Egypt
Beast coins
How much is 1
75 South
Nationalized
I've been doing
8 ton
Research
Conspiracy
Beginning of the Federal Reserve
A lot of it has to do about
Hundreds of pages of
Congressional Record from 19
Like I've been
The figure out exactly like
What's going on what are they lying about where are the specific lies
Come on the show
We need State currency
Like
Dislike
You didn't
You don't know why we have a federal response understand why we have a national currency
You understand why
The gold standard was abandoned to begin with
Like
Because all that stuff created so many problems
And those problem
One of those outside of
Like legitimately
Right side of the Great Depression
We have not had instance
Of a severe back run
Spence
Write the Federal Reserve was founded
The stimulus package was
Federal Reserve came about in like what 1914
And then
The Great Depression
There were three instances of
Collapse
Close to
Since then
Look before that in the 15 years prior to
For the 25 years or so prior to the foundation of the Federal Reserve
53 Giant
Like it happened all the time back then
This this whole ship
Is nonsense
And the fact that Alex
That means like
I don't think you've thought about this Alex
I think what you want
Is the Sun
That's the thing about
Conservatives
Want
A real they don't want a solution
They want the problem to be what they thinking
They wanted micro problem just like when he was like
When the government doesn't have as much money it's just like when the family dozen
You have much as much
Right
Nearby okay
Why you think that makes sense
That makes sense practically
Practice
That's a f****** dumbass idea that you can pause
I just don't want
They just don't want to accept
That there are evidence-based solution
Handle
It needs to be an ideological
EBay salute
Whatever you are advocating has been done before
I didn't work sorry dude
Never work
Because of the
I'm so happy
I wasn't alive
When the consequences
Where around
Brave the real
Leave a bunch of liars
Wework
Together back in the seven
Later
I don't want you to take that I just I was just speaking
Glibly
When I said that
Really all you want
We watch local currency
Local
Stuff like that
Hi
He doesn't he's not
Because he wants
A unified whole with
Sweden currency
Because he wants those
Be separate from each
He wants
Secession he doesn't want the United
It's all happening
I should be clear this is beginning of February 3rd
Children
Pirates
Official title
These revolutionaries
Actually you're a counter cleaner Revolution
Jokes
Cool boy
Shades of present-day Alex in terms of going out to break with a murder threat
But he doesn't do an act
Is Prison Planet.
TV membership Ray documentaries
He didn't even put out the Obama Deception
So like
Probably years away from him having
You not
The thing that does make me
Is
In a like
With the quote from the Declaration
Something that I am
Kind of interested in right now is
What happened
Trump is
It was like what happens after we prove that he cheated
Right
All of his things should be invalidated
Isn't that the only thing that makes sense
Is if he is impeached
Rid of
Also we should be able to kill him for treason right
Yeah I think so
We don't we don't have access
Information
If that is the case then that is the prescribed punishment
So-so
Why
Zoso
Shouldn't
F****** everything
Be president
You're wrong like Gorsuch
Should be gone
There's no way to do that
Right there's no way to really do it Beyond going to have like a revolution
Pooping like that on everything
What happened
We are the cops right now
Because all those question
Continuity-of-government
No one knew what was going to happen
If the president died
At that stage where there is no plan for the continuity of government
If we find nefarious heydrich
Like trying to continue being a country after we find out that
Our country was stolen
You'll end up with
Is
I've no idea.
I was going to try to say something but I have no idea
Like my suspicion is everybody's going to try and
Tend
That it's like
Know this
This is normal
Like we just we just
We just impeach Mike Pence as president
Pencil Park
Him being lame.
Decisions I can make
I don't know. I don't know
I don't know how to drive
I feel like it
It's it's so irresponsible for us to assume that we've no
The capital T truth about stuff you can see how everyone
What is behaving like runaway artists
Curry facts
Trump's lawyers
Don't
Testify
Because
You're going to commit perjury
Fight
It's not good
It's not good is my favorite
Is my favorite legal b******* right now I love it
It's absolutely not true
That's not corrupt
Who cares we got too much to get through shut this line
Alright
Because that's
I just want to bring back in
The sharp Focus
We got overthrow the government
Because they're coming after us
They're going to kill you
We have to overthrow the government
Makes it
Not that impressive
You said something later that brings it into a little bit
More Focus
Okay we'll talk about it when we get there but for now I found another
It's different but
That is his
Support
I'm certain organs
Control
Supposedly
Alex hate to be NRA now doesn't like the NRA and 289
He's fans of Larry Pratt group gun owners for America
And I can't remember the exact name of the group there's a group called like Jews for the preservation
Kindergartener Shelf
Find recovering on like
The next episode
It's in February
He has the guy from that on and that guy
He is aggressive
Becca's notes
Yeah
And he is he is rude
Total crude on on one level because
I think this is actually one of the
One of the differences between present-day and pass
Could be
I would be willing to be like all right I got you Alex you're not
That big of a hypocrite for this
Because I don't think 2009 the NRA with as crazy as it is
They still were a bunch of s***
And Alex's
Wrong
To say they want to help take away
They weren't like the
Ted Nugent
Oliver North
That wing of
Of crazy gun show
It wasn't
It wasn't like
People probably want
Without giving up his principal be against the back then
And before them now
I kind of could I could accept
But it also track
With all the different changes
Write like all the other stuff that we have up on the board
What are the
The policies
But the Koch brothers are probably ask
Switch
He was to take their money they support the NRA
This Alex Jones
Has a paranoia towards almost
But if the organization has a blanket paranoia right now
It's almost it's almost
Anything that has his power as these organization
Like kind of
Is it concept any group
They could possibly switch
Towards Liberty
Or whatever
It also includes him
More than an hour of television
Prisonplanet.com
So
Imagine
Running around
Once your house is your property
So the only reason I kept
I think it's demonstrating
Like
Really
Really nice
Recent version of
Because he's
Getting it
Getting this stuff
Really scary
And then he's like are we going to go ape in the infowar
Which is kind of a buried plug
For himself
Visit the infowar I run the infowar are you going to support that spiritual plug
What's going on there
The mode
So I think that it's really interesting
You see like this is the colonel
This is the Steve that will germinate
Can grow into that
It is now been proven super
Like if we just point it out
Like now that's that's true.
Betsy DeVos we just pointed out that she stopped
Thinking about diversity
Yeah I like science
She just stopped
All of the things that protect
Here's a joke
You point out with the globalist
To do a call-out in point out what races
David amor
God
Don't we have enough on Scott Pruitt
The very least for the rest of his life
Agree
We can't do the show if your schedule is like this
This is the last time that we have Jordan has a showroom
Derby record
Agree agree
The issue is also that none of that stuff
What to talk about
Tommy Brigade now he's always been
Award
This point out from his buddy Mike Rivero call is guy who has that show
Really happened
Also on the Genesis
Communications now
He's also the guy
Reminder who has
Heated Alex Jones
After the two of them had a bit of a fight about whether or not Alex was
Israel
Mike Rivero
And now works for the
Man I just wish you were still around to tell us what really happened
Nada
It's still around
Rivera shows up again a week and a half into Obama's
I'm already calling into token president not because of his skin color but
He was going to cut defense spending it was a token amount
Prisoners are still other places
How many breakups a complaint
Different words
Anyway at this point
Two of them are having conversation
Guess what comes back up
Knuckle gate 2009
Congressional
Congressional leadership
I said I'll do whatever I want and then you'll notice that the story has evolved a little bit
Quotations
Anyway
Before
Continue to do it
Stand up
President address
You president
President like that terrible mayor of Chicago
According to the New York ballerina
I'm a pretty pretty ballerina crack knuckle cracking knuckle
Quoted as cracking is not
I don't know man
Wrote
They wrote down asterisk
Crack
Asterisk
In quotation he's also
Quoting like I don't know if it's
New York Times
Alex just going based off what we need
Told him
Anyway this
Yeah that was very defiant if I had been Barack Obama in that situation Ron would have been fired
Right there on the spot
Barack Obama does not move
To establish
Or assert his control over the White House
Process
He's basically he's already crippled for the rest of his administration
Freddy business owner Magic
Soldier
The Empire's on the Run
Okay
Spoiler alert
Is that did not start massage
Also
Chicago
He did vault
Tear
That
F****** Trader
Fat
He
Tear with
Israeli
It's kind of weird that American citizen volunteer for a foreign government
Service
Benjamin Emanuel
Has named Yahoo
Bye Arab Skirmish with Arab
Describe
Brothers
Honor of his brother
I can't reveal what his original is burnt
Was
Pretty hyper
Israel Israel
Kind of guy
I filled the idea that wrong would go over there
Like that make
Weird at all
To say that he's an IDF Soldier is
Stretch
And then
He's not American
Born
Mom
And they say Obama was born in Hawaii
Jewish crazy
Like that kind
He's willing to say that
In 2009 but it's just
Further proof
You did
State
Play Kenny willekes
Blonde who are
Like scoring potshot
The only reason you would
Critique
Throw out his dad created Mossad
And he's not an American
He's an idea Soldier
Like
I hate
The state of Israel
Like that is just
Is a proxy for Israel in terms of
Someone to punch
If not
The entirety of Israel
He is
Using Israel as the
To discredit this guy
Knowing full well that a lot of info Warriors
It's very hard to say
Chicken and egg
Who do you hate more the chicken or the egg
It's not quite the same as the way we understand
Did the caller say he doesn't believe they're Obama can prove
Sounds right the reason is because
This neck
The caller
Is
F****** amazing
Okay
Never heard about before
Endive
Now besides that I have a very important question
Years ago in 2004
Gastonia show
His name was
Retired Colonel dondi Grand Prix
And I listen to that interview and I was highly impressed I even
That you have the transcript
I want to see a real quick
Episode
The ground
Trinidad out and he said
Wouldn't he
Member of The Joint Chiefs of Staff
But one time
Okay no
He said that
70%
He was
In communication on a weekly basis
With friends of his
Work in the Pentagon
And he said that 70
I believe it was 70% of the highest
Is 17 military time
We're on our
That they were going
Better by blackbear
Wondering what happened to that and another thing is
It just blows my mind that there is no
The change to me like
There is some people
In the military higher up
With some integrity
Break
He had major heart problems
Too many race cars
Serious medical trouble
Winston County Branford
Man I don't even know this dude still alive
The Grand Prix you f****** a****** for Faith and are
Also
Make me uncomfortable
That's too South
2 South
North of the Mason-Dixon Line price new
You are a
Whatever I
I swear to
God
I can't listen to an episode from 2009
Is lousy with weirdos
But I was never listening
Don't Grand Prix isn't even the gaskets on the show gets brought up and now I get to learn about
So I went and found the transcript of this
To cut clips of it cuz you have to
It's a mess how I was able to pull it up on my phone
But
Grand Prix
Alright
Playing throw it on me
It's spelled D o n n
Space
Grand
Chiari
It's not is at least
It's not that
He claims
72-hour non
Stop Symposium military
Commercial and recreational pilot
Right after 9/11
72 hours non
Stop Non-Stop
Hangout
3 days
No sleeping
Just a bunch of Pilots
Screaming at each other
I bet unanimously
9/11 were not controlled by human Pilots
Had to have been remote
A 24-page report
The Grand Prix
Load up a 24-page report
I need send it to the government
It may not
Who was General Shelton at the time but
You can't come up with the name at all
Pretty funny
Cuz none of these assholes
All these weird mysterious deep military resources you have don't know who's in
Charge of s***
Just seems to be a problem
Do you know why
Cuz they're not really
They know the names of the people who are
So.
The government
Had to have been aware of
Alex
These copies got out in the original
Quote
I got a telephone call and I
It was the fifth
March
2002 State at the time
You said no,
Use the Marine Corps lingo Semper Fi Semper Fidelis
Always
And so that
To him
2dr Grand Prix held was an indication that like food I know that I got your message
Well that's because his name was Steve the Indy 500
Gray
General Shelton
I don't know this individual Shelton tells Popular Mechanics
Quote the name doesn't ring a bell and I certainly never saw a report you rendered alleging there was
Some type of conspiracy
Or that the National Guard pilot shot down flight 93
They're part of the North
Airborne
Letting you do
Interesting Lee
His Symposium to 72 hours in poziom and the report that came out of it have old
Ever
Been reported by Infowars
Added under newspaper Imports
Portugal
Interview
Never give the name of
Newspaper the news in Portugal
Can't work can't work with this
So this
Also come on
The fox app
Them had
In that 2004 interview
If you can get shaved
Savannah Grand Prix
He says
You see as I outlined in book 1
He wrote a three-part book which will get you in a second
As outlined in book 12 as well
Frozen book 3
On the verge of a military coup d'etat
And this was long
78 days of bombing
Pilots who worked with that possibility
I was told on the morning of September 11th
Only it was an administrative or we call it cold today
The story of which was
Call the silmarillion
Over reversed
Grand Prix
Yes in fact
Alex
Counter-revolutionary Hunter
Counter counter-revolution
You're getting picking up AAA
How to recoup
It's been a piece of
Like his world
Where he's pitching that narrative
As being like
Oh
There there
People in the military who are fighting against
The coup that was launched on the morning of September 11th by Rumsfeld wolfowitz
Right near Albany
People fighting
You been doing this over
Over and over again
I don't think anyone realized
I don't see this ever talked about like
Alex Jones reportaj
Being like Oh yeah this feeling to make that argument
Lowlife
Like a junior in high school
Fire time
Gundam Wing and was like
Oso reality right there
The fun part about this interview Grand Prix solution
He's a goddamn military insurrection
Is Alex
I mean it's
They're federalizing everything
Militarizing everything
The classic takeover are they not
Yes they are
Alex
Am I bringing clearly at book 3 the only way we can stop it is with a classic counter coup d'etat
For the military stuff
Last
The classic included
Or bring the military in
And under the Aegis of the disemboweling the civilian
Hierarchy Federal
I'd like that he can use the word
You just correct
That's nice
Ulta
Classic counter-coup
I think it probably only I don't want I don't want the new Coke
That's some b******* right there
Bring me back to
Classic Coca-Cola
I think it only exists in propaganda because
Is always a narrative
Used to just
Stuff I sucked up ax
By being like we were just fighting against the more f***** up preemptive strike
Israel using miniature nuclear weapons
John Legend Wild
Call him ddg
Determine
There were no hijackers on 9/11
There were no cell phone calls
Everybody craft pilots and crew were unconscious within 8 to 2:18
If you can take it for
From their eight
18 minutes
Weirdly specific and yet at the same time
Time frame
Also he gives out his phone number
It's another phone number on the air
Alyx review
I don't know cuz someone might have it
Someone mood
Alex reveals he is amazing
We're about to go back to the colonel and his amazing revelation of the North Dakota National Guard
That I had been moved to Langley Virginia before 9/11
Play 93 / Pennsylvania
He says he's talked to the pilot
His info checks out
Danganronpa reviews
Who shot down United 93
They are National Guards have pointed out that ghiberti is a lieutenant colonel not a major
So that doesn't work he was nowhere near United 93 on
He took off from Fargo North Dakota and flew to Bozeman Montana to pick up Edge
Jacoby Jones
Director
Are the New York State emergency
Give me Zen flute Jacoby from Montana to Albany New York so Jacobi coordinator
17000 rescue workers engaged
Famous Tate
Response to 9/11
Jacobi confirms the Days event
I was in Big Sky for an emerging
Manager's meeting
Someone called to say that a text
16 West Bozeman
From there we flew to Albany
Jacoby is out
Flight 93
Dismiss that because we're turning Colonel Gibney
Was with me at the time
It disgusts me to see this
Because the public is being misled
More than anything else
Disgust me because it brings up
Spheres
It brings up hope
It brings up all sorts of feelings
Not only
To the victim's family but to all the individuals throughout the country
And the world for that matter
I get angry at the misinformation
So it seems like you would probably lying about that
Because
There's also electronic records of where these plans were or gibboney
Open system problems when you look into Colonel John de Grand Prix
The first of them is it he's always references a turtle but there's no consensus
To be a colonel of
The Bayou that Alex reads on his show says that he's a retired army colonel
The Grand Prix refers to himself as both an Air Force
Turtle and various blurpee post about himself
Online
The Marines in the Air Force
Also refer to him as a car on the cover
Bio on Amazon
Probably because
Did put that in
Is the barbarians
Inside the gates
He asserts that the Holocaust
Android
Teen harder to create
The state of Israel
Pretty much all his arguments writings of History go back to an argument
Basically
The Grand Prix
Too good it's real fun
Liar in a lot of a lot of information
Some of it
Definitely
Comes from hemp
Alex gets back just a second
There is real discussion out there about secession we have an independent in Hawaii
We just found it on the fact that Hawaii is not legal and so I would think that as we
Song with the fall of Rome
As the central government bankrupt itself the outlying provinces
Start to break away and assert their independence
And I think ultimately that's what we're going to see happen again
Hartford
Got to go away to come back baby
That's History
They weren't quite a work
Is what Alex's
Real
Makeup
Good riddance also fake
Break up
The United
Yeah is what you really want
Do you like well maybe we'll come back together any non globalist government
But that's
Foolish
Well that was actually kind of thing that I was talking to you about
A while back
I like
Every 10 years we should have a re-up
It's like every state is like do you want to stay in the United States or no
At the difference
Yeah it's different but it's theirs
The reason that
He thinks we're going to come back together is because
He doesn't
No
But what is telling you on is the idea that
We will
Out of choice
Hanging together is almost like tradition
Is that if we break up
Everybody good
You understand
Union breaks
He knows that it
The union breaks
Is never going to join another Union
Gay right
Texas is never going to join another Union vet
Allows women access to abortion
Texas is never going to join
Someplace that
It's not
Basically a Christian
Reconstruction
Government
Theocracy
I'm not
Let's let him go
You're not looking at this
Bright
Mexico Tire like
All the states
Become
Dissolved in terms of the federal government
Every state for themselves
What if you were trying to reconcile
Attitude of Doberman
Most of that middle
It doesn't vote with Progressive
Value
Rextac
Yes dude end up with a
Giant
Chunk in the middle
That becomes a white
Christian ethnos
The Pacific coast
Richard be there
Wrightwood Avenue Inc
And that's about it
That's not good
It's not good
Toyota
Well you know he doesn't
He does understand that absolutely.
Does not
Have the capability
To extrapolate consequence
This to his balls
I think I think on Sunday best
You at best you're right when he knows the text
This won't come back
That knows a lot of the Country Walk
Comeback ideas
Swath of the country
Which it would be even weirder because Chicago would be
With the code
And that'll be garbage everywhere else
I think he knows that
Texas
In particular
A lot of other states
Could create a Confederacy
Oklahoma
Isaac
He knows that those places would have the votes
Needed
Create
Where are we
Talking tough time
Bright
Here's the situation
Did he understand the endgame but he's advocating for
You disagree
We can agree to disagree on that
In the near future
About that
I sent from my position
Understand
Some of these states
App Store
He lives in would be able to create
Kinder version of the
Never possibly exist as long as people are involved
Opera
So
You got your recording
Sunday this is your last night
Adulation
Cut
Where Alex Jones breaks down music video by 3 Doors Down
I thought you were out at the first hour in my punishment is I don't get the
Hear the
Construction
3 Doors Down videos
This is the worst thing that I've ever done
Citizen Soldier
3 Doors Down
It does it's a song about how people are stupid
Soldiers
Alex
We came out 2007
Originally
Height of 3 Doors Down
3 Doors Down in 2008 the end of 2008
February 2009
I don't know why you're so mad about this is old news
Year-and-a-half-old song
Three or four months
Alex
The last hours of the show really really pissed off
About
The Superbowl come
Does the Superbowl
Commercials was 2000
One of the big commercials does Hulu have that commercial with Alec Baldwin
Hulu sucking people brains out
No
But I think
There were aliens they're sucking out your brain because you're watching
Too much Hulu
But it was
It was based on the idea that
Alec Baldwin has a nefarious voice and then also
Correctly the aliens were the aliens
From
Underline
Alex never make this up text text
I'm not mad that's just crazy
This we do need
Alex
Super mad about a commercial for
High-fructose corn
Alright
Commercials
Hey I heard
High fructose corn syrup inside like poison
Another like
It's not as bad as you think
Exact
Commercial
Not that bad
It's not like
I heard the pipeline is going to destroy the Native Americans only only leaks five times
That back
Juan Valdez Coffee commercial is not
Corn syrup is good
Hey temperature
Not going to kill you in the back
You eat chips those are probably is bad
I can take on the commercial
It's
Some of the best analysis I've ever heard of my life
Add after add after add after add after that after that
Super Bowl
Real quick I saw a couple of these
For a fact a couple of these corn syrup
No dudes
Basics
Galaxy
The Popsicles
Under the sea
Wind
That was a Target man who
And associated
Lollipop symbolizes sex
Okay
Advertising what when what
Your last year in high school.
Before you drop that trust me to write bicycle is sex
I took advertising because
He could have had a
Sheffield did you remember that commercial with Britney Spears and Bob Dole
Where the fireworks went off
Bob Dylan's looking and then Britney Spears dancing and then the fireworks go off in your life that's a man coming
And they're sitting there with it
Popsicle
This is a Garden of Eden in the middle of the garden is easy is this flute
Applebee's
What's a gaucho
I just
In the garden
She's happy to Shana children
And she shows that she's more knowledgeable
Loving giggles
There are others
This is what they're doing
What other layers are there
Keep.
I also want to stress
Popsicle
Bro
It popsicle
Crazy
Sex
Red red is the color of slightly higher with Giggles nails
Children running around leaves rustling
Everybody like that psychology everybody likes it
Now
There are a lot of other like
The popsicle stick
That's got a joke on there
Everybody likes jokes
When you're licking the pops
Psychostick thinking about your own dick
Everybody likes those at Merrick
Super always there all week
There's always a metaphor for sex and they're also a humor
Humor
I took advertising
I mean like look
It do it this thing that's really fun about this
Is like
Yes Alex is making a diesel
That like
Beer it'll get me chicks
Advertise
It's like it's like taking that
Like School of analysis
Xact ROM Direct
I tried to apply that to like
I see I've seen these commercials they are not at home
Alex Jones murder
And they were like
We got to find out if he's
He's fit to stand
Play Kaya Tressa
They be like
I don't think so
IQ is way too low
He's probably kill somebody
Trick him into thinking
He is innocent
He's like
The Fugitive
Every all humans
MSRP
That would be
Is this guy is crazy
It would just be a drawing of mist
Subpoena
It was probably mr. peanut
I don't know where that but I love it
Nicely done
B roster
All around
It's your fault
Zanies fault it's also dumb degrandpre spell dammit dgdp probably mostly his fault
Yeah
We're on Facebook
Austin
Beerland
Temp
Phuc yea
Some seats are going to be brought
Absolute
Cutting this episode
No
I think I do
I'm going to
The president can pardon
I was actually strolling
Through the rest of this
Yeah
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color