Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
Damn
If you were a necklace so mad
Pre-show conversation
Started with Britney Spears and that ended with
I believe
But if the means are getting everybody murdered
Maybe change your f****** mean
We're putting that aside I would save the day
If you were that
Are you
I don't even know I'm too on my deals just from the job
I was I was sleeping
Clearly much like Lazarus I have
From the tomb
Describing this show to Lazarus
Okay I know a lot about
And my buddy over here I don't know shitt
So that's it that's the show that's out that's what we're all about
Sorry there's a need to at least look
We did
Sincerely argue about Britney Spears music for about 15 minutes and that led into an argument
Whether or not it's okay to act like the other side
Whether or not it's appropriate adopted the tactics
Of your enemies when they are children
It's not a stupid question I rejected V
And that's why we lose
Anyway
Not going to make us lose
Still couple of new donors this first one
Smokey Copeland
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Positive things about probably but I don't actually know who they are
Argued with frequently
Thank you so much Robert
Appreciate that thank you so much Robert there's two that was really great sir
But Robert Arista project
People really just want to hear the Brittany
A argument
We should we should record a depression I want to say
Episode ass off
We're already like the month I got I got all kinds of fire and fury
Time to f****** fight
Rough
Not into this episode for today
Did you know the 2009
Maybe we need a little bit of a shift
Is the weather decided to do is look into Project Camelot
And I found
Some of that you want to talk about
Yeah the disappointment in your voice
Says to me that we're not doing
I thought the subject
It's way too big
Project Camelot hilarious story to tell you as soon as I can
Necessary research
That's on the back burner
It was like alright modern-day Alex it is
Coordinates on Monday
So I looked on Sunday like
This is no good either I'm not going to do this episode
What's falls into my lap
But people posting
Alex
Tweeting out a video
Okay Mike Austin Bernie Sanders
LAX airport
Yeah stuff that I want to see I'm not allowed to I didn't tag you in
Alright
It's really
It's really a bummer it's it's really an indication of how
Pressing the s*** is getting in the present-day Mike Rotondo stuff the guy
Wooden house
Him being on Alex Jones Show
It goes
It walks the line from like
This is kind of funny and weird
This is really sad this is becoming a very sad story
The American office in British
Subway
Like when he's
Trying to harass Bernie Sanders in the airport
It's like
Stitches
This is not funny
He's got his done along with him
Hey son is yelling questions at Bernie
I don't think you do that unless you know his son's voice
And stuff like that
The bomber
Specifically like that's a stimulant kind of
Evidence of it but like that kind of behavior I haven't seen outside of people who do like
Coke
I don't know if his
His supplements
Create the same kind of
Affect
He's sweaty
Not from running
He's just sweaty and like disheveled
And
Grinding his jaw
Bother an old Senator at the airport
And it seems like
This made me love it or leave it
It made me
So sad. Because I love Bernie or anything like that
This is Bank.
So I decided let's stay in the past
And we are going
To continue on with 2009
Business
February 4th and February 5th episode
All right here is an out-of-context drop
Don Mann flecainide
Alright alright alright alright
That is the kind of
White
I'm fine are you fine with time
We got we got to start at year on February 4th
Yes
A week and a half
Roundabout
2 weeks
Into Barack Obama's presidency
Still boggles
That we keep
Saying that because
Is it like in 2 weeks
Not even Jesse starts with
Obama's already going to kills man the battle station
Spiral further out of control
At the same time Obama is just like
Moving in
You just got people within like Michelle is like
Get rid of that f****** couch George W bush is a f****** a******
Anyway here's where his head's at on February 4th
Star67
Okay
You've been fairly contradictory within the same sentence
I don't think
Bush ever had a 92 /
I don't think so
Possible
Alex
In inaugural
Inauguration
Vienna a bombing at an inauguration
You have become
Just a. Like I said you were adjective
Okay I'll go with you
I got
I'm just I'm just going by contact
Clues he might
Still believe that the inauguration has
Roku I forgot I was on the day of the inauguration so I don't remember
Actually Megyn Kelly
A little bit of a past and a little bit of leeway because his head is still in a really f***** up play
Because the FEMA camp
House resolution
Yazzy
Dissenters
Rides at
And I'm getting confirmation
Tim from the chat room that
D2 right after right after 9/11
It's pretty high Erica sucks you know but you know how it goes
You America
Announcer
Never really
What's up
I mean if he
He saying that they announce
What he's describing is basically like the back page of Mad Magazine
Dinosaur movie like the number 47
Overlay these bills on top of each other
He's copying a cutting and pasting different magazine articles and sending it in the letter
Exactly right
Precisely right
The only book he ever brings up when he talks about reading books about Nazis
Books about now
But hold on
All about
How to control
I probably read
On The Purge
Admitting
They say
The only way to get up to those numbers is to include a mismanagement and famine stuff like that
We only killed 60 million
People that we
And I'd studied with the professors
That were pretty accomplished
Some pretty like
Seriously
Credible
Sources
Yeah they read big-time players
Legitimately most scholars in the world
About oral tradition
For a class I took on homeric Greek
Okay I started with another group Professor who was
Nationally
Recognize in the world of Greek studies class from a guy
Who was probably in the top
Three Cheese's nail rapper
Yeah but that's not the point
Wannabe high-level Scholars
World of like
Alexander
Mesopotamia
I'm not
I'm saying what did I never heard from any of them is how many books they read
Not once
Did Professor McClure come over and say like
Hey look you should listen to what I think about
Because I've read 75 books about home
Well maglu had those big coke bottle glasses and he would always walk
Can it was a shock
Delightful
Mike's amazing conversationalist so I'm just saying it whenever I hear someone
Once a like I read this many books
On this stuff
What I hear is you haven't asked
Because people who are actual Scholars on stuff don't really
They were doing
But why
So you
As a way to impress be
That's the only reason that you would say 50 or 60 bucks
That's because the people that you are talking to are illiterate never have read 50 books
But I don't understand why you think that's a good
Because if you're reading 50 or 60 books about Nazi
Really there's only
Maybe a few perspectives that you
You can have about
You got it
Yeah exactly
Bad genocide
Superbad
It did happen if your book number 4
Then you're getting into Wild
You're either a scholar
And you teach
Venus of the six other books
Did you read looking for an argument
You know you're looking for something to backup your feelings
Maybe the Nazis weren't so bad
Alex
Some people don't
Talk about is real
They can't believe the shows for real
I'm for real
In this prominent of a fashion would actually get up
Of course
I'm looking
I know
I know they
And frankly I'm into Humanity
Live forever
Is that like to play
I love you
Okay
So the only reason that I can't equip as long as
Cuz it's kind of derivative
Before 2009
Did that same s*** that like I'm Immortal as long as my lying is here in the past
Is living on through me ago
He
Peace
Of his weird spirituality made me uncomfortable here in 2009
Like the genetic mysticism bulshit if you're like 40 and you got a few kids and like
Like Spiral paranoia I could see it
Since he was like 9 he's like by age
Fairy clothes
So that's crazy
Very interesting
That's like a Perpetual in the background
I meant secondarily I kept all that in because
He doesn't really care even about like
The things you saying it's all just
Avenue for him to be like yes this is real
What does that mean
That means I'm big boy
I am a big boy
Believe the show is real because if it's real that means I'm
Super Brave
Kind of what you trying to reinforce in his audience
I kind of feel uncomfortable with anybody who's really in
Black Levi's 501
Paul Stanley
Even even another like a certain way
Ancestry.com bulshit
Because the wolf
The only way
Reason that you are looking that stuff up is like this Lottery idea of maybe it's
Maybe my jeans are
Special he is kind of what I'm hearing when you start looking up
Where is my genetic lineage from
There's a party that thing
I need
Need to know this because maybe it's really special
People might be motivated by that but also its
Justice like a b
Some people are just like
Isn't this curious
I'm kind of curious about.
Too much
I don't know if there's any
The appropriate diet
You should have this based on where you
Your genetic
The history is
Like where your ancestors are from
I don't know if I should admit that put chicken fingers and fries
I don't know propriate diet for my way
Don't know where that would be geographically but
I don't think you're right
Explains that the globalist
Yes
Are super afraid of the Patriots
And then he tries to scare his
They have called us out and they admit their own counsel
That they are
Invincible
Clip is much longer than this but I want to point out that if that is true
In any way
Yep
It's really not that hard to make them fall
Yep Alex
Conceivably has been doing these videos been doing since then
For that 10 years so if the globalist all you have to do is call them out in like right
Already
Terrified
Have you standing up all you have to do is stand up
It's been 10 years
Furthermore
They're going to kill the president
Is that
If they don't
The globalist
He will not
Make it 10 for the
Write your family
When he says the globalist count
Sprite do you see robes and hoods
100 Global account
Nobody can see each others face
These nuts
Nature of their attack
Is so over-the-top
It's 2
Collapse
About that
Jeff Martin auctions
Pictures of
Boulder dash
Like it
A a frog
You got to follow it up with something better
I would hazard
It is not your government has been hijacked
The state government
Do not be reason that I kept that in so long
Is babe
We're just seeing some fear
Also based on like
The globalist are afraid to but you should be really right there
But then at the end there we continue this be at this thesis that I started
Representing our last episode
Which is the Alex
Hate
Government
To destroy
Big government specially state and local government that's the weird part at the end there I don't know about local
Cousin rappers local
He said that the federal government
Nokia
Is controlled by treaties
Governments are
Which is crazy
Now they're controlled by international trade
GoNoodle
What is what is he in favor of
I don't know like you just want states rights and I understand
Beats are also controlled by these globalist International nonsense
You know who's not controlled
Sheriff's must be must be
How do you have a strut how do you do that like how do you have a city
BV largest
For a County
How do you know
No counties
The county governments could also be subject to for and treat
You know what my city is your home
Dave
Couple guys
We all have a little bit doesn't go anywhere connected
You are now
I don't know how the secretary of state was actually brilliant
As a propaganda technique
Very thirsty where the sentence called
Carbon tax
Is paid to the
The banks
F****** genius
Genius
Because
No
F****** stupid that would never happen and that's insane
But everybody hates the banks because they destroyed the world
Bedtime
It's the same thing that he says about your taxes
He says that all federal taxes
You pay go directly to pay off the national debt
Right on the money that's owed to the Federal Reserve
So all of your taxes are going straight to the Federal Reserve
Complete lie about a quote
Kumquat
Sweets
Misrepresentation what he was talking about
Supernatural
And then because of this none dare call it conspiracy that I'm doing
Juno's Lake
Who owns most of the federal debt
Like the national debt
Cuz it ain't the Federal Reserve
Isn't it
Call bunch
But it's not the only like maybe
Best Western music
Yeah isn't it Vons and such a lot of it is private investors
Private investment
Search for Ian or
Domestic its private Investments also gone come out of Social Security and s*** like that
Good Investments like all this stuff is all just
Not really
Much more complicated pictures
Anyway
I need a certain sense you could
Consider a hedge fund buying up a s*** ton of bond
I suppose like that that's a good way of looking at
But it's not investment in the continued existence of the United
Those bonds are meaningless
If you are trying to overthrow the government
Care about my
All you're doing is a nefarious flared not caring about nothing
Right which is
Behavior usually a huge thing headphones headphones
So
Tristan Wilds.
But
I got to keep trying to keep moving the block
I feel like we're coming out of a little bit
Slow and a little bit of it is because of our
Fight at the top of the show
I meant another bit of it is
But he's clips
Or just kind of
A little bit slow here at the king
I promise you
We're going to get exam my favorite stuff ever heard of the show
There's a pattern pattern to plays out over the course
These two days
Just makes me laugh
So f****** hard
You're going to love it
I don't know why
Hey guys stick around don't know I don't like that last one
Self-conscious about that last clip
I didn't get to go out today
I slept in a little bit
This next
Buddy
Bloody
Hey buddy
I'm doing a lot of finger guns at lately
And this isn't how are you not having a great day
Text Alex talks about
He talks about what it's like
Like to be on the phone with a globulin
You talk about this guy I believe it's
Thomas Barnett is his name
You was going to do an interview with that we've heard him talk about this
Stop us Atlantic bait apparently you started
Slithering lizard on that
Moses I don't know
Extended impression of what it's like
To be on the other end of the phone with the Cowboys
When is next flight
Controller
Just checking
I don't like any of those
There you go
But wait
Literally
Never
Since John Leguizamo
His one-man so fully embodied multiple characters
That was so bad
Even though he tried to use an evil voice
He had some great ideas
I'm not going to lie to you
I'm not going to lie to you that evil voice was really bugging killing it
Maybe Alex
On you
If you start the phone call
With we're going to
To defeat you into
Aggressive whatever answer you get in response to that
A little bit Europe
You got to own a little bit as an adult
Threaten to destroy it started with a high
Maybe maybe even answer your family's doing you win some you lose some
He's trying to destroy the family
The only impression he does on the show your f****** wrong ears the next one
Bernie 415
Most of this
Legitimately
Most
The first hour of this program
Is it real quick little bit
Little bit too similar to the previous
This is actually an impression of like you talking about the globalist
America Unearthed
Pretty close to after the last impression it's sort of another character but in that universe
So you can
Here's my problem
Then I feel like you cut out the part
Of all these clips where he goes
Do you guys like impressions
It wouldn't be crazy if I
What is
Literally right before the clip you were playing right now is be tonight
That's where we're at
Alex took some NyQuil and watch
Braveheart
This is the stand at Helm's Deep all the way
Well
Dark spirit
Alt-right
Haiku
Affiliate
I see the enemy
I can stare right past orders males
I know the spirit
And what you just call
In the Heart of Darkness
Are we now in a Twilight Zone episode what be like
What's going on
Two-Face
Impoverishment
Jordan slave is near
Your death
Is a guarantee
Guarantor
Play change voices
Anymore
Is he saying that to us
What do you mean
I mean he's he's content difference
Who won The Voice
Right
And that's
The character of
The person who is an evil spirit
Write any dozen
Vicente
And then he just keeps going into unless you so to me it's like the voice is like
Doing is your not
You're not
The cuts that are happening
Like
There's a star White
I feel like there's a star goes to
But maybe wearing a bowler hat monocle
Mr. peanut
Nikes Peter Jennings on Masterpiece Theater
Peter Jennings
I don't think you do either
It's right
What you lived
True face
The facsimile of real ale
That's when he slides into his normal voice from that voice it's much easier transition
That's what you're saying
Receive a crazy person
Here's a
Big question
And I think this is one that
Really needs to be answered
Specifically
How long do promises think White
Forever because if he if you forever
F****** crazy we're the ancient enemy of the New World Order
The Republic
You specifically mean wife
Weedon Libby
And I mean I think only the Mormons think we've been here even before we don't talk
Order comes from the Bavarian Illuminati in the black nobility of Venice
I could talk about that
So they were Americans
American Amerigo Vespucci
There might be another f******
Researching about weather
Just can't agree that his
His is the name
Gary Allan lies about Christopher Columbus and what was going on around that.
What gonorrhea I feel like gonorrhea is what
Was going around along that time of it
Research
Appreciate as I pulled up a list of all the hosts
Beasteater
That is a hero
John is a hero
I regret to save it
None of those are the people I was thinking of don't know
I don't know why
Diffusers newsman
How about classic
Was around when I was
Watching it is
The kid but
The name does not ring a bell anyway
Russell Peters
I hear it's David
Sofia liners
Alright
Vet vet
I can
Help but feel like that
That felt like an audition
Monologue
Okay I can see that you know that
Let me show you what I can
Can do
Like he's
He's impressed nobody's listening that's not the audience in Macbeth
Which radar is that place
You know that's what he's doing
Lookout Ford Ranger
I don't know I don't think that's necessarily I don't think I'm accurate I don't think I'm right
It felt like that
Look what I was listening to it I felt like
This is a demonstration of
Skills this is almost like a nuclear attack
What we're capable of
Alex is going into all these demon voices in like
Playground
Pretty pretty pretty pretty strong demonstration of everything that's in your tool kit
When did you want to put him in a play
Like for real
Dover Delaware
No I don't like falls on his head
Made me really just the way that we neutralize Alex's world
Alex
You might be a good actor let's just putting him in like Off-Broadway plays and then maybe
Now maybe
Text now maybe he
Baby starts to really
Fuel
I hate to try to remember plays now
First of all used to know a lot about him first of all
Alex Jones is not going to work and live theater for a number of reasons
We know that
Put it in Tire segment of that like possibility is
Call plays a very marketable commodity in that world because you can't sing
At for musicals
Except for doing the comedy roles who don't have signal in the musical
He done that with me the timing
We can't put those roles
Now he also can't dance
So
I mean
You just got to put your heart
Hearing
From the chat remedies
Goodwill drop off
We get to the first
Alex has Gaston
Video of nevermind
He has a broadcast over the course of these two
That's not a good thing problem do at all
This first one is a gentleman by the name
UCLA law professor
And this is why Alex wants to
He's going to set up
He needs to get
Get out of this interview in this next
Eugene
So essentially what this is is a application of a volume
Is Hillary Clinton
Yeah and she voted for a pay raise for the Secretary of State
Call me before she becomes
Secretary of State because there's a conflict there
In voting for raising
Salary they lower the salary back down
To what would have been before
Benefiting from
Haven't voted for a pay raise
But this
Is unsatisfying for Alex he believes
But they're still in the emoluments argument
I understand that even then
That's such a symbolic
Sure as well right
Oh we were going to give the Secretary of State a pay raise but because
If you accidentally voted for it
You get
20 grand last
Has any expectation
Here I will be Secretary of State principal for trying to become president
Yeah exactly exactly
That wouldn't have helped
It all
Maybe she could
Giving Obama
The appointment
Maybe maybe a little bit
I don't know
Look
The issue that we come away with this like
The real fun is
Like in present-day theme
Massive emoluments problems that we have with before he actually took off
Never brought up any of that
Stupid all this
Dante
Does butthurt liberals complaining about tonight
And now we see in 2009
After Obama's become president
He is
Doing this week s***
About Hillary Clinton being made Secretary of State
There's two things one
That's fun
Hillary Clinton's and play
That means Larry Nichols is probably around the corner
I haven't heard him yet I do alright
And whenever Hillary comes around Larry Nichols is not far behind
Going to see some 2009 nickel
Hypocrisy meme
NOCO
No I know
I'm just I'm just I'm just tired of it how long how long did we
The-daily-show-with-jon-stewart
Side-by-side clips of
People saying the exact
And it didn't do any
Would you rather than
Like would you rather that not
What happened
Right I don't know this point I don't f****** know if there is a
World
Like I don't even know what my ideal world is
Like I don't even
Here's my ideal World transition to make this argument ucla.law
Professor
Not agree
Violated here here either
That it's not like
Senator Clinton is getting any extra money
In her pocket because of the rain
Diminution
When she was about to be appointed
So they're like
We got it we got it
The lawyer has gone native on Rogue
Bagua with lawyers
They go to break and then come back
Republican
Democrats have generally taken
So long as when the
The person
Enters the office
The salary is no more than what it was with the start of the Senator's term
Call Dad
And I think that President should have some weight
What was the
Brownie
Well I think that's right but I am unaware of any
Venereal pasta
Upright law
85 and everybody said no no no
So he's arguably Galaxy's
Such a bad guy
Well hold on
What
Do what what did they give you more slaves
Yeah what the president There is close to the original intent of the founders
Who didn't want blacks to vote slavery
So Alex is having a real tough time with you
Yeah cuz he's like
Who's the lawyer professionally good
The letter of the law violated violation in
Historically Republicans and Democrats
Agree that this is a way of resolving it
70 Years lyrics
The situation was
They wanted Bork
Be in the Supreme Court
They wanted pork in the outfit you got shot down
Their second-place guy was like he had a conflict of interest
Whatever
I'm not doing well here
I got to shift
So as we've heard in 2009 one of his favorite things
Complain about is this LA Times story
Where a lady was on a plane
She spilled a bloody Mary and that she got arrested for terrorism
He's talking to a lawyer
And
Talking about the thing is this is this is Alex's issue
She is so little control
Exposed over and over again like either
Boson that argument about Hillary Clinton but you got nothing here this is really weak
His world
I just want to be super clear about this
Cuz you can go you can listen to
Reposado
Find it I don't want to misrepresent what is actually happening
The lawyer himself does day like
I can you know I understand the people might have a different view on this and they can make that argument but I disagree
He's making his argument at being
Pretty polite to the idea that like
People like Judicial Watch
I don't know I'd like to see their
Yeah I got a lot but if you disagree
Historically
Yxy
I feel like I just want to be clear cuz I feel like I misspoke a little bit there
I'm like I'm paying to get like he's dancing on Alex
I would love to see your
That means
He knows your argument is
You're right
Yeah stupid
Yeah they get into that LA Times
Alex brings it up before commercial break
Because that means
This guy's got 4 minutes
That's not good
Okay
But I do know who spent a lot of coverage
Commercial break I actually looked up a case which I think you're referring to
Jelly time story
About Tamara Jo Freeman
It turns out
He was not prosecuted
Intersection 8802
Plead guilty
To violating a pre-existing
Infected 4249 us
C-section for 6504
Which is interference with flight crew members in attendance
Which sounds like
It is true the Patriot Act
The Patriot Act
Turn off light.
Conspiracy
Yes in fact actually I was reading some comments by a lawyer I know who is this
If you want you can find them at the plea agreement in which he describes what's going on and what's the strategy
The Patriot Act
The flight attendant
Farmington
So Alex is
All good
So long since we've had anybody
No this is
Legit
Started jerking off a little bit
It's so moment-to-moment
He said the moment the guy said it's all over again
I actually had time to read this article Alex
I've made a huge mistake
Terrible idea
But see that's what and I think that this is really interesting that if you if you take
An external View
The entire situation
You disabuse yourself of
Caring about what's happening
And you look at it like
Oh this is why Alec
What does 345 minutes
Demon impression
It's because he needs
To do that in order to get enough people on his side that don't pay attention
To the fact that this lawyer is just picking apart
His narrative
Well know that wasn't
Tomato to the Patriot Act
And it's really not it it's an issue where
Pleaded guilty
T2 interfering with flight staff
And the only way that that is
Punched it all by Patriot Act
Dude's pants definition
From
Actually interfering
Two including alright conspiring attending
To do it
Yeah murder is bad but also attempted murder is bad
If the Patriot Act change
Just murdered
Two attempted murder is also let's throw that in the law
Illegal to
I don't think you have a really
Okay cool there's other things
Complains about the stuff that's
Softest
And weakest
And the part that even I as a dyed-in-the-wool liberal
Do not like
I don't have a problem with that
Like the idea of changing it from
Well I mean I just seen Cody obscurity of someone up
Sprint ant
10 conspiracy
And stuff like that
To like
Kill a stewardess
4 something
You probably counts I guess I'll probably fall under Murder
Let's not get bogged down in this because what happened
Alex
Really sick
And reflect on it and then
How did it go
He's like
Begets to B and reflects
So we know that Alex except that his argument is wheat
And then he decides that yes this law professor
Has a point in eye
No synthesize this information further on in my life
Sits around is like a
Think I wasn't
Reasonable
Admiralty
Sovereign citizen on the lion
Constitution
I love it I love it
So damn much
I love it
Good person I would never
Do that
It's just a
It's just beer.
Erica Hill
What channel
Suggest
In order to put some
He's got to reflect on other guests
But he does like
Such as
Okay
I got call Aaron and
Hundreds of thousands
Aw
Spoiler alert
Car wash
Beckbro ksr1
3 *
It's one of those things like I get it
You want
To have
Like this person
Bi-Lo
You want whatever they can give you
It would be like Patton coming on our show
Caldwell it's still great I love you
I think you're working on Oswalt
No but that's that's right
Confidently say ksr1
You don't know s*** about who this guy is,
You are a guy who gets
Drunk at listen to the highway
Wrong with not doing anything about Hip Hop
No you don't have to
You know that you shouldn't either
No I think you should you should have at the very least a cursory knowledge
All different types
It would be nice
Isaac
It's not wrong
Did not know things
About
Other musical genres
If if
Ghosting
To your periphery
Did you
Just
Reflexively reject them
Or if you pretend you know tons about it
And you don't
Willie Nelson
Waylon Jennings
When when you start getting into Willie Nelson Waylon Jennings we're in a very different world than
Big & Rich
I know but I really was very different world than big and f***
But I was still a little bit of credit
What do you know about George Strait
Snow
The cursory knowledge of diarist
Inexplicable
Loved
Do you know they have to move refrigerators
Remove these color TV
Money for nothing
Boy that song is really f***** up
And not f*** it will never
Ever forget the music
The block animation will haunt me till I die
Do the Walk of Life
Another one
You don't know s*** about Dire Straits
George Strait
You don't have a response
You have a responsibility to but that Eazy-E
The world of country
If we were to have him off the show
I would probably do a lot more
Right listen to the best
Straight you didn't like like
Amarillo by Morning
I hate every
Is big-hit
Is the one word
Police
That that one
All right if you just reject out-of-hand musical-genre you don't know much about than your kind of an a******
Alex is not even doing that
Use the same ksr1 misrepresented in a sycophantic
At the same time
Is that the little bit too much
The only reason I brought up any of that stuff is just I wanted to put I want a picture of your face
Stars like that's what I'm say
The only reason I brought it
On your face that you
Fake get judgemental about people and I don't know anything about country
Alright alright
Alright
You're just different back to the Britney Spears I give it all over anyway interview earlier
Did not
Go Gray
Clearly never met
On this episode
We're not going to listen
Any of it cuz it doesn't really matter
Rob this is actually February 4th 2009 is the first meeting of Alex Jones
Peter Schiff
Economist
Austrian School Economist Peter Schiff
He's on because Ron Paul's out
Directions for
Yes this is synchronicity
Situated I know that they've never spoken before because
You keep saying Ron Paul's out
For you it's not like that
The two of them don't know each other there's no
Whatsoever
An hour
Edit just leave
To Alex then coming back
And being like
Selsun gold
And so clearly
He is even aware enough
Say some scary s*** about the economy
Yeah
More like Failure to Launch
As far as our
Would that be
I don't think they don't like each other
Alright
Brag
You think I was literally says to him
Hey what you tell people what you predicted
Peter Schiff is like
No
There's no there's no snow
Synchronicity in terms
Look like
Everyday
I think in 2009
Bob is the
Preferred
Guy
Just set up Ted Anderson
Gold pictures
Gabion everyday
We got to get more people in that in that
Peter Schiff
Is someone who Ron Paul his advise like this guy could do the job
He could do the job for you he loves gold
We need a Solid 4
Exactly
Need a middle Innings Guiles
Later
Alex has another guest on that he
He's never spoken to
2 / 4
At this one
It's also probably
This is a guy named Peter Wallace
Who was a lawyer in the Reagan White House
He is a guy who
He's been around
He's been around the block
People who actually know stuff like that even though he's a lawyer in the Reagan
You still f******
Nose
Yeah like why Alex
Hubris
That he has
Oh
But
But a three-headed dog that protects against
I think it's
Because he has enough Gaston that like
Can bend the railroad in a bit
He thinks
Or do pick up on like this is what the host
Wants to happen
Uncomfortable
I think he thinks that
This guy Peter Wallace
Alex
I want to talk to him about
And boy he doesn't agree with Alex
Now they're open
Cotton
Collapse
Well I don't know
Anything about any of those things maybe they maybe they are happy
By the way
This literally just wrote down this is why
White voice shed
Call Dad
That we could have
Depression
That's why
The government is acting
In such extraordinary ways
Why the Federal Federal
Reservist
So much for the treasury Department of spending so much
Crazy trying to avoid the possibility of a recession
Because
In the 30s
The diagnosis
This has been that the reason
We had this depression
In the thirties with that the Federal Reserve did not ask
Satisfactorily
As the economy
Declining
So
I think it's I think what they're doing is necessary and I deserve it
The only reason I told you
You shut up is like that
Super important to Alex's
Tire world
The Federal Reserve is acting appropriately
29 stock market crash
Quit because big did not
Interact
They were made to stop
All these pants were happening in the late 1800s early 1900s
View because of
So much fear of them overstepping their bounds
We had a terrible
We had a terrible disaster in the Great Depression
Yeah because they didn't
Sprite and
In 2000 we got a really good example of
Them
I'm stopping it from being way worse than it what could have been
Exact
Disproportionately because of conservative
Yeah but that can't put that on Wallace
This guy is pretty right
He's nailing and I do love
Don't know anything about that
Don't know
With Eugene's
When it was like
I'm trying to talk about this emoluments thing either
Well let's talk about that
So now he's like I was like well
I got to find
I got to find some
I got to find something to talk about
So he brings up another one of his narrative
Chihuahuas
You certain
No
It's not heard about that
Delightful
So there's that all about it all about it
Alex tries again
MarketWatch
Didn't see that
Did not see that
Talked about on the upstairs light
To be like
Jimmy
Then what
Give me something
What it's like to be you know like maybe you're on a bed date
You met online
Tender or some sort of like
You don't know much about each other and you're sitting there on the date and I like actually don't like sex
You like oral
Mutual masturbation does that work for you
Never heard of it I got to go
That's kind of what's happening it's like the f******
First down
He's negotiating down to that lady at the North American Union
I have not heard about that that sounds crazy okay
As a as a response to Alex
I don't know
The f*** are you talking about
Lawyer whatever the
I'll be clear about it there interview goes much longer than
But it doesn't really has much more subs
It's more
It's more of like Bruce
Alright
I'm going well
Peter Schiff but that one's just
It is what it is
Do you have this
This first interview with Eugene
And then afterwards I was like
American lawyer in here agree with me
Here is what he says after this
But I feel like I feel like he's a loser
Yeah
We had
We need him Haiti's if he's got the ear of many people
Voice caller
Caller
Cardigan
Where he's like
Alex
We need him
We need him for that.
Could you not be a bit
I think it's
Interesting
Angle to take
Washington d.c. if we could get him listen to Infowars for a week
Hey babe brought up to speed immediately think I was in
Anyway we're now moving on to February 5th
Alright
Real bad
Real bat
Alex starts
Additional
Two weeks into Obama's birth
And now two weeks in a day
Starting off
You show here on the 5th
By complaining about Al Gore
Yeah and then
Sing
Some weird stuff
There is all kinds of about
Hit the more popular version
Put him in jail
The state knows best
Background on all of this
Sure
It seems like that all over again
Listen to where it goes
Establishment
No
Right
Okay
I'll agree with the last
Couple words
No I know that's what's fascinated
It's surprising
Invest
Right at the rise of
The Tea Party
February 2009
It's really interesting
If that level of
Insight from Alex
Because I think he's totally
Absolutely not
In terms of the New World Order existing or anything like that
Stuff is a little bit
Stupid ideas
He's saying a lot of stuff that is attractive
Two people who follow me
He's trying to seduce you into that line
Because
He's got these people behind him if you just replace the New World Order in that with
The coax
You have exactly like his assessment is right on
Yeah but
I think that he has
Hughes
This is free
Whatever changes
Because he still hasn't
I mean you look up on the board
He still hasn't abandoned
He hasn't changed his positions on these
Very foundational thing right
I know this because it just seemed redundant
Clip-on one of these episodes he's like
Slavery just became big going to prison
You nailed it
You get paid $2 an hour that's pretty much labor
To hear this is back when Alex is what you would call
Crazy as opposed to Craven
Like generally speaking
No I am not saying that it's crazy to have a beer cuz I'm thinking about going crazy
Prison is just slavery but currently like the the use of the lizard voice
That's bulshit
History of prison
I agree with you
Arguing when he makes a good point
I'm arguing that
His his ideology
Is built out of a cent
Paranoia
Luna theater
And occasionally
Emails
Whereas now
It is built out of
Whatever makes me mad
Is when did he make that transition
From what I understand what you're saying
Because you listen to way more Alex Jones than I do and then you give me a prism to which no but I think you're
Accurate and I think it's not this time
It's jealous
I'm the same way that like
A couple episodes of Ron Paul went on Glenn Beck's show Alex
Respond reply
You don't even like Ron Paul Ron Paul we're Buddies
I accept
Far more than my own absolutely correct
It is accurate analysis
Adore
The rise of the tea party and we see Ron Paul consistently
Associated with it
I think that jealousy is going to grow even more info
Be what ends up breaking Alex
I think it's going to be what ends up
To the point where he's like
F*** it
Yeah I'm in
Let me be the
Real mouthpiece
This guy is no good
It doesn't work
The money behind it needs a new mouthpiece because Glenn Beck
So sullied
Doubt in the mainstream
I think you're going to
To end up with
Alright completely retracting argument
Now please retract your argument about Britney Spears
And then immediate - 12
To Britney Spears
Certain
This isn't true
Honor last episode
We talked about
Alex Jones's
Market
Ability to breakdown adver
Yes he's amazing insight
M2 Super Bowl commercials
Because we know we know
He took advertising classes
Hold on
He actually never said classes
I took Alberta
Edit psych Warfare
That there is a corn syrup commercial with a popsicle
Sex
Was
No
When did Batman
Yeah but
Naruto videos like 16
7 years
I don't know 2009
Shockingly close to when I move to Chicago
All right so because
Cuz I watch one episode
No I don't know but I don't I don't think matters
I will say if it is on
The only episode that aired is that one with the carousel
I could be your through Higher lyrics
I have no idea that show sucks
Y'all god dammit
This is Britney Spears all over
Premier 2000
Alright
Anyway
So the reason I brought up
That corn syrup
Is because
Alex
Clip
Brings that
Go to backup
Not his analysis of
The commercial
And it also made me realize
F****** miserable
I didn't
Realize
Did people live next door to him
I just left the studio or his house
His house
Yeah I never thought about like
Oh
Alex husband
It turns out he has
I was talking to somebody on my front lawn this morning and they were
Your
Mediterranean food
Can't wait for that
When your when your neighbors stop giggling at you and talk
It's because they talked to you a couple times.
No no
Not a big fan
I'm going to
Like I actually think I know I think I've seen the house
What's online
I see that pretty nice
Cuz you lose in nice houses in both of us like to do even if 2009
Suburban like
Lawn like
Everybody's house looks
The same like I see that settlement kind of
Feel 280 out out on your lawn
And people talk to you
It has to have that feel of like you got the
Driveway
You got the lawn that you have to
Every now and again
Like that's what I see
We're paying neighborhood kid to mow
Exact
I don't know
I just hunt
I would
I like the idea of like when you're growing up
I think I don't know I don't know if this is
Uno growing up it was always like this
Archetype of the horrible neighbor was like
Camry won't give it back that was early to punch line of the
Terrible neighbor
Let me
As of now thirty-four-year-old man
The only thing I don't want
Is
Guy who yells about corn syrup
That's the neighbor I don't want
I have neighbors I talked to the bunch times and never been like
I do a show about Al
Alex Jones
No I am
Kind of moron Alex decide if your neighbor is asking
Corn syrup
They didn't
I actually didn't know that actually his neighbor was in a hot tub with three other globalist
At the same time
The neighborhood
Ucz is corn syrup adds
There's no way that conversation
Even started there
The conversation
The
Started with like
Hey
Your lungs
Looking
Nice
Yeah well corn syrup at killing you all right well I'm going to go back inside you f****** Lititz
You got it
Okay
Finger guns
On this episode
We see
What's
I'm going to have a
New f***
Krewe of dude
Ran I go
Lawyer
I got a f******
White House lawyer
Economist
Do Ron Paul VI's me to talk to that murdered two out of three out of three is great by
Holyshit Terrace
So now moves on to the next day and goes back to like
Scaring people
I have to scare people
And so here's what he does
If it takes
This is
Most of you
Beginning of the episode
Yeah
Oh
Text
As far as Minnesota and the two places he comes up with or where he is
Weird
Publix
4 minutes
Very exciting
Wingstop
Supervolcano
I was looking at it so much action
In the air
Let me through
How is
Will it hit me in the nuclear winter
Oh certainly
What but I mean can you give it to me at a lower price than what it will be
I can't do an impression but I wish I could do it a person
Holy s*** that's
Embarrassing like that is next level like
We're going to have volcanologist daughter's going to tell you that is about to blow the craziest thing I've heard probably going to
Decrease the temperature of the entire world
Although that's a rock
I had a I had a fun
Was really
Interested about nada
Reading about supervolcano sure and the magnetic poles switching
Sound like a little bit after 2005
Like iOS pretty late but see that was when the History Channel decided like
We're not doing great with the Nazi stuff for a bit but we're going to switch
We're going to switch mood we're going to do the whole documentary on
Supervolcano in Yellowstone supervolcano
Every 500,000 years how long it's been since
About 500,000 years ago
Every time
Are you f***** up
I actually found out when supervolcano came out
It came out in 2005
I know
I just read about that
You just laid out to the plot of the movie supervolcano
There's two different things that alright f*** off
Alright
Is it raining
Attract
So if you thought that was like
Pretty
Gross
Like in terms of salesmanship
I agree
To know that he
What is a certain a certain way
I am kind of like
Get better at one thing
I think it's still as clunky now half the time
Away from the prison
You see all of my transitions is the best version of that like
When I say speak
King of blank
In your head you think alike
The times it went well
You forget about the X like
Everything has a bunch of times they do not work out
And you just
You forget about that wait hold on did you just say
I think your transitions are always good
My mistake did you look at the platonic ideal of the
The platonic ideal
Hey sometimes like
This is not fair
Yellowstone
Courthouse
Earthquakes in around Yellowstone
Last time it blew up a devastated large depends on
One Direction
A supervolcano
Volcanologist
Later in the transmission
Anderson
European francs Swiss French and others
That are
He did it again
Are you done yet
Yeah yeah yeah
Did it back-to-back
And even made it clear why he's doing is coming
Teeth on the line
I clearly like there was a problem with the phone communicate
Galaxy of tension move couple more of these bullion
I am so
I've never I've never heard Alex.
This the same thing
Twice in a row
All right here's the narrative Yellowstone
You're going to be f*****
How you doing
Sell that gold baby
I've never seen him about this
I'm bummed about this
It's cuz I'm really excited for the volcanologist I like
Like your volcanoes
I would say
Alex
Alex is Now setup
All right we got this volcano
I'm terrified
You have to
To be terrified to take a little bit of a
Into
Selling gold
Right
Volcano
Oops I meant
Monty's
Is it going to be on
What
Guest world
Not even
Now cuz there's like mine
Dachshund
So
Easy easy real big Christian reconstruct
Gymnastic Coronavirus
Create a
Code for white
Ethnostate
United States have those names
Yeah
He also is a guy who's
The show on the den
Communications Network
Part of the cross-promotion right also makes money when
We all do
Good times and so
This is the only clip that I have of
Interview didn't you just tell you everything you need
Personal he's going to tell people to look up the
Trilateral Commission logo
Already terrible
If you're listening right now
Going to give you a little bit of a head
Head Start feel free to look it up you can go to trilateral. Org or just Google trilateral Commission
Yep find their logo
Description
And if you're listening
Tri-level. Org
But their logo
Well if you look at it there three
Arrows and you can almost imagine
Flight 666
There's no way you can miss
Linda Perry
Pacesetter of the logo
Is an upside-down broker
Christianity
Fair enough
I would take people's criticisms
Anything like even the trilateral commission if you want talk about like them
Having policies that you disagree with I'll listen to
Are you coming out of the box with
I got to be honest
I'm not listening to the rest of it
Cuz you
Have indicated
You could
Almost
No witchery arrow is
There's three arrows and there's three sixes in psychics
And then if you look at it you can say Google on your phone real quick the logo
So you can see it
Because it's so it's really funny that he saying Thursday inverted broke
Ben Cross
Cuz when you think about the cross the Christian cross
Right
How many points
Are there on that cross well there's the
Right there's the one of the bottom break
And then about
75% of the way up
There's the one on the side with the one on the other side
I've never seen the Christian cross but doesn't
Four points on it cuz otherwise it's just kind of like a
Divining rod
Or something like that
Maybe a peace sign
Alright hippie peace sign with all right
Looking at this right now
Nah
There's nothing
Even though
I'm even looking at one of those who don't want to Google
Supposed to be like
The evil version of it
And it looks nothing like the
No that's a that's
That's it
No that's like a it's like a shity tattoo it's like a
No Crossing
Absolutely
I want to bake Christians into blue stupid s*** like
To help them become enemies of their enemies
Not hard to do they already do that
Good point rev-x Armada Grapevine
This is what I was trying to come up with
It looks like a recycling logo
Yes exactly that we went to
I was thinking biohazard but the reason I didn't recycling is.
When is the perfect gallon
I'm so they can
Get to talkin about like
The the global
Cuz of course
Anyways
You know that recycling is what Jesus
Oh my God
Recycling
Exactly the way they hate him so
So they talked about
This being
Exhausted the worst motiva plant in the world
And Alex
Alex is like
Should believe it
Sure
We talked for like 9 hours
Daniel estulin
We got gym talker
Boy
That's your go-to terms
That's not
Great let me tell you something
Jimmy Kimmel could never get Daniel estulin no certainly not absolutely not
Also grand an
For fun
Did come on Alex Jones Show
In the lead-up to
To the 2016 election
I told Alex
That
The Rothschild
Are supporting Trump
Right and the Rockefellers are supporting Hillary Clinton
Alex is like
I agree
Is a guy that's crazy
Sounds nuts
Can't believe any of that but it's just funny that I was going to be like
Absolutely not he would never be into them
I don't f****** know his beliefs are like
The lottery ball machine where
Where everything is just too like swirling around then one suddenly pops out in the vacuum
The Escalade
When has that Beyond
The stuff we've already talked about
About him like he has that
In his
Throw it in the bag
You might remember that earlier this episode Alex said that Al Gore
Got caught on
Buy-Back list
He's trying to get kids
Turn against their parents remember this video
I think I might this this sounds sound absurdly familiar
You try and Jog your memory whilst I look at you skeptically
So I remember him being in a gym
It was a video that was like
That very well could be right
30 degrees
Looking at him
From
A distance of probably like
150ft
And you could see just a part of that it was almost like an assembly that I remember bro people were sitting on me
I wasn't looking for you to describe the measles then
I want
I'm sorry but that's the problem I remember the image another word
Like like if I was going to
Encapsulate what I think about what
He said
It was probably something along the lines of
If we are going to
I can't talk and pull it
Remember
Let's see if this jogs your memory
Nugget
That is exactly what I was
How do I live
Isabel shopping bag she forgot
I'm very very very environmentally conscious children
State is Bosch
State mandated close by
So this is the first
Peace
Advised
It's about what is puritanism
From the beginning of
F****** America
No
Puritans used to say is a good idea
He's also described
Like good best practices
Oh you mean like using
Specifically about kids
Calling bulshit on their parents
Everybody
Oh yeah it's all great stuff
I got the idea that like if you wanted a rush
Hang your goddamn clothes
Have you wasting electricity and water
Had a dryer
But you know what we also had a basement
We hung clothes to dry
My parents are pissed off about like
Daddy like wasting resources
We can do that my girlfriend and I are discovering Bowl
No hanging
Fine
Let's
Other
Consideration
That's another substitute
If you don't have those
Consideration
Everybody back I wouldn't do that I would like also every time I wash my
Clothes like I need them now
I do not wash my clothes until I have no clothes to wear
But same thing with like
I I grew is like a
I grew up with never having a dishwasher
Bigger
You can just wash dishes
Shoes by hand
Rag use less water
You can do that
So that was always the
Principal that I grew up in
It's not like
Whatever whatever is going on
Like that Alex is describing
In this
Article
Is just older
It just old ideas
But he's taking issue with the idea that
Children are like
Getting into
And that to me is weird
Brittany is strange because kids are being taught
More or less. Like
Hey guys
Resources
We may not have him
Prolong
We might have
Reminder f*****-up
And you might
Be the one
Who are going to stop
In fact
You will be the ones who were going to suffer
Will not will be dead
Pinterest
Dumb s*** your parents are doing
Because they're going to die before they have to deal with
The consequences
By the way
All of them have led to you dying a lot faster than you should
The idea that what Alex
Seems to be taking issue with In that clip
That we just listen to is
He's
Madoff
Kids are asserting of voice
I don't understand why that is a problem
I don't understand because
Shoulder the burden
Right
So you are not
Capable of unless you're
Denying or Define your parents
Until you are all right
Also f*** them they're just meat
Exactly so I guess. Can you disagree with them
Super weird around
You are playing the Clippers algor
Control
It's about
I have to practice it
Here it is before I say this
I need you to know that I am already right
Because
Baby what he says is going to disagree with me and read what I say
What you need to know
Music
Through the lens of the always baby
You picked up on the exact subtext of that
I'm sorry to keep
Keep bringing up the fact that
I'm going over all this
None dare call it
To do in that world one of the things they do
So much
Is that preemptive
Groundwork
I need to be on board before we can confirm
You need to know that you need to view it through the lens of me already having told you what it is he's going to say
If even when he says
That is not what I told you he's going to say
You need to know that
Truly saying
The thing I told you he's going to
X
With no car
You might have some thoughts about the other
F****** allow that to possibly have
What is a what is
Slept
My
Exactly the same
It's crazy
Real quick it's really funny cuz Alex is
Just playing
He stole from
1 backstroke
Cuz you can hear Glenn Beck
Chiming in
Sad
Yeah I did hear that
These just I thought that was the person who was videotaping
And this was at the time where people still use Giant
Dude that's sad
How's the weather right there you know why
He has to do that because
He's stealing clips from Glenn Beck
Cosmic Eclipse packaging Glenn Beck news
How
Wow
What what
Kind of murder wait wait till the end of this
There are some things about our world
You don't really, none of that much
Central argument
Pretty much all the audio from the stolen
Glenn Beck
Al Gore
Commando footage that he found
I would posit that
Al Gore is saying
Is that
Certain
Things are entrenched
In people's worldview
And you children
Younger people
Have an ability to not be
Entrenched by that be able to see the bigger picture
When we were younger
The example would be that
Civil rights
Parents couldn't
See the forest for the trees
Because they have been brought up in that context
That Mill you did not allow them
60 outside of that box
For you
Perhaps
It is
This climate stuff
Your parents don't understand it maybe you do
He's speaking
Specifically to people who were involved
Like a climate
Yeah
Not like
It's not
I can't
Imagine
Anyway you
You can hear that
And Missy
I really can't
Like it seemed so clear
And
70% of people thought Martin Luther King Jr was doing the wrong thing
Because again
You guys don't know this because people pretend that it wasn't true
But Martin Luther King jr. was a
Really really
Really unpopular guy
During his time
All of you all of us kids
Realize at the time
For f****** insane
You
You can f******
How can you not
Look at that and think
S*** I know exactly
What he saying
I know exactly what
F****** Santa
How is it
Possible
We're
Perfect
Oftentimes whatever there's a crisis
This point it only illuminates
Where
Problem
I'm sorry
Potentials for what
We can make
Sort of
Spiritually what's going on in
That clip about
The consistent
Problem of the past
And the consistent promise of the future
It is what it is
Doesn't agree with that
I would save it if you
Don't agree with that
Argue
On the merits
Against
Climate
ShopRite
Except that metaphorically
You're saying that fighting again
People who are anti Civil Right
Like I don't
There's so many
There's so many thing
On
The right because of
My
My family and the people I know
Understand where you can
But
You can take
What he said
Turn it into something bad
You're insane
Like there is no way that you can listen to that
And not process it correctly
Unless you are f******
King Kong
There's there's just no way
It's not possible
If you look at that
And you say there is something malicious in that
Behind the idea of you should never trust
Your parents
You're a f******
Your f******
Idiot
I'm done
You know what
Glenn Beck
He's a really good guy.
Are we going to f****** mailed in 2009
I'm thrilled for you
But I'm even more threads
Cuz we're about to find out
Million
Dude
We're about to find out what
When
Not strange
Sit down
All right with Smog and stop being fake and circuiting real
Stop being polite
And start listening I've never watch the real world I was
Had to pull it volcanologist
You know I got destroyed in the reboot
No
Oh
Now I know I don't have
Taste for that
Because this dude
No f****** time for a
He is just about to science
And it's delightful
Okay
Dr. Robert Trombley
Exactly
I am self physically
From
You got to expect that Alex
Thanks
Did this guy is going to be like
Tomorrow
You should buy gold
The only thing that happens really fast
Is Alex
His narrative
Boston
But thank you very much for happening
Delighted to be here with you
You're talking about asteroids that I was originally trained
So how about I was very interested in that as well
First of all four starters a relative to Yellowstone
Brother should not be any Panic or or a fear
Amongst the populace at the end
The moment that's pretty clear
Pretty blonde
In case you thought that was a little subtle
AKC
So it's only erupted
3 * 8
Entire history
But there is no cuz I said there's no real cause for alarm at
At the moment
Attract the earthquake activity
Quite a bit
Blade
But this is a common occurrence
That's pretty blunt pretty
It's really cutting dry
You know how
In his life
He kept trying to like
We got to do what I want
Look
You've already said no to the stuff
Let me try and throw you into this narrative and maybe you'll say yes
After that come on give me some
The next
Five or six clips
Are Alex
So desperately trying to be like
Please make people scared
Work it's so gorgeous
My first
Response to this clip
In the context of all of the other clip
Is like
When did somebody else take over booking
Isaac
Lego is rubbed
Sicilian the mix right
I don't know
What's the temperature
Somebody is booking gas
And occasionally
Feels like they're like
Alex Jones is f******
Stupid and I will show the world
You know cuz like
The reason I'm laughing a little bit is like
How do you spell
Good
Goodbye
For us
Is one thing
Good 4848 Infowars Booker would be a completely different
On good faith you booked him thinking
He would go along with our
Took
Difficult time
They continue this conversation
That tickled my brain to a very serious
Rock Hudson
Who Was books
These guys robbed
Gibson
Is another guy
Broken away from the
Of course
EEOC lawsuit
Shark sound like
He wouldn't talk
But like
Live laugh
You know what sucks tooth there's a bunch people who've left who have gone on to
Just be like
I want to make my own
I'm going to be just
Slightly smarter right and act like I'm going over to x-ray right
They're the guys who know this Camp don't know why the Tam works
They just don't get it
Entertainment
Yeah
I don't know anyway
I know why is it getting booked
I don't know I don't know
Nobody
Here's
Here's what I say
What I see with these guys
Today
Is nobody was pretty
And at this point
When we live in
Everybody is
Protect
He is
He is this
This fragile
Week
Contact with people that disagree with him
He's going to cry and scream
But back
He is going to just
Like mickley
Call like talk s*** I think what you're not taking into account
Is that like
Alex's
As he always has
On a Warpath
Against the globalist
Making b******* off
He hasn't entered into like
The pupa
Caterpillar exactly
It's not grown into a
Haha you're right
Rarity has been surrounded by like
You're talkin about is like
He has people who
Are alike
Etan
You up
Just like Trump's lawyers are like
Don't don't talk to them because you're under your going to lie
But at the same time he doesn't
I have also.
Cadre of people
Damn talk to
So you dumb
He doesn't have like
You know
He doesn't have
Larry Nichols isn't there
Steve pieczenik
The two of them know each other I believe that that
He's not around
Right
Justbet
You like a lot of these
Classical weirdo
Visual who have been a part of his life
I can always put my elbow on you and you
Are you lean on me yet
They're not around
He has to do
Not AR-15 I love 2009
Because this is
Chaos
It's the Wild West
Yeah but
Also suffer from frequent volcano
And
That is your ideal Transit
Russian
The greatest one you've ever done
You nailed that so Alex
Keeps trying to
To get like
This guy
Probably
To be like
You should be scared
Thank you for like
No
So here is Alex asking
Is there any day
Is there any danger of erupting
That was the last eruption
Okay first of all
No there's no real danger of it erupt
Looking at the MoMA
North my normal or take on this is it would
Probably be a rapper
For several hundred or even thousands of years
Okay so that's not
He does not go on to invalidate that.
Well look
The world
It seems like we're entering it
Are aware there's way more eruptions of volcanoes
Is that true
It could be but there's no real indication of that at the moment I mean it's not that
It's not acting up in the normal
Read it out in Alaska
Totally different super volcano
Rita's name of volcano is
Sky Zone
It's like why
There's an uptick in volcano
The right there's a lot of volcano
I'm going to go with a hard no
No that's a somewhat Avenue
Illusion that we normally have about 4260 eruptions
The year
Love it
The reason that it appears that way it's because of the
Technology in the mass media we have
Now I mean you know 10-15 years ago
A lot of people didn't even know when the Rapture went off
Except those of us in the business
And sometimes we get that
We're a week later even longer
Option gloves off anywhere in the world including in the oceans
And so forth
I mean in the ocean
Look up like that
We know about it
So that no that does not
This is my favorite volcanologist
But why do people like why are people freaking out
Yeah
Well
I don't really know why
Like I don't know why
I want you to please
Speculate and make people afraid
Please
Nobody answer after that like his response being kind of like a giggle is like
The reason is because
Love you people like
You Alex
Yep
Why are people more afraid
Because
Hour ago on your shell has you were like
It's going to
Pause the world temperature to go down when we had connection issues and I was listening to you
And you said some crazy dumb s***
The craziest f******
Yeah because Alex is having
Such a bad time
It is not getting his way at all he's got to take this to like
The craziest level possible
Just tickets
YouTube give me something right
I know you don't
Causing earthquakes around the world
I wonder what happened
Hydrogen bomb went off
Molten magma
I suppose it could
Okay
You got it.
Nail tools supposed
Night forever are you
This s*** is not working out so hard but he's like
What if what if what if
If if we were to Nuke this volcano justify my fear
That's great
It would maybe
Anyway
I
Could not love this
More
50 Cent
Alex Jones
Captivate
Isn't it
Like isn't this the Alex Jones that was that was
Willing to
Be dunked on
Still pull his neck
He would never
I've talked over this would have been yelled over
There's no way that he would have even
Finished
F****** set
But this 2009 Alec
He is
Willing to not just
Not just listen to this guy
But like say
Yep yep
No
I get what you're saying
But I'm pretty
Have you ever gone to Narnia
Narnia
Aslan
Wasn't around at the time
Would Yellowstone erupt
Like it's
I love this
I don't know babe cuz
The song in the 2000s on by
Yeah great so hard
Great stuff
Episode
Three out of four interviews
No the other two days use able to like
Spin out of it and be like
Write this out of it
Embarrassing goes on an hour and it keeps to being like
Well what about if we nuked
The only Rose to that
Bad on air
It doesn't really matter though because
But honestly
I'm just a big fan of especially
Also
I was trained as a
Astronomer
So
Smart like a million different
He's not even saying
But
Clear
Text is like
I'm going to explain
Like I would
Child
Exactly what
You notice that this volcanology
I've read
60 books about volcanoes
He's so
Ancient
Installers trying to make sure that Alex
And Alex's listeners
Knows it
In all honesty
It's not that big
So this is
Boast of
Fun
About February 4th and 5th
AimPoint
Close
Alright
That our batting cleanup
Some of it really terrible
Some of it
Find Target
Nothing good
Alright
February 5th
Alex has an interview with a guy named Aaron zelman
Who's the president of the Jews
Gun
Preservation rate
Run right preservation
Sure
I didn't know there was a group
I don't exist anymore I have no idea
It might just be Aaron zelman
I have no idea where this organization is
I would say
Interviewed
Not go great
Cuz here's how it starts
But you are right about a tires
Situation we are face
Weather
War
I literally War I war on gun owners
By the government
A mission that could cost the United States
Final solution
Second Amendment I'm not trying to be funny
You are kind of trying to be funny
Hey hey guy you love it and I love it
But for guns
So it's bad
Is it bad
If we had a holocaust for guns
I like legitimately
I'm one of these dudes
She doesn't really get mad about
Stuff yeah
I'm not I'm not
I know I'm pretty chill generally in terms of like
Unless you talk bad about Michelle Branch
Britney Spears has back to the Brittany
Generally I'm pretty chill
For me which
Weird underpinning to this entire episode or Mandy Moore
Is r
Episode
Argument about Britney Spears
I'm pretty
Cool
About stuff generally
It really makes
Pretty man
Like
I do I don't know
I'm not Jewish
I'm not naturally
I have empathy for
Jewish people
Yeah I have an anger
The Israeli government
I think those parts
Occupy the same
Generally speaking
I'm furious
When I hear someone be like
This is the final solution about
Gun
The guy who runs
Jews for gun right preservation red
I'm not trying to be funny
First of all as a comedian
A pastor a former comedian
Second
The only way you're going to
Make that
Talking
Awful jokes
Yeah
Is if you really don't think the Holocaust happen
Or you'd think it was that big a deal
Per unit used
Term final solution
As a way to poke like
Hey yours these people trying to take our guns
You still have your guns now 10 years later dumbass
The only way you can use that language
Is it either
You don't think the Holocaust was that big a deal
And the final solution is
Not something that
Jews should really be triggered by right or
You got to want to wake up nauseous
Yeah
Not okay but I just have to ask you the question
I mean ultimately
What is your final solution to this
Asking what is your final solution
Is not good
I don't like it I wish I didn't have to do it but I had to do it the joke was there
But it's
That
Is better
Benson
This is the final solution
Well because I was trying very
Specifically to be fun
Avila's re-air until 1 but I'm addict
I apologize
But this also should
Indica flower
This should indicate
To you a little bit about
Again 2009 Alex
Texas versus press
Right Alex
Present day
Lorde
2015 to present that we've listened to
Don't bring up the
Jews for the preservation of the Second Amendment
Maybe that's
Piece of his world
And Larry Pratt
Gunownersofamerica
Vouched for it
I hated the NRA back then loves them
Weird
Next
That's all I'll say about
You're a nice gross
Clip
Is it
Very
Different story than what he's about to
Directions
By the way this is confirmed
No judge
There is real chocolate
Letters
I'm here always
Pepsi
For me that's just the same impression he did
An hour and a half
Second
In the context
Today
Sake
That's my version of you doing
Dismissive
Scampi
I just
It is this
Gibril
For the kids
This turned
Did this this nightmares
No no
Come real
Aren't we supposed to
When you
Look at Alec
Is bullshitters
You look at his
You're so
Being nightmare in 2009
Where you laugh at it
And you say this
Never happened and then you look at it
The present-day and it's
F****** real
And none of us
Really should have to
Do you know
Feel like
We were wrong about this cuz hoodoo
Well people who are listening
She's been
About the light
The whole time
It's never really been he's never really been all that
Nope
Like
When we
Came back
We were
Very surprised
Does the Alex being mad at the
About that guy who got shot
Psych
It was more about the
Cops killed
It could happen to whites
Sprite
That's what it is and if it happened
Anybody else
Ike
Clifty this life
A little bit of bad heavy has a like a
And
Huge thing
You expect
The guy who directed loose change
And does
Periodic shows
4 hours
Bull shows
Continue
Yeah cuz like
Jason bermas does
Later in two
These there's no David
No there's no
Crew He has Jason bermas
Right
The Jason Berman
This is doing another
He's moving to Austin
Are you doing Michelle
So obviously there's some money
That is come
In there
Here's where I
I don't give a
Here's why this
He says some
That like I don't I don't
He understand
Coming out of his mouth
I don't think Alex
If you listen to
I don't think he'd under
How
Crazy with
We're doing what feels right and that is expanding
Neighbors are friends and family first
Information
Absolutely
So like
Did you understand what happened
Yeah
Ted Anderson is buying
Yep
On Hannity on Rush
Do you know what are specifically for the purpose
You know that I got it
Gold
He's buying Midas resources add he's not buying
Alex Jones Show ads
No on hand
From another conservative radio show
B on a competing Network
At the same time live as him
He would never do that
Who's playing these guys
Because Ted Anderson
His whole business model
Also involved
Pudding
On
Arkham
Keating
A receipt Theory blogs
All his gold resources
Because it was two separate businesses
It never really seemed like all that much of a trouble
So all of these shows
Head Midas resources
The stuff going
Anybody who makes
Anybody
Anybody who makes shrimp
Neal Boortz
These guys Mark Levin
All of them had
From Midas resources to sell gold
But you know what he wasn't trying to
To do
Build Alex
Mrs. Ian
He was trying to sell gold
To those others
Scared people
Yep that's what it's all about
Pretty well you did it the best
Because I was the most
He was the one who be like
Oh I will be calm
Cooked out gold sales
Yeah yeah
Everything about myself
In order
To fit your mold
Thought you never
And that's why
You still sold
F****** ads
Do people like Rush
Call Sean Hannity
I just want random Pants dance
Why didn't Hillary ever sell me pants
That I never knew what
You don't know that he didn't
That's true
No right
I didn't know that
But that's
Peconic aquarium like 8
Guys
This isn't fair
Like the idea of fit
Jason bermas
Is like
I'm going to move to Austin
Because Howard
Siding is it
Person is buying
Russia
Like
If Ted Anderson is
The sponsor of fire show
And at the same time
What is the sponsor of
Hannity
And of Glenn Beck
That gives us the legitimacy
The concept
Yeah yeah
I'm going to play this
Alright I think you misheard
We're doing what feels right and that is
On Rush Limbaugh
That's going to bring us some money
He thinks
Anderson
Is running
On Hannity and Russia
Show
It's going to bring them in audio
It's not he's running gold sale
Commercials
On those shows
It's not going to be like
Hey
You should check out Jason bermas has a new show
No I check out
Alex Jones
I got that
But if you've got a guy who's sponsoring
All of those shows
No
Okay
Alright because
Even that
Even in that but we
Replay
Jason bermas
Understand
Hey bay Dorset
He's our guy
The facts
Cheese pudding
Is expensive
Places to put ads
Means that
Will soon be alright
He's going to
Them
To come to us
That's not like
Our sponsor is their sponsor and therefore there's
Equivalent
He thinks
Like
Where in
Baby
That's what that
That's what's behind what he's talking about
It's crazy because just wants to f*** himself
Using
You and Alex
Easy A
Dn.y and so miserable
Mostly cuz the show generally does everybody like
Please go to our website
Absolutely follow us on Twitter at
Riverview
Also we have inexplicably been gaining listeners and everybody who is
Listening
For whatever reason
Thank you so much
It's it's amazing
Thank you all
Your turn
Yeah it is my turn
F****** obvious
Go goddamn fuckyourself ice
You f****** Nazi goddamn
Bulshit organization that is
Destroying the lives
That you have no f****** deal with
Can't handle that
If you are an ice agent
You are a
F****** nuts
You are going to f****** Nuremberg Trial yourself
The goddamn Jets and I hope I hope
Adventure
You are prosecuted
The same way
Prosecuted
Whatever their founded goddamn
Don't f******
F*** you
Already
Go fuc yourself
Just a technicality give to somebody else
The show
Who's on the show
Correlation to the previous
Position that we had regarding guy
I don't disagree show that I just talked about
Then it's going to have to
To be goddamn Schiff
Chef fixative this was the beginning of the end for uShip
Peter Schiff
Alexandra Thurston color