Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody work
What up have you ever asked yourself the question of what you would do in Nazi Germany
I have I have thought about that
Haven't been reincarnated in present-day because both perhaps
The reincarnation
English Freedom Fighters defeating
Okay alright alright
Becoming too much of a problem
We are molded in our mothers wombs are born 4th
In the lineage with race memory has the creepiest conversation I think I've ever had I don't like
No sense
The real irony of that is your ass
For a way to sum up the show
Bottom line is I know a lot about Alex Jones
You don't know anything about him
Today but
Knowing a little bit about gravels is always a good idea
It's always spiritual
I'm so today we got it
We're going to be going over it
But first I'd like to give a shout out to a couple new donor
New new policy
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
I generally say team
Screw
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Yeah
Another one
Diving headlong
We appreciate it
And tell your brother
Localistra
Right now but also it doesn't
Really hit a lot of the evil parts
Antlers
Website knowledge fight.com
Paniolo
Yes thank you very much
I hope
Theraflu
Now
Suppose you want baby
And their babies become Donuts to me
I don't know I hope it doesn't
Cuz I'll tell you that right now
Sucker rap
Today is Thursday the 7th
That means
Coming out on the 8th
Which is one week 14 real one week
One weekend that crazy is Austin Texas at beerland
Not doors 9
We also have some
Comedian
We also have some burlesque
Ridiculous
I also
Tastic episode to go over I will not give away
Tease you know how I knew you would
I put too much time because you are
So much time
Being anxious about that some very nice
Will be
Different times and then you will come to the conclusion
Correct all along
But
Tootie's everyone big picture of Pi
Here is the Twin Towers falling out of
Contact drops from the episode will be going over
It's all about
You know people do that mean
We gotcha
Contacts drop
If you would like to come to my job
10 p.m. beaverland
In Austin Texas
What is a podcast
Are going to show up as we learned last
Because I have that Zoom recorder we should be able to get true whether or not
As amateurish as the last
Episode
It's listenable but
That last episode we did
When you listen to that recording
You pee standing up
I can entire episode that would basically be a plug
Ferrari through
A bunch of Austin
Celebrities favorite one
Ethan Hawke
Cuz I love Ethan Hawke I'm not sure I actually love him I don't know anything about him as a person but I love his work and Richard linklater
Fairfield
Ethan at least
Maybe
Three if you count
Before midnight of my favorite has both been before and during
Every section of the day
I love
The first two of those
Okay with
The third man
I love it
But they're great Before Sunrise or sunset
Got to catch a plane
Go home
And then after B
Yeah no
After midnight the song
We're going to chill out
Cena I'm thinking about round about that day after midnight we're going to let it all hang out
Especially if you go to the shop so I decided
Ethan Hawke
Threw some episodes
So I'm like you know later so I was like we're going
To do this thing
I looked at his birthday episodes and they weren't
So great I was like
I'm going to work out there
I'm not going
All of them
So then I was like what about people whose birthdays are June 5th
Do that
Is it that you know what
It was weird I thought one person
Who lives in Austin who birthday is June 15th I'll give you one clue who it is
Cancel
We will not be in Austin on June 15th
Show at 10 we will be there
Because
Some very good comedians there they will be not very last show
Everything is over because that's Bailey's theme song pro wrestler bayley
She lives in Austin now according to Wikipedia Anna birthday is June 15th
I didn't do anything about it wanted to play that song
Together
Trolling allwrestling
We're like oceans baileyana
Knots out
I'm so what I did in
Something else while I was looking for
Completely crazy
Do you want me to tell you what's up
Bill Ayers was on Infowars
What
Bill Ayers Weather Underground
Alright I'm and it's pretty great
Times Bill Ayers showed up
Terrorist
Pretty awesome
So before we get into that I want
I want to do
I realize I tried to set up a soda before I got into
Something some world news I wanted to talk about
Going on right now
No but this thing
Which operation Backyard Brawl
Sutherland who alerted me to that thing so give it up to Aaron it's not fair
Cuz I already I knew f*** off you didn't know you texted me
The stuff was afoot
I didn't know this specific heat
I see people I see this sort of stuff getting posted all the time
What's bigger a more Focus
He doesn't know what's going on
Bunch of weirdos
Sounds like a homeless in
Noticed that like
Why is there hair dye here Ohio
They brought in Craig
Organization
Call Vets for child rescue
Which Alex Jones has given at least $20,000 to
Based on no evidence whatsoever that
This is clearly a place for children
So I was following mr.
Corset
I got to figure out what's going on here where's the oven
That's why I started watching videos
No but I wanted to understand what the argument
Dismiss
Things out of hand
Even when they're Ludacris
Couple years ago they did the internet
Reddit
Fortune
Phone number
Lesser scale I didn't go as far with it
With this Salt Lake City daycare so
Call Funtime kids
Yeah yeah I remember that nuts on it and like people
You're probably traffic
Taking children for sex photos
I mean that just makes it
People started coming up with fake
First off in like
I'm trying to track like do background checks on people who are allegedly
Involved it was it was just
Play Madness
In terms of
Would like the length
We're going
Just because this
Daycare center
Look weird
And someone posted about it on Reddit and said that they've never seen anyone go in or out of it
Facebook
Absolutely said this turned into like this
Is weird
Bike week and a half
We're people were like coming up with fanfiction
In real time
Basically about the daycare center
Are there.
Appears they're doing the same thing now with it
Crazy cuz I got just before we started recording
I was checking up on it
#on Twitter
Found a body
The Patriots
Sylvester child rescue in the
What's the I don't know some other Facebook
No
It's 30 miles away from where they were originally
It's the wrong directions
Tucson
From where the
Mayor of Tucson is a Rothschild
Child family history of the universe
Incredible
Someone's going to get killed I'm not around this
But like the wavy things are a
Oscillating
From like a couple years ago and I was watching it with that daycare
But now we have this
Which is still evolving right now in terms of like what the
Where people are going to take
Fun narrative
Search qanon is that involved how much they can paint Vistas
Some sort of
The left wing
Jewish
When you want to make a big deal out of an unrelated person's name being Rothschild you're playing on archaic ABC
So
To say
I mean I don't know what to say cuz
If someone
If someone were listening to our show that does
Just believe that
View that it's stupid
I don't care to all I have to say is
Stripe it in
Cuz this is going to be happening
A lot
There's going to be a lot of this
It's going to be a mess everywhere
Calmer heads must Prevail I believe
We got to go Bill Arizona
Something that I've been thinking about all f****** day
Cuz I rather have you read this New York Times article
About one of the children who is taken away from it was a Honduran child
Take it away from this
At the border
I did not and then just sent to a foster
Chester Hollman
Michigan
And it's just the entire story of the
And I thought about that all day today
Only thought I could have is
You know that thought process
Stuff like what would I do
In Nazi Germany
The Nazi
You came for
The Jews next door
You know that
If you cooperate with an ice agent
You would put a Jew in an oven
But that's the reality of it
You can do that you can answer that question for yourself
So
Don't pretend to be the hero ice agents are Nazis
If you if you are cooperating with them
Better you are right if that's who you are that's who you are
That somebody goes billares right what they found this like encampment right that had no debt
Enforcement did come and check it did have a cadaver dog going through
Child skull
This together and recognize that Ono the reason that
That like
It looked like there were underground tunnels when there weren't is like why is it so hard to
Define the place that
These people are supposed to be in
Serbia child skull in the middle of the desert I don't know maybe hiding
Maybe maybe they're a bunch of people in militias
The go out
And like knock over bottles of water that are left out for
For immigrants that crossed the border maybe they died because of the
My baby
So do I think about all that
The Backyard Brawl
But it did waste a good hour of my day
I did like that there's like
They're f******
These people can't get their shift
Cuz they're like turning on each other now there's like
Some of these Baga accounts are like
They're pissed off about how Jack pasovic is covering it in their life
Enjoy
It's like you had you created your monster and I'll deal with it
Goodnight
Bill Ayers on
This is
I have no idea
Couple times edit
It's really confusing
Cuz you walk away with a couple of conclusion
Right there one of those Alex is terrible at his job
But he thinks it does he thinks he does he has a picture in his head like
Arch leftist terrorist
And that's going to be a problem Ira members that would be sinking
Like
I don't know how to depict it other than I think he thinks he's like
A guy who's running around throwing bombs that have like pictures of Lenin.
I think that's a fun supervillain
We're going to ride our knowledge by comic book
Probably will happen
Probably not
Call Alex
Conveniently doesn't understand that bombs would that explode the picture
Right
Also doesn't understand that
For that
Child
The skull of
Arizona
Have to be related to that crime
Describe
You'd have to include
Pyridium
Part of the crime scene
It's a crime my buddy
Live in Tucson
Thermocouple time
Real drunk
Went to Juarez
That's an interesting
I went to a lot of Bordertown
Anyway
A lot of Bordertown
To say I like it I don't know why it tickles me so but it does
You got to go
You buy pills
We were going to do
You just always thought we were going to buy prescription in Mexico so you go down to Mexico You by Pillsbury
You're back you're white than I going to check you when you cross the border
Go down there and get drunk with like Friends of Friends
Juarez
Great time
Blog
Let's get to the Cypress cliff
We were we went along with the band
Opso
In this first clip Alex's starting off
Getting to his head
But one of the things
Does gears
We started to
Not started to notice
But started to discuss
This is a really shity
Trout
Where he assumed
Conclusion
These straps off
Before the interview even starts
He wants to make sure that
You know how this is going to end
Free inoculates the audience for my
Hey if I do a shity job
Know that the reason is because Billy or suck
Because your short-term memory is gone
You did not tell me
Normalcy bias
We are now reaching the Flash
Horizon
I'll be quite Frank
Butterflies
Physically
Thinking about Billerica
I just know it
So there is the first dance
Distance of it that is
The first diet well-liked
Sono Bello
And no matter what he says
You already know I've made that conclusion if he says yes
Also what kind of is it would be like
You're working for the mega-rich trying to destroy us all and Bill is like
Yeah totally you got me
Also
Who was the mega-rich
About specific
So you can't have a Flashpoint
The can't happen
Concurrently
What's up dumb f***
You're listening you're listening to
Consciousness of the universe
He can say whatever he damn well pleases in that sentence
With a masterpiece
Alright
Obama on Obamacare
Another tattoo
America
Grass wall
Green Beret
Hundred first Airborne Division
Weather Underground
Confidant former leader of the Weather Underground
Revolution Style
Larry
101st
Blogspot.com
Let's go to a clip of a man speaking from the grave
They also believe that responsibility
Octopus counter-revolution
Best B
Guarded against
By creating and establishing
Educated
And teach them how things were going to be
And when I put 25 million people
Soleri grass wall is
He's an FBI informant
And what have you
He's referring to Bill Ayers
Okay go to vomit Alex was just speaking.
Former FBI informant who quoted Obama
By giving Obama cloud is a terrible spy
Hi Alex
It's important
Keep in mind a couple of things
Has been
Timeline
And his character
Relation of things
We challenged ever since
Came out Road
Facebook
Believers in 90
About
Infiltrating Weather Underground
Right people who were involved i e Bill Ayers and Bernadette Doran
This is bulshit
Also
Background when you can like when you look at the
Nothing to say that like veterans
Maryville
But someone who is a Vietnam vet
Who is part like a
Super decorated
Loves the army
I can't like
His website is Larry Grant Wahl 101st
In honor of the hundred and first Airborne he's a part of Shrek
Idea of him infiltrating
Anti-vietnam War group
Probably going to be like
I've got to look makeup looks
Pretty bad possible
Clearly the thing I am again
They don't respect the work that I've done
Whatever
People for no reason so I don't I don't
I've looked into him a bit
Because they were killing
Violence and chaos.
For a reason
And he couldn't process the fact that all of the s*** he did
Look for nothing
I've looked into him a bit
It's tough to find
Too much
Specifics about him and
They were up to
He's a little bit more difficult because it was in the seven
As good of a record at
Please Dad everybody was informing
Infowars
And his daughter is appeared on Infowars
I'm going to say I don't
I don't trust
Highway 280
So Alex still has been
It's really
In the first Clipper we heard he's setting the table for failure
Are you setting the table to make it okay once he loses the dark
In this next clip use setting the table for everyone to like fields
Threatened
I also
If you heard
He said
Do they have to worry about
These
These folks is the counter-revolution
Alex
Clearly believe that
Is the counter-revolution
To the marxist-leninist
Whatever.
Is part of the
This clip that requires little
Personal to him
I have been in a run
No
Witness the blood
We better join them
Stuff
Check
We're not stupid we got
You're denying your program doesn't work anymore with us
Be advised
Revised
He has to be listening that's right
That we know what's going on
Play Christmas classics
Hispanic
Exactly Y-12 level powered
Eyeshadow
Homeland Security
Evolution
Veteran Alex
Makes us country operate
Dog whistle
He's doing there if you
He's casting himself
And all of his
Cadre of weirdos
Support his worlds
Lesbian
People who were
The counter-revolution
Higher government
Everything Homeland Security apparatus
Everything all the boats
Succeed
The boys in blue wrecked everything even now the revolution
Communist hundred percent
You called The A-Team
Sure and The A-Team
Alex Jones
Ba baracus
Jakari Jackson
Alright alright
Until right around the
Use
I don't know if you made it
He definitely wasn't there on election
Tonight I'll tell you that much
Pretty close to
Alex
Asserts that
Communist
We can't happen here
Baby
It is happen
Our borders are gone our country
World planetary fascist government
What a bunch of communist
Justice Gary Allan
That's interesting
I don't know
I'm doing a lot of research
I have man
It's pretty crazy
So what is a fascist world government with
Communists under it
Hierarchy
I mean like
Pyramid
Oils and sugars
Stop
You need the least of the graves of the Communists on the bottom right
And also vegetables of Compton
Socialist
We're like fake socialist
No notice capitalists don't actually exist
What caplets are really just passed
Socialist
World's socialist difference
Pyramid of ideologies
Socialist
When were talking about this like the world DVDs espousing is
You can boil it down if you want to get released
Powers-that-be
Encourage socialism
Acceptable lashing out at
Right because they
Secretly wanted
Create Monopoly
Control of stuff
You have socialism
I like
Judas goats who are leading people
Victor
Something that we're all like
And you're going to get some
He's leading you down this path
The promises of free healthcare and what have you
You take her eyes off the prize for a second what do you know you
You're trapped in communist
And it all works
Corporate
Monopolist because all of the
People who thought socialism was couple monopolies over everything
So you figured it out put it on the system is already
I meant the government and nonsensical fantasy
And if so needless
Capitalism works really
Pretty crazy
If you really take apart capitalism as it is
You get little chunks of each of these days
And so you pretend that all of these things are completely separate from each other
What holidays you're really railing against is the capitalist system that you profess to love so much
Right right
The other the other thing
That I think is fun
Is that because
Ben
Spending
What time
In this
In this world
I can tell you definitively
Gary Allan
Stupid
The guy who wrote
The guy who wrote none dare
None dare call it
Conspiracy is
Really dumb
Like legitimately
There is can't believe it has no reason to think that this guy
2 proof Dan I will
I will I'll give you a couple pieces of proof
If you want peace of proof Trump
History or a preacher
Let's go with the preacher
So
I've never had to ask myself
This is the visit
Belittle used
It's actually like he's manipulative lie lying
About stuff
It's smart to manipulative lie lie about
Alright
You want to do something stupid
I want full on
Unmitigated stupidity
I want him to
I want to have him walk underneath
Bucket of water that
Magic is at just falls on top of
We'll just for fun because people might be.
None dare call it conspiracy
Father Pedro arrupe
C5 right he takes this
Completely out of context
Indicate the guy was talking about
The communist
Conspiracy of the elite
Confined that speech online and
And I have
Catholicism needs better marketing
Atheism
That's all
Wildly autocorrect
Wish you could in 1972 and a twelve-year-old Alex Jones would never be able to find the full speech
Right there driving you might accidentally
Yeah
That didn't exist
Form is it did
The first chapter of their college
A
It was called
Confuse me with facts
And then the last chapter
Dakota
The Layla piano outro Eric Clapton
Gotcha
Is him trying to make his argument
Except
Hughes view of the world
Which is crazy is crazy
Psychological Issaquah
From page 10
Psychological problems are also involved and people to look at the evidence
Insiders
Which is what he calls the globalist
People are usually comfortable with their old beliefs
Conception
When Columbus told people the world was a ball and not a pan
They were highly upset thinking of a lifetime
Outlook
Intellectuals of the timer like
Where in electrical
Even if mix
Level stupid
Stupid
You know where
If you look
You if you look at those chips
Sailed over the ocean
It doesn't just fall
Couple of them
The reason that he was butting heads
People at the time was
The world
So do you know where the idea that Gary Allan
Working off of comes from the idea that there was some sort of
Tension between Christopher
Columbus on the intelligent Elites of 9
No understanding
Richest people of the time
And it wasn't about the addictive
Is also about heliocentrism it was about whether or not the Earth revolves around the Sun or the sun around the Earth
Watch
House arrest because he was a dick
Patron was in the Catholic Church
Eddie rode all of these letters in and then put it out this book like
I was he knows I was just trying to give
A possible way you
You could be yeah I got you
Columbus was
But also
I'd look
Just f***
Christopher Columbus
Being at odds with
Intellectuals of
What's the time
It comes directly
Plot
Of the 1828 book The Life and Voyages of
For Columbus
That was written
Bye
Washington Irving
I was about to if you say it was the same guy I was going to
Was most famous for having written
Rip Van Winkle
And The Legend of Sleepy Hollow
Great books you wrote a fictitious
History of Christopher Columbus and the time
Gary Allan
Who wrote none dare call it conspiracy is using it
As the centerpiece
Of his first chapter
In this next Passage
Also about the same
Right after the one I just read
And the typical flat-earthers
Headset
Interest involved in their own egos
Abuse on Columbus for challenging their view of the universe
Who don't
Confused
Our minds are made up of they said
What's
He took the name of his first chapter legitimately from
Him not knowing
About history and taking it all from a Washington Irving
Fictional
So that's the kind of book we're dealing with that Alex is being like a pretty productive socialism going to take over
This is a guy who's riding a believe that the man in the High Castle
Castle Israel like he's writing now about our history is like a castle
Time travel is possible in there are multiple dimensions
And that's why
Dimensional
That's the trick
I want to put too fine a point
Time travel
Dementia
That's the kind of book we're dealing with when we talk about Gary Allan's none dare
NADA book
Like you know how in endgame we were going through it there all the victors
Quotes that were made up
He makes up quotes
There's just
So much s***
Crazy how bad this book
Why not
So now we're
Minutes into the intro of Bill Ayers
Still have not heard from him
Chris 43 put yet so
I know now that this
This is really shity of me to have named
This clip Alex
How to do brief
Freaking froze because
Might be a pot Kettle situation but anyway
Ladies and gentlemen we are an hour of this worldwide broadcast
Joining a sheer on the 20th
He is
Weather
Underground distinguished professor of Education
Involved in Ayers is written extensively about social justice
Democracy in education
The cultural context of schooling
Has an essential intellectual ethical and political
He is a former vice-president of the curriculum division
Educational research Association
Is just let him
Have the floor the first three 45 minutes
This is way of saying like
I didn't ask for that I didn't know this was going to happen
This is going to I'm preemptively letting you know one how I hope this ends
That whatever it is he says is a lie because if I don't let you know that
You're going to watch me get my ass kicked and all the floor
Areas
Scholarship and should our kind of
To be mocked
He was reading that resume in your life
S*** that dude got a resume and then you go back and look at other Infowars gases like
He is the captain of the happyfun ship boat
At Bunker Lance bar
He runs at a run
Anti-communist trivia we've got a guy who will sell you a postcard with all the words
To never get arrested
All you need to know is that Alex would have f******
Gary Allan on every
Everyday if you can
Resume
Common core education things like that that's fine
I want to get into Obama
Legacy
Obama
I am so amused
Socialist leader they thought would come or
Or will that be another
Weather
I want under Steeler
Bill Ayers George loss of asking about
Larry Graham
Progressive
Thank you so much
For coming on with acid billares. O RG
Thank you very much
That is built
Boy he's there
He just learned he just
Intro
I would leave earlier and then still be like
Well it's fucken do this
And also there's a bunch of points where
Alex has his mic
Way down
We can talk over if Mike is clearly turned off or are you staying
That's not fair
Is Mike is off and he's just laughing
Like a clearly he's just like what are we doing cuz not know who Alex Jones is
That should be
Now that's what makes this fun
Neither of them really know what the f*** is going on right now what
One of them should have responsibilities to know cuz it's his show
The other one
Accuses
J'accuse
Build-A-Bear
And this isn't
Then let me just start with Tommy
Brickshelf because
Most communist Center socialist
Person
Do you endorse the type of communism
Russia and China
Global democracy and democracy
Right now
This isn't over
You can see it Alex
I got to make sure I don't let him talk
Yeah yeah yeah
Equation of God
In terms of the government libertarian
I believe that we need more democracy
In any democracy the solution to our problem
Let's come at it from this angle do you change your house your views changed since you are one of the
Weather Underground
Shakira
Way to present yourself when you're the host of a show
Like you just like
You let this guy
A very
I know that you're calling me communist but realistic
Sick leave
Much more complicated than that
Different facets to my philosophical
Long pause
Have you go somewhere else
I would prefer.
For Alex
What are the things that
Asmus goes along
Bill are singing bunch of s*** that Alex realized
I hate this guy
I have to set him up
Yep he was a terrorist who is trying to check
About it
But in principle in terms of
The real world
Well what what Alex just
Heard was
I accidentally said
Fairly similar
Because
I think that
A lot of the good principles that Alex
Pretends to believe in
Bill Ayers believes was a definition
Of what you could call a classical liberal
Here's that
He has to be like
Can't allow that
How much are beds
I mean no I'm not a I'm not saying that it's a perfect
Comparison I'm just saying that all of the stuff he described
Alex wants to co-op
And imagine that he is the is the description of those
Actually lives
And he's a f****** fraud who actually is a
Conservatives fascist ask
Still have
Dropping
You still got a conservative
Because
Some of the exchanges that they have are not to be believed
Text Chunk
Resigned
Coming together
And what Bill Ayers would call
Let's come at it from this angle
Weather Underground versus 2015
Well I mean
Catastrophic
We should
So you don't
Unfortunately
You got John McCain completely mainly Elena Chang
Because I think we should call
I think we should become a nation among nations
What is your view of
Barack Obama then
I did not edit them I did not edit this
Splice that to be like through that
He can't real but that because
S***
I am in favor of those things
Or at least I am supposedly
Put all the Sonic also I'm
Supposed to
I hate Bill Ayers
Post
Yeah
You're not black
Come on man
What are we doing Disney rake
That's the idea
Like he's really screaming he's really lashing out Obama
Through Bellaire
Somewhat
Billares is it that Obama is
VSCO
Need to know if you had
Any
Interest in Bel Airs before the
0%
Caribou
Focus look like
Fears about cultural Marxism
And stuff like that was part of the John Birch
Society
That's the world that Alexandra
Come from so I can
I could see him being a name that Alex was
Aware of
How many p
People work
Even aware of Billiards. Before Fox News
Add him being associated with
Obama
You can't imagine that Alex
Research
I think I was I knew bellairs was
One of my friends not growing up but
College with Kyler
Something about him bombing all the time joke
Which is good for a roast
My first year of Comedy certain way
I'll take a medium
I'm so we get there at the end of the clip
We see we hear a mascot out of adolescent
What do you think
Let's find out what
Think about Obama
Alex would assume that it's
I love the gyno and this is
At the end of Obama's tenure so billares as watched all of those things
He just described that he didn't want
PD expanded by Obama
Well
What is your view of
Morocco
Barack Obama
What do you think
Community College
Pragmatic politician
You can examine
Bill Millers
Very good tactics
About getting a
Village
With the village Elders have
Common ground
I understand that but you're not
You fight for
Oh boy
Maybe two minutes into them talkin heard Bill Ayers say a bunch of stuff
Andy realizes I cannot let this man
Anymore I must attack
I have to attack and from here on out
We are just going to
People
A bad time
Rikers Island
Got to be a dick
Alex
This is a
This is a smart move on
Undoubtedly
This is the this is how Batman
Smart move
Difficult
Turn off the f****** line
Put it on robtwo
Right that is a girl that is a smarter movies to be like
Caesar salad
Committed to doing this
Interview what you have to do really well right there is
You're lying about everything
Who is older also characterized the idea of us
Agreeing on something as being a
Evil attack
No that's alright
What's the point of even talking
Well we're never going to agree on it
Confusion
I hope you can do that cuz
To be his game
Just trying to
Keep Bel-Airs
Confused
Praying it works for
So I know he's really ugly
Fillers
PetSmart
Alex
Dump
The powers of the
To fight against
PetSmart which is yelling
Saying confused
Right
I know we
But how that is
Now Appliance
Twitter
Backyard brawls
All they're doing is yelling
Old
I'm so Alex wanted
You asking that last
Who funds
Is his way of
The following up on what he said before he has you where he's like
He's going to come in and
Pretend that he doesn't die all the mega-rich
So here's where this goes this is
Like this
Is nuts
From those guys
Retired professors I'm not sure
Define Liberation theology
That I know you're fully aware of the University campuses
Is he
Are you excited about geology
Taxes for George Soros
Roosevelt
Real place on Pulaski
Revealing that you
Like what you just said whatever he's at
You don't know who I am is it him being like
I have a paranoid background
I'm a paranoid
You saw through me immediately
Admission that like
Started my work
What is instantly
Also Alex is pissed off that use the word
Because he doesn't understand that work
Which is
Giggled
Chinese government
The CIA says 60
Are you sure
Nothing about you
No no
Deliberation
Is a connection that he's implying
Between George Soros and the pub
So him saying I didn't say that absolutely not true
I was about to get into asking you about George Soros
Geology
I don't know much about Liberation theology
Organizing stirring up
Liberation theology
I love you
Talking about
I am a professor
Professor
Now the witch
Center on
Ideas
Wherein we communicate regarding those we stay focused on the top
Using that topic we then
Take angles towards it
And we try and see where each other land
And then we try and convince each other of our positions and whether or not
Inferior or perhaps
Equal to each other
You however have taken everything I've said
Ignored it and then completely different direction a tentative mischaracterized maybe everything
I had a when I was in college I took a class on
Pomodoro
Yoshi fight
Rabbi
Define for Liberation theology
Probably that's that's exactly what that is I don't remember a ton of what I learned about the tour up because
Quite frankly
Stuff going to come back
They really remembered about him
Experiential
In the class
Conversation
3 Florin,
Yeah and impressed upon us really early in the
Where was
The beginning of any kind of like real conversation you
You can have with anybody
The definition
You have to be sure that you're talkin about the
The same thing
Before you
Can get anywhere
And I don't think that all bills.
He's trying to nail down what are we talkin about if we are going to talk
Fliptop
I'm ready to talk about Liberation theology if you want
I don't know a lot about Liberation theology
George Soros
But I don't know a lot about the Pope
I'm really not
You are okay
Remember about Rabbi signs
Class was that
He had this
Videos
There was a
You should always has a rash
Moving out
Now it would be like to espouse
Apple X
In life you need to go about your
Your
Expire
Looking at them
Assessing what they're bringing to your life
Think positive
You can walk away from them
Choose an interesting idea
Something nice to hear when your 8
Entry-level religious studies class
If I were Bill Ayers I would recommend
Do that an end of this interview early Alex
What is ovulation
Bring me to my life
Not much
Got to go
Cuz he could have
Well but he's
He's like
What are your right now is him
Going into
Full-on educator
Like this
Not being able to this is the a****** in your class
Who is just trying to
You got
50 people in a
F****** room
And everybody is like I'm hungover and I just want to go to the edges want to go to my next class or whatever the f***
Turn the looks at his
Staring daggers at like we're going to be here another 25
But the professor is like
My job
Is to educate
There's no education
There's nothing to that
Less quickly ended with
Alex
Who is saying
The community organizer
Just liberation
Theology
Prompted built a Slowdown
Pieology
Community organizing
Bellaire.
Fake laugh
Because he knows what
I know it is
I've known what he's doing this
This entire time
It's not hard.
He is going to accidentally say what he's doing
In a little bit
But before he does that
Search the weakest link in the chain
Before he does that
Explains if'n they come back from commercial today
Super butt
Offer that time explained
Eli's
About
Volaris
Serious discussion
Supporters
Christian call in
Here's where I stand
Professor Ayers
I don't know if you've read
March
Ultra-rich
Fun socialist and communist movement
Population
History shown that
Collective delivers hell on Earth
Force worksheet
I disagree with you
Fundamentally
And I guess you believe that we have a real form of capitalism disagree with that
Sitting on top of a socialist management
We're back to the food.
He's a fraud
I have no idea what you're talking about but
Classifieds the CIA
Where do you find
Here we are
So there we are
You are Alex Jones
Yeah you are f****** called on in class
Funeral 16 on history channel Ancient Aliens bro
That's crazy
Spoiler alert
CID
Power
The CIA was formed in 1947
Bright
Mouth and tongue
And Power Inn
Officially
Was the first act officially but he was already
Pretty much an hour
Nobody has created to make
Mauser officially
For control of China
Chiang Kai-shek
And I
What ended up happening was around 19
36 or so I
That we decided
We should be back in Chiang Kai-shek
It's going to
To be a huge hassle
Little bit behind on that one
A lot of work China govern
Yeah and it's
We withdrew support
Because we knew that it would be
Live
Count log
Unbelievable
I'm so
To the extent that the United
States government decided to not get involved
On behalf of
Someone who was our Ally
Yeah we did do that
We passively allowed Mao Zedong to
Power
Was going to happen
Immediately following you can always following me
We're still dealing with the Rams
Locations of the Rape of Nanking
And that's when you get into like
If you have a
If you have a foreign power
Decimating your entire population
You're going to wind up getting a nationalist leader who says he's going to protect you from
So
Reforms in 47
Now is officially in power in
Timeline
Does not working
Anyway
Leave it like
Within a year-and-a-half
Of the CIA formed
They were able to
Craft their ability to put into power
A dictator in the biggest country in the world
The CIA was only officially
Put into place
Vine
Faygo
This is where we would do a jack off
What do you like
Alright buddy
It was Declassified before congratulations
For some reason
I just love the idea of
A completely reasonable person
Confronted with
The most unreasonable person a person but no type of which this guy is like
You're texting the wrong person
Shut off
Bomb
In my world that is the most reasonably priced something reasonable thing to do
Betsy's like the most reasonable
Justice
Like
Do you exist
Like that's what I hear in this interview the whole time
Unfucked
Your
This represents
Oven steak
I'm not going to reach you
I don't know you might be projector
Too much of the
Because I
Like I'm projecting a ridiculous
I think he was
Annoyed look
I believe you crestfallen
I think he I think he maybe
For a second
Quickly
Into
Intellectuals
Superiority right just like
Figure out what he's talking about we could talk about it if I can
If he will actually say what
Kind of
Bill Ayers
Stop having conversation and starts playing sudoku
Our you got up
Cambiar in an hour
Refuse
I think went
So poorly
For Alex
That at this point
Just got to like
I think he was hoping to
Trump card
For him
He's like
I got to get
To it so he just gets Patty about the bomb
The interview
Mild-mannered
By our government
Property
Position
6000 police officers
Because you know what I'm going to do
Of what you're saying and then
You say
To say what I want them to say overlay them with
The things that you don't want me
I'm using you as a prop
Alex
First person to
Ask him about that
He has been a professor for how long
How many job interviews do you think started with are you going to bomb us
FBI
F****** grills him about test
Crazy
Okay well I've made it through my entire life but you know what
Alex
You got me
Come on
I understand
Impetus to
Let's paint things
Isn't it no way
You never you never heard anybody
Your bombs
Put the number of Bob
Leave me to think like
Everyday to bomb the building they accidentally hurt somebody
Baby like now we did that that was
Unfortunate whoever
Overdid it you take the blame
I can find really is like
Weatherman
Related people
Townhouse
People got hurt Worthy
People who are making the bomb
Yeah they say that that was an inch
Sounds like
From Baton Rouge
Became very
Careful and make sure even our own people weren't hurt
Truck
What are those
That seems more like an insta
Just like
People who were involved with Weather Underground also trying a problem
Subway
Sort of the thing that they were in
Purple peppers
Sure
Oh yeah
The plot of Die Hard
For a long time go for at least
What 30
Which one
Cygnus conversation turns out
Trying to jog my memory like nope don't care
So
The other one was
There was a bombing
That
Got injured at
Around the time
The weathermen
Which was not necessarily A weathermen bombing
Right no one is
Proven that they were
Rap
Like I would be willing
I don't know
Approved it to me
If if they wanted to hurt people right
The effect like
The wave
Able to operate as a terrorist
Organization
4 years
Right
At least believe they could have killed a lot more people if they want it
A smartphone involved
You could have had some
I'm really great
My gut tells
They wouldn't
Do all of this
Is politically motivated
Like legitimate
Extreme vandalism as he called
Who didn't even die
You guy gets hurt
Right that seems like a waste of the entire principle that you can imagine that
Part of the reason that they were successful
For so long is that they did
Actually kill
Bright like that was kind of part of the big deal the priority
Just destroying property
Destroying rich people
That's far more
Important
Legal system
A million
But
There's nothing
Maybe they did
There's no way for it there's no way for me to know
I don't know
Motivation
A project chaos
Fight Club
I assume
You think so it is much as they age
Asteroid
Empty building that
Yaga
That's gross
We abandon our podcast
Call Chuck Palahniuk fuckyourself
I believe
Sincerely
Kill anybody
If they hurt anybody
It was not in
Unfortunate
Side effects
A bomb
That seems like a really shity
Like anybody
Gets killed by a bomb
Was
Entirely their intention
To not hurt
Their intention
Was to destroy property
To bring attention
That was going on
All the murderer
Exactly
So
I believe they had a
I guess all I can really say for certain
Is
Everything I know
Hearing bill
As much as I've read
I believe there was
A desire for a politically-motivated Act
Alex's
Question
The only thing that
Can be
Responsive
Yeah
Super weird
It's also exactly what you do
Government
And we engaged
Crossing Lines
And blew up that building a false flag
Lightfoot
Absolutely not
Another like
Shift of the quest
He's just constantly child
I don't like your answer
Whatever your answer is I'm going to disagree with it I want to get
What do you want is already assigned exactly
Realize I said exactly
It's interesting because it's like
It's like an interview
Unlikes
60 minutes where there's a
Bunch of God
They never ant-like think the answer is never
Play It's almost like
It's just one side.
Right show a picture
Of the gyrus of the guy like looking at
Interview
The guy didn't
Show up
This is
Clint Eastwood yelling at a f****** chair
At the yard
Do cuz
That's what it is it's
It's like if
Like if Obama was
In that chair
And he was like well actually
I've been politely explained like wow you got it
Some things a bit wrong
Ivan Clint Eastwood through smoke bomb.
And all Clint Eastwood
Putting rectangular in reality there was the person
Significant
Not about Obama
You don't but that wasn't
Who is the voice of the great but the inflection
You got the info not that wasn't
Episode
At this point
Velazquez Buford Alexei
What about Larry grass wall
The guy who we heard
Who is the FBI Informer
Man who had canceled
The weather
Had a bit of a
Now
This
Response
Larry gives
I'm not Larry
This response
The bill comes up with
Is Zoloft
So exactly what you would
How you would respond if you work making something up
And it is
The biggest problem
A Alex
It's such a
Huge problem
Pretty much a creature of whatever whoever runs the justice department
Preacher of the justice department
How's the justice department
I believe
Military
The levels make it sound like
He said more
And the
Broadcasters like
If he did
Cuz this
Straight off the Alex Jones channel to make that sound like
Cut off from their crazy about that
Or why didn't they not
You don't mean like
They are still
The business somewhere in there
That's terrible
Alex
For just a moment he's like please stop
Please Bill Hill.
Human-to-human
I'm just trying to do my job here man you're trying to do a job
Jobs
Bill I'm not so stupid that I don't
You just made me
Me do
Was agree with the Nixon Department of Justice
Was awesome
I'm going to retain my boo
Grant good source
Come on man
You know what it hears that here's what they cut out
Hazel Dakota
Alex going
You're mean
You're making me
Feel bad
Could have also just been
Kicking into autopilot in
I'm selling iodine
Pocoyo
Or maybe just a long pause
Red's out and then 20 minutes later
Yeah
I actually buy that more than anything else
Cuz
Clearly you hear it
You hear it that's not the same audio
I know it's not but it also I could recreate that
I could like without a
I could
If I was like overly
Excited
Vicky would be
He's so aggressive deposit Mike
I put I can't let him stay anymore anymore
We'll go to Commercial and get back to it
Cuz I mean the obvious
The obvious obvious
I'm still
I've held down a job
Disability
Otherwise
Is that
Every
President
Yea or
Right
Strange
Over and over and over
Like within
Democrat
As we speak
But Democrat
Throughout the history
From night
70 whatever down
So what are you talkin about we're talkin about
48 years
View
All that time everybody is just been like
Malik
Simple
You know how I'm not in jail right now
Alex
Petkovic guy
Lies
Cuz if he was telling the truth
I committed a
Capital punish
I would have been
Put to the death penalty
Yeah
There's literally no other
A prescription for that crime
Shared enough to
Plant someone in the organization
Credible
And came out with that information I would have acted on it
Who was president later because I got it I got a spoiler alert for you
Until the time
That VI
The Weather Underground stopped existing
Public administration
Did you get caught up in the end of May
And what have you were busy
You still have until 77
Weather Underground
Inactive
So
I don't know you would someone would have
I guess that's all
Now here's a here's my other boy
Butcher
Disturbance
The s*** together
Alyssa money loses it again
This is
Is edited
Siri I don't know know know that
Commercial
Right.
Celebi come back from
F*** you talk to you first of all first of all go f*** yourself
Go fuc yourself
He's got to leave earlier or maybe I didn't know anyting
I don't know one of the two you piece of s***
Well that sounds so petty
I want to hear from Seville air support
What are the odds Bill Ayers supporters are listen
To Alex Jones
You haven't heard of the Facebook group
Info Weather Underground. Org
You support this guy love to hear from you or is it 100
I know your website Bill Ayers
Dot-org
And there's a red star a black background
Holiday
Mao's cultural revolution
Dial system
Yeah he was wrong and he was lying
Macy's
I don't belong to you
Play the question
Did I say that
When did I say
What the f***
What is
Torrid
The visitor View
I love his interview I wish all interviews were like this
I'm done with any kind of conversations that exist I am all about some random dude just say
People who are
Befuddle you almost I want befuddled
Everything diagram that to a certain
You have like
Him being like what look
You're a dick what's the diagram
Kudos
Where it's going to land exactly but it's going down
He knows all
You start with
Like a
You say you're not a maoist
Look at your logo
Hippie like
What time Macy's
You know
There's a lot of people who have logos that are similar
He's not staying
Anything other than like
Baby I just like the color scheme
I think that's kind of the bottom line
Famous
, you son of a b****
Well I'm not famous
What are you doing with this show knows who I am
What is
It's so great here's what I say
A purely
Alex
Is just
Trying to Middle
Cuz Alex wants him to lose his ship
At some point Alex just wants him
Get mad one of us has got it I just want you
To get mad and yell at me about something
So I can cut that into a clip
You specifically lying about something hard
Did either of those things but
He is going to get some
Really good audio
Himself losing our
Talkin about
Children and their parents and their families are
Absolutely
Melissa harris-perry
Wait a minute about what
Local community
And just as strong as our militaries
Domestic security
Okay
Wilson you know what
Alex had to and did admit
I'm wrong
And then had to move along
Because otherwise if you let
Drawing attention to the fact
That
F****** Bill Ayers just made a point there's like okay there is a community interest
In people's parents not being shity
Now is that is the case do you think there is an advantageous thing where the community
Does not benefit from allowing that abusive
You're wrong
But that's where the
Mulan child Army
Can't actually argue with an unreasonable Act
This is the
This is perhaps
The most perfect distillation of it that I think I've ever seen
Really astonishing
His bill is
Because it because so many people it would take
Unmute
Like with with members of my own family where it's like
It takes a while
Get angry the whole time they like
I don't like where this is going I'm I'm not
Feeling good about this
And then you get there
And they're like
What word
You know like that kind of thing
He just did it in two sentences that's astonishing
But also
Also
Why are you doing this
What are you doing why are you doing this you could not do this
I don't know I think it might have been like
Nephews
If you did this
Siri
Not I'm not I'm not presuming that like billares nephew or niece is like a fan of Alex Jones
This guy's crazy
Are we still on
I will show them the clip the next day and there were like a look at how around their babies
So funny
I can't think of maybe like a badass
Are very few explanations
For like
How because I mean
Bored
There is
Probably
3 minutes
To the beginning of the interview
Where
Can see in his face like
Oh boy
I'm kind of in for it
Stick around for the whole lot
So
It is next
Jester's there
I would say this is
The point where Bill
Start
To fight back
A little bit
And start to be a dick back
Okay alright
Do you know where I'm coming from
Bologna
Melissa harris-perry
Mouth of Sauron MSNBC
Tommy's
Show me show me show me some
Melissa harris-perry
Real quick
Who's going to play it but you
Hear that bill is still talking like
Cuz he needs to
Has 43 years
Marxist-leninist
Stop stop
There's no other explanation for that response like
Are you lost
Yeah
Hard
Why
You would play that clip again
That are
I love it I love it
So this is good
Alex brings up eugenics
Which billares is
As you can Eva date like look at all of Bill Ayers writing
Father and
The white races
Superior
History of interviews.
Donatello
Visionary talks about
Is good German
Trump
Call Alex asked
Eugenics
Honestly
I'm not that I regret on
Some levels
Really like
Bill Ayers
You on some level think like
You know I know
You didn't mean
Anybody with
Those bombs
Stream
I have a difficult
I think his answer about you
Eugenics is perfectly measured
I think it's a really good answer
My only thought that likes so far
Listening to Bellaire
Is listening to him call it at
Extreme acts of
Vandalism
Is kind of like
Alright dude
Just f****** sake bombs
No but that sounds like
Extreme acts of vandalism sounds like that late
Steve's early 7
Wendy's Abbie Hoffman kind of like
I don't like you I don't like you from
Whatever
I don't like I don't like Frick you like hard drives
You blew that s*** up because they were doing
I'm infinitely worship
Some of it is no use
Sarek
Is eugenics
Are you aware
Gable Wars
Black community
Represent
Vestigial
Asus eugenical maybe you never got that high the power structure but that's what it is
I don't know
Racial superiority in white supremacy
Has never been
So again I don't I don't accept your premise
There's a lot of that
F*** are you talking about but it's tough because
I think a lot of people don't know that that's an option
You can be in a conversation with someone
No I don't accept that
No
But
Until you can
Prove it
I'm just going to say no
Amen
Because
Iowa
Smart man I am welcome
To you proving
I got nothing for you
We got we have nowhere to go with
What conversation is there to have
You're arguing something that's made up
Definition
The term
I Say I Do
So there we go
The middle
The knot Alex
Like a
So now Alex brings up
Tragedy and Hope
Hundred page book
Once again
And studying
Passages
Taken out of
In the nun are called
Such
This reading
I think it's a
Amazing
I would love
Maybe
Three-month break from doing this show
Where I could go to
No the Bahamas
Bahamas
Degrees
Take me to Greece
If you would like to donate to the
I think it would be fun
To have a relaxing
The week
Or so where
I do nothing else
Get through
Cuz I've read a lot of it
Really
Interesting in
Death
Alive
Piece of
Historical
Narrative
Really well
The paragraph
Low into each other super well
There's way too much information
Right
Somehow
Down in it
Okay there's a lot of like
Donation for why certain pieces
History flowed into other pieces
However
You do believe that the passive voice is fine so I'm going to hold you I'm going to hold you
It's the same thing with John beholder
Like I started
Holyshit I
Didn't really
Now I do all day
Some good sentence
There's so much to be gained by
Reading Buffet
Yeah
I agree
I would love to
The other
700-page
But I haven't ridden
Read of Carroll Quigley
Tragedy
Cuz I get the
I get the prime
In tragedy
Is it
No it's the humanity keeps
Fighting with
Pizza forever
The whole part is
She hopes that we can
And work
Schedule
Horrible
Dailypay to Hope in the Hopeless way to track
Specific reference
But I found
From Alex
Yes wrong
Derriere
From Joel skousen
Cleon skousen
For many of these dudes
Who reference
Carroll Quigley
Every single
Reference that I
Define from the
I go and I read
50 pages
Each Direction
And they don't say
All but these dudes
Claim they say
They haven't read the whole book
They haven't
They take
Just out of context
Yeah and they do that
In order
2 attack
Ver version
Liberal is
Existence
It's not important I only bring this up
How to say that
How to stupid
And
Quickly who's Bill Clinton
Favorite author
What's f*** Bill Clinton
No idea
Understand
Why they were funding fascist and communist
How the whole game work
Not
Big corporations
Kobe 11
I don't know he was
George Soros who just got caught finding 33 million
True
American government
Got his ass
Love it
Getaround
That
Is that the robber barons who funds are better than the robber baron
Who don't fund me
I'm sorry I just
Which what would I have
To do
With this
Finger me
The robber barons
That don't exist
I don't know
And you said nothing
Fine I don't know why you're ask
Remind me about it
The people that I associate with George Soros
Even though I don't know who you are
All of the demon
Do you really talk about
The foundations
I don't know what you're talkin about
I've slipped out of character
I'm much more comfortable when I'm doing the character of being Alex
I don't like being all right all right
Let's try the other way all right
I don't know what the scene is
You would never pay you would never make it past level 2 and
Second City
EagleRider
Maybe our off Beach
SNL you got three characters but you're going to you're going to be relegated to a writer
To write you a story about
This next quiet
How does get a transition
Trying to get this show to land within a reasonable amount of time
Like I said
He's losing
This is what I was trying to
Set up
Character
Butts Foundation
Talking about
Macon aggressive
Accusations
Fake left-wing ideology
As a form of domestication
Controlling
Executive orders
Right there already if you've lost the coin
We lost the point
Can't breathe
I can't breathe that
That hurt my neck into be hurt my neck
Do you know this a pinto just got stood for that crash
Alex
Quickly realizing
Referring to
Ago I think the ID
FairPoint
Perfect
Phil just making
FairPoint
Dancin
So far amount Bills team
All the way back from
To now
Only problem I have with him is him calling it
Extreme acts of
Turn the phrase 0 problems
Alex I will say his
Like it
Seems like his Kryptonite is someone saying what do you mean
Yeah
If he's used to flattery and then a change of subject
When were there
Friday
A land
Another plug for kept Around the Clock
There's no way he'll show up but if he
He does
I will just keep saying
All I want
The only dream I have
Is that David Knight
Shows up
That's what I'm I want David
I want to give David Knight of microphone
Just so we can both be like
Big shots and then after the show we danced around to like came out of a lady
Did David and Goliath that's possible
I don't I don't discount that is a possibility
Buckeye
This probably would be the greatest
Cast of all time
You and I just bothering you
But we
Personalities
We got to finish this
All right so I'm Bill billares an hour
Doctor talking
The point is
Still working under the
Assumption that he
I love God
Right
Ubill
I think there's a culture Clash here because we're not controlled left or control
Colibri bulwark and have the right to control their own guns
You're about to watch Chicago
You're an old-fashioned
Either we should eat
U.s. military
Homeless
So
This is Bill's way of having
Blackwell
Literally ready to be homeless
Or know of the homeless there
An example is a
Specifically tailored
Alex
I'm saying that it is a ideology
Suggest everyone should be
People being arms that they don't like
Bill 100% is setting up Alex
To say some
But he never calls him out on
Actually respect the hello
Bill
By saying
We should arm
Is that
Precipitating Alex
Well they're crazy
Which is actually
Indicative
Some people shouldn't be allowed to have dry
Accidentally revealed on air
Through his
Stupidity
I am his just be
Lulled into some sort of comfort
Yeah I don't forgot anything I made it I think I made it alright
Good Lord
90% of the homeless
Puerto Rico
Obviously
Homeless people
Boston
Shouldn't they get some help from the community
Shouldn't allow them to get treatment
God dammit
That's amazing
But at least he hasn't he has like 32 at least like
Here's why
Here is why fighting games
Will always
Have
Far greater
Truth
Witches
If somebody just pulls a Street Fighter combo on you like that
Hadouken
Die
Play the next match
Everybody knows you just got murdered
More like is it
That would be
It wouldn't be a cat would be like
Nice try
Stripes
Retail
Salad
And then revealed that he had no
Scan and then burned it
To the ground
That was
It starts with k more sexually attracted to a man
Vista Avenue three-year-old dude
God damn it I would make love to him immediately you don't want
I'm totally fine people having Guns Over
Feminism is more about their bill
Eagles space in economy
Homeless people
Alex being like let's not
Which also indicates that
Have the second amendment has limits
Argue against
Most of the time
I meant the idea of like
Hear music
That is a
Secondary ping pong
You're crazy
Look
Ardent
Tennis Pam
Bill just hit a winner
I'll tell you that right now
Cross-court forehand
No cuz that was a note
Minutes
45 lakh in a row
Dog at these to serve God
Alex just got murdered
Is the best
Alex does not really understand how bad he just got murdered
Adidas on a certain level
You realize he was beat
You don't
She does not know how much
Process pictures
To which he was just
F****** ground or does he understand how deep
He's already
Is brutal
He's 6 Underground at least
Like this entire time
He's been trying to
Present the image that
Bellaire
Which we know from his label
Or his logo that is very similar to
Bye
My bills later
On this episode
Of the communist
Play a Communist Revolution
It's going to exhaust himself
You just basically admitted that its welfare system
I've been illiterate
Gotcha
If you read anything I've ever written
You know that's exactly right
Send something
Now I just
Want to have a conversation
Bill about
You should try and get him on
The Pitbull actually bet you could Brito
Send an email
Are you looking for
Schezo retired academic
I think that'd be great cuz I I would be interested in having a conversation about the pitfalls of a participant
Participatory democratic
Economics
System is well
Because that is not exactly an infallible system on its own
Like
All all I am
Light at the end of the day
I love watching Alec
But what I'm really interested in
Is talking to Bill about what's going on
Like he is a fascinating
Stories
He's a brilliant guy
I wouldn't know a man I'm in love with belt
I'm in love with bell
Well
I'm in love with him
Here's where you're going to learn
About
If you say he's a soft yes on white genocide I think we just made a match
Your girlfriend's position is
This next clip is
Is more about whether or not
Obama's
And then Alex
I wanted to find out if he had ever seen a film by Joel
Gilbert
Who's the caller
Do I take on that
Filmon how did he feel about it
Frank Marshall Davis
I never knew Frank Marshall Davis I read about him in the New York Times
Alright well
Barack Obama
Alright
Also Dan
You never need to say
Ivan listen
To every show
That Alex has ever done
But anytime you have ever said
This is a caller
The accent gives it away every time
McDonald's
Regardless of what
Accent is somehow
Every accent that color has
Is f****** banana
Alex is color accent
It has no consistency it is just
Oh yeah
I swear to God I could
20 voices
I can pick 6 out of
You would call a tour planning
Like this is a Louisiana
Alex
This is an Alex accent there's just
Trust there's a
Uncertainty
There's just a
Certain quality
Here like
Stimulant
In people's voice
You can hear
Pothead
Someone's voice
Look at you
Tributes you can hear
In people's voice
Patents joke
About Darksiders
I bought that you can tell when a person is fat by hot butter
Like your ears like physical trait we're talkin about emotional traits
We're talkin about
I understand that
The conversation
Then it's an emotion
I agree
What I can
Cuz I wasn't invalidating what you were
I'm sorry
I'm sorry Dan
I love you
Yes
Do you think
It's there already
I know is going to be Rock
I'll tell you what whatever it is I think
I'll tell you what Alex
That
I am
First up
Shock this is still going on
Bill is still here
He's very patient
Howard
Real bad so everyone involved except billares
Bill is
To Hillary
Bill Clinton
Bill Ayers
He's already made it clear that he doesn't like Bill Clinton knowing only what
It's at Beth
Milquetoast
Before Hillary
Seems like he's only into Obama when he was in college
Hungary with a lot of
Seems like it has whole life
Zion Market
The kind human being we were friends
Yeah
But if your girl
Person
Milkshake
With Obama
Yeah metaphor
Well who would you share a milkshake with Hillary Clinton or
But also
Alright it's not in
Tennessee
Sarlacc miracle
Hillary Clinton
Milkshake Rand Paul
American milkshake
Life long time without milk
F*** Hillary
Bad sex
Why
What if I
What does
If I started with murder Grandpa
She's a militaristic.
Around the question of
Tourism
So now
Alex is kind of realized
We have three more clip
But like
And the other two are Alex like
Desperately
Yeah
He is now head
Right you're talking about milkshakes right
Let's skip all of this s***
Let's just have a good time
We've been talking with really have a heart
What's going on
Waterboarding
Sepsis shock
I'm joking
God dammit
His riffing is so bad
So bad
Conservatives will never be fun
Man I love them
You know there's like
You go out to like how
To host
Like the Potter boss sisters here in Chicago
Andy Fleming and Jay Michael Osborne
You're hosting together
Not like one of them
Say something the other one
You see that kind of roofing in the
In the wild
Urus
It's it's
Nutsert tool
How often
Alex
Say something
Presenting as
A joke
And then he'll get mad
Put your joke was just
I'm in
Cheney
I like
He has no reason to think you're not
The only
You've made it clear
Is queer
He didn't know who
Who you are you know what
And here's what
You like
Paul
And she is already established billares has
Did he also the
Maltese
He's also a wolf
Street guy on the outside
Maybe
Exactly
Public
Don't know about the time we're going to get the
For you to get there.
Alright
Throwdown
I found a clip
German episode that I don't think I'll ever be able to
Play ready right now I got to stop
But I have
We don't have a
Radio DJ
How to clip of Alec
Text Jones
He says
Cuz I
Everything I say
Every time
For the washing
Yeah whenever they don't
Editorial
That means
Position of
The paper
Now is that true
Then put out a newsletter for
Years in all of the things that were written in it for unsigned
But they were all written in the first-person
And a bunch of
F***
Capital letter to the LA Times
Washington
Any other news
Ron Paul newsletter
But didn't have a byline on it is
Anderson
Cancel that paper
Is
What article
There's a device
Terms of like getting away with murder
It's crazy
Anyway
Jesus
No I'm fine with you
So
I would say
The only
Caller
That
Michelle
Okay
They're kind of like
Throughout
There's a train
To be at game
Wonder
I have a question about
And admittedly
This guy
Coming at
Bill
From an aggressive
Disposition
Already questioned is an
Substantiv
And Bill
Which is
Unheard
What Bill allows
Insults
Has clearly throwing any questions
Duxbury
Professor who's dealt with
It's like a road, who's been on the road for 30 years it's like all your hat you think you're heckles
New
Metro Taco Bamba
Tire rack
My question that you look at the current state of educational system is absolutely just black
Plus
Navigate to be inappropriate
For you find there's a better model than what this public systems doing to demolish the brains of the young children
Chicago
Go to Chicago
Education for the people
Education
Obedience and conformity
Real quick
Don't say anything
Want to tell you
This Exchange
Terribly
Just ahead of time
Exorcist
I'm positive
And when I
I'm pausing here
Enjoy
That gorgeous
Just sentiment
But he gave
I meant
Reinforce
So bad
Troub
Music
There you go
How much for dinner
Washing systems
Wait a minute
Doughboy
That's Alex
Falling in love with him
The same way
Eufaula billares
Dunking all over the American government
Did a.m.
Is Nancy Pelosi have a basketball in her balls right now is like and what just happened
As far as the American government
F*** it and billares is right and go fuc yourself
We're more in
Alex
No I apologize
I'm sorry
Look how is how is Maddie
How many f******
X on the show
Has anybody ever come
To the way I feel about this
First time
There's a guest on Alex's Joe who is like
I'm 95% on Jordan size
But he's come on man let me know
I know that's why I'm leaving the fireplace
But yeah I know it is it is interesting because if you had been around 7
Is Matt Bomer
Who
From the tick
Yes I believe
Alright
Like the cartoon
Patrick Warburton
Using both
Also on Newsradio
Season of Newsradio who cares over 40
Alright alright
Flying a bird
Don't care about anything that happened past season 3 on news radio
Phil Hartman
But I know I agree I watch Newsradio and then Cry 1
So at this point
Jordan we've got ended
Flowers
We will do it better by Garren
Then Alex
Is this
Perhaps
Good up till this
Worlds
Worst dip
I've ever heard
If there was a tie
Time for Alex
Gracefully get out of
Interview
Against his
Riddle the kids is The Logical route
Eracism selfie
So are ya versus Zeus
This is so hilarious
I do appreciate you joining us
If you come down often will host you in studio
Strawberry milkshakes
Hotel room
I want to drop the truth serum
What is that mean
Veritas
I don't know that
Yeah that wasn't it for sure I don't know this I don't know that for sure
Newport NY
At the end of it
I don't drink milk
Do you want to come to the show
So let's
Outside
For Alex
I love it I love it so much notice is that
Bill Ayers
Who's birthday is it
Marshadow in
Beerland 10 p.m. the most important thing in our website is knowledge fight.
So quiet
Because my
Point of view has been represented Soper
Perfect. Even screaming your ass off and I'm tired
Girls are Twitter
You're brilliant
Good Facebook group
You should join the group
Because I post way more on that then
Facebook
Yeah we don't do the twin
That much at all
They only have this
Were they show it
A certain amount of gas
Bulshit
I want to play that game
In the group
Much more people see it
Please join the group
Anyway let's get out of here but
You are
Appreciate everything I have a great time with your wife
Get out of here.
Dumb dumb
Piece of s*** FBI informant
Zach a garbage
Go fuc yourself
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color