Alexandra Thurston color
Breakable do Dixit around Vic novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about
Today's novelty beverages
You were Fury
Stop
So many different things
Happening
Concurrently
Much much like app
God damn everything upon yourself
Random stranger
Just walked up to your office
I was like
One I work for Chase Bank
At work I guess
Video podcast
F***** over by Chase Bank at the WWE Network they hit me with a
Right now I'm down for the count
Yeah it really terrible couple days but everything is looking up cuz we're here
Absolutely brutal and we're going to have a great time
Jordan
Interesting podcasts
I was hoping
Actually
Use your joke
This guy walks up to you and I
I will show you the beer land in Austin Texas
I have never rehearsed a bit why would you imagine that I would just come up with like Jesus
Beaver post
Say thank you to our new sponsors which I would like to do right now
Say Rudolph the like to thank you in Austin this Friday
Jordan
I get to that
Execu to new donor at there what's going on Dean
I'm a policy wonk thank you so much
Thank you so much Bob
I'm a policy wonk
Bob Dylan
End of the Home Improvement television series
This Old Donation
Yeah well right
F*** out of the gate by going to knowledge fight.com
Support the show and I would really appreciate it
Is there a second ago we are going to be in Austin Texas
This Friday 10 p.m. doors open at 9
We love to see you all out there tickets still available
I think only at the door
They'll be avail
Today at once again we are doing most of our advertising to people who already live
Listen to the podcast
Have decided
Whether or not to go
Long ago
So I'm service
Grateful to everybody
Then who is already
Thank you
Yeah so I wanted today but I wanted to do is that I wanted to
Celebrate
City of Austin
Yes and I will say that I have found a great Austin related episode for the live show
But I found another offer
Episode ostomy episode
Episode is that like Schaumburg Chicago
Is that the kind of thing
Sort of
Like about Red Rock
Or whatever
Redwall
Series of books about mice fighting
Jacques
But before we get to today's episode
I should say we did record an episode over the weekend we were going to release on Monday and the universe soft
To not let that be recorded
And it got lost
It was
It's really fascinating because
The entire episode was essentially about how
You felt it that what we are talking about doing that episode
Cosmically we then did not do that we were talking about how everyone should ignore Alex's,
Bizarrely the episode doesn't record as if it were God's a
We actually recorded the Epic
Right I can guarantee that this isn't some way that were stealth say
That you should drink some MB
In that episode we did Cover also a little bit of the other stuff that Alex talked about on that Friday episode
So important that no one is talking about that we do need to play here at the beginning of this episode
Not heard by The Beatles last night I can almost remember
From the June 8th 2018 episode of The Alex Jones Show
The show a couple hours before he calls in
To talk about Anthony Bourdain
He calls in to say
Alex how refreshing is it to be a president
That essentially flips the bird to the globalist
The only place rustic line.
Resources for x or landmaster
Yikes right
We freaked out and screamed about this for like 10 minutes yesterday
No need to sort of recreate
Hot intelligence services
Hook up with Russia
Dominate the world
Geographically
Dominate
So that's
Not great which I believe
Dominating a globe makes one a global list
The only thing about that I still cannot get over is
What is the third faction of the paddock
What is it
So we got the Patriots we've got one confirmed faction the other one is
Or at least
Controlled vampires
Miss Molly
Schnapps
A very
Patriots Patriots
The globalist do battle International
Sit around and just laughing like a ha ha ha
Absolutely
Like you can trust
Aficionado there so absorbed
Communicate
Have they turned
Coded language
None. It's like you're all right
We're going to be going over is the November 30th
An episode of
Of the Alex Jones
I'd like Mary Austin
See if you have any idea why I
Have chosen this as an Oscar
Destiny episode
November 30th
Right
See what happens in
Just at the first Thanksgiving
Christ was crucified then correct
They do
No
Alright correct
Bethlehem
Are you sure
November 28th
A 220 something in the morning
Larry McWilliams
What
A ton of bullets
At the police station
Mexican consulate
Also shot a bunch of bullets
Epi Federal Courthouse
D i was shot down by a cop
Eventually
You had let me die written in marker across his chest
He also in his pocket had a copy of a book
That's where the Hydra
Exactly.
2-acre
Call Dee
It's kind of like a loose-knit a group
Call yourself a priest in this Phineas priesthood
And he had a book about them and their history and its occupants like
As if you it was Catcher in the Rye for him
Which speaks volumes about
What he was about
So I went in the outback
Some of that I knew
Probably
There was more property damage
From what I've been able to go
The most Austin
Mass shooting I can think of that
Even their Mass Shooters like we don't want to hurt it
I don't think I want to
Congruent
You got to go to the Mexican consulate after that
Also our friend art Acevedo
Police chief
Yeah
Speculate
That there was real
To believe that the attack
You've been politically motivated
An anti-government attack
Also might be linked
To feelings about immigration
Being a
You tried to set the Mexican consulate on Spotify
Alright
Acevedo
Seems pretty obvious
From Texas monthly shooting up
Consulate shortly after President Obama
Executive order regarding immigration
Certainly
He's also if you looked over.
If you looked over social media you'd find that he had
How's the lottery
Positives
Stuff about Ron Paul
Some sort of connection that he had their philosophically
No that was the thing that was that count to the bank
I just knocked out of the bank
Up to the colors you have to stand on the thing
Bullets up in the area according to the law
Okay
So I would also accept sliding a piece of paper
To the teller the
Because I have a flashlight
This guy was a mess
He had a lot of them
Indications that he might be
The guy
Would be doing this
Skyrim stuff
He ended up
Getting shot by a cop
Judy is an old white guys 49 year old white guy
Galaxy around
Stop it
Stop
Because the guys in old white dude Alex has some complicated feelings about it
And again
Kind of a fan Alex doesn't really know what
To do with it and we'll watch him
Spinners wheel
And on the 28th
He took the day off
The 28th was a Friday
He took that off
Because he's like she busy masturbating to this guy
Thanksgiving
Maybe maybe Thanksgiving
Panera pre-recorded show does really funny
To listen to the morning
Great interview with Michael Savage
Alright
All right bro
So here's the first clip where Alex
Disgust is what he
He thinks is going on
The 30th of November
Also wanted most defensive
Things I've ever heard of the Chevy place
ZZ Top
To start the show please
For 6 p.m. central
Bottom of the hour
As much as possible
Talk about
Austin Texas
We're a few days ago we had
22 am
Running around shooting up the police station the Mexican consulate and
He's right here
Who's my hero
Hero I'll give you on that event
Austin shooter
Government motive
I saw some online videos of ninja swords and stopping
If it's the same Mo as the sky on East Coast
Okay okay
Your take on this one
You want him to have a gun he already had swords
The police station
Training
Smoke bombs
I would say David in present day or so you wouldn't
Alex doesn't like this this argument of like they're mentally ill
Folks
Notre to throw bombs at Pharmaceutical
They're all just
Already
Allowed for this
To be like right
Any chance video game in this year
Please compare
Oh okay
Quite shooter right
That is not going to go with
He starts with
This guy lives
What I pray
No
He's not going to say that he's not going to say that word for word what this guy does is what I tell
You're not going to like this
I'm not going to like this
I just sent you email people
You don't really know when they're going to strike
Bolts incidences of
How do you do that
Dad
The problem is
As awful as that is there's a certain part of my brain that's like
I never would have made that connection man
Never would I have even considered that
Possible to connect those two events
I don't know
Goodonya Alex
We're figuring out the single worst narrative
That is humanly possible
I don't understand why you would
Put those pieces
Alex is going to say
How could I possibly put those two piece
Shooter that shot of the f****** Mexican consulate in Ferguson does Ferguson have a Mexican consulate
Why does Austin have Amex
Chicken consulate that was another question of Texas
Is Austin On the Border
Not quite
Calm down
You should a hundred percent of seeing that, can I take a nap
What are the similarities
The end of November 2014
Alex's
Desperate to discredit
The situation in
Ferguson because it doesn't
It does not look good right we have a situation we're just
Not too long before where we're at right now
The
I wish I had the
The exact date
The policeman
Who shot Michael Brown
Wilson was acquitted
I have the right date
Exact
Of course I should have
Obviously made the connection
That Alex would make a negative connection
Shinto
A white man
Murdering
Right and then everybody be
Rightfully outraged by that
To a white man
Shooting up
Police station
The Mexican
Consulate
And that of course
What's in front of him in his own City
Is an act of War
Supremacist
Active White
What is the reaction to
The states
Perspective
You just made me feel really good even after all this time
See things through Alex
Look at it like
You've gone native
I'm willing to throw this guy under the bus
Even though he's my guy the only way I'm going to do that is if on the way out I can't
Two legitimate protest
Right
You know might have involved a little bit loading here in there
That wasn't the entire protest even most of it
There's an argument to be made
Who cares
Did the issue is
You take
White terrorism
Black Proto
Right conflate the two and all of a sudden you can
Can complain about both of them in the same way it appears that your Rising above
The racial tension
I'm just trying to get us a fight with each other
Literally deranged
Lunatic shut up a bunch of
Police Federal Building
Tried to burn down the next
Can consulate like now this is a protest
We could go line-by-line
Everything that that guy did Alex
Suggested that people should do
To certain extent I'm sure he
I guarantee
I would never
Force you to do all this
But if you went through everything that Alex Jones said
From like 2,000
Sooner or later you get like
You should shoot up the police station
Does courthouses need to be shut up
I got Mexican consulate
I got
You know what
Who does it got a bad feeling about those people I'm very proud
But that man
Conflict that's worse than the DM
I tried to get my Mexican citizenship
Two papers there
And they were like
You're not
It's very it's very difficult
Alex is operating on a bunch of real hard
Hard-and-fast
Sources
Write imaginary information
Imaginary
Never like that
I never liked that
Say quotes
Don't like that
Flash wait for criticizing
Police shooting
Fpi just got shot
Real quick about those FBI agents
CNBC article about that
Two FBI agents were shot at a barricaded home just miles
From the protest rack st. Louis suburb of Fergus
It's an early one.
Play police.
Both suffered non-life-threatening injuries after the shooting in Norfolk
St. Louis County
The incident occurred around 3:50
Teen a.m. local time
Authorities in St Louis County for dealing with violent protests after a grand jury decided not to
In Divergent
Some police officer Darren Wilson
Over the fatal shooting of unarmed teen Michael Brown
It was not immediately clear whether the shooting was connected
The teddy on rest
So it's probably completely unrelated saying
At the time that Alex
Able to report on it
Is this the same city
How far away were they from Ferguson's
Question why don't the cops ever invest
All sorts of stuff happened
That makes protesting
NSAID
Necessary
That is not you should not be allowed to
Who's close quote
According
This was an article in Time Magazine
Not the villain
Violent protests
Violent riots
Necessary
The headline was
Right
Do you a bit of that article that Alec
I want to deal with
He's never read it
Probably quote
MLK's
Letters from a burn
No it's just more of a
A discussion of
The realities are in our modern time in Iraq
And
Violent protests
The Tea Party Boston
Some tea party was
Being the way it is B
Writing is only ever looked
Bad when
The group that doesn't plan
Always
Look
2 people who really don't like
The content of what the protests
It's just
It's not the right way to do that
It's
To just accept it
That you're going to get f***** in the ass for the rest of your life
And for the rest of your children
534 the rest of America
That's the right way to go about
Sure sure
I don't want it I don't want
You deep into that cuz we will get into in a little bit
For now I want Alex to get back to these headlines
Cuz he's got some
He's got barnburners
Medline
Story
But a link from CNN
And a link from time Maggie
Alright that sort of thing
He goes Wherever not much to talk
Turn off
Now everything is always a
Okay
Well we're going to Riot
Necessary
That's from time
It's not
Ferguson protesters were peaceful
From
Infowars Time Magazine
A protecting Ferguson businesses
Another result
Explosive Infowars Nightly News Last Friday Night
So there's an article about have the brave
Brave Oath Keepers are protected
Heather being attacked by protesters
Right now picking up want to talk about is Alex in the last clip before this one
We'll talk about how there's so much going on involving like the Saint Louis
Situation
Hey this is great
This is not going to be a full episode where we talked about the
Realities of Ferguson that other people have done much better jobs than we ever will
Entirely
It's really difficult for me not to
To point out that during the entire concert
Immigration with Ferguson
Policeman was relieved of Duty and say Louis effort was caught on camera and Oath Keepers meeting rattling off horribly
Racist homophobic nonsense
What
In the police
There was a white
He said that there are at least four sodomites on the Supreme Court and called Barack Obama art
Quote undocumented president from Kenya who is also later
Went
Hovering
The protests for CNN
Yeah
Physically assaulted him
Camera
Right so that was a guy with the oath keeper
Keepers
Kind of mentality
Hey
Do you know what they do though
And you got to give him this
They keep their oats
Sure
To be racist
To keep if you think that this is a like a like an isolated incident during the same time
Policeman real birth of the
Department was suspended after video came out of him pointing
Semi automatic
Quick service rifle at peaceful protesters in
Screaming should have done like quote
I will f****** kill you
Very strong strange Behavior also
The policeman Matthew prepared we was on
Patrol during the Ferguson protest would end up being suspended
For posting stuff
On Facebook like quote
These protesters should have been put down like a rabid dog the first night
And quote
Where is a muslim with a backpack when you need it
Guess that
City Coronavirus
It doesn't take any pics I have utility
At least at least he's 142 and that's
Also everybody talks about and rightfully so I don't think it's wrong to talk about Michael Brown
But it would be really pissed and I'll point out the during.
Queen Michael Brown's murder
The acquittal of Darren Wilson many other on our black man
St.Louis
Squirtle murdered by the police not just to name a few I could Jimmy Powell
Avon Derek Myers Jr we're both two unarmed man
Meijer
Say I'm so that could be
Casinos
Pretty terrible
Long long history that goes back Beyond
I believe the dollop integrate episode covering that's if you want to learn more about that from the check it out
Because much more like
In-depth situation going on there and his
Dia of like
Please pour Oath Keepers trying to protect the business
Chiweenie 49 year-old
Situation works itself out
In some ways
I mean I don't I don't mean to
Like you could have really killed a lot of people
He was motivated
It is very naked
We're talkin about we're back to
McWilliams
Yeah the answer is no
The answers honestly no
There's look I'm not
I'm not saying that there should be some sort of government Final Solution on white men over the age of 40
I'm not saying that that's a good idea what I am saying is that there is no
To the fact that we would be better off without the
I'm sorry bro there's no reasonable argument
I'm sorry bro just B has been
Alright alright
Clearly
Born in the show Alex
It sort of made his point
And that is
Use literal white terrorism
As being the same as black protest
Which isn't true
But
I respect that you've been concise
Because at this point it's not very far into the episode it's maybe 10 minutes in
From here on out
To try and approach from
Different direction
So if he keeps talking about this though eventually he's going to be like
Aaliyah big fan of this white terrorists right
Like the more he talked about it the more is going to
Leak through the little cracks
Axon is
Rhetoric
Guadalest exploit Isis
Black Friday
Gotta Shekinah
That I seen the culture a white Friday
Rivers gallbladder problem probably
He's talking about
Diane Black Friday
He's going to try and tie and Black Friday
That is
The globalist
Lower those prices
So much make sure that
People will trample over each other
And remain divided
In order to keep us from
Fighting against the globe
Interesting Theory
That's it
Social Engineers are using the right effect
Free home
He said that's right that's right
Sorry
Week 7 my Bernie
Homedics
Are We Now picketing to shopping tips
Hold on
Black Friday ads
Alright
So
Yeah
White terrorism
It's Ferguson
Fault
Black Friday
He's just associating
Whatever it is that. Is my
If it was
If it was Christmas he would have been like commercializing Christmas if it was the Easter he would have been like we've got the our Easter sales
Like he would have just done whatever is
Regional Airline
They just mad cuz he had to go shopping
The other day
Well it doesn't like
Does end up being like a
5-minute ramp
On the show it goes on quite a while
Stop sales tax that is
What's up
I'm out
Consumerism for Quality consumerism
As a merchant as some of the cells and developed products very successful
I know what specials and deals
Because the scam of Walmart and Target
They raise the prices the week before
Discount
We don't do that,
T-shirt high-quality supplements
Water filters
The whole thing
Pretty impressive
Realistically
Ferguson is bad
But not in the way you think
Stand-alone
It's cuz he's got the pivot from
White terrorism threats from black Friday's an inside job to a Wii
Wheel of something
Consumerism
He's again
Consumerism just the Mindless type
Wahoo
Also by the way
No no
This behavior that I authentically condemned
Yes it is still terrible
But not
The way
Play it look okay the Bible is all about those like don't lie
I'll I do work online
White Lies
You know that's no big deal
White means good
Live
GoodLife generally sales are like two
Determined based off MSRP
Not off what does
Surprise
As two people put out
Quality product
So many like
That one button
We have
Also those shirts were not made by
Wonderful wonderful man
That could be interesting
I did send my shirts a text message
Nope
But guys
Just jump
Let's do it
Alex is now
Successfully done this
Kerri strug level gymnastics
Acrobatics
Just amazing work of art
At pivot and I expect
Of course
This shooting that happened in Austin
He lives in Austin
Responsibility
But you're
Can't talk about it without bring up Ferguson
The only thing that he can do
Because to me
Police station
Mexican consulate Federal Building
It's really no different the white guy
Democratic Party
Black neighborhood
Funny
Mr. Brown Tujunga
I need some Thug from the cops on the fridge
Even well
While trying to decry
The Democratic party's co-option
Of these peaceful protest
And turning them into a racist attack
Meant to divide
Even though even in the middle of doing that he's still got to be racist as f***
Now might not
Got the time to show you this
Covers for dollars at cost for $72
No this is a copy of magazines at
So kindly got for us by listener Keegan
Look at the cover of that b****
Great
So
Forever watching a cover of the Infowars magazine
Scott George Zimmerman and Trayvon Martin is a half
And half of the same face
With the words divide-and-conquer under it as if to suggest
That murderer and victim are the same
This is his
This is where he's at but he's not like this one to white person
The victim
He's never here
He's made a cottage industry out of demonizing immigrants
Because of this
Is accident
Just a few hands
Mexican gentleman
Because it wasn't
Shot that
Accidentally went off of bounce off of concrete
There's no intent
So like that
What I mean this is
It's hard to take him at all
Seriously
Just like
You with your saying that Michael Brown is a thug
Didn't you think that the police
Didn't lie and you acted responsibly
I know where you coming from bro
Same place
McWilliams
Like you saw the video evidence no other way
So
That's why my favorite article
Goes to read our
Ones written by people who are like
We need to
Standees
They don't like being called racer
Because racist
Is a bad word
Are they
How could you prove this racism
They don't like that label.
You can't tell them that the race I would offend him
I wouldn't like it either
F*** yourself
I don't like
The label cross eye
I either but
Might be choosing
Right Alex Jones
You got to you got to wear that race cannot go buddy
If you want to put out a magazine with a cover
Stab magazine
Glove white nationalist
Join in
I didn't edit this point with Alex
Dwindling numbers
All across the board
His best bet is to just
Put all the chips in white.
What you first have to have crossover appeal
The last year Alex Jones
Go to alexa.com
Ranking
Site
1000g
In terms of
His position
As a website
They're expanding
3200 Orso 4100
100 in the last year that's uncanny
A terrible drop
Weird times
DoubleDown
He just loses listeners of on both
Remedy loses the actual hardcore big if you're not hardcore
Exactly
Also make art
Very different because
Finally everybody in the you know
Rightwingwatch svr will be like
Oh we can just discount
He's a white knife
F*** off
Maybe
So
I would like to tell you
Pointwise
He's always right about
Cuz it was
It's no secret at all
To repeat it
Jeffrey
So
I've been able to
The Gleam
That most of his own
Understanding from
Mystery
Green
I might've
No I just
Like I have a
Weird thing about those
Like
You just
Get fit just a little bit wrong like like take it for granite
Granite
The possibility I might have
But have you always
No
Idea
Could you maybe one of the faith
Who
Gleams
Mask
There
The cube in a cube
Hey there fairies
Lake Anna midsummer
Leave you hanging
Enjoy it
Adverb
I've deduced
Got some fun with that one
But I figured out that most of Alex
History
Understanding at 9
90 books about
Write all these books about this
Civil War
Just comes from
And Nazi
As demonstrated by the
The American Revolution
Nope
You have some problem
But because markedly after
The seven year war
And the final ratification
It created
Some people
And so America became the Revolutionary idea
Savers
The elites
The American system
By the 18th
When people get
We can't compete with regulations
Child labor
Flavor
We can't compete with
To take it over
You see the rise of JPMorgan
Rockefellers
By the Dutch royal family
Rothschild
The robber barons Rothschild
If we they were regulated
The other opposition
Okay
I think the problem is clear
People having
So we should do something about that right
There's another problem that is like all that history
Korean Lord
So accurately has
Declared
You believe that
A lot of a lot of history.
Come from his
None dare call it
SeaWorld
We will be dealing with
To detail
Revolution
The model
Because everybody
Not a good model
Terrible model
It was a bad model I apologize Freedom that will get coverage
Freemason Abbey restaurant
Favorite
Freedom
Selective breeding
So that's a little bit
Maybe you don't have a great grandpa
Books that are filled with lies I would say that it is uncanny
What the
This is the guiding Quest
Of the show
Right where he to be
Are you not lunatics
Person
Bright
You would open up the phone
I'd like have a reasonable conversation about the
Right but as soon as I heard him ask this guiding question
I said to myself
No goddamn way he's answering that question
Rebellion
We should have this topic all throughout the week not just on this Sunday show
This is such a big issue
You're not going to cover this at all and I'm going to guess with your next
What is legit
I feel like it's like
Court definition
New
I take everything on a case-by-case basis
This is a lot of there's a lot of
Circumstantial stuff
Cross-culturally that
To us doesn't apply to other folk you know
In terms of the historical
Basis of our society
The revolution
The Japanese newspaper system
Circa I remember that amazing music
The Japanese
Portmanteau
Feel good doesn't feel good coming out of your mouth
I almost said it and I was like
I could defend it in a court of law
I think so.
I think where I put on trial
Boxer
I'm actually going with
Rebellion I felt like that when was pretty good Vine with it
I also think it might therefore what a legitimate Rebellion
Probably Falls
Berkeley lower than Alex's
That like
It's very it's very,
Because later in this episode I don't I didn't keep it in because Alex doesn't respond to
If you responded in any way I would have kept
Equipment
Truecaller WhatsApp
Legitimate reason like what the final straw for you
And the caller says
If I see the government rounding people up
That it's time but that's the final straw
When the immigration policy was enacted
He saw
That the government was rounding people up I decided that was my break
King point until he has absolutely
Sure
Confirm that you will
Stop doing this because I don't know who this caller was
I'm not worried about Alex
Just moves on to another topic after the caller said right
Absolutely that is a Line in the Sand
Is callers words on him
Although I would assume
But back then
Superlatives
Hey cuz how you get supplies by FEMA camps all the time
Though what we are aware of now
Is that that is not
Our threshold for reveler
Turns out it's not
Turns out that if the government is great
Yeah I would love
I would love
A Egypt
We should be
Revolution
The government is rounding up people separating them from their families
F****** police are murdering people
The all of our Institution
Are f****** destroyed
They are left in
This is
Perfect
Revolution
It turns out that I
People's Revolution
I want to join in
But I'm not going to be the guy to
Throw the first f****** Stone it's pathetic I hate myself
It's a complicated thing and I don't
I don't
Right there but the reason that I don't I don't agree with you and I feel kind of shity that I don't agree with you
Is that ice
Still don't think
If that's the right way to deal with it
Right I still think that what you're going to end up doing
In that case is making
Things worse for the people who are large
We're going to be French Revolution
Unfortunate
You and I are
Described as even though we're
Especially me pretty damn poor
Barely boujee White young males
I don't think we are in a very
Trouble
Position unless they try and organize
Is orgo weatherman on people's asses
Doesn't blow up
The temperature bring awareness
Plato people who are being
Victimized by Ice
There's a really decent chance at all that would end up happening is radicalizing war
People
And ice
Remaking message
Situation
I don't know what the right solution is I don't
Grudge people think
VIP like
We got to get
Hoorah
I don't know I still think of Courts
Conceivably are the right way to go about the other card things around and Garfunkel
I think the the
My my
Feelings are a general strike
We're not trying to overthrow the government break
Your s***
I think we're finally going to f****** your s*** scale version of like a blocking traffic
What happened
Control the government
F*** with your bottom line I guess I don't know I think there's a good in between
And I just
I don't know
Anyways let's start
What's up Alex Jose
I love so much
That is
Here
Where Alex is getting Petty coming in from a commercial
Infowars.com
Powerboat races 1996
Coward
Infowars.com
So that's the shop
Detect
You take that little bit here comes that lie
Here is
Time Magazine
On Friday
Good work
I just ripped off.
I would love it
So
Slader
He juggled Rush Limbaugh by dropping paper route
After he's complaining about someone
Ripping him off saying powered by truth
Google did I couldn't figure I'm sure he's talked about going back but
I couldn't figure out who he is
Powered by truth
Cuz that kind of suggest
It's the same way that
Things are powered by gasoline
In Tavares you
Burnet
And transform it is
Yeah
Yep he's ripping off erotic in it
He's women Opera
Done before this but I like to imagine epistle
Nanako beginning
Not but
These headlines
It's not what the name sounds like but even like no matter what
If there is a
Is racism in the way he says that name
Question
You know
Eun haoh
Nai believe
Wait do you like
Comfortable
Hard pass
And she goes on to just say it's wonderful
Okay
Here's one out of
Is lying when they say Ferguson protests were peaceful
Those aren't articles from
From CNN or any new articles that's just Infowars coverage
Other article
So now back to this time article
Nautical that Alex's
Saying goes on to
Violent rioting is wonderful
Cheese for it
That's great
Right I mean
You you'd expect him to actually get into
To be arguments the Nuance of instead of
Misrepresenting the headline and then lying about what's in the body
You know what it could be
Look
Basically all he does is
Look I mean
With that my tractor
What's the capital
Young honor Blackman
Angry Bird
Text and I know I know
It's what we do with that anger that
In such a case is rioting so wrong
Rights are necessary part of the evolution of
Society
Unfortunately we do not live in the universe
Utopia where people have the basic
Human rights they deserve simply for existing
Until we get there
The legitimate frustration sorrow and pain
Other marginalized because will boil over
Spilling out into our street
Has quote normal citizen
Watch the event of
Unfurl on their television
I'm praying the Twitter feed
There's a lot of head-shaking finger-pointing
Privileged explanation going
We wish to see
Seclude against
The people involved
Does separated from our history as a nation
Dehumanize the change agent
Because of their bad and sometimes violent decision
Because if we can separate the underlying racial tension
The clearly exists in our country
From the looting in the rioting of
Select individuals
We can continue to ignore the problem
I would put forth
The peaceful protesting is a luxury of those already in Maine
Stream culture
Those who can be assured
Their voices will be heard without viola
Those who can afford to wait for the chain
They want
I risk sounded racist but if it was a white kid there would be no riot
Another person another person wrote on the T
Tea party page
History shows us that blacks in this country are more apt to Riot than any other population
They're stirred up by racist black people instead out to cause problems
End of story
Set the post that she is referencing from a two-party base
Sounds a lot like Alex
Yep blacks in this country are more after Riot because they're one of the population
They're one of the population still need to
In the case of the 1992 riots about Rodney
30 years of black people trying
To talk about their struggles of racial profiling but still vastly unfair treatment came to a boil
Sometimes
Enough
Is simply too much
Then after that Catalyst event the landscape of Southern California
The National League
Police forces take
At no point in the article does she
She say
Is good for the rioting is good
Discuss the underlying causes
And what's going on
The conversation that Alex G
Unwilling to
She's on one
Explains why it is
Is a reasonable
Thought
It is not an irrational
I thought it would be a rational if white people ride
Over anything
If that's an irrational thought
If you've been depressed for
Always
If you are being murdered
By the cops
Who are ostensibly there to protect you
Tannerite
That's a totally reasonable thought
It's another thing to I think
Just like it wasn't
Ask her if it was a
Away from like
It being
A riot riot
Do you know
Also you also have to add in the fact that
These stains
The same things they are saying
This isn't the right way to do it and all that bull
They said
Colin Kaepernick
Buick
It doesn't matter how severe
What what does it matter if you write if they're going to say the same thing if you peacefully
The bottom line is always
Yeah exactly but I don't shut up
Wait your turn that's never coming
It's important
I think some of that is important
This is the article that Alex refuses to read Brett's misrepresent
Service
Of trying to tie the situation
Ferguson
To this dumb dumb
White
Springhill can't believe he's tried and tried to set fire to the Mexico
Can consulate at 2 in the morning
And was not drunk
Had a serious like legit plan
A head-to-head he's gone
How to getaway car
He laid out his funeral clothes at home
With a note
He left a bag of food for his
Pat's on his neighbor's door
You know you can tell the FBI you didn't know anyting no one knows about this
He had his braces
Hover
Write this guy
This was not like a I'm drunk
2 in the morning on a set the Mexican consulate on fire
Cuz
I don't know I don't like
Text
In the show Alex
The question earlier
Presented
What is
Is the time
What is a legitimate Revolution
And he gives a pretty narrow version
I believe it's actually a minor increase in tariffs on
That be correct I'm doing
Very narrow
Let's say you're a Ukrainian in 19
Perry's Pizza
Raping your wife
Disappearing
They're invading your country that is clearly
You got a ride
Somebody's coming down the basement where you're hiding take me to concentration camps
This is 2014 right
70 years
Your presence
Oh no no no no no no no no no
Ukraine
Ukraine on your mind
He's totally cool with that
He also
Ukraine specifically course
Also by the way
Because we're doing
2018 is
18 right
November 30th
Nosotros
Cirrhosis
Somewhere between 2009 and 24
Gotcha
Which
Unfortunately does not narrow anything down and not a lot
Is that are open today
Anywho
Redundant perhaps but
Do it anyway
What's his name
Larry Steven McWilliams
Because I support the police killing
Shooting
Civil War
Well
That's only these two things are the same
Onlyfans
Whether or not
It is bad
To start murdering
Even though in this case they did not
Right even though in this case it was not the
He certainly could murder
It is X Corp Alex reads a news report
The point on that last
The reason I have it in there
Again just to reinforce the
Can't deal with this without
Changing the goalposts
Got moving it down
And I actually have
Damning thing to bring up at the end of the
In order for Alex to cover the news about busy
He kind of has to treat it like
You'll see what I mean
He has to put on a mocking voice just to read the news
The f*** is that
Horrifying
He shot over 100 rounds at these building
That's not good
I mean
The white
Supremacist have enslaved black people for hundreds of years
Like what are you doing starting a civil war
F*** off
So
Of course
We know that
Lying just below the surface
First of all this
Natural fear
About the second
It's interesting, as much as I would have expected
He's mentally ill
The guns
Of course it's it's sort of like
The idea
Is in place
That this is like
It's fake
Until I get the cap off flag.
Course like that
It's always
But I would have thought there'd be more fears about the second amendment that there actually are
White guy doing it they're going to come after your gun
Yeah
White people out there
Crop up
Not here we see it
And they're playing
Again
Is the flying fish
Flavor Flav was at church
With TV shows or dramas at movies
Where crazy people go
Hugo Chavez voicestation
Right
But just by cops suicide by cop
Try to create a chain reaction
Or you hung out with a bunch of weirdos
Your biggest fan
You go and do speaking engagements if people keep coming up to you.
Specifically
Sometimes it's a good idea to blow up the policeman Tire career is largely built on denying that a guy who blew up
The Federal Building actually did it
He killed RFK that's crazy false flag
And all I need to do is say Elohim City all of a sudden I have an arc
Come on I've got an argument
Elohim City
Holy
Makes perfect
It is just
Abso at this point Alex
Where we going
Do you understand that the police are the second most awake I've done
Announce
Why do grandmas real quick who's the first most
Take me to might be it might be the Army is number one he doesn't specify but also I want to know what the old awake means
Aware of the globalist
Conceivably there's parallel the police
The 2nd
Most awake
A number for
You know what's crazy
Number three
Elks Club
Shriners
Shriners absolutely all marching bands
His
Write up
I'd like to see his
What time is it
Where's the where's the grass I love
I would really really love just to be able to go
Over this. View at I get to the bottom of exactly what hooray
Is an online poll or how many drops out of junior college so I assume he's not big on
The scientific method
Based his entire life on Monday none dare call it a conspiracy of the scientific method is a really
Reality is not
Part of his cap
Is that a reality made
God-awful scared police
And they want to overturn the chessboard because we're winning and start a civil war
Liberty moments
Or Washington
People to go out and do stuff
Statistically shofar extremely low chance with Patriots
But the media trying to hide it like a
Realize what's really happen
Stuff going on there at the end
Mama is cockamamie
Just do it
Looking into Sovereign citizens find out how often they
To the cop because they believe they have the right to
Travel on roads without a license
And then get really upset
The King's Manor,
And I don't recognize the authority of
Admiralty police
Police officers
What I find really interesting there is that he's like
A patriot shooting a cop or Superluv the odds of a black guy burning a build
In his neighborhood are super low
We're being lied to about this stuff
It's the reverse
Is he
The only conclusion
No making a direct limit even this incorrect comparison for both
Not even that
A white person is most likely
The Sovereign citizens
The freeman-on-the-land and all those types of weird Patriot militia types who are
Real
Real against people having Authority
They shoot most
And then you get into like
You're right there's like people are the ones who resetting fire
You see like all of the the indications of
Agent
Pictures that were on the scene in Ferguson
Infiltrated protest group
You know you get those sorts of
Vacations
Because
We're watching
They can't false-flag these any
They can't engineer
Because it was real
They hype it up
Like it happens all the time
Yeah
Argument is
They can't do it themselves because we do it for them all the time
That is kind of part of there
Strong
It's not good
None of this is good
No for now
In this next clip we get
What's real
What's up
Shut up voice Department
Anime
Infinity Cube
Spring Meadows open
Keep being weird about it
Further
This reported man
I don't even know if he's real
I don't trust the media they're staying
And they're saying
Then he was mad about open borders
Which who knows about that
I mean yeah
You know
Do you know where is shockingly similar take on the situation to Alex Jones about
Going to make people who work against open borders look bad
Storm
How would they say that
Greenpoint's Alex Jones
The feeling that he was awake between Voldemort
Vladimir possible
It's probably some
Weird
He-who-must-not-be-named
You can be sure the Hostile aliens really control the country
Going to use this
Us
So that's one of them
Quotes
Talk to tax on the part of the angry white man
Is a dream come true for any Jewish or darky gun-grabber
An agent of genocide against White
The putrid smell of Zionist rmx
Kinfolks black against White
And the US Constitution
Heavy in the air here
Guiding father Odin chimed in
Good attacks
Let you know there half-cocked because they were attributed to a white say I think that's used
What you're hanging on to
That just
I think I think you're holding on the wrong feet
Alright
Cuz I don't want to engage with a him staying darkie
It's not good
The media picked up on the story we want
Again here nonstop about how all
Racist
Government
Aerial view
The overwhelming sense
A lot of their post
Is just
Very
Vineyard Way
To demonize be
People who
I don't like you
Immigration
So
It's like they can't find
Any other exam
It's like come on guys
Put together a list
Maybe
Put together a statistic
All of these crimes that have been committed
And develop some sort of pattern
Come on you guys can't do that these are false flag
Okay so when you do do that
I get it
But they're all false
Yeah
Once again
Coincidence we've ever seen
Does rhetoric matches up with
Literal
White supremacist
Yep
Tried
On their side
I don't know
Marion
Is pushing all this multiculturalism
Because they want to wreck the society
Black Friday or Cyber Monday special mother-in-law specials across-the-board
Quality
That would
Wimbledon 2019
We haven't heard from him
Goodshit the enemy is multiculturalism
Nothing
Damn was that a good attitude
Is multiculturalism is Black Friday
Just want to Roller Black Friday
This is a quality consumers
You almost accidentally
Equality
Goosebumps MSRP the same f****** special that you have
45 supply.com
Exist anymore
Alex Jones
Website that he was using
And I did not
The correct paperwork
Subsidiary that we called him out on
And
Now there's a new website
If you go to 425 supply.com
It links to and forwards
Through to Infowars defense.gov
Not yet actually figured out if that's a legal name.
Not the one time we actually discover a crime nobody pays attention
Oh well forgot whenever we discovered a crime
Say something stupid
What's Grimes
Randy Quaid
We were going to get this was a sad night for Austin
And
You know it could have been a lot worse
Thankfully no one really got hurt except for this
McWilliams guy
Right
Big shout-out to Austin Texas we will be there on Friday
Very excited
To go down
MC the Mexican consulate
Check out the remodel
Remember the consulate actually is our rally cry
Play the part of Colonel Travis and I will hold down the fort at the Mexico
Can cancel it
So yeah will be there I actually do have a group of a
They were former Civil War
Sierra we re-enact
The whole thing
You got to try and shoot a horse
Yeah it's part of it
Rough
It's rough it's a weird day for everybody
Friday land
You guys have heard this
A million times
I don't know where bad marketer
I've had a roadblock
A terms of doing episodes this week
Because I'm so excited to talk about the episode that I've got for Friday
See you all there
Appreciate it
You can find all sorts of
Information and
Write-ups in
They're specialists
No
Some of the non-existent website now
We are on Facebook
That's where we are even leave a review
To do also
That's about it.
Even though I was not heard last time
Is it still your turn
There's no one else on this episode
No it doesn't
It's just Alex McWilliams and a collar that
You you were
Alright
Alright you're going to have to take from The Real World Dan
The Ukraine in 1935
They were the good guys
I don't know
It was just the first thing I saw when I looked at my screen
What's the address
What's a Bad Revolution
Go fuc yourself Dance Dance Revolution
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color