I'm a policy wonk
And to give you a little bit of an introduction before we get into this episode
Tell you what's going on here
What's going on is Jordan
He's way too successful at stand-up comedy
And I have therapy one night this week so we could
Could not find the time to record
Luckily for you and for all of us
I have this episode that I'm going to release today that I recorded
Pikachu back
With my friends a very funny comedian
And
I'm excited to be able to release
For you
I'd give you a little bit of context recorded this episode
A little while
And I did not
The time to
Release the episode and
In the meantime like right after
Justin and I recorded this episode
When I was about to release it
We needed
Emergency episodes
It had to be done
You know how it is
There's a forward momentum in a natural narrative that sort of Taken
The shape with Alex Jones Is Life
You know we can
Marches forward sometimes things
The cop by the wayside but
I'm glad we have this opportunity
Double back a little bit was cuz I think this episode was great
And I think you're going to really enjoy it
Hilarious
Tastic
Episode of a couple things
I wanted to
Get off my chest
First
Is a very exciting announcement that I'm not going to make now
What's Jordan does get back
We have very exciting enough
Do I give you
And I look forward
To telling you about that I don't know why I'm
Teasing it now but
Who cares
I wanted to take a moment
To acknowledge
That may have been a little bit off
In my interpretation
Of the last
Whip from the February twenty
Ford SHO
Where are listen back to it and number of time
Mostly out of insecurity and
I fear that I had
Misinterpreted
I think I might
I think it's entirely possible that my analysis
This was off
I'd literally off
But spiritually
I was not wrong
What he says is still horrible
What he says is absolutely
Indefensible
You should never
Ever encourage people on Twitter
To harass
Anybody
Especially about someone else's
Children so
The context of that is
Absolutely unacceptable
Inexcusable Behavior
But
I am big enough man to recognize
And publicly admit
That I might have gotten
Some of the
Particulars about what he was saying
Slightly off
To my credit
He does swallow some syllables
Pretty Solid Ground I think
Feel better now that I've got that off my chest
But
Oh well who cares
I am going to feel better here in about my
Because I've got this episode
To share with you
I hope you do enjoy it
Again just thank you to everybody who's been getting on board
We really appreciate everybody listening tweeting out
Stormy night here in Chicago
And I've
Waiting to do laundry all night
Someone's been hogging the laundry machine
Only thing that makes me feel better about the fact
That I have to go to work
Tomorrow in dirty clothes
Is the fact that I know that you guys are going to be out there enjoying this episode
And that means a lot
Here we go
Let's get to the episode but you know until
Jordan gets back
And we are we
We meet again
F****** policy walk
Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody
Sitting here in the studio with the replacement Jordan
Very much ready to
Take a journey through a day in the life of Alex Jones listen to a bunch of
This particular episode
But you were telling me before we started recording
You have you've dabbled
In the world
Trips to the battlefield of the Infowars
College
Sure
W years
Which was like a great time to be radicalized
Did you like young you have feelings
Make a difference you're definitely right
Yes you are so right you know everything
And you're not Bounce It All by jadedness
Or self-consciousness of your ideas are young enough wasn't real to you
Perfect
Yeah I'd like
None of my roommates are friends like really cared
Either way
And then I had one buddy
Who was like
Very into like
Liberal politics
And he was like always reading like Al Franken
Those books
Yes that one and Rush Limbaugh
Yeah so I dabbled in some of those
Listen to air America when
Backwood maren was working with Samsung
Yeah I just like that was about where he took me and then I always had like
Appetite
4life
More fringy stuff and then I was like you to was becoming new and I just
Theater
Dow Jones
Watch loose change
Loose change
Like like worst
Which chain
Watch loose change
What you watching
The Obama Deception
Reception
911 road to
Tyranny
Listen to Lil B
You don't keep up with it
I strongly recommend that you don't
Don't think I told you the last time I really got into a big was like
Recently was like yesterday
Joe Rogan
Sure
That's kind of like required lesson
Yeah I was I was listen to Joe Rogan
Unlike I have that his
Always be a funnel
Yeah
With Rogan but if you see Alex Jones on Rogan you got Alyssa
And I'm glad
We did we did a huge breakdown of that
How much of a drunk
Idiot Alex
So hot did you watch the video okay
Utopian like I take these headphones off and he's like slick at his hair by yourself
Things you don't know is actually Alex
No matter what
What temperature is it
Studio
Has a crazy
Eartip
Okay you're in a really weird way compulsively
Headphone stuff I think was actually his ear itching
Okay
I've done some research into what causes ear itching
End
Nothing definitive yet
I have to be
It's got to be all psychological
What is a signature product that we are almost certain Isabel
What is this thing is it are you a force
What what's the metals for some metal
Silver
A couple of advertising
A product here as we go along
Today we're going over with the event
Of February 7th
On the Alex Jones program
He starts the show out
With a little bit of
Showing of his Humanity
Okay there's a there's been a death in the family
And you take a little moment
The show 20
To honor that
And then quickly
Take it into a weird
Crashing through the lies and disinformation is Alex Jones
Information
Today the breakdown
Taking place against corporations
A out-of-control oppressive
Technocracy
I think that's all
Mother was almost
Weather
I want to pause for a second
You know I would never make fun of someone for
Giving it up for the relative and
I feel very
Sad for his loss
I mean that very sincerely
I'd I'm not making a joke of this at all
Sorry for your loss
She had breast cancer for about 6 years
That's not the butt
There was
Just bad timing on my
Six seven years ago decided to not be operated on
And that she would just go home and God was ready for
Almost 93 years of age last night
Where's our word Savior Jesus Christ
Love so much and you taught me so much
For the 30 year old woman
Call Schatz
But my mother was four years old and
Brother was
That
Paralyzer almost killed her and took her
And then I think about the sv40 cancer viruses that were vaccine as well
How they soft kill my grandmother
Yep it's vaccine method
Turning into an anti-vaxxer
Cool
I mean
If their plan is to kill everyone in there
Early 90s
60 years after taking a bath
Three more planning on 6
3XL Sophie
Again I don't want to block
The death of Alex Jones's
Cuz getting that
Missouri
I don't know what
Seem
Is going to paralyze you for a couple years and then
You're fine
I meant give you cancer
Decades
After I don't know I don't
I don't think that's
I think
BBQ
Pinkity possibly attributing coincidence
Or something
He's attributing nefariousness to Quinn
You know something that just happened
Like
Sure so you can literally just be like
You could just take someone's death
Which is a guarantee
Well that's
I was just being alive
I would like a I wish I'd done some research on this number in front of me is how many people live
I'm sure it's a shockingly low percentage
No I think is like the average
Like 70
Sixers my bad yeah
After that
It's like
Huge
Zips down very quickly how many people who have been soft killed
Live
That's
Genius vernacular acrobat
He's perfect at that sort of thing
Yeah I have the dirty.
Kill
It's just like cuz it getting
It's just one of those things where it's like
You know like you could you be like what people are getting vaccines and not dying
The soft kill
Yeah
Disprove that
Everything is on
Disprovable
Oh man what could be
Do you think
But he can take this
This eulogy for his grandma that turns into an anti-vaccination message
Triple Lindy
And somehow involved
Fly products the Oklahoma City bombing being fake
Near-death experiences
You can work both of those in
Hoping that he does cuz I don't want to be right
Because to me then it's just fanfol Maasai don't want it to turn ugly into
Iodine
You said
Early 1950s
In the early years old
Military
As well
I just think about how magic it is to have
Progeny into the future and I'll be one of their ancestors
I just want to deliver
I really can't say no my favorite was the meaning of them
But it's it's
No one asked to do on your political
Globalist program
Which of your grandparents is your favorite
Well you know what
Cuz he wants off killed
And I hope spiritually
Resonates the plane
Would God
Has Fallen
She was very very few days ago
Conscious talking about
So she believed she was already in heaven
Marine Corps sniper in veteran helicopter pilot investigator best-selling author
And he died from cancer
God
That same
Near death or death
Experience
Just know there's a lot going on in this world
But I just want to know that I love her and I appreciate it and I can still feel her presence now so I can feel
My first grandparents went Jerry Jones my dad dad
6 years old
I will carry them forward with me I hope my children will carry force my energy in my spirit
Genetics and so let's just all think about our fallen grandparents
Of course our parents and everyone would love
But you know
Is beyond
So I think that would be a great opening segment if he cut out about 2 minutes in the middle and that last
Fart
If you wanted to just jump on the show and talk about his grandma great but do you know
I don't I don't
Can I get on board
You politicizing the death of a 93 year old
It's so much
Yeah it's dance
Yeah yeah
You know we can't really
I made a mistake
In the same way that he made a mistake over the show that has well
Never want to do that
Some like real polish
Okay let's bring it on
This is he doesn't bring up his grandma again for the rest
The show
So we're fine
This is
About people being
Mickey
Forgotten government
And
The mediator
Trying to be full of s***
First off
There's a
Trump
And pretend that he's discredit
Trump has agree with their overwhelming Lee document
Trump is his own person
Because I don't want to sit here and make
But everyday I see scores of these articles
But the media is covering up terrorist attacks
The Washington Post
For myself Paul Watson
Countless others but they only show screenshots you can't go see it for yourself screenshot
We go show
Where police seized the FBI
Is Trump has troll the media
We spoke at Central Command Florida yesterday
Headquarters
Because he knows they'll bring all this out
Also I want to tell you that deposit any point
Okay if you have any thoughts
Feel free to jump in
This this is insane
Cuz
I mean
The argument could be made that the headline Infowars is behind
The stuff you saying
They kind of
That they support the same thing the trumped-up
Not necessarily the Trump got it from them
The other is that
That was some shameful s***
Go over that list
They misspelled San Bernardino
Oh no he misspelled the word attacker
27 * 3
I'm in a bunch of the bunch
Almost all of it was cover
Mainstream media
DS maybe Undercover
Where do I sign on fatality knife attack
Yeah that's
I don't know man that's weird it's like
Yeah it's like you said it's I don't know
Armenia's just like the normal media
In terms of like the 24-hour news
Yeah like there is shady s*** going on
In the government
Like there's not enough
For you to have hours of programming
Deyana
No that's true so you're going to have to be like grass
A straw
He's going to fill 4 hours a day
Does salmon temp
Like so
F******
How is this about Oakland
Everything that happens has to be about something
In the narrative this comes up
We think that you and everybody else was
Suggested that
Is being way too generous
I don't think
He blocks out
What time at all
Is essentially a ring
Yeah
That's for sure
Alright
I've got to fill 15 minutes here you like
Buckeye got to
Advil 4 hours
Everyday
Every single day
But I mean
Future of
Information
And whether we turn the
I mean that's his issue right is it's like
If someone is genuinely like heck
I want to give a voice
Independent Mail
Right
Great
Those things like hardly ever exist
Cuz for them to exist they have to be like
What they cover is accurate what they're covering is important
Blah blah blah
Sure
You could argue that like maybe they don't cover avmc because of like corporate interest
Sir because of some other interest that's like
Dubious or just money
Yeah
That's what he positions
I'm just being honest
Spotify
Your your message is
Conspiracy
So you have to fit everything into that box and its global
Yeah everything has to be about.
We've documented at least
Totally
Tons of Lies throughout just
10 episodes of the show we've done so far that really like Justin
Encapsulated for me was from something from back
Play Jones watch
Or regular like believer like I always
Was like okay but still fun
So it's not like I was ever like
Escaped
The church
Story about
Like
Is basa
Is the it's the gay shrimp story shrimp story I do not remember
Chemicals into this
River
Turning the shrimp
Gay
And returning an actual shrimp shrimp In this River
Well here's the thing
Is it based of real science
Pesticides
Runoff into the Stream
They have
Do you want to call it
Estrogenic qualities and they
And so much so that these small species only like a shrimp
Flip their species female
A female so they can't reproduce
Okay about in like biology classes in college about
Pesticides
Getting on like unreported their damages and it's
Causing these problems and it could be causing
Uptick
Can breast cancer
Bring me a real kind of issue that is alarming in an undercover
Undercover
But he turns it into
It's turning the shrimp gay
Course and they're doing
Because they wanted
Experiment
Turn Oscar
So then we don't reproduce
To keep population down
Antenna
Trim population to like whatever their number
First of all
You're so
That's what it's that's what makes him worse to me almost doesn't feel like I want to get back to this but I don't want to interrupt you but I have to go
Equip about this on Today Show
About to get shrimp
Kind of
I don't care
What is this being force-fed 25 year old kids about what about sex
So yeah
Even just in passing on this show he brings up his idea that there is
Something being introduced to try and turn us gay
Yeah
It's weird to in like that's the other thing that's like
Not troubling but just like a shame
Because lights
He doesn't seem
Hateful
Percent
Globalist
Yeah that's true
Hateful towards them but like I've read articles to about like mm
About like other media Elites
Pushing
Trans issues because they want to like
Destroy gender lines again
I confuse the working-class article
I mean online
They always take the whole paragraph to be like
If you are trans
That's fine there's nothing wrong with you
I recognize that as a real
Like
I'm just saying that
They're using that they're exploiting that real identity that deserve to be protected to like her
It's nice to see that their craziness is at least coming from
A place where I think that's even being way too generous
I didn't read the articles on the Vigilant Citizen
What is the time now
With this clip Alex
Is is is
There's a
It's basically
I don't care
I mean you are a victim
Your identity is because you had something done to you and I
I pity you because of your
Your you're
Okay
Dude it's
I agree it's not good
It's just like in the world we live in it's just like you know it could be worse
Oh you know like that there's politician
Like like people that make the laws
They're much more openly hateful
Then him
So that's why it's like when they say awful s*** like that it's nice to know that like
They're better than even some of the people we've elected in terms of
What time to be like
Look
You're just a victim I don't hate you
Hateful in a way
What is the kinder
Soccer
Great deal of time
Accusing Michelle Obama of being a transgender person
He pretends he's just joking about it
Other time
Very serious
Like what
What you doing
Came out as trans then it would be
Greeted the presidency and the office of the
The First Lady by
Secretly having a trans woman be in there
That's a man that's a
The first man so basically his ideas like
She doesn't have to say it
We just
We understand it and so the agenda gets out without it being like it
Eventually we'll go and then the joke's on us
We've been tricked
This whole time
It's it's insane
It's it's
Let's be honest
Yeah I mean it's transphobic and it's homophobic
It's it's all that it just like
Itches
These people
These people are so
In a world of such
I don't know emotional state
Baby will be easy for the hunter beets
Outwardly hateful
Always at least take a step back
Optimistic
No I don't I was going to say I have more respect for Michael Savage
But I don't
Who's that
Even more hate
People radio personality
Is awful
He is just outwardly
That they're part of a
Agenda
I think what he would say is there mentally ill
Kind of yeah looking now
No no no no no
Yeah maybe
You spent at least a decade in a bottle
Let's get back into Alex
This clip is going to start with the
Him touching
Baseball news
Supervillain George Soros
Antonio some more stuff
Say about that how Trump is really
When you stop somebody you can't answer
I want to stop really quick I don't think that it's true that
Google where they're coming
Exaggeration
Okay but also I don't think it's as nefarious as Alex think
When he says the people were told not to say that things are Islamic
Terror
I think that's probably due
I think you got to know the fact
Before you make pronouncements
That's first of all
I don't think it
Do we gain anything by
Attaching Islam
To terrorism and say that explicitly
Weren't staying Islamic anymore
Because they didn't want to like
Destroy possible allies they could have in the
The Middle East by like
Yeah because one you're trying to like
That was like
Area is
If you help us we won't
You say that word
Well when you start using Islamic Terror the compound word
Gets connected to
Did the terror
When is the noun
And it is certain point it
It becomes
You know like a soft kill
Becomes
And
Counterproductive
If you use that term aggressively to label everything
Then you're going to end up with
At least the appearances of a holy war
You're going to end up
Two people who walk
Vietnam
Boosie like I do they hate Islam
Ain't that
Really bad
That's very bad
Who's the only people in whose interests that serve
Are people who actually want a holy war
And that ain't enough
No
I don't think
No I don't think
Does he ever touch on that at all
Funny you should ask I have a clip about what he thinks about Islam
Turn into Comics Unleashed
But like I said
Okay
And when you stop somebody you can't ask
Weather coming from cell phone
Places that are warzone
They can ask
Perfect size that route but you can MRSA
Violation of the First Amendment
When you sworn allegiance to a murderous military desktop
Necessarily
He's really saying those things about Islam as a whole
Yeah but I don't think he's doing
Nearly good enough job of being specific about what
Also true if you're not paying attention and you're listening to that you're dumb
That's kind of one of the messages are going to take away from it that Islam is a military death
I guess I just I never really heard him talk about
Jesus as much
In this episode when you talk about his grandma
I knew he was Christian
But I thought he was
A little more secular but
No
Praise on it
I didn't know that like I said I'm a little out of touch
So far off
Is weird deep end
Appraise on air
But he also has this
Weird version of Christianity that he's into
Like he was talking about how I
Exposed Oklahoma City
He got up
To the Pearly Gates
Let's get them back
Weird
Mystical element
Version
Christianity like I said it's like it if I were talking about with
With
Like that
Gay and trans
Thing where it's like
Clip the old lady clip in the dying on the operating table
Basically like the way he talked about like
Well other people in other cultures have the same vision so it must mean something
What's my keys
Somewhat inclusive in a universal truth that can be kind of
Interpreted
Culturally
Wondering is that what it is
Most people that are bad Christian
Forever
Don't really like other religion
Yeah cuz there's a predisposition
Like I'm right so they're wrong team sports wondering if he is one of those questions or if he's more just
It's like I think
He feels the same way about other religions that he does about the gays
And the terms of like
It's cool you're fine
It's cool there that that's worth
He has underlying
Horribly bigoted
The demonic
Colt
Leaders
I've gotten this
T-Mobile
It is devilish evil
She has on a number of occasions
NSAID
Much more
Inflammatory thing
Don't work in this episode 2
We won't listen
No religion that is
Killing other
Alright
Cool
Let's not wrestle with the Old Testament
Medalla
And the other thing I ate it Bears repeating and I don't I don't think I have a clip of it
Best Buy
To this day he still is not recognized
The shooter in
Quebec
The guy who shot up the mop
He's not recognizing that it wasn't
Okay
I don't know if they ever arrested him
Yeah I lost track of that story but that was the only suspect
Like they had fun
I thought they arrested
It's so funny
What you
Believe
Your brain kind of just goes on autopilot cuz I was like
The arrest of that guy knows definitely the guy but then as we talked but you know what I also did tune out of this
Story and didn't really see how it concluded
Suspect charged with murder in Quebec
Quebec mosque
Terror attack
Because we heard he was arrested
Quebec City
Who was formally charged with
Counts of first-degree murder on Monday evening
One day after the massacre of the
The killed six
One day later
That was pretty quick
The suspect was identified
Twenty-seven-year-old Alexandra Bissonnet
Student nearby Louisville University
Bissonnette was also charged with five counts of attempted
Yeah you looks good for it
Pick up the wrong guy
Dick's it seems like
I don't know Alex
To tell you that they got the wrong guy Alta
Patxi's
Little
Or does he think is a full-on false flag
On the show
He and his gas were talking about how was a failed
Because whenever you have Shooters like this usually they
They kill themselves
Yeah I didn't kill himself matter went wrong
So he chickened out
Something like that I don't know
You know I was telling you earlier than getting into their headspace yeah I'm not that be
I don't
Yeah Jason has made you feel better
Yeah
Yeah I got business more s*** about the media
Press secretary Spicer
And Alex
It's telling a story
I'm sure he gives us a little bit of traffic
Idiot
Stop
Republican
What should the priebus
Not the one.
Or at least I
Pray to God
With this current Administration
Alex
Jackson
Checks out
You've got this whole thing going on where he believes that there's a
Split in the Trump can
Between the Trump loyalist
General Flynn
Trump
And then you got Sean Spicer
You got kellyanne Conway you got reince priebus
Who are like
They're just f****** come along for the ride but they're established
Republic
We just packed up cuz you already have
Enemy friend
It's amazing
This narrative
It's so fast
Dude like
Something like a trump presidency
It's just so interesting
Like
There's no better time to listen out
Oh yeah because the world is turning almost
Alex Jones
Sure
With his that he always takes it to the next level
Next level
Annie's Next Level what it's like
The really great / worst time to
There's a moment
Play Quiet Moments for him where he's like
I don't I don't I don't know how
I don't know how I'm going to operate
I don't know
You get a sister
Reporting the news
He doesn't know how
I've listen to Infowars legit
Every day for the last 2 months
Police
I ate hurt
I have never
Heard them do a
Piece of legitimate Journal
Yeah I have never met.
Call to anybody David never check the fact
Documents
Alright
They have all these documents with a site and then you go read them and they don't say what they said they say
So it's like okay you're not reading the things that you're saying you're reading
Fake stores
Do you got
That's all they have
It's insane to me
Premise that you had of him having to
I know it was a joke
Crazy Ray's just report the news station
Yeah I mean that's fair
He's an interesting dude I don't know I just
So did you guys talk about podcast about the Joe Rogan interview you said
Three and a half hours
The things
So you talked about that were
Polly Paulson Tower
He's talking about how like
Trump's not globalist that's why I support him but I'm not
Flower was about
She said some
I don't want that warrant
The most awful things I've ever
That was in the first hour
I can't blame it on the drinking because I've heard him doing on his show unless he's a chronic alcoholic that's a possible Theory but
Siri
By the end of the podcast he's talking about
Like
Like vampires sucking the lifeblood out of these children
12 dimensional beings
What
How do you have even the
Even the capacity
To sound reasonable even for a second
If you also have those
No absolutely it what bit do you know the thing is
He he he
Those beliefs
Really well
Clearly that's underlying
A lot of his beliefs
Vampires
Extra dimension
Beings
Mmsbee
2nd dimensional beings that want to get up and
Third Dimension Bakery that's his demon narrative that he has
Yeah literally beliefs
That stuff
And also believe in Jesus
None of that
That's in the Bible wow that's what I was talking about earlier his version of
We're getting to like
Overtime will figure it out we'll get a better assessment of
Like what his
Christianity really is cuz it's not really gnosticism either it's
It's something
And we can't quite get her finger on a board for sale
Play that's what they all say is like
The I guess that's the thing I
No I just mean we can move on and stuff I don't want
Just the idea of like that's to me what's always what I've always wrestled with with with Alex Jones
He's he's never been someone ever thought could ever be
Something important to me in terms of information source
Things outside the mainstream
Bolster what I get from the mainstream
And I like good f******
Psycho but I liked my psycho I'm like at or below
Yeah like a psycho and tens like
Interdimensional beings
But you just weird that
You can ask
1210 and all the numbers in between so it's just it's it's
It just it just
Full-term baby
Who tried his best to be a wanted really good
Con artist
But it isn't now you're able to
Forget people
I prefer to think you're not as crazy as you already can you go on Roku
You get high and drunk
10 comes out
That's basically how I would look at view but I think it's probably on
And even like 7
Upscale bleed through on his own show when he starts screaming the whole bunch
Clip it's probably about 4 minutes longer so
It's what I would describe as him attempting to do some media criticism
And in the middle of it I think
He accidentally leaks
Not League
But he let slip some of that I don't believe in
Is Drew but if it is
Indicates the Trump might have committed
Locked up
He gets mad at Anderson Cooper a whole bunch
Tell me if you want
Just trolled you
You are the ones that are now talking about we don't cover up
You cover up
More police unions are coming out
The shake your finger at us
And say we're covering whole kind of like we said the polls were fake and Trump is going to win
George Soros was directing the Democrats
Exactly what I said
Major sources
Chicago PD
Honey
I don't tell you too much here
But
But you say we got all the Intel
Andweknow
Video
Oh hahaha of course we cover Islamic care
I'm not sure what the victory is here that he's celebrating yet
Legitimately have no
So is he saying so
So he's saying that
Trump said hey CNN there's TV happening that you're not covering cuz you're covering it up
And then they say no
And then because they're saying that they covered it there now cover
But obviously just bring up stuff for
The past of cover
Yeah
Alex is not good at like
Considering options outside of what he already believe
There's not like an alternative possibility
It's all just like this
This is the truth
Globalist
Bad Trump good
Anyway you going to play this clip
And interrupted a whole bunch
It's it's clasica Alex Jones
It's it's weird
And like I said he
He hasn't alternative
Narrative
Of how Trump ended up running for president that I
I don't think
Okay
Lucy with you
Police the police
Alright
September 2014
Anderson
There's no scoring system
It's come out
You will no longer exist
Thousands of innocent people
He might have been celebrating or he might have been
A journalist
I'm not sure
The Cooper in the southern
Everybody knows your comment okay everybody knows your fraud
Abro job done
Acosta
Adequately these attacks
Most puzzling person inside this list
You see mentions of the Paris attacks were 125 people.
Terrorist attacks
Under it if your regular service says braking house releases list of uncovered
Undercover
Under
Cupboard attached
They're admitting they didn't even cover them all and what we're saying is they underreported
You don't put a picture of him
Looking for someone
It's not true
A very white genocide
Narrative
The talking point of of
White victimization
Did the facts
Pictures of black guys on the news
It's either
It's almost it's either not true or the opposite of what is it
Yes but
If your audience base as we broken down like
Overwhelmingly over 50 years old male in
Easy to scare
And
Maybe our
Really good at research
You just tell them you have course
You know they think they are researching it by the Internet by watching his internet
And the
Trust him that he is done the
He is not
Sure
You want to say that some things aren't covered
Recover everything
Like I said if you go down this list I have the list of all the terrorist
That the the governor
Put out
And there are deep big one
Fitbit got
The coverage
Some might say too much coverage
There are just one
We're like a foreign citizen
Why would cut
Bye-bye a potential
Islamic person
In another country
It's it's it's
Embarrassing list
Supposed to be
You're right
Alex is totally right about one thing
It's trolling
Yeah it is kind of fall fortiva
That's what kind of to me that's was kind of terrifying about a trump president
Sure
Ignore it even though that's really the best move because it's the
President
You can't ignore it.
We're going to have
Everything is going to be deregulated
Privatized
We're going to leave in a
Bizarre dystopia
Yeah
If you just ignore back against that you get caught up in these
Weird Labyrinthian live
Alex Jones Is Right that they're putting it
They're putting it on their own
Scroll
White House releases list
Uncover
Beetle Terrace
So how did most people watch CNN like at the
Airport at the doctor's office
Because to be perfectly honest they can't say we covered all of them because again they don't need to cover a knifing in a foreign country
It's not it's it's
If you if we are expected
Deborah coverage of every
Again it's not good
Someone got stabbed or sexually assaulted
Not necessarily
Global News it's not something
It is it was probably covered in that local paper or to wherever that I would definitely assume
I don't know how foreign media works.
Anyway
This gets weird
Everybody knows about this
This is America
Again
Let's go back to other Jokers
This appears to be
Are not reporting on these attacks
No one knows why
Sitcom told him and general Flynn
There's been a deal made with Saudi Arabia and Al-Qaeda to take over more than 50 countries
And we got to stop
Women double-crosser they overthrow Ally Egypt
It's a major
So
About Lee says the military I think you know why
And you are the ones that came to me
What the f***
Trump
To tell him to run for office
Stop
The
To stop by to switches
The creation of Hillary Clinton
Barack Obama only one man
Treason
If it's true but it's
That part is bizarre
It might have something to do with Bazaar Russian
Terrible things
Whatever happened
Totally opposed
That you everything that was in it
Propaganda 4.5
Communist Chinese
And Hillary Clinton and George Soros and Saudi Arabia
But back to this flip the reason that I said there's like it
Fairly treason
I believe
Is that
You have these generals
Allegedly
Story
A little far-fetched
If it were true
There would be these dudes
Who have
Security clearances
Secret information
Enter coming to private citizen
All around insane person
Donald Trump
Telling him these clothes outside
You better telling him these things that they should not okay that is weird that you know what I think about that part
Clearly class
They plan
Some sort of revolution
And use and disability
Other things that to Alex talk about music
The Insider people in the
Information agencies
Are the ones
Delete stuff to WikiLeaks
In order to
To help drop
And if that's the
McKay's
Added into what he was just talkin about here
That is
Straight up tree
Yeah that is like we had
I don't believe that
But it's true then we would have essentially an insurrection
Our government happen
That
Is way scarier
Yes
This clip ends
Anderson Cooper
Talking
Well he's talking
Know that there's a video montage of him
Reporting from all of these
Relocation
Okay okay
They just show footage of him
Cuz they were
Important enough to be flew him out report
Here we are man the gloves are off no limits
You really want the rest of the story
Cooper
You and your idiot audience don't know what's happening hoping you're still some group of morons
Cooper is a monster
Great-great-grandson
I agree that the that shows
Outdoor Republic
Every single one of these people
Who knows what they're doing conscious is undermining this country
Every single one
You know why those military commanders today
Not true
That list the White House
I know because I was there on the ground in Ottawa Canada October
Oregon man killed a reservist the national War Memorial
What it was
So he's saying that
The news media didn't cover the Pulse Nightclub
Bethel on the list of underreported terrorist attacks
Yeah
About 30 with
Aiding and abetting
I'm going cover the covering the f*** out of that covering it now
Was that crazy where they said
Something like the poles thing was under covers all of the
Everything that could
Possibly be cold
I wish it was
But
The list is embarrassing
It's it's time to stop
We all got an asphalt
We heard yet
I'm going to skip over this next
Clipit swear
Alex
Explains that there is a
Does flight clubs being organized at Berkeley and other universities and faculty are involved
Universities are starting fights
Southern University sanctioned
Offer left it
To learn how to fight
Lincoln take out these
Conservatives when I come to town
Young again
Breakout
No and don't know no one.
I read the articles that you posted
And it's just us
Some people who are concerned
That there's going to be attacks on minorities
Ndawn
Lgbtq
People
Heritage
Leather calling it's like clubsound cuz it's fun
The university has been like we're not involved in this
Real
It suggests a clear-cut case of his lying
I want to get to though
He has an interview
At the end of this episode
With the guy
Named Darrell hamamoto
Is Professor
He's really again
Liberal b*******
I want I want to play this cuz I want to give
The listeners I want to give you an idea
How interviews go on
On his show
Cuz it's it's really bizarre
If you've ever watched
Interviewed on a news show
It's on like that
In any way
A couple of them
I'm excited
With the introduction that he
He gives
The reason I want to start with it is because
We're both
You know what have I have
Spent a lot of time to stand up
Yep we know what a good intro is yeah we know what
This is a bad intro
Cuz it's like if someone is introducing you as a performer and they spend like
5 minutes list
Incredits
Then how you going to get up there
And then how
Professor hamamoto starts
Is bizarre
Okay so this this sounds
Is not a good host
I'm just going to work
Alex's throne
By what ends up happening with snowmobile to start stock
I'm excited
This is Brooklyn. What's he bringing him on for or does that
We will we find out supposed to be an expert
And her talked about her
Hear it from what I understand he's an expert in like Illuminati stuff and Asian American studies
Also use
Discuss how there's like riots in Berkeley
Of that stupid liberal
Listen to this
I have talked to Mercy California
Formosanus career
Bealls I undergraduate degree
Is recognized Authority on Us Media popular culture and sexuality having published extensively
Generation College
I am University undergraduates
Friday.com
This is gotten so crazy that I don't even know what to call it.
Thank you very much Alex for inviting me
Before we begin though I wanted to compliment one of your frequent contributor is Rodger stone with this excellent
Buck here
The making of the president 2016
Ordered to Infowars
The first draft of History
For what that's worth
Academic historians will refer to when they write about this
Not just an American political history in world history
He goes on like another minute talking about the book that you can order online infowars.com
Superman
I got to tell you about a bookie
Do you sell
I don't know probably one of the gift or anyone
Stocking stuffers
He does eventually get down to some business
Brass tacks this clip is
Super Bazaar
8/2
To do with
You know the protesters
Howell
To know just what they're really like
Also
Immediately after them
Just talkin about this book
For like the
Scaccia
Ozzy not knowing who is president or Maxine Waters thinking Russia attack Korea
He played the coldest clip of Nancy Pelosi
Slipping up
Same President Bush
Sometimes
Eleni also
Play discover Max
The waters
Saying that Putin invaded Korea
And look she's an old lady
I get the maybe she's
Not the best representative in the world or whatever
But she's not an idiot she just meant
How to say Crimea inside Korea
Got there pretty f******
Close
I'm not saying that
Great I would prefer you dumbass
Yeah yeah
Walking
By the Republican Democratic establishment
Arrogance and fossilized brain structure
Absolutely but I'm not going to dismiss them as being Veronica
In control but it's from sources
Under control
Pharmaceuticals
Most of these people who are
Battle Frontier
People need to be checked for mental health
And what have you
Immediately after saying that there are essentially wave going through the air that are controlling
Cool man
Way2go
We didn't check your mental health
Yeah
Clowns
What's wrong
Moto
What we're seeing the attack of women
Behavior
Well it's already been declared she chirped transhumanist
Gmail
Institution such as
Same old story going back to skull and bones
They're promoting polyamory
Which has multiple husbands
He meant Pollyanna
But he said polyamory
Which is a much broader thing
Both Partners has more a multiple man with one woman
Professor of sexuality
Seto who runs over
Who controls at that family
Remains to be seen I have some some some
And the men all day
Absolutely
Strategies Sears
Well
Is one of our Solutions
At this point he pulls out a guitar that he has sitting next to him
Okay
It's on normal guitar
It just happens to be pink
That's it
There's nothing special about this guitar okay it doesn't have anything drawn on it
Just a pink
Awesome
Because when he said that we have
Pussyhat
I thought for sure isn't
Pull out some
Giant dick head
Respect
A professor hamamoto
Coming with
Crops
Good looking as soon as the interview started you pulled out the book
He's going on a guitar
Some toothpaste that he would order from Alex
The road prop comic
Moving out of state
We're going to use the phallic
Guitars
Fry this happens to be a squire guitar
Social justice
Warrior Rally's
With my little Fender Champ champ
Esquire Esquire
They said I'm sorry brother we just can't let it happen
And this is part of the
Cultural takeover
What do you think about that
Tulelake
So much
I mean that's like
What do keep in mind this is the guy who's playing
Screening for mental health
Wait let's try to go point-by-point it just is almost overload
Looks like it is
If you think the guitar is phallic I do not want to know what you
Your cock looks like
Yeah but if you like oversized balls
If they're like
For just the body of the Court Oregon
Troop formation
South Whidbey
For her pleasure
What then wait what is why is
Rap and hip-hop there's a conspirator funking hip-hop's conspiracy to get undergraduate
Urban Jungle Rhythm
Braces
Sorry my brother
Idea that
These guys are homophobic
So he's proving that by taking his quote on quote gay instrument to try to play with them and they say no your
Honestly
I don't know don't know
Elaborate on that at all
And Alex's interview-style is not
Look I'm going to call out
Prove these guys who they really are my take my gay instrument
And they're going to say it's to gas and then I've proved my point
Be with my super gay instruments
I think he was saying that I have the gayest in
Instrument I could possibly find
And of course they loved
So of course
There's no way to take that that makes it like less hilarious
I've listened to the entire interview
And I don't know
Guitar gay
It's pink
Weird that you're generalizing
Your Pinkett are slightly more sure happening
Guitar
All his instruments gayest instrument
Phoenix instruments
From like a laptop or whatever in his living room
Into his kitchen
So like I don't know what kind how many instruments you've got degrees
Look I think is this a failure of this like
Like this
Higher education
He might ironically be that which he is
Critiquing
Unpack is like
No baby just teach it to uc-davis
Let's not like a mental real
He has like a sitting room next
To his kitchen
That I might be
I might be pretending
Navigate to studio apartment when it's not
Or you might have like some divorces and have alimony
You never know what people's lives are like
Yamamoto
Live in a one-bedroom
Apartment
Situation
Like that, Moto
So that was crazy
That was not
To that last part was
Wow
They wouldn't let him sit in
There's no way that's the whole story
No
Dudley price that
Hey bros
Can I sit in with my gay instrument and they were like
Do that
All that's weird you need to leave narc
Guess there's some real hate going on here
Like everybody
Concert like I don't
I don't know if it every protest there's music
OK Google
Just people sitting around
Oregon walking
If there's this potion involved
Unplugging your aunt
Is that weird
That's fine
Choice
It's a little bit much as a lot of people around here
I've never met anybody
Current
New College
Save-A-Lot
Never like
Why wasn't collagen
Nothing like any other women like guys or girls
Friendliness
I think I would have go to protest with friend
Is much like
Eternal socializer
I guess I did get pamphlet
People and stuff like that
Now what
You know what
The fantasy was that
You'd meet somebody to pass you
Some grass
You're offered to A Whole New World Revolution
It was never like that
Especially now that I'm like in my 30s
I go Android
I didn't I wasn't able to that day I was busy but
I did go to a number of lawns
Around the elect
After the election
How to make a stomach feel better
It did it did it made me feel like I was a part of sea
Secede
So many different
People you know a lot of diverse
Causes being represented all-in-one
There's a lot of solidarity I think it's good
The only gets likes
Splintering
I don't think so because they're all merging as one to be like all right look we all have our
Big picture we know
All of us
If we
If we let this guy
Yeah
Central Time
The next thing
The next thing that's
Oh there's more hamamoto there is
Koodegras baked
Oh no
He goes he goes deeper
He had some thoughts about who these broke
Bizarre
And who these radicals are
I don't know how to put
Too fine a point on this
I don't agree with
I'll just leave that right up top
We'll see what you think
Is because
Hypotheses based on what we already know about.
Much obliged by the way as I stated before were concentrated in the east
She and others of a certain specific
Even though
The majority are
Great Christian
Americans
I think they're coming out of the Alameda Naval Base
Are are the products of what colloquially is known as the super soldier program
And what is that
He's not done yet but I want to point out that Justin
When he's at the super soldier program you raise your eyebrows and just gave a nod
Like
You look of your face was
Incredulous it wasn't like what the f*** you
Red look like
Oscar Healthcare to education
This new generation
Naval personnel
Military service at the core
Northern California
A Flying L
What's just means a government background
Exactly
The ordinary
American sovereignty
Institution
I think
Shadow libraries
Shadow Fight
Apply your packages
The two chanez Shadow up top
Go to Shadow organization, Beyond The Shadow version of this podcast next week
These like you know something maybe that we know
And Alex
You know what dude to go to your
Again like
More cynical but God damn if it's not more probably spot on view of
These types of people in terms of like
When were talking about
Like
I feel like I was defending but just more kind of just speaking on the fact that like you know like
If you're gay that's okay
Like I don't hate you
It's also like
It's weird how they
Keep doing that all the time where it's like
Well
You know it's not the Navy that protects us I love those guys those are those are great guys
If the shadow
Yeah yeah
It is weird how they always like separate and then retract
But it's still like
Do you are still calling out the Navy
Well it's it's like
Cynical take on it
It's one way of creating a narrative about the world and never having to
Take responsibility for things
Exist in the real world
Because it could be like oh no my narrative involved
These other things
If someone from the Navy word alike call in or
Whatever hypothetical way.
These people I've been
All this is crazy
Will start thank you for your service but you're not in the shadow Navy in now but that is compartmentalize
Know what goes on because someone called me
Okay
What is caborca scallions
Interesting interesting
You know what it comes down to me and I hate I hate that it sort of boils down
To this
In many ways.
I think
So much of it comes
Down to misplace
Masculine
And like weird versions of masculine
Please
Elaborate I'm interested
This guy a lot of his
Research
Is on the
Desexualization
Asian box
Popular culture in American culture
I'd love to read a book on it right now
Say that women don't want to date Asian man
I got some real s***.
The stage
You left for the untapped evaluation
The one I like 1027 that early but I was I don't know if you do know or not
Huge Steve Harvey fan
So I knew it existed I was just never up that early
It's one of the greatest Defenders of
Fake phone calls I've ever heard
It's just all actors gacho embarrassing
He is the only
Radio personality who's more Christian
Outwardly than Alex
I want to get back to you I don't want to
Interesting
Research topics about
Did you sexually
Location of Asian man
Of course
That in your mind
And then on top of that it is about these protests
The idea that
The coming future is going to be ruled over by women
Is just an incredibly
A massive fear of
Women
We having any control over
I think that's what a lot of this boils down
I can't believe he's a
Teacher
Like a professor
Here's what I would say
When you're in college you're still developing as an
An adult in many ways
Think it's right to
Someone who's in college
You shouldn't treat them necessarily like they're full grown adult
Cuz they're still figuring a lot of stuff out.
That that sort of thing
But they're not so impressionable that having a challenge
Teacher is Dane
So if you have a teacher even if they are a little bit wacky
Yeah I could take a class of his
When I was in college
And be like
It wouldn't make any poop damage would have been like you I'm taking all this
Yeah I'm going to ruin every party talking to
About it
Bring us to the end of our clips
Let's
Did that this day and Alex Jones my man
That was a hell of a ride
I don't like I didn't like today's episode that much
In what way
The disappointing performance for Malik
I'd rather you didn't go off the deep end
Yeah and the stuff he was
It just wasn't
It wasn't Alex enough
Yeah there's just
Something you can feel
You can feel it when he's on and when he's not in it
Just felt like he was
Really on
It could be part of it
And now that we've come to the end of this
I feel guilty
A playback
No
Cuz I was like I was a nice moment
To start things
Eminem in Oklahoma City
Yeah it's a it's a it's a nice.
Method of what we expect
Yeah
Soft kill
Grandma
Basils Redman I did it I had a great time
But until then
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work