Everybody just I wanted to stop in here with a quick introduction before we got into today's proceeding
What you were about to listen to is a live episode
The my co-host Jordan when we were down in Austin Texas
On Friday evening of the last week
June 15th
Such a great time going down there despite the ridiculous amount of travel in a very compact
Amount of time
Time was very tight but everything was so delightful and
I don't know I want it everybody but
The list is so long
Later and discuss more of the details of the trip whenever me and Jordan sit back down for the next episode
But for now I just needed very sincerely to give
A broad
Thank you to everybody who came out and made the event so fun and it worthwhile to do all that ridiculous monotribe
Also
Thank you to everyone at beerland they were so spectacular and accommodating
And I
They were able to record the show so competently
And then also send it to me
So quickly that we can put it out here on Monday through a big thank you to them
Everyone over there
Thank you to all of you for Warriors 4 not come
Another thank you cuz we'd rather not deal
Which y'alls ass is
I think I'll probably take a nap and
M4
A regular in in Studio One
Babe
Drink
Was like
Why are you
Because I
Lies the rub
I figured why not
From Today Show
I am not a wolf and I'm not ashamed
Vicious
Giant
Memes
I have various doing the battery enough
25th 20
In the history of Alex
Today's episode
Refined
Wistful
Which
Was Dick
We allow the psychopathic control over
Hollywood movies
First
Public Service angle
What happens when the machine
Okay
Are you talking about
There was a lot of weight
Okay
Army of bears
Army of bears bears perverted by Sheepdogs
Vicious sheepdog
Sheepdog
Bicycle
I associate
Bernard
You like Sheepdogs
Richard sheepdog
It kind of works
The rest of the world
Caribou
Is about
I just don't want to
3 hours
Where we established
Thomas day off like real
It is the animated contest of Liberty
The problem is
The great men and women that have delivered as to this current position
Schwab's
Before
Got2b
Commercial
There is a way to save the world
AWOL
Is coming down
How to watch Game of
Beginning of the show
Half hour
How awesome is Joey
So much
Popular
Clip is
For reasons that I know
Because I've looked in
I'm here ladies and gentlemen
407 Central Standard Time
Make news broadcast
Sunday
I figured that a lot of stations out there
Tryouts broadcast
7 years ago show
Think that's a bad
That's true
Maybe I could produce horse this
His numbers are
Dangerous for people who are little
January 20th
The numbers do not match
How many
It's like over 100
60 / 100
Estimate
I mean
From
Cremello
It's not a city
Are you telling me that
If you work
You would suddenly here Alex
That would be a bummer
More
You're all going to die
Okay
All of us
Where else would you find global
Have a good flight from Alaska Alaska
River Field
What Ibiza Filius is a f****** River
I started looking
She had on
The Sunday show
It wraps getting off at thinking
Alright
And it's not even impressive
With a population of
The rivers
Yeah
On the ground is very very clearly
Declaration
Hey guys
Don't be sassy
All of the radio station
Corpus Christi
Minnesota
Broadcast
Because
America
Power structure in the system
Like to fund it
Okay
Like all of the progressive radio.
The time to show that I should
Just lay it out there
Dalek broadcasted on KLBJ here in office
Fatalistic
What you're saying is
He's gone
Lasertron
Alright
Albums of river
This was
Certified service
Play One winner
A show about retirement planning
That's good news that was one hour of it
Retirement plan
Okay
Feeding helpline
All of them
I'm trying to keep a very sunny face on
And he goes
Everything is totally fine don't worry about
It's
If it were true that
According to him it's Friday but according to archive.org in the Wayback machine
You can find this traffic
January 26th how would you describe that grass
I would call it
Precipitous
I was really hoping that we could have a PowerPoint presentation going and everything
In terms of like
September 2014 Jones was about 1,200 global
The 12:00 top website
You drop
2000 rankings
Terrifying
And can you go to mysteriously if you go to prison planet statistic
It's from the exact same time
Same drop
Which leads me to believe
Something is
Is it up
So at this point
What he would like to
Represent
Okay
U.s. is 544
Nope
We're 356 in the US
My bad 350
Trash can
Download
Film Noir about it
The Femme Fatale is Alex's
Lost
If you want to see the same
But what is the Alexa
Of his website and msnbc's website
The MSNBC one
Is current in 25th
The one of you
It's from
In 2014 in September
He is very
Manipulated
It look like
Never happened
Who cares
I care about this I don't know why I care about that
Cannot help but know that especially because he's
Bring up a Lexus
From another website
You might
He might
From the website
Okay
Alright
Melaleuca.com
Alexa.com
Amazon music
It's not true but don't worry about it
Because other website
Is the closest
You find the Rush Limbaugh has 14 million he's number one
In the game
When do we start climbing
Population
Super male vitality
Alright
Was putting in his Superman
Toledo
The b******* about
Here's a clip
But for you
You're not far off
Because of a bumbling stuttering
Hillbilly redneck
College degree
Other men
It's game over and let me give you a message that I've been given for 20 years to fit in my heart I've always
The right there real quick before I get to the message
Call Larry Nichols
It's just
It's just a delusion
These are real
I'm here to blow the alarm
To get the real Warriors up
That's all I'm doing I got big Long's
The real Warriors
Mike cernovich
Jack Potomac
I'm scream and come out of the woodwork
Real Warriors
Cool cool
I'll tell you what
I go down to St Louis
I'll say this
Lead me to believe
We got some problem
Billionaire
No
You've never liked I am a millionaire who owns like
I don't know my own children
That's fantastic
Yep Goodwill
Accountant
Importing years to finance his operation
Have comments supported us
Sports.com
Because
Free bone broth bro
Eagles
Stabbed
180 something million dollars that he's raised over
Which one of yours if you break that down
Divided
Everything cost
Valerie
Probably mostly salary
Well I was saying something now I disagree with me so we can
I suppose so
Start this episode and you disagree with yourself the moment you heard the X
Alright
Area were never so clear about ideas
Cuz we are one
Williams
Shakespeare
Picking up a little bit
2015 Alex Jones jobs
Trump
Propaganda
January
Where were
You might think that
Your trailer
Social
Real fun
At least
Stupid
Neocon Palin's tea party takeover will facilitate
Call zornio calling and saying she's taking over
Three exclamation
Even more disgusting
Is she as good as
Magic cruise Palin
Cruise
Like at the end of the day what reading
Who knows
Ticket is Ted Cruz Sheriff
Call Sarah Palin
I'm sorry I'm having I'm having
Precipitation Branch I better stop right now
Alright
To clean up his language for radios
We can't save
Converting
So real fun
Ted Cruz
Did Cruz drop out
Ted Cruz a crossdresser
Now
Acquiring minds
Very weird
So that's pretty strange I think that's
That's fun
It's real fun shift you made there buddy
Very nice
Patriots at 1
Football
Under what
Vicious circle
Deflategate
What's going on
Remember
Did Ted Cruz deflate the football
Care
Particular
Sports Authority
So I don't have a phone
Bent out of shape about people make
And then 20 seconds later
The Patriots
Everybody wants to email
Everything else there's
Taking the high road on this one
Is there a conspiracy here
That's what you're really been screwed over
Or is that Obama
I've quit doing stand-up
Like
If you were
Yes how how do you work the ball I would say
Cancel this show
How do you feel about Dan ball jokes
Is it like a
To do it
That's fair
Give me what all right I'll put my
Three months notice
If you like
The Renaissance
The primary motivation early she's expressing
Episode
That the primary motivations
Globalist
Crush everybody
F****** hate
His world
Very weird
Weird
I'm here
And their state
Is 2
Launch
Years ago
Was the Gutenberg Press
That works
What
First
Coronavirus graph
Also
Do historians agree that the Renaissance didn't end until the global
Wish
But from my understanding
Primarily
Something happened in Italy
Yeah
Europe
Maybe baby
Okay
Tuesday 14 15
I wouldn't
Licenses
They try to take control of society they fund mouses and they fund Dalton and they fun eugenics
But don't worry about it
Italian Renaissance
Beginning point but a lot of life
Which part of the film
Never heard of it
The American Renaissance
Between 1876 and 9
Discovered
What he's talking about
I think this might be 200 episode
That's enough
Happened
Before the Civil War I think Alex is illiterate so I don't
What are you talking about
Fun fact
There's a white supremacist magazine called the American Renaissance
But they don't have as much to lose
So they
It's very clear they're talking about white people
Absolutely
It's fun code
American Renaissance the sound
Donald Trump
Because he's the one candidate
Who points out that we should accept immigrants York
We don't need Muslim
Vote Trump
American Renaissance
Very similar
I don't know
Eastern Europe
Are we getting a lot of Russian
Never listen to a podcast very uncomfortable
During me reading about a white supremacist
You never heard of
Keep talking it's a weird thing
Alex
Burlesque
You know you take your medicine
We can all have fun
Al Gore
Here's another one
His quotes
Eec
What do you
Alright
Furious
I mean baby.
If you
Humanity was put
Together
Yeah
Spoiler alert
Do you know this
ETA is looking into helicopters
Very efficient
What's going on
Alright
Can I get another
What's up
There's a God
Hell yeah
Just celebrate
That's me being petty
Just that
Izod
Where's the funeral
One and a half Stars
So the only in that article is this
It is crucial that we build public will for an agreement
The purposes of climate action now
Through the issues
The article is about
Public transit in developing
And improving
Public transit in existing urban areas
So I have to go further than the Daily Caller
Business Insider articles
Hey I needed to drop in here because
We have a situation where the recording of the the episode here
Look up the card that we were recording on
And so there's a little bit of a drop-off in terms of
Just a little bit of the conversation and eye drops out
Just wanted to fill you in on what we were talking about
Susan the middle of a conversation we're having about algor wanting to ban cars and I guess I don't need to reset it up you guys
Is just heard it
Business Insider article
It goes on to explain that Felipe Calderon
I was quoted
It's talking about how there's a priority that we don't build up cities that pointlessly have low density
I just for the sake of people using cars that's much smarter
And much more efficient that we should have hired a diarias
With mass transportation that's Services everybody much more efficient way
Hey somebody who lives in the city with amazing mass transportation
And then also look at it as transportation out to
The suburbs were a lot of people like to live
I you feel very much in line I very much agree with that
Also Alex is reporting on this of the story
Is him saying that
Al Gore wants to spend 90 trillion dollars in order to ban cars
Which is a
Misrepresentation of things
At the show would ask if there was actually 90 trillion-dollar
Hours in the world and I said I do know that
Because of his Business Insider article and then it goes
Business Insider article
Quote it turns out the 90 trillion is a total of infrastructure investment that is likely to be spent anyway build
Pulling up in a grading City
Brian Calderon are arguing that it be spent more wisely
Able to burn fossil fuels
Just to get from point A to B
Trillion dollars in something without Gore is encouraging people spend it's a reference to the amount that would be Spa
Event structure projects of this sort anyway
So there you go. That's what we were talking about
Will jump back to where the recording picks up
With another
Bulshit story that Alex is telling
All the best folks
Now we get to
You probably
Favorite story that Alex
The bad
Stream the German newspapers
Description
His rule
But they will not
For a feminist landowner appointment
Michelle Obama's kids
I've never been more
Do Germans
Oh no that's
There's a
The article that he's going off of headache
11 converter
Absolutely
Is the story that he talked about his super fun first of all
Men's rights to piss standing up
And that's really funny because I haven't
This story is about
Who's landlord
You have
You spill
Around the toilet I'm suing you
Because
Covered
Your eyes
Ended up being
Sounded favor of the
Landlord as a man
The rhythm of your speech
Former tenant to court
Marble floors the bathroom in
And he said was
Spray drops from
Trivia
I do think it's really funny and everybody
If you want to look into it
A little bit of
Debate in Germany
About whether or not
Publix
It's just a question I have
You say you're drunk enough to piss on the wall you're not drunk enough
Alright
So anyway he's not done with this
The feminists aren't trying to make boys
Elementary School
High School PE setting
Because it makes girls feel bad
What
Tell you how to urinate
We did a whole lot
I know I get it
Make fun of nerds
That's the worst Tim Allen I've ever heard in my entire life
That's required
Excited when he wants to talk to Google tell me how to
It's probably one of my favorite
Sometimes baby
I don't know if you know this but
I feel like that's important
I decided to steal
Sounds like it's cute
Clipper
Is one of my favorite things
If
If you really listen
No
Did Alex knows
Show on KLBJ
In Austin
You just tell like
B****** f****** droopy dogs
Incredible than white
The Time Square mentality
The world is so much bigger than just dominating
Universe
No
The premise
Tired
Alright
So at this point what he decides
I got to feel bad another
40 minutes
The radio
Make some calls
Publix
Culture adopted because it was the most efficient
This is
It's a class that this Arizona professor was teaching about the problem of whiteness
Historical implications Canary ideas
Contributor to society or whatever but
So now just for fun Idol
Culture
Cedros toothbrushes
Money
Artillery
Adventures that might not be right I might have missed
I'm going to stand by it anyway
Toilet paper
Perverted
Reliv Wells before
I feel like whatever you're like
All of these cultures that literally invented all the stuff we built off of
Just because
Came up with the number zero that's
Changing the entire scope
Humanity
Doesn't mean
Big round of applause
You love
Infowars supplements
If you do then you know that
What is very wishy-washy about
Is whether or not
Super male vitality
Is a boner pill
He pretended
When he wants
Tubi
It's like
Superman
My wife
Debate
Once and for all
With this
Completely absurd
How much does Shayla
Nailed it
First
Directions to wax
Drama
We have one last clip to live
Come to here
Franklin listening at home a Cascade of roses
Fun
Literally the last
On KLBJ
Global government has taken over
His Radio Show in your area
Real quick I do need to stress
Episode
This is my last episode
Farewell episode without ever
1004 Sahara
It's a support.
Yes
Infowars.com
For your support free openmedia for granted
Portage
Planet
Infowars.com
Show producer
Communications Network
From 11 to 2 p.m. Central Standard Time
Rivers rivers
Breaker breaker one conspiracy
The show is the largest
Sunday showings
KLBJ 590 a.m.
In Austin Texas
Wow
Tell BJ schedule
He's not interested
Retirement show is still on
Their retirement show is still getting played
Also really fun I found this while looking around trying to see
Figure out the bottom
Next
The people at KLBJ were so kind and generous
Allowed
Were they were they kind and generous to quote
You're right now
I can't remember the rest of the lyrics I got to be honest
They allowed him to broadcast
If you was on
Listeners of my show here on
The decision has been made to move the local programming on Sunday
And even though my show national news
Good fence
Heard on Sunday evening
Broadcast
Continue
I really appreciate my 590 KLBJ
Vindicator
2 / 100 stations
Dimension 100 stations
I found an article that was posted on the internet
C.j. Morgan
Who's the guy who hosts
The weekday 7 p.m. tonight
You went so far as to post on their website
The following headlines
Jurusan I'm ashamed we ever had him on this station
Random broadcast in which we interview gym during sxsw
Freedom nugget segments on Charlie Hodges
I don't care I don't care
There's a freedom
Misspelled
That's a good show
Come on
I don't like the first word
I really don't
I do like the idea of
Eventually it became too much
He's at his blatant disregard for any rational truth
The way he capitalized
His listeners
Our encounters with truly mentally ill followers
I was needing his help
In parentheses
He hates his fans by the way
It's too much
Is that quote
Overstudying a year-and-a-half summarized everything we've ever tried
I will say that I wish
I wish I would have spent less time
Like low his raising
I talk more about that
I would recommend everyone look into
I don't want that out there
Everyone out there in Elizabeth
Make
Make a techno remix
Of Jordan saying I'm in German
If you need one
I mean
You know
Broadcast
I suppose were supposed to
Facebook Facebook
Indeed
I think it's yours
I love it
I don't know how to do
I don't think
Themselves
Burlesque
Thank you so much for coming out
F*** yourself Ted Cruz