Alex
Novels about Alex Jones
Hey
I was
If I were
Use the subjunctive
Someone utterly unfamiliar
Love
Okay
Just
Just the general sense that life could be better I would say first of all the passive voice
Bisquick tacular
I would say this
Absolutely
Security First
Episode just got to address
In the room
Record on Monday night got to a little bit of a row a little bit of a fight
If people were watching are going to listen to the show that I feel like it's
Appropriate address we should at least
I got a couple message
They were nice from people like me like they don't worry about stuff
Should I wasn't mad at you
I wasn't mad at you interrupting
Spikes
Expensive liquor
In the chat room they have a drinking game and I physically have to wait to talk
So like it's not
It's not that I'm unfamiliar with that dynamic between us or even that it bothers
But I think a lot of people might not like Danny Jordan responding
Oh my God.
We're having a conversation
What about the children
Concentration
Excuse whatever language
You prefer
Seems fitting
But you were talking about how
You aren't sure if
This is really that new
Atrocities with the United States
Of course
Other countries but
It isn't that
Agree with you
Because
I don't
Necessarily think
After we turned off the recording was what I was
Get to say
Which was
The lack of adjust
Certifiable
The nation
For this
Deniability
When a drone
Accidentally
Kill the child
2A Mediterra
Like there's some sort of psychological buffer that
In your head
That allows you to like move on
No
Abject
Cruelty
So you are making your point and I tried to butt in
Disagree with it
To make
ORD to sort of
Include that in the conversation
Mmu steamed
Right through there should be no government
Bad idea
Like that
I didn't get to say the thought that I wanted to say I just disagreed with you on your road right
Alright
That was going to paint me in the box like I've
That I was a
A Centrist on
Children
Freedom
And I'm not thrilled right
I can take it when someone wants to like
My love
Like I can
I really am
This situation in this story
I've no interest
I have no time for it
Even people who mean it well
And none of this is to say that you were intentionally
Behaving in a way
Braided it's not mad at you
I'm not mad at the hypothetical list
I was just super frustrated and before Levi throw my head
When I'm trying to think through that thought witches
Which was something that I've been thinking about the whole day
I could tell you were doing
I was just trying so hard to get to like this this
Reconciliation
Because you're absolutely right
One of the big reasons that this is so much
Is despite all of the cruel acts that America has
Committed
And continues to come
This one is just
So it isn't different and yet it is so massive
Different
To sit down and
Got to be another
Yeah
Dispatch In Our Lifetime
It does
Feel unique
Kaleisia tea
I'm not I'm not right
I'm fine saying that acting on it now I probably need to sit with those feelings
For a little while
Know if I fully support that
I'm not sure if it matters
You know it
It's hard and in the other thing I think is
Particularly hard about it
Is it like
Not to say we
We called this or anything like that
We've gone over over and over again
Hey Alex Jones is representative of this
Tired
Voice of white mask
Nationalism what you're seeing is other ring of particularly Muslims and immigrants
It feels really terrible
Because I couldn't
Stop anything like temperature right now
Mark feeling of
Surrounded
That is kind of a bummer
I don't I don't know if that
Place of ego
It just kind of everything everything really sucks
What
The feeling of the inability to
Like even a desperate
Situation
Right
The ability
Feels feels
Do does that rally
Protest that'll be taking place there's organization
Yeah couple of organizations that I
It feels desperate even
Haven't done
It doesn't feel like you're really make a difference
It does matter
It doesn't matter
Do something
Figured what Alex Jones
Kate is
Feeling a powerless
In the face
Giant
The Behemoth evil
That's stupid
Direct action is always possible
Even if it feels like it does nothing
Should do some
Well that's one of the organization that I that I looked into two
Today that
I will stay
A couple of
That I research that are direct action you know they're not like the Red Cross where they have an operating budget
Or anything like
That like I don't f*** around with that
The first was the legal age
Which is entirely devoted to
You getting
Migrant children
Represent a
If you because if they've been separated from their parents
70% of them or something like that have nobody
No representation they have more milk or
Necessarily
And then the other one
And then the other one was I think it's I think it's actually becoming popular
CES
The big reason that I like them a lot is because they are putting it not to
Just words
Legal defense but also
Toward a permanent
Baleful
Spray Urban
You like if it cost five grand to get out of
Prison Tuesday
And you don't have five Grand Avenue
You stay there
With this permanent Bond Fund
Because Bond aren't
You know it's not like a perch
If everything goes well you get the money back
So if a bond is setups
Sufficiently
It can operate
Definitely
And
That's one of the big things that I I feel like we should do
The other thing is I think
We should all be
And what
That was a
9 Minutes of our episode
Bailing
On the episode
Because
We revealed I will reveal in a moment Project Camelot episode
Kind of negative Cloud hovering over
What's supposed to be a jolly good time
Yeah we are we are absolutely going to enjoy the f*** out of
I can't wait you might actually not
Because because of how much I'm going to enjoy
It hits all this passive voice
Get onto two things that I've done
Fence Atlanta
313 in
The past
And it just happens to converge in one person
Perfect you fall in love with the city of
Thank you so much everybody on Friday
Reviews of the wild episode
Those positive reviews would be impossible
Helped us
Set up
Absolutely
Before we could go on like to I instead of thinking any donors
Today like to give
Thank you
Books in Austin
Facilitated the
Along with
Yourself Georgia
You pick the perfect Apple
That's not it
Because much of the work is get at coordinating
Master Bethel
The people on the ground in Austin
John Duggar
Rory
Everybody on the ground who made that show possible
It was
It was the most fun
Nerve-wracking
Couple of days
I think of my entire
Quadrumvirate
Rocketeers
Three Musketeers
Because of their I help it was
Spectacular
Recognition of that I would like
Officially
Jesus Christ
How to read
I am out of control
Abused by white people
Joseph Stalin
Thank you so much
Austinites
So prophetic
Is it his admiration for Hitler and Stalin as being complete badasses in your life
Well he's being facetious and then we get our own and
Hitler and Stalin were white
That's true
Let's go
Was doing the world is all this Holocaust
You'll be like
It's all just
It's all babies.
Minimize that
Stop and I'm sure Alex
I don't want to hear anybody
Talking about
Force
I don't give a s*** I don't want to hear about space force from him
Because I have other people to tell me about it
Nll tell you something about our
Jedi work
Okay it's not just
Chilling
Snapchat
But you learn and I see episode 1 of Game of Thrones
Somebody's got to kill and will you put it
Yourself
He was
Jedi
Episode of The Project Camelot Hellyeah
And every episode
Exact same way
Kerry Cassidy
So we will never forget
That is not a gas station
Hi everyone I'm Trey Cassidy from Project Camelot and
Very happy to be here tonight I have a very
Good
Old friend
Haven't heard or seen from him in a long time and one of my conferences
He's a wonderful researcher
An investigator and dinna bring him on
Stream here now Steven Kelly
Steven say hello to everyone
I carry
Join the club
She's she's really excited
Fiona
She's good means if she's excited
You can tell by the sound of her
Either he's a wonderful research
Wonderful monotone
What are you got
I don't know how to put this into work like
Cuz you know what every single time we meet a new person through Project Camelot answer my responses
We found a real crazy.
Like I always think we've outdone ourselves in terms of really unique
Version of crazy
The random pants
I think he's crazier than a diamond gusset
He gives me multiple feeling
Where is Mike Epps other people like a
Because we like
Pictures of murderer and
That's all I got on that Kramer
Not that other space pilot guy
Cuz he had a
Do nothing
Decade in his twenties and now he's like actually I was in space
Brought me back to life
Got to reclaim
Sometime
I get it
This guy Steven Kelly
Is like I got
So many feelings about him
I prevail
Going to be a mess
But here the full gamut of human emotion today
If you
I get up to Jedi
Padawan
2 carats
Again
She tries to like
She tries to distance
Self
From some of his ID
Immediately
I was going through my library and I realized that somehow
Audio interviews with you seem to have disappeared
And we did get hacked
We don't know what happened some of the radio shows they disappeared so I thought I'd bring it back on
It may seem like we're going over old business but it's still current so it's all good
Yeah well you know I think it's been was November
When you know the whole
2012 2012 2012 path of this when I really came out with us and I think that's when you leave the key
So yeah
Actually I quit before that we were in touch but
It's been awhile so I can play
Subway
It's her so it's been awhile
Which is not a good well it's because he kept saying
Because he's coming back
He has not like that tip even though it's all good
It's agencies just like 9
Memes exactly
He's doing that
Either
He knows it was wrong but now he has such a good sense of humor about himself that he's like one of myself for it
A lot of people do
The predictions were wrong
But there was like a wave of waking up
What happened
On December 20th
December 21st 2012
What's the date of the beginning of the Awakening
Still happening
Also
How is that relate to the end of the world
Oh okay
Just nonsense
Christmas December 21st
Right
It's the beginning of the new phase in the Mayan calendar and everybody okay
The cycling over of a new
The age of Aquarius
Full
It's wet.
Rationalize
The Doom p***
Around what time
Who's coming back
Hit the world
So
Crazy
This point
We get
Steve
Ssb4 credits respect
Hey
Like I've spent a lot of time with this guy
Alright
Discredit
Pretty familiar thing
So anyway you are a
What you call yourself is a next contractor for the NSA and CIA
Can you explain that in a little more detail
Alright real quick that means I am not a
Agent CIA agent shr9
Withdrew I never work for Langley Randy's places like that what I did do as I
Was a contractor I worked in Bilton
Was unemployed for these the Cowboys agencies that they set up on the side out there and and of course
The CIA when they do
Operations of half the time they're made everything everybody is disposable the whole operation is disposable Cyrus one of the
Disposable people then of course
I got involved with the Ollie North people
Of course right of rice
Iran-Contra
I wasn't Expendable guy and then Oliver North
It is because there's so many
Soda
Enough people have had to go on record
This is real but also lie about
The exact details are right
Like this wiggle room
People who will never tell
The whole truth
But there are enough truth is out there that you like I was ever
But you don't ever be able to confirm it but it is so much more credibility than to say I was in
That's why they play this game
The same reason
Why you would say
I'm a part of the NSA I wasn't NSA contractor
Deny that
Instead of saying like I'm apart of
XYZ program
Like
You're just making up
What years make up a program
Careywood believe
General stores
I don't know if you knew this actually had a secret space program
General Dollar
That's the weird thing about the name they trick people
Dollar General dollars
Ordered
So many of us and I was only born
I was just bored because of the way that the Dollar General works
I'm out I'm out I ran out of
General Dollar
That's fun
Do some reason
North
This guy.
Two other people I've heard on
Project Camelot
Stream you guys know each other then like wait
Like
Dysentery
He's business
Right right
Right
Which is why Oliver North is now the head of the NRA
But the only way into the future
Write an spacebattles
With lasers and they're going to run at legal lasers
I don't think
Caesar like
Worley
The only thing I've seen that
Gunsight
Targeting laser
You find any
Proof
He even knows
Anything
But like
Higher land Blazers
AMU put it in through is what
It's so like light
Whatever you understand about life
Steve was involved
With Ollie North
Loving you calling him Steve Cove Court
Now would you be surprised to learn
Sirius group
I am not
Happy dealing with them I work for the CIA again in but I did get involved with Billy Meier people and all that
This business for the play against in the UFOs men
More crazy stuff with the secret agencies and eventually got
Hooked up to Templars
Bilderbergers and The People Under The Getty that I call the caver
Don't really have anything to do with government per se but
First closer to the world the new world order those people
How are you check my watched everyone
Alright I was originally a contractor working for a cowboy age, blah blah
Now
Somehow that works out I told her the details
Take people back
One time I quit my job movie theater when I was an usher
I overreacted
Are you committed treason or whatever
National Disgrace or you're selling cotton working with the CIA
We are not going to
Bouncing around from Secret Agency
Man-to-man and they were like
They're swoopy
So
What do you know about Billy Meier
Swift
He's a switch to
He's a sweetie
What is a Jedi but not a condom
They wave their hands they make you believe
Here is a UFO
He's most famous for his
Very easy to the Bronx hoax photos and videos of UFOs
These photos of General Improvement
To be just a result of
Take a photo of a
Photo
And making it look like the exposure was different
The Flash's difference
Anime missions are going to be
Hugest
Take pictures of the animation
I'd say that he took those pictures from a space
That Greg
That's pretty awesome
Or
Even in America
He I would take pictures
News of sci-fi movies that were playing
And claimed that they were alien
What's this
I saw a couple of examples of people found that were like
All the points
Similarity
Feel about the Natalie Portman film annihilation
So one picture
So good
Hot women
And two of them
Blurry picture of two of the members of the show girl group the gold diggers
From one of the Martin show
There's a huge mess
His videos purporting to show UFOs in Acts
To know the product of him making little model
And using Force
Perspective
Cinematographer
Explain how he does it and his ex-wife
Come out and pointed out that in one of his most famous videos
Do you recognize their homes trash can is being part of the spaceship
So you don't know
This is what we're dealing dealing with a guy who has big dreams
You got Big Dreams
And everybody is just pulling him down
You need do you need pump
The brakes on that cuz that's how it feels right now
So are you
Contact with aliens
For decades at least dating back to like a 19
Detox to art
Is oldest
Most people he talks to
To talk to RAV4
Course the website Billy Meier UFO research
Dot-com
Amazing archive
And not surprisingly what you find is a veritable Gold Mine of fraudulent prediction
Mixed in with things that never happened
Predictions
For example 1975
It was in 1977
But the prediction mysteriously was never printed until 9
Yeah
Tons of stuff like that
Was he wrote it on envelope in invisible ink and then put it in a bag
Deposit
That way he wouldn't alter the the future
As it occurred
Brighton team knew what was going to happen
That when they were exchanging one of their ball the time
Invisible ink envelope
This is awesome I got the face
So what do you think about Billy Myers
So far
Also been
Billy Meier Play Avatar of the great prophets of Elijah Isaiah
Jeremiah Jesus
He claims with a German guy sent him a fragment of a text
He bought me gif
Black Market that said quote
I am the herald of Truth
And in this Mission I will once again amongst
Important
Barbie the names of Elijah Isaiah Jeremiah
Aziza Mohammed
Billy
Alright Muhammad
Do I Shall Serve the People and Prophets seven times
Until their way of thinking
To that of the Creations law and directed to the police
Astounded
And confirmed it to be accurate at about 8500 years old
Accurate
8500 years old you know it's
Crazy as there is,
So many Buddhas and then gym
The great Buddha Buddha Buddha like colloquial Adventure
Familiar Astro
Tyrus text from 8500
8500 years ago
So you know the next
That this is this is on the down low
But the next Dalai Lama
Davie
Davie the Dalai Lama
Aiden
Braden Braden Braden is actually spelled
Dude is that like behind the extent
Harmless UFO fun
He tells his followers of the end times are near
Is clearly fake photos and videos
Proof
He is the all-powerful aliens
The chosen to guide
Needless to say he scared a lot of people
Super duper rich
They always give
Why do they always get rich
Easy one word
Scaring people
Yeah I know we be evil we could be so rude
So rich
The hell we don't
Alright
All that other stuff leads to him
The cavers
I don't know if I should
Should tell you
All of what's going on so I'll just give you a broad stroke
Steve
He believes that there's an underground city
Cujo
Underneath the Getty Museum
John
Piece of evidence
I don't know if
We'll get to his reasoning a little bit later but he believes really feel like you just
Divided
Do you believe there's an underground
Aliens and
Underneath the museum
The people who run it are the caver
Isaiah who like the Illuminati and all of them actually report to
So like the cavers are higher up this
This is his way of trying to pull rank
People who
Come close to the top of the food savers
The Illuminati's just the foot soldiers of the caver
Gotcha
You're probably curious about what
The stuff
When he was going to Steve was at these Cowboys agent
He was working
You're probably curious about that
No I'm working
They called themselves
Do they call themselves the cameras
Riddler in Olivette
Cuz I feel like
Spelunkers would be a better
All will become clear in
Do time here is what he was working on
I'm still involved with the CIA again but this was for another project involving a big giant flashlight and call the
Plasma beam
Eventually of course the
At least three times I had
People coming along who I don't really know who the hell they were actually two of them turned out to be
Reptoid
Oh boy
Work
Flashlight
Yeah
Video games
Because we already have
Nugent flashlight
The light that baby up
Is that really what is going on I apologize
He does bring back out another time
Like the context of it is never flashed out you never explained
What it was for
Who in the world
Smaller generally speaking
You looking more utility in a small flashlight
Portable
Especially when you're in
Cuz you couldn't
Flashlight
Sevilla opening
Giant
Play that right now
I'll tell you this
Doesn't come up
Just
The museum and how there's a
He was working with
Couple of people I talked about in that book one of them the guy which name is
Vince
Which was like a Handler
And he died they actually he was a cave or he was like a Handler he was the one that
The first came up with the word cave
And he was he was one of them he was like work underground at all that
He came to me when I was working with the CIA doing the big flashlight project Argo again
Acted like he was like a marketing guy he wanted to come and help me market this project that he was a music
Chandler
Well actually from day one I knew or something weird about him because
He didn't speak Lakota English his English was
Used words
The wrong words at the wrong time
You don't like
When you you meet these guys that aren't real
But human haven't been human for very long is that they'll do things like they haven't been doing it for very long and in this
Language of course is one of the clues they
So they can just before literally anybody who doesn't
The best single
Someone who has their second language
Strip the language really bad
Or they'll get really excited about the
Skin
They're not you
Being in the skin of something new it's a new experience so that they're all running around hoe wow this is such a great
I really like this
That kind of thing that's usually a giveaway but this particular guy bench
They killed him I think they killed him because he told me too much
What it came up with Kieran stuff and he talked about the underground something and activity York
Heart attack
Alien
Skin
Restart run around saying I love having the skin that is suspicious
To get
Refuse what I if I had
Ask him
You're contending
That Vince the caver
Who was the
The super creative guy who came up with calling people who live in caves
Capers
Came to him
As a Kimber Handler
First
He was coming to this guy
With marketing advice for the flashlight
Presumably what is your marketing plan for the big giant flashlight
Your flashlight too small we can help you we can help you with that
I don't know
Brittany
Is this you
Rihanna's face
Here's why this is brilliant
Because he
Slave just enough track to make it like believable
For someone like Carrie she can walk along with it because he
He's laid out like I was working on this this
I met this guy
He's not drawings
Straight line
Between thing
I was working on some other project
Show me market
Giant flashlight
This is another thing I was working on
Right there's a bright there's enough like
Confusion as to like
Pronoun reference
So
Have you ever thought to yourself
Why is
I can't see Venus
Will you sir
Need a big giant
Right
It with
Million
Easy payments
28 million
Sure get a flashlight
That spans the entire size
And God damn all the goddamn
Here is here's how
Steve knew something was up beyond the guy loving skin
Call the great English
Here is
How are you doing
These guys
Clearance
Doesn't make any sense for normal person so that was pretty clearly
But
He's good at making
Stats for a normal person
That is mean to you saying
Stuff like you
Pretending
Do you like these
Like anybody to talk to Alex Jones
All of them
Text Stolen Valor for
So he's like impressed by the guy's ability to bulshit
Basically that's what I
Somebody who has clearance that no human being should ever
Experience
Which suggests to me
Who is giving clearance
Is all clearance coming from capers
Clearance flows uphill from
Alright alright
WWE really was some sort of CIA or something or something or other
He never came out and said that the first day I met him he said something about silver he'd even use the word silver he's you
Is non-ferrous metal
But I knew you was talking about silver
Non iron metal mean silver
So
Isis map
You never said he was
But no mortal being should ever experience he was talking about non-ferrous metals
CIAA
Colloidal silver
And Alex Jones
Infowars store
There's a lot of parallels that I'm going to drop
Between
This is one of the more Infowars
People in Project Camelot world
Of benefit
How similar they are
What I'm hearing from this guy is that he's a far more like
Like usually The Crazies
Everybody else's
Is doing all of the
All the fight
And all that stuff
And where folks
Pakistan
Expanding Humanity
Kilton
If you'd like he's he's like the guy he's like the the blood guy
I don't want too much
I just get the vibe from him that he wants to Warrior
Not like a guy who's trying to
He's like on the frontlines fighting
Spacebattles for you
Alright
Crazy
But here I am
We find out how
How did Steve wake up
How did he snap out of that program in Voorhees like a happy-go-lucky guy does working for
The CIA Aster
Before that
This might be what he was working on
At what point did you
Kind of soda go down the rabbit hole
And wasn't it your brother
Yasso Brothers definitely involved
But when you talk about going down the rabbit hole
You know you talked about the Getty let's just say that the big wake-up which is everybody think about the wake up the wake
Moment
Who's sitting across the desk from the guy from the NSA guy when they start tell me about the
Slaughtering a village of people in in Honduras in the middle of the jungle
That's my kind of snapped and realized it
I was working
People who weren't that nice and they're capable of
Stealing everything in the village
I was really naive at that time cuz I thought we were one nation under God and we didn't do those things and it was the bad guy
And I thought you know
They were obviously they didn't deserve to have that happen specially their animals and everything that's when I really snapped
Weird
Estranged
Who gives a s*** if you kill a bunch of people you killed his dog man
Alive during Vietnam
Also it was the system of
I believe that
Well that was a
That way
People out loud
I think that if I were to take that to me I would say you were live
A very blessed
We ignored life before that right
But good
And this guy was the first time you were like
Does Christian Brothers like haha we killed pigs
As eating a bacon sandwich
You can't kill
Mad about you
Twice
Killing the animals
How could they do that
Whatever whatever
Could have could have gone either
Brother
And now
Where did the brother
The Apparently has brother I can't prove it
You have to prove literally everything otherwise I don't I don't believe he has a brother
Suspicious
Find out about his brother a guy named
Who's another guy
Is mentioned in a artifact
Recovered from
Egyptian black mark
Absolutely
This story
Just
This is so convoluted I don't even know how to do
Describe it but this is where we start to get into like him bringing in the veggetti
Story
The actual
This is
Is nonsense
Yes I went through the processes of learning all these things and getting hooked up to Billy Meier and all this stuff
Again Billy Meier
And get eleaf my brother on everything
And what happened is that
She has a friend named Dawn
Worked with another guy
Team gym
In gym
Was a gifted
But he also his father was a high-ranking high-level Mason
And
Mason City cop killed the father
And then when they kill the father they came to Jim
And it basically handed him the keys to the kingdom
Which involved
A box of Cuban cigars
The big expensive house
The job of
Trust fund manager for the Getty Museum
Another box of cigars
But these things do you know
You got understand it's like there's there is Magic involved
Cigars
Did
Nice house
Museum brave other perks
And also Magic
Well we'll get to what he means by the magic stuff here in a second
I love Percival Dawn and Jim
His brother.
Come back up
His brother went on a tour of the Getty Museum
Was weird and apparently
Because he's Avenue
The stories of
We got
Vincent dog
These are all the most mundane white dude names for a secret Global conspiracy that is
Going on since the dawn of time
Navigate to Vista I want to tell you a lot about that
You brought it up in that last
Explain what you mean
By that Magic's remind me about bloodline
Everything is Justin e because you got to remember you're talking about people that have
Looking Glass Technology
White
And I know what you're going to do before you do it
They knew these people knew that I was going to invented
3 beam laser
Before I was even in the business
And when the day came that I finally actually invented it and designed it was sitting there at the drafting table drawing
They were standing behind me over my shoulder watching you do it
And I knew it
You should like
You know you can start to learn those things
It's all about this psychic
Sure I didn't you become a remote viewer
We'll get into that here in a few
Thanks Gary
What is back on track
So I wanted to learn more about
Steve 73b
Steven the three beam laser to find out what I can learn about it
You know is a lot like
All of the
Ensign Forrest
On Project
Repeat what he says about him
SA
However if you find these bio
Animal lover
They give you the name of his
Laser
Which is
Cayendo
Gave me the jump off
Read to learn more
So oshitwaddup this going to be I'm going to I'm going to sit back I'm just going to let this wash over babe
Information I was able to dig up that on August
Second
Stephen D kelly file for chapter 7 bankruptcy
Liquidation
Howard Hughes company
Skate industry
Reflecting assets
The 5000
$750
$661
That is such a low stakes laser company
I'd like a little a little bit later that little buddy
Grant 5750 dollars in assets
Is reasonable
Successful company
For $12,000 in liabilities
Is very low for any kind
And a company
After 7 usually end up with much higher
Bankruptcy
Equity loan and he was like I can't pay this back pops
I have other suspicions about
Without a compass
Right that's the walk away from this
Liquidate it
You're able to find
Cross reference
With one review on it
This review is from November 4th 2010
And it reads
Crook!
He will take your money and parts
/ firearm and won't return it either
He won't return phone calls or emails
He has a history of ripping off the public
Consider yourself warned
So
It turns out
The public with what
Why did firearm show up in the in the mix there
He was selling weapons
And weapon accessories
Business
What he said
He will take your part / firearms
What he meant was
VSCO
Was like Hey I'm going to put a laser on your gun
Yeah and then he just kept
Probably sold.
You look a little bit deeper you come across a bunch of
Fred's on gun enthusiast message boards
What is that
Has anyone done business with the laser manufacturer called SK Industries
I sent him an inference
Steve Kelly
An hk53 forearm
$350
To mount his lasers
3 months ago
Now he's dropped off the radar
Concerned videos
I've been bamboozled
Done
Bart Allen
First one
Yeah I sent him $300 for an IR laser and you never sent it
I should have caught on when you screening his calls but I wanted to laser so bad
I sent you the money anyway
Of course he never answered
Another call
Another one
I sent you money for a laser in October after he got the money stop replying to emails
And after a few phone calls you stopped answering my calls
He seems to be very nice in
Individual to talk to but it would seem he has no intention of supplying the products he advertises
Another one
Really nice guy I know what these are all different people to
If you still get a shout-out
No reply unable to get any response
Men are the last one
Steve Kelly Byrd me too
I sent an MP5 repair Plus
Surefire forend light assembly
Any Captain
I'm out over $1,000
You're not communicating
Anyway I sent a buddy over to his business
Just get it back
A coward wouldn't
Come to the door
This asshat has a lot of Bad Karma
Buyer beware
So he has a deep
History is
Going back
To these reviews are all
Generally from be like
The 8th 2009
Yeah.
So i f
Liquidate
Course
I'm Shady dealings
I don't want to have you and then it sort of caught up to him
On the message
Switchboards beagle
Kind of fine with defrauding guys who won
I don't I don't I don't think I want these people haven't done laser but
The same time I'm pretty big on non scam
You know when you say you're going to do something you do it as a business
If you're a guy
Google
Who can put a laser on my gun
I'm super vine with it
But I think that he probably gets boost
Credibility
I don't know
Entirely sure if his career as a as a truth-teller overlaps of his career as a gun
Scam artist
I think that something happened
And the
New career
As someone who might end up on Kerry Cassidy show 911
No this is my working Theory
But the timeline of his life
Is such that
He got in trouble
I found a bunch of other stuff
I can't really
There's another guy names
Steve Kelly
Who owns the company called sk9
I am like
If SK
Industries
Right
Kelly
Brisky's spell Kelley
B Simone would be selling Weaponry such a similar business name
Do all Kelly still weapons must if you are a few Kelly who listens the show please send us any
Email gmail.com
And let us know what weapons
So do you make lasers for knives
So this is the preliminary stuff I was able to
Figure out about him
Career
Superfast
Twitter
A strolling
Garcia's
Nevermind
Essentially version of all of Alex Jones
Without the fear of being sued
Steve-O Twitter
Something about how they literally eat your
Instead of just saying like making Ally up about that California law about that decriminalizing
Right
You just as Governor Brown in California wants to give people Aid
Because he's
Secretly gay
Parenthetical
You've been married to a woman for 13 years
Stuff like a Russia Insider article with headlines like
Call Kazarian Jews
To run US foreign policy are the swamp
Where is Alex we'll just sort of hint
Actually come out and say f*** you it's the Jews for Donald Trump
Is against get on record
Steve isn't famous enough to get f***** over
Yeah or it doesn't worry about that
10 followers
Hitmonlee
He says all the same stuff as Ally
With less filter
Boats
Hatred
Of all of the Infowars a JC
People
Alright recently posted an article about how Jerome corsi
The Mossad
All right he hates Craig Sawyer
Fair
Alex himself
Alright weird
He seems to be okay with Alex there's a whole story I need to know
The other thing that I was able to find out is that
Steve Kelly
Well he plays up his CIA credentials
Haha
Hugo one
If it's not the only person
He was one of the main people
When the first people
To come forward publicly and make the argument
The US created
Even the crazy person Nails in every now and again
Created the Power vacuum
You're saying that he actually that he believes America actually uses the shadow wife
Alright alright alright
He would you eat he did so on in interviews
Russia Today
Potato channel in Iran
That's alright alright he made the claim as early as 2014
Immediately made the rounds on the right-wing Bloc
Facebook group
Gerontology
911 group
The Deep ties to Alex Jones
The path
There's an almost 0% chance
But I would believe that Alex
Did not get the narrative
U.s. created Isis
Directly
From Steven Kelly
The same is probably true.
Where does Easter come from
They come from Giant
Flashlight works
How is it
Why God dammit
We just got it
Evil
Look at houses f****** life worked out
Got weirdos who want their guns back backing up your door
You got to keep coming up with new Rod alright
So you're a remote viewer right
Here's his response
A remote viewer
Well you know where all remote be with real skills
The way
You want to do it
You have to ask
If you able to
Okay whatever Chul it is that you need to do the mission that you're doing
You have to ask for the permission first thing you do is ask for permission to do the mission
To be part of the mission
And then you say thank you
And then you say please give me everything I need to complete the mission
Including the protection
And the two wholesome skills and whatever
And so if remote viewing
It's really not that hard to do
Okay
I don't know when he
How to do remote viewing explanation was
What you just got to ask to do it
Home Depot
I don't believe that remote viewing is real so I have trouble with that but I will say
Psychologically
Describing is a really affect
Tool
Cuz like I thinks it's a lot of times we have
Ingrained blockers
In terms of
Productivity
Getting anything done
I mean like
Even in terms of like a motivation
And stuff like that
How to get in shape for you want to exercise
Like that often times does help to create
Some sort of like
You know
Make the Declaration outside of yourself
Create some sort of like a
The mystical experience about please give me the strength
Exercise call Fremont
You go to the Getty Museum
Laa and offering at the Secret Door
Your talkingshit and I was just trying to make a positive out of it
There is a way to
To validate
Experience
Pretending to
There's something valuable in that
I think you can get a lot out of it
Like I've I've experienced and even in the last like
Month or so like the power of
Telling yourself that
You're going to remember
Like if we're meeting for me it's like a very difficult time motivated
Myself do when I wake up in the morning right down my
That belly
Very valuable
Pass towards being able to lucid dream
When I was younger
It's very difficult to find that motivation
I found that it's much easier
If I tell myself
His commitment
Is non verbal commits
Ben is if it were to
Some Divine Authority
I'm going to
Remember my dreams or allow me to remember
I don't think it's the One X
Giving me
Permission to but there's some sort of psychological
Jump
Surrender yourself to a higher power
I don't think there's any I don't I don't think there's
I understand
But I also
I think that's all crazy
Maybe you just haven't
It's better to a power High Enough
Cavers go to the gallery
So
Now we're going to get into
Finally going to get
Thank you
But I should tell you
Listen to something at the
Beginning of this clip that is very Alex Jones
Apposite
Generalization because there's a
Janelle Garcia
Gene memory
Race memory
Yeah there's Jean memory
Cellular memory and then there's also reincarnation so you can have different variations of the stuff
Show me about my brother
For quite some time
My brother got recruitment process when we're drinking Jim somewhere into the process where we were briefed
They realize that Jim was getting free
And it was when
The real quick
Brazos of us briefing
Jimmy
The cavers realize we were briefing Jim
We probably might have just told them
Make no mistake he hasn't
Explain more of what do you mean
But
We had the remote viewer the first remote viewer go down there into the Getty and see what was down there
They didn't know that they knew that happened
Because these guys have
Like one of the first levels that you run into when you go down there is kind of like a Hogwarts
If you will it's it's like a university for
People
Super-Soldiers okay it's a super-soldier university sort of
Magician placard so the whole nine yards all that stuff
And their job is to go do all these
Magical things but at the same time they're also acting as the security they're supposed to prevent people like me or whoever
Amber from going down there
Causing trouble
No
They're not always able to do anything they're certainly able to
To see you but the
They alerted okay so another words when we first met that first
Excursion down there
Almost immediately
Alarm Bells went off and they all knew that this happened
And we were confronted
This is when things got really serious
No it didn't
I don't I don't
If I understand correctly the timeline
Is
They were brief and Jim
Alright
I had a weird thought all right
Another like
S*** we got to remote view this
Yes so they go to the first remote viewer
Which I should say is actually
Because I watched another lecture
Alright
Get down
It's only to the first level
A university very similar to Hogwarts
That trains both super soldiers
Is similar to the movie
Soldier
Black magic
As well as
I should tell you
Of course
The whole nine yards which I think it's actually means every
Everything
Except for that last
So I'm never going to get a first down
At University
I need to be queer
Yeah he's never been to the Getty
Yeah save just had never even been they've just had a remote to go down there
And make stuff up
So I watched this lecture he doesn't need you he's already filled at all I wanted this lecture that he gave about
From 2012
It was from a convention
I might have been carries I don't
I'll say that we had a better audience
Vincent Austin
The turnout was paid
I learned
From that
The first level down when you go in
Cuz you got to get past
Security doors
There's not even a versity according to his lecture in 2012
It's the first level is full of Nazi remote viewers
Were there to stop other remote viewers from get again
Quote
They're not very good at it though he says if he laughed to himself
And the audience
They're not very good
Maybe so f****** uncomfortable
But there's not the remote first level
Now hold on the second level
Don't understand the second level is covered in gold
There
Linear unimaginable depravity goes on it
It's just like it's like bacchanalia is today allowed
That's unfair
Even
Even not the remote viewers deserve laborer very employee you should be allowed to enjoy the bucket
Go to the f****** gold bar
After this point is it real murky
3000 zero
?
Clear elevators
Which I find
Dubious
There's a quote from the gross domestic product of the country goes into building these condos
Hi that's like what what
Condo
Seems like literally everything else that's done would be
Impossible
Well it's weird you think that Medicare Social Security Medicaid makeup
Two-thirds of the
National
It underground chamber condos
So Below the living areas are a bunch of
Train
Let go to the Air Force Base research centers
My favorite part is always the weird
Very specific
Weird detailed destinations
And it's crazy
Crazy lecture
It's actually kind of worth it
If you've ever done stand-up
It's kind of fun to watch because you get to watch a guy who's like
On his homepage
He's in like a f******
UFO Magic
Convention or whatever
Still Bob Bob so hard
View of the audience
Believe him about the 15-20 minute mark
You can just see the energy
Sucked out of the room entirely walking around
No
I got a really impressive
People he's supposed to talk about the Getty
He's only talks about it for maybe like 10 minutes of his
35-40 minute lecture
Most of it's just rambling about how
Things could be better
Did he give
About the gap
He's been there
He says that he has
Bi-Rite
Of the place
But they can't
Sherwin
Because they're copywriter
But he has the
What
Beans videos pictures of the art maybe weakest of Teas
Sir well they're getting checked your week.
The Getty museum is full of Art
What does beer make sense
In front of us
Painting
It's hot
Plays in the room
And then
Control copyright
I thought it was
I thought it was Disney but apparently that's not
Who that's that's enough
Other piece
The physical evidence has no other physical evidence
He pulled out of his pocket
A parking ticket
Fat cells
Some point in 2000
Something
How do you claiming is from before
The museum is open
Like during the day
And that it says emm at means employed
I don't know the DM means employee
I don't know what that I don't give a s***
He also says that it's from 10:30 and that's before the museum open
Cuz he says it opens at 11
According to the internet museum opens at 10 a.m.
So I don't know what that means either
Like I get reelected
Task
Paper
And years old
I don't know it doesn't
Anyway
What it proves is he's a weird dude for carrying that around
You don't need that
No I was I was
I was on board with everything else but up until this point
So
You said this lady which that we've discovered right from other materials
Was the remote viewer down there
Her name is Jeff
The Hogwarts
Her
Shut off all sorts of alarm
Executor has wrote the greatest fanfiction I've ever heard which is
Hogwarts Nazis
He's got Siri
They feared for their lives
What happened instead of trying to kill us they actually this is when they actually tried to recruit us
By this time obviously they realize that Jim was
Was dealing with some people on the outside that were
Trouble
And
People right now and he said no
You want me on your team this is my team these people are my people and if you want me
Why people come with me
Are you following me so far
I'm not sure isn't Jim just being brief
This is a little bit after all that breathing
You saying is that the cavers
Anyways oscopy
Who's involved with the cave
A talented account
So he's because he also his dad was a Mason and got the keys to the kingdom which was a bicycle
Magic
Oh yeah that's
So
Begin the cavers are like
You're working with the weirdo
Dislike
Yeah but they're mine
Do you want me to
You take them
And they're like a controlling the Illuminati
Bargaining power do you think you have an account
This is like that
You have in so many movies
Where is like
You got to bring my nerdy
Friend in right
Text Brandon
CPA
Doesn't happen
The real world
Kills your friend you're in
That was still so they said fine so then they went and went into a recruitment
My brother was me
I'm trying to figure out who it was
I'm supplying with all this information
Anything
Psychic testing in stores
They had something going on
And the first thing they do is they offer a military rank
Are they taking you a rank of State like a major or something like that Air Force Air Force Major that gives out of
They do that so that they've got you
Contractually
Secrets Leavenworth after that
It was sometime after that they found out that it was actually me we were having dinner
When the guy First Financial guy forget he realized it was actually I was alone there looking for it
Told my brother he was a pale Shadow with me which is something he'll never forgive me for
So
Okay this is
Alright also told me
That I would be the one
To destroy them
And at this would be through
And he told me that I was also in a very militaristic mood I was in the gun business I was
Best weapon development
And training and I actually was going to say I had a militia but let's just say I had a lot of young guys under
Uber
Of that nature
Sounds like you got a militia it was an orgy
He's got a lot of
Young guys coming
That is
F******
Scariest
Shitzo
So
There's a lot to unpack their psychological
Perhaps too much
There is
That dude
Is so jealous of his brother
Raising
That's another one of those weird things they always throw in that weird like there's always the weird
Detailed lights
Oh and it goes to the f****** island of Catalina
Also
My brother isn't a psycho
Because me so I don't know why my parents love him more than they do meet and now I'm trying to plug in love you guys
Look at me I've been stealing gun
Psychic
Powers all over the place
Underground cavers who control the Illuminati
Tire world
Are still
Offering
Military rank
In order to avoid
Throwing you in Leavenworth Prison
Seems like it'd be very easy to
Disappear you
Like it wouldn't really are in a case
Yeah there's another grasscity it doesn't matter
No one has ever seen before and that they
I can never go back to
But we're going to put a
There is definitely an in for a penny in for a pound
Reptiles
Area 51
But I've heard never come out
Actually they said they have an underground tunnel to Leavenworth
Says 12 Leavenworth 12 Catalina
Felicity
I thought we were going to attack
A dog whining
It's a little annoying.
Read episode of Lassie
I would I would I would like to unpack that more but at the same time I realized
What
Project Camelot his shity production value
We got them
So I'm in the next clip we get to
Blowing hard
And revealing a very Alex Jones
Mentality
About him
Self
Remember in the
All the times Alex Jones
I could have been one of them
All the time
Steven body that
I'd given up this whole
Elitist
Underground
Masonic
Gods on Earth
Should have tried to save the people on the surface because
Obviously we don't deserve to be treated like
Expendable cattle
You're right what they think of us
So I give it all up for that for everybody else but there is now we're actually winning because as I've said so
If we actually can
Occupied
Open up Pandora's Box
I don't even have to tell you what's down there because once that box gets open
We will have Paradise on Earth
Paradise will have free energy
No pollution
Green food
No more Chemtrails vaccine
You name it
So all of that
Is very much like Alex
Especially the last part
You name it
Yep which is one of Alex's verb
That leads me to believe that it's possible that Steve even listen
Infowars
Hey Hazel
You can
Vaccines very much in line with the Infowars mentality
What technology
Supported it down there
Are you proves that in no way
Like Nikola Tesla or Elon Musk
Nicola
Nikola Tesla
Cuz I don't think anybody really has Tesla
Give you serious
What am I
I feel like you're
Perhaps the least of the issues you should have
Alright
I told you earlier
Shocking similarities
Infowars
Alex Jones
She hates
Infowars people
Like the actual people
In-N-Out Store in these idiots out
Tucson
Trying to make everybody think that
Human trafficking is something to happen
Walking across the sand of the desert
It turns out that the internet
Conspiracy Community is turned on
Now pretty 100% behind the idea that that is a
Diversion
From real child traffic
Picking which I guess
I'm not entirely sure
That because it came up in his bio
He has work
Deck protection
Detail
For like
Hillary Clinton
And so now he is
Sure you are persona non grata
I don't know
I don't know how to feel about that
It's one of those things that I take
I take no pleasure in the
The wrap
Eating each other
Because the ones that survive are tougher
When to con artists go up against each other and one prevails
They get a boosted.
Credibility
For having vanquished
The conman
Amore reinforced conman
I don't know I I wish they'd all shut up
That's not an option it's the Highlanders
Subway
Kill another con man power
Yeah there can be only one who experiences the
And then
I don't remember the app
Actual end of that show or movie
I do
Just reflecting on my
No
Like he's from Egypt
Buddy has a Scottish a
That doesn't make
And why is the music
The Highlander is
I got it
Supposed to be from each
He's supposed to be for me to dude look it up it's bananas
That'll be our next step
Episode but for now
We get a very rare
Saint project
Adam
Death
Kerry Cassidy
Getting into a disagreement
I'm just going to say that
Alien base it's not an alien base is definitely a human-made base Highway
Whatever
However
When you consider
Human
All right this is what's important
Aspect to all of this stuff
That and people ride this is where people get confused because I deserve you earlier today
Deal with the aliens and the
All right here's the
Hear it conspiracy theorist in Cars Getting Coffee
What I want to hear
These
Mark Richards.
Or if they just let them
Gaston like
Tonight Show
Valenwood crushed
Cuz Fallon if Ellen is essentially the mainstream character
That's really all it is
He is there to smile and make you feel like you're the
Rate is very low rent
Exactly you can't hold a candle to Kerry Cassidy
Carrie doesn't this
She's I know she does
She doesn't believe she's the one will
You will admit that perhaps
They are indeed
I'll be goddamned if you say that they're not aliens
No
As this clip goes on
Familiar
Blood libel
I will get into it actually
Jesus.
Uses a really funny word
Connection
Loose
Human
Negative human emotional psychic energy
Right right right
Human
All right this is what's important
Satanic
Aspect to all of this stuff
This is where people get confused because it's just that I didn't interview earlier today and it
What's the deal with the aliens and the
Demon
All right here's the connection
Loose
Human
What is the connection dead
Ruben the alien
Eva diva
It's loose
You're stupid
Freezers not lose
Negative human emotional psychic energy
That's about what they talked about you know they're collecting his babies and they're stealing Schumann
Dollar Store
And torturing them and drink their blood everything else will yeah yeah they do all that but there is something else
Statik selektah
Which is not of this
Level level that Ronnie check the oven higher level
Course
Product
Speed collected from us by the higher-level entities these aliens if you will
Lettuce nutrition
Call the black goo
Product
Ashley product from E-40 density person into this
Realm of the 4D where it is stored and collected
This is the sort of thing people are having a hard time understanding obviously most people are not quite there they're trying to
Extend through understanding things like adrenochrome
They're certainly far from understanding louche
Captain Stanley's
Dude
You know
I love entertaining
And Ed like trying to follow
Follow the thread on that tunic stuff that was a man shooting words out of his mouth and it was
Pathetic and he should be ashamed of
You like to humor stuff to an extent that
Wildly frustrating for me because it's like
I like it it's a point
You got a dog
But this is too far
Search Pro
That was bad
He was clearly scrambling across tonight
Because that's something they don't
Apparently
The caver world
But so what do you know about
I don't know what to do lyrics
It comes from a novel
Book
Robert Monroe
Call Zafar Journey
Lived on and is retained as an idea of negative
Human emotion
Same thing Alex talks about like a
Psychic vampirism
Stuff like that
Got it
Little do they know they can just make people laugh
Be fair this guy is
Creating a Lotto app
Suomi we've gone over the adrenochrome stuff
Before
I'm bored I'm bored
Now I'm excited about Lucia
Can't fourth dimension
What is it
Because I know exactly where that is
But
It's
Because
Non-falsifiable not verifiable stuff it's like there's red
Does a transmitter between our world in
Negative stuff and bring it over there they stockpile in
All right man I watched
We will move on
Cuz we'll get back of the dance
Here in a bit
Where is the third but we'll get back to it here in a second
Cuz we got to talk about.
But it is also
Associated with what we would called demons
And this goes back to Lilith
Which is essentially what we would refer to as the mother of demons who was according to
History is Adam's first wife
Now believe it or not people think they attributed all sorts of activity on Earth to Lucifer while it's not really Lucifer
Actually real
The real quick right
Everybody knows that
The reason that Lilith is
See No Evil
Because she has control over her own sexual
She was nuts
Serviam to Adam
Alita in the Apocrypha
Track
That guy would be like
She's actually the devil
Because she would not be
Women
Cow
What's
To do
Do what they do without
Or don't do what I tell them to do
It's like
What could that be
Super Bowl
Spoiler alert I didn't get a look at him
Donna wormhole
From the Lilith Fair
And
B7 first love affair
But I really liked got their start on me like
Winning local
Getting to be on the side stage
1897 Loop
Lauren Hoffman
Great super-awesome singer-songwriter lady
Awesome female musician
That just you have those
Big-name
Folks
You have no idea where involved with it
Before they were big
It also
Little trivia
Little rules
E97
Yeah the tour
Yeah
Perform on every date other
Then Sarah McLachlan
Wait on the Lilith Fair tour
Royal
Jim the CPA
Incorrect
I did not know that
The cigarette
Ever
She was on the seven
Floor
Brutal song
When you talk about these underground bases this the thing that I really want to get to it
When we go down under the Getty
You don't
There's a point where we stopped
Okay
There we don't go any farther
It's called the bottom
Mmm maybe the day will come when we can go farther but we're not
I don't know anybody has gone past this point
Yes
And this is were really awful point
This is the point where
You're gonna really nasty s***
Yeah
So I don't know what the hell is down there but we talked about aliens yes that's probably where they are they're probably down there below that level
We don't really
Stewartville cavers aren't
Aliens
Turn clear
Demon
What do you say Naruto
Just cuz we got a parts it out a little bit
Is I can't bring myself to imagine the next level
Right I know that I would have to say some rude
What's a really f***** up specifics and I really want to do that
Tina this is where you call it Alex
Cuz Alex
Can come up with your your horrible f****** nightmare scenario your own Alex
Jim was a great
EPA though
Is true
Come by
You just don't see that kind of talent
So in terms of
You do a lot of this by remote viewing if you want to call it. But you disperse going there in person
Did you go there exactly one or did you go there more than one
Do you say go there are you talking about going underground and just visiting the ark
Underground
One time
Am I mistake or if my brother went on a tour with
Who does not have the same psychic powers that I do
The pale Shadow but I just got to let you know my brother
Went on a tour
I don't I don't know
Just to reinforce
Closest we will get to a full-on Kerry Cassidy
No later later okay there we go
Sony remote if you want to call that is such a like
Ascension flight like
You don't know what I
You know what you're not doing what I know of other people
Harry doesn't quite trust remote viewers
Cuz she's kind of being shity
Mmm episode with Courtney Brown
That we did
She was like she
He doesn't think that everybody who remote views
Is telling the truth
Or knows what they're doing
It's a strange
You don't even have physical fake proof
Right right
You might just be making this up
You didn't even bother to take a photo of your TV and redo it
But he's in with Billy
Billy's room anyway
Vivi's cavers
They've been planning
Forever baby thousands
Alder plant
And they know
The day will come that they might get sound out
Ameriplan
This makes me believe
Steve story wailer
You see that's the thing
They've been planning for this
For hundreds of years
Obviously this
What we're dealing with this a
Conspiracy but the people that we're dealing with here
I've been working on this for thousands of years is Audi
Are also equally equally ancient
And they've been planning for first
She stayed one day
When the day comes that we rise up
And confront them that they will destroy everything and try to destroy destroy the bunker but destroy the end
Interesting
Shiplap
Which
First off
Which day was
We talked and thousands years ago
Like biblical like
What are we talking about
Bigbang
Are we talking about when they were created or when they evolved to let you work this out
And if your plan
Includes
We're building this thing to f****** chill and have a good time
But we at the same time as no covered Spa
Eventually the day will come when they will come knocking on our door
If you can see that far in the future you see a future where you don't
Have them
Knock on your door
Baby don't even f******
Because I watched
His lecture about
I have a little bit more
Okay
Here's a quote
About this
There's a book written about 100 years ago
Very very controversial
Throw you in jail Just For Men
Call it book at book there's a chapter with a lion
He says quote
What beer do we have of the blank
None
If we have an awesome weapon the underground
The Metropolitan
He goes on to four leaf clover
Goes on to quote a passage
This passage
Protocols of the Elders of the
No
Yes
OU the big one
What is a
Always
So this is the product this is protocol number 9
He's working office
And what he says blank he's just as he doesn't want to in the room say
Goya cuz that's the word clearly black
Clear
He's talking about in the lecture
But the
You may say that the gullible rise upon us
Arms and hands
If they guess what is going on before the time comes
But in the west we have a
Dance this maneuver
Terror
There's a very stoutest Hearts quail
The underground Metropolitan
Those Subterranean quarters
Before the time comes
Will be driven under all the capitals in from whence those capitals
We'll be blown into the air with their organs
The fact that he says the underground Metropolitan
He references at the end
The organizations in archives I can
It's a little bit later in the
That's a bummer.
A little bit later in the lecture he says this
Messages from the protocols of the Elders of Zion there I said it
I'm not an anti-semite
I have a lot of Jewish French this book was written over 100 years ago
Totally accurate
Sorry for going
Yeah wow he believes
Without any proof a
I do PS4 remote viewing and passenger
Just from the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Trans-fast
It's great it's great
Is f****** crazy just a super-rich to do like I need a bigger space
The kidnapper
Movie with Kevin Spacey Kevin Spacey
Yikes
Now that's what the Jews are planning could be
But
Be
Protocol
What's weird about Pez is that people don't know is that it's all about taken down
Spacey
That's what it's always been about
Spacey 4th Dimension
So the idea is that one
Humanity finds out
Right then
They will blow it up
And then it'll kill all the people
Along with the people down there
If I had thousands of years
And magical abilities
Brake controller
I don't know any of these things
Magic
You can just use Magic
Really the thing about magic is your imagination
And the people who talk the most about him
Magic
And it being real
Sub-Zero imagination when it comes to
You don't need to blow anything up
Just release gas
Or something
So anyway so much better being evil than evil people dance
Because the
Like he's not evil
He's a manipulative liar
Like the evil people in this situation are made up
He's imagining fake evil people that he's working again we can do better than the Shadows
In his mind
Because he's crazy and is a guy who ripped
Hours of our brothers
Ice cream shop go check it out
Make the best ice cream this side of the Mississippi second location open
But I'll tell you what
Psychic powers
Can't compare to your
I don't think David I don't know if he'll ever forgive you percent
I don't think as bility I think it's just a function of memory
Anyway
Yeah the ideas are going to blow it up
But it right excuse
Hear me out
Cuz I feel like they own it
You can't just blow up something in Los Angeles
Without an excuse
This is where Trump comes in
Hold on
This is a real-life drama right now
Dion
Donald Trump's meeting in Indonesia with
And obviously they want 2nd nuclear episode but what's really going on behind the scenes
The CIA was using Kim Jeong hoon and North Korea as the
Excuse
Or a
Scapegoat
For when the time came to blow up the Getty they were going to blame it on North Korean
North Korea submarine
So Donald Trump is basically removing that
And what's what else is happening right now is that not only is he making peace with North Korea so that they can't use that
Excuses are you
Right2know
Precipitation of some sort of event
Of course
I'm getting through channels coming from coming down from the White House actually that
They're actually talking about the Getty right now they're talkin about the nuclear trapdoor at the Getty so
Right so I suspected the reason why we don't have the Marines crashing down the door and the reason why we don't have down
Don't trip out there saying okay what's up with the Getty
Is it they are aware of the nuclear bomb
You know
Uno
The whole bag
So his conception isn't there's a nuclear bomb
If and when
Hitt has Steve and his militia get together
Storm the doors in order to
I don't know get rid of all the evidence of satanic Temple's ground below this
Work even that
Work like in terms of like
Do you know what
Mutually assured
Annihilate
Yeah that's way better
A bad plan mixture between like Watchmen a little bit
Little bit of Lost
I've only watched the first three episodes
Nuclear
Thermonuclear bomb
So wrong course
Which actually works
This timeline lost
He's coming up with his philosophies
There's just so much b*******
Crazy
You know it's like a playhouse so many pundits
Failed
Comedians like they just don't have a sense of humor they don't
They don't get anything
As far as humor creative
Showing up Indies like
Racist b******* tirade
That what they're doing is being like provocative or funny
Like this
Exceeded
And then realized I probably hit my feelings
I still like having fun but I was never
I was never like
A complete failure
In some definition of assail
But I
I am a failed stand up
As already
Yorkie
Good as I get to the world
But I'm not
To my own expectation
Sins of my own experience
Those people like Gavin McInnes
Wright was a failure
He was never funny
On stage
Dave Rubin
Flowey song
To stand up so there we go
The only person who's even close to that world
Who is
Like genuinely
Pretty funny as a stand-up is Rogan
Right he's not even fully in that world
YouTube he's descending quickly into a caver hell
Needs to be much more critical of the
The people he allows on
Oregon needs to
To be better about calling about a couple episodes on recently
There were.
I don't need to tell someone what they should or shouldn't do with right there were good
Sentences on each of those episodes where he was like
I appreciate that if you want
Have these people on
Embarrass them God bless
What do you want
Not again if you like
Showtimes
These guys are like that except field
Like
It's even that far
Fiction
These guys are like people who tried to write fanfiction
And failed it that no one can understand GoPayment not even trying to write fiction like trying to
Write fanfiction about somebody else's stuff because they can't come up with their own ideas
And they realize that they couldn't even come up with their own ideas based off of other people's ID
Which is just like a random ass
Yeah
That gives us a break from Alex Jones everyday
We get now to carry
What about the notion that
Donald Trump has been going around supposedly arresting at least some pedophile
We've already talked about.
Maybe doing
Military trials
Offshore in Navy vessel
And I'm hearing this
So it's not just a rumor
Kind of
Jessica's mobile
Not a river
Multiple people
Also
Even if you had military tribunals
Pretty Rae
Like an international waters
You still got to put them in prison Leavenworth
They're still going to be a record of them somewhere it's not like you can just diss
Hear them or kill them
Can disappear people they said there's no due process you could be in acting
Pedophile
The boat give him a second trial and then kill them
There's no did not look at death penalty
We all feel like maybe there should be
Did this argument doesn't work
No
It only works out it only works
It's like
You believe like
Carrie
Steve dude
These people
Which you've got to prove
Confined with that
You still got to prove it
It's not like the burden of proof is any less in the water
If it's an international waters and probably even more severe cuz now you're under like un
Egypt
You know you're under the Osprey just withdrew from the UN Human Rights
Cancel we can eat whomever we want wherever we want
Amazon that
Great job guys
Everleigh
Expressed her opinion on the old
Is it for him
Tri-form XO
When she says and their fingers world
When she says In that clip what about this
To bring that up
Right she's not waiting for an answer
She's bringing it up and then launches into another thing
She's in favor
Because of the overlap between
Stolen Valor
In the intelligence Community yeah yeah mixed with
Secret space program bulshit
Heavy overlap
In the two about light
About
She's being lied to
Robert David
Steel it has been on her show
I bet he's the one if you don't remember he talked about the children
He's been on Project Camelot
Told her about
Working towards
So whatever behind as there are exist
In both worlds
Course and I don't know if they're all the
People but
This Probably sounds
So
Boy I tell you what
Boy I tell you
Earlier that
Before the night
Before the cock crowed three times
Before Paul denies our Lord
Makes a Bigfoot
And that is Terry
Brings up Mark Richards
No
It seems like they do the murderer
Jesse's not impressed
I guess you might know about my interviews with Captain Mark Richards program
Time
And I go out to
Add to interview women prison
And he's talking about these you know
They are
Going to try to arrest
Usher
And so on but they're never going to get that. The highest level
I know what I have to say about that
And there's at you know there's Draco involved as well because this is a big war
Not just into one level
I want to play that 300
Draco bout to compile of it I got perfect I noticed that but I f******
Tim forgot it
Go fuc yourself
You wonder what I have to say about that yes and there is a Graco involved
As well because this is a big war
Another level
And yeah and I know but let me finish just so I can paint the picture a little bit more
Sylveon
And rescuing day did rescue a number of the object keys
What they said happened was the next night they were abducted Again by the gray
They could be lying s*** but you know I know
So you know how do you look at this
You know you're at your spot
Most people are not even close to being to this level let alone physics
Yes it's
Petition to get the military to
To storm
And Terry takes issue with the idea of like why do you have a petition
What's that going to do
In the background argument
Yeah but hold on
We're going to talk more about that
The petition is a finger
Waiting at the latch
On Pandora's Box
How far is the secret space program and in all this is concerning
Its relationship to what's going on but Underground
It's the same people
Okay it's the Third Reich the Third Reich is very much involved we have the we have everything is going on in agar
Catherine all that people people don't have any clue as to that we can't begin to talk about that because most people listen
Way over their head
Oh s*** you said
Chinese bus
Oh no.
Right which is not
Right but I mean
Haven't we
Can't we get past that are we at the fourth-ranked at least now the problem is.
Fail
Who problem is agartha
In a number of contacts.
Word to mean number
Generally it could be used as a
Feeling term for like the Garden of Eden
In some weird internet can
Conspiracy world
Did not know that
But something along the lines of like a mythical city like El Dorado
In the same
And somewhere else
Because he's mentioned the Third Reich
I unfortunately know that 100%
He believes
Hollow Earth theory
Because that
Is very specifically
I believe
They come from all of these balls in the air how do you have the time to believe in
All of this
Can't you also just believe that likes integrated a lot of
There's a 5-hour video you guys can watch online if you want to about the
I watched it because I
Used to work at Groupon
Wait did you just watch
Not even that
That's literally the first soundtrack
Not vaguely once I don't know which one
But it's there
So we believe in this
Way back in the day Atlanta
Stephen Libera
Existed highly technological
Wonderful
The story it could be that the two got into a war
They started experimenting
And they blew themselves up
That is the plot to Disney's
Right it's also a lot of the mythology that comes down from like Casey's on the
Theosophist
I'm not going to lie to you
Love The Frighteners
Huge fan of Back to the Future
But
Man
Michael j.fox
Atlantis was incredible
I mean time is shown
Back to the Future
Not going to get that argument now
So as the theory goes that
Survivors of Atlanta
Just being highly evolved
Slide to the interior of the Earth
Quarantine order to
Guest help
Humanity continue to evolve
The remainders of it
Just the people
The highly evolved
We have either like
Generally
Are very
Weird
440 warring faction
I don't
Want to come
Continue once you start saying they split
Why what
Fine
Continue
I'm going to bring this backed out
Warring faction
The Shambhala and agartha
Which are the rec
Maybe two groups
That's true that like one of them's the Templars and one is Mason another picture
Do schools
Better faking to be at war with each other throughout the Universe.
Sure why not
Search through through there.
Target
Doesn't seem hard they're rooted in the same group but used
Appearance of
Kind of exactly what Alex
Globo's
Who was on the side of an ox
He was referring to
According to this entire mythology there is like
Realize is a lot of this comes down
From people who have channeled alien
And stuff like that a lot of it comes down from like
Very discredit
Scholars
In the same way that Alex misrepresents
Primary sources
They do some
Some of the same
But
There's no solid evidence
Sometimes both
Admire
Your
Knowledge
Vista
I'm literally
At a place now where I am
Astonished by how much you know about this
God damn it you don't need to know this stuff life goes on no need to know about
So there's no evidence of this at all
In terms of real thing
Proponent behind
Humane talking
Pinheads
Is Erich von daniken
He is er always Bond
Guy
I love this
Was Carl Sagan quote about Erik von detten
Book is called Chariots of
Of the Gods
A lot of it is mistranslation
Like Sumerian
He had no knowledge of
You making giant Tucson
Experts in Sumerian
Can
Translated
Perfectly right
I don't know it
Perhaps
But Carl taken
To say about his
That rating is careless is Von daniken
Sisters were dummy
Should be should be so popular
The silver commentary on the credulous method
Despair of our time
I also hope
Continuing popularity of books like
Chariots of the Gods in high school
In college
Logic courses
His object lessons in
Sloppy think
I know no recent books
So riddled with logical and factual errors as the works of Eric
It passed Works Von daniken has referred to the
Quote book of
Dzyan
Which does not exist
That seems like a big sticking point is referenced
It's a figment of Helena blavatsky
He's imagination
And only exist in quote her astral Realm
Round of how the Necronomicon of the Mad Arab Abdul alhazred only existed
Lovecraft's fiction for L Ron Hubbard's Excalibur
Real
As a piece of evidence
In a lot of his work
Just because
He is
Fairies
Central to this
World this
Is Ancient Aliens specifically V the hollow Earth version of
You need to really
Like
Equally like
Discreditable
Is really like almost
0 is like
He's at that Pappy of the mall
So I want I took a little bit of time to look at it
Is the dispensary event
Yeah perhaps I don't
I don't know like that's the thing about him
Is I am not entirely sure that he necessarily
Has the same like
I'm not a literal Pez dispenser
The protocols of the Elders of Zion defense all of this b*******
From that store
Is that all of this
Yeah
So
And stuff
Particular seems to be router out of disbelief.
Who created anything
Great
These tribal cultures
People like Erik von daniken
Whenever they
Surprising
Critiques of him
He just
He said
To just quote ignore the realities of our ancestors
They constitute the ultimate in racism
He belittles the abilities and
Ingenuity
As a whole
Before writing Chariots of the Gods
Done time in Egypt
Prison for fraud and embezzlement
Course when he finished the manuscript he had a hard time
I'm selling it
Because people like now
You found a publishing house that as well
Put it out
Completely rewrite the book
Okay
So
They are this is the producer meeting
Reggae
Listen I'm your literary
I've got you
This amazing day
8 is
Going to be
We're going to give you
60%
Of the proceeds
Alright
We love
It's great
You are
Amazing
We have somebody rewrite
Cornell said now
Much bigger
Successful
But course
So he had to have it Rewritten
His book was Rewritten
Under the pseudonym
Wilhelm rubber store
No
I wasn't that b*******
No it's probably because odermann was a Nazi writer / filmmaker which is code for propaganda
Great he was a Nazi
You did not get paid
It always comes back to its
What is wrong with you
I don't know if his theories were asked
Actually like Heating
Jews necessarily it certainly invalidates a lot of trouble people
But it is
Interesting that the guy who rewrote it was a Nazi propaganda
So a book
Published
Super fraud
Having falsified Hotel records in credit rep
$3,000
Over a. Of 12 Years
He unsuccessfully
He unsuccessfully entered a plea of nullity
On the ground
Another credit Institution
For failing to adequately research his reference
It's a good argument
13th of February 9th
70s
The three and a half years in prison
Wichita book God's from outer space
Also
I have one more thing I want to read
I hate to read straight from Wikipedia
There's a lot of respect them generally as a source
You can find the the backing evidence
I didn't want to rewrite it cuz it's
It's just
Dead on fantastic
So this is another
Damning indictment
Sew-in gold of the Gods
Which is another one
Cold
Is a lot of things that's a sequel to
What's it called
What was the first product
The gods was the first one Gods from outer space as I believe his
His follow-up
Call
But he got way wrong and then there's like
Describes an expedition that he undertook through man-made tunnels Within
Riverdale has tires
Natural cases
System in Ecuador
He reported seeing Mounds
Goldstream
Statues in the library
Containing metal tablet
Considered to be
Evidence of ancient
Extraterrestrial visitation
No other explanation
A local priest father
Krispies
A collection of gold
Extraterrestrial route
Lexie said with special permission from the Vatican
Love it
Walter Spiegel
No Expedition
Description
Have the photos in the book had been
During the night
During the 1974 interview with the artifact in the tunnel
Pretty embellished some aspects of the story to make it more interesting
Call Beloved
Make it Aki mazing got to get people that you got to give a little bit of a lizard that like
I don't know what you got to put a little bit in there
Sell it
In German we say a writer if
She's not writing cure science
German
And that's what I have.
Four years later he admitted he'd never been inside Cueva de like fry
German for dramatic surge
A geologist found no evidence of artificial tunnels in the area
Father crespi is gold artifact
According to an archaeologist
Consulted by Christina were mostly brass imitation sold locally is
Tourist souvenirs Lovett Lovett
Love it
Let's
Huge fan of every story that begin
A local priest found
I know we probably have gone too far down a Devon
Second hole but whenever I hear him say agartha that is like that is a big red flags
Especially in the context
Text of Nazi
Because I know he means hollow Earth
You mean
This version
Yeah there are those words that like I know what that means in this world
Because I spent time on this message
I've studied this
Stupidity so much
Did I know
Where is just roll off your back or you might be
Be confused by it
I had no idea it's
Play never have occurred
To me that there was a hole
Like that's like that's the interesting thing about this
This world that we
We live in and Wyatt
It's awesome that you
Spent way too much yourself
Through through the
Is
So many of these aside
Some of these little like tossed off factoids
Are like me at like in my world I would just go
But with the knowledge that you have it's like
No that's not more b******* that's b******* that points to the
Point to this b*******
And that b*******
Encapsulate the entire whites
It always comes back to white supremacy
Mercury Lego
Next to the other word probably
No I can't
Well it's it's it's like
Like if I could talk for another hour
Privileged knowledge of the crazy
Yeah
To say that crazy
Privileged knowledge
Oh weird
Humanity
Because most people don't get
Because they never put the time and like watching
Video
Right don't find someone who is
Uno's
This guy is out of his Sherpa of b*******
Mountain
And you show us
Why
It smells bad
Infowars LLC
No kidding
So at this point they're all the same f****** Mountain
Already
Steve
Is made a full pot
Emmett he has said draco's
That's a
Mark Richards a little bit
Course
Here's what I
I hate that I'm saying
Cuz I feel like it might come off as misogynist
And I don't mean it
Edsby
But I think he's in love with
Because the way she is so defensive
See that now that I don't think
People generally are unless Road
Do you know it doesn't
In a way that is beyond a professional
You could just be like hold on what
Yeah yeah
Anyone else challenges
He's a very different
He
Their interviews if he is like
Will this guy said some dumb s*** she's like
He said this guy said some dumb s*** so I believe him
She is interviewing
Says bad words
She goes ape contradict
Hey Ya
Pacific time
Innocent why would I say
Spike your mark Richards doesn't understand it's not yes they're not going to give up
They will blow everything up before they give up
Ashley I would say he understands more than almost any human I've met on the planet
By virtue of the fact that he's dealt face
Forgot years and so did his father
Aside from that
You know I appreciate your approach
I will say that there is another level at already
Already it's like
You don't
You were disrespecting
My main guy
From
Before this like an interview
I respect your position by
What sets the
Movie Pitch meeting
That
I respect what you're trying to do
Which
Means goodbye.
For sure
This guy named Eddie page
Do is got documented evidence
Showing that he's a group of 33 Pleiadians that were brought here
And I met with the president work for the CIA we're guarded by the CIA
Their entire upbringing and
That has just entered our
I don't see car atmosphere but very close
From the space station
AnnaLynne
Mothership so it's checking on to it and
I think I can't remember the exact
Measurements black something like 18 MI
I am. Tori things so he said there's more on the way and he
It's interesting because I'm having them on the show
I think it's tomorrow afternoon
I'm having a bath
And I'm just giving you this heads up because it's interesting
Question is saying that the
Contacting the Pleiades are basically
Sort of
They are in a brought Jesus they were
Original genome human genome
Right
Prometheus
Ridley Scott
Not asbestos
I still think it's a lot more
Sing the people gave it credit for
Idris Elba
Fantastic
Anyways
Reality
Clips not done but
I do think there's a remarkable moment there where she like
Whether this is real or not we could talk about another time would you like to talk about
The only thing you should ever be talkin about right
Time for 8
Cuz it was a whole other interview that
Boy
You give me some
Red flags to
All of his information comes
Like a psychologist
Directions to General
Sarah whenever so many children
People f******
Locked up
He supposedly was in Vietnam
Morningsave
He was in the aliens
Is any thought it was like 5 minutes
Later but it was 11 days that he'd spent on an alien ship
Batman Batman they had to regress a
Patty
Miles away
It a different uniform or some s*** right
Doing drugs in Vietnam
I don't know I don't know it's true
Conversation but
The question is is that they're saying there's no way that we can fight
The Draco
And when and when and which out sort of their help
And
Mark Richards this thing is I know this is
But you know I talked to a lot of people Steven
And Richards is saying
He deals with
Originally came from the dinosaurs in the Drake alignment
Sixty-five million years or more ago
You are working with our military
And this isn't he goes into great detail about this and so
He's saying that they are offering their help in other words we're in a situation where yes we have
Some tool
To fight
These beings
Earth is been a playground for these beings now for quite a number of Tiana and
You know it's it's kind of I think it you know I appreciate your approach but I think yeah let's not be simplistic about
There's a lot today not that many of them out there
It's not that there's a lot more of us
Okay this is why they want to kill us off so
So badly because this this whole idea of seven billion humans
It's really dangerous
You know it only takes like four thousand humans to equal the power of a hydrogen bomb
Doesn't make sense at all
I don't know what that means
What does that even mean
And kinetic energy that's like from all of our blood vessels in all of the movement
That's what the 4,000 people made of antimatter that touch 4000
That is not the case if you have like an atom of matter versus answer
It's a hundred percent energy
But that there's
Right
Exactly
Exact
But like
Carrie is
Shutting down
Sick of it
You don't respect Mark Richard Ray
I don't want to talk to you
Right
Think
Steve Fields at
Forget his punches
Rhys wants to get his points
He is also kind of
Checked out
Navigate into
Something that really scares me
I told you earlier this episode that I have feelings
Yes about this guy
We've gone through a lot of different feelings about the clear when I was
Laying out that you liked
People off with a gun
But I'm actually the next couple clips
Illustrate that I'm actually
Scared of this guy
The only people who are on Project Camelot like Richards killed a guy
And all that
I'm not scared of him
Isn't Vacaville prison
I'm not really scared I don't think you do it again
I think he killed the guy under was an accessory of the murder
On a certain circumstances
Yeah I don't think it necessarily
He's a really scary dude right
Steve Kelly I think it is a f******
Scary dude
Beginning of this clip
In the next clip
Play that out
We already know that you may or may not have been running
Militia
Here's what right here's what he's doing
And we're waking up that's the thing is like the stuff that we're doing a little Jedi Army okay
Okay right now I don't know how many there are
Nope but it was stuff that we do
We just a little tiny group of people gosh
You know I'm thinking about what's going to happen when I've got
200 million Jedi
I don't give a damn
You know what this is thing
For 25 million years
The dracko the Anunnaki and the gray have been running amok and destroying everything is screwing up for everybody
Universe and that's over
And where
Us humans that maybe the hybrids that were created by all these guys I don't care
If you're a gray hybrid and Anunnaki hybrid or or a reptile hybrid
We're still on humans
And we're brothers and we're going to work together and guess what the Creator put us here
Tequila
Toastmasters the slaves arising up is like 80 all over again
First
Then all the grace on the moon and then when the next time they brew rolls around and we get a visit by the Anunnaki ring to take them
And we have a lot of help out there
I'll tell you
You talk about Pleiadians my God
The Playdium could even get into the Getty until we open
The door
So I don't know what the hell I'm not sure where you're getting that information
What do you want
Play me just when you go down there to the Getty and you're getting ready to open the door you got all these entities that have been there for 100 million
And you're sitting there waiting behind you
Sure yes there's a lot of help out there we have a big old cheering section and there's a lot of you see this the thing
All these densities
They don't work together until
They work together
And it wasn't until our reality merged with the reality of these higher levels than any even became
Reality for them to even get involved in
Sitting out there on the outskirts
They couldn't even get involved in the stop until we simple third density humans
Allowed it to come into our brains and make it reality because it's not it wasn't even part of the Matrix until it was in our
That's not the information I have
Yeah okay well I'll let you know what resonates is what resonates and I'm sorry you have to go back in history
Farther than that and I appreciate your approach
By the way six dimension
So and then maybe more than that.
Is a function of time
Density is what we use density as a function and dimensions do you have to deal with
They squabble
This is this is like tuna
Arguing
Whether or not
Star Wars and
Lord of the Rings happened at the same time
Yeah like this is bananas both of you are talking about made up s***
None of this right why are you pulling out 6
Yeah it's pretty crazy
Densities
All right what do you know about density
I don't know s*** about that
Moving outside
It's a measurement
2 something
So it's hard to say definitively that this is the exact
Steve is wrong
Cities from
But I would bet almost
Everything
Is where he's drawing
On October
In October 2008
The user on the message board above tops
This person claimed to be a part of the Illuminati
Whose personal responsibility was to make him
Himself available
A question
People have
In order to fulfill the requirement
People have free will
This is exactly the same as ours
Using lesser Magic
Tell you what they're doing before they do it
Right so you have this message
Be any question
I'm not going to tell you
But you're at you can ask me any question
It's my responsibility
It's something the Illuminati Bloodlines have to do from time to time
Fill Our obligation
Songs of question
And it's honestly really satisfying
As far as
Very clear roleplay
He sets of rules ahead of time like quote I will decide whether or not I will
Two or permitted to a
Your question
If your question is not answered it
Is either because I cannot.
Disclosing her because I can
Was lacking in one or more of the following
Respect
Intelligence
Decency or that it was otherwise Unworthy of being dignified with a response
Preclude pretty much
Answering
I just didn't want to
Seems like it everything is cryptic enough
SB meaning
Like
Super bloodline
They control everything
However at one point
The poster goes by Hidden Hand
Specific
Pacific prediction
And to predict
Send are not good
There will be a new currency by the end of 2000
Circles as the latest nailed it
The other predictions
Specifically that said realshit
Quotes
Francisco and Damascus will be on
End of 2010
Possibly even sooner
So this person was super way off
This up because the entire thing was largely based
Around the idea of
Different dance
And how There's a Great Harvest
Which spoiler alert
Was December
21st
Yes the Noonday winter solstice son of December 21st 2012 is
The time when the lord of the Harvest
She'll return
You might know him as Nibiru
In preparation
Nonsense
Course there's also a bust
Is work is this
I had to write this down because I could explain this
Probably take me I'm already past
Is pretty heavily derived from Gnostic ideas
Where there's one that's the root of every
Right from everything flows
I'm going to accept that
Alright
Introduced in
In terms of the internet
Experiencing
Itself as with free will it would mess
Sincerely desire to experience itself
Externally in this division must
Bmac
To make his wildly simplified a ton of Illusion
The created
Of different levels
Can experience different aspects of the infinite one
That makes perfect
It doesn't but I think
Simplest way to explain
Usher
So these differently level delusions are called Dance
I turned the poster ends up using
Time
Throughout the dialogue
That happened
Course we are said to be in the third density
With the first density you being just a cheap and conscious
. just whatever consciousness
You're you're alive and conscious rappers
State of conscious
Where your conscious of be
Sure and then that evolved
To the third when the consciousness
Becomes aware of its separate this from
Which is to say
The infinite one
Sure when you reach
Absorb
Unity of the internet
Sure however
When You Reach
The 6th
You have the option
Either progress
Ordered to send to help the lower levels evolve
I am going to
Use one of these on your back
All of this
Explain
May I have the more you talk about it the less I'm interested I have to get through this
Nuggets or details about what densities are a little thin
But the fourth density
Search was the density of love the density of wisdom and Light
Density of unity
That's what that means you just get to make up whatever you want to believe me
So
Is I'm positive that he's getting
These ideas from
Because
Have you overlap right because
In his lecture
He literally says that we need eight
51% grade in the
Other side of things over the past
To the next level
Which is taken
Exactly
In order to get to the next density needed
In order to
You get to the next
Have to be
In service
Two others
Then you go to A+ level
To self you go to a negative
Selfishness versus
The entire thing is basically about this this
Rationalization of
The idea of the Illuminati
These people
Who need to make
Very serious
Evil decisions in order to make sure
They go to the
The 4th Dental
Under the
Negative
Version
So they have to be super
In order to go to the next level which is good for everyone else does
Cuz it helps them
Work off their karmic debt
Right it's a load of all right
Bright so I've gone blind
It's all the things that you said
I've made me go blind
It's a hundred percent what are you talkin about
Ateez in
I understand you like why would I even know you're going blind
Mad that I
When I see you about that is like
Complex
Ridiculous
Load of nonsense thrown together
As though it made
Any sense
At all
I'm not you're arguing that it makes sense but I'm arguing with that
A hundred percent I know this
By the Erich von daniken version
Now it's the same thing I can tell you he's getting that
From this
Yeah
You making it suck also spoiler alert
Can handle that
Did the Earth is hollow and
Yes definite
It's important for me to point out
Internet hoax
Is almost
Certainly riff
From what's known as the Rob
Material or the law of one
It's basically another in a long line of
Channel documents alien speaking through
We talked about
Underpants episode
Yeah the reason I just
Is being like the raw material is being where he gets it from
Is because
Steve got his II
That book came out
The raw stuff came out
The 1980s
Yeah Hidden Hand popped up into
Cuz I'm one of the gun sites that I want
There's this review from
Yeah
Though I eventually got what I ordered I had already written it off as loss
Because I took a took close to
6 months
Remember correctly
He wouldn't return calls and I filed reports everywhere local cops even knocked on his door and spoke with him
And I was talking with ATF about him as well
When he did what he did send
Enclose the business card
The company spoke to
I made some comment about me
About 2,000
He got reported
ATF
Raspbian
Fraudulent
Sale guy
Diversified portfolio Illuminati
Inside Iran
Just ripped off stuff that you'd found on message boards
And the internet
Turned it into entire world
Complete
That is what I believe
The things that I know
Now
Here is why you need
Need to be super afraid of
You talk about being okay this is the thing okay you know you know about all the super soldier
I know you people know about that everything
Can I have this entity
That we referred to as Rambo
And Rambo is
Toxic waste
Okay and
He pretty much will do anything I want
But one of the reasons why these guys won't touch me I think
I can get away with these things
I don't know if he's met Rambo you'll know what I'm talking about I'm sure that people listening right now that have been trampled
Call Cherian OU
Ever meet Rambo
I know not to my knowledge that sounds like a you know a discarnate entity
He's my altar
Okay
Yeah I don't know what he is exactly
But he's very active on this plane
And
I like my bodyguard I guess something like that I don't know what you call him but he's been very active lately so
That to me sounds like
I dissociate
Hurt people
Rambo Florida that's a multiple personality kind of b*******
Multiple personalities
Please doesn't exist
Dissociative
And the fact that he's aware of it leads me to believe it's not so
Siri
Other alternatives
Involved
Operation
This f****** scary
The idea that he used to have a militia and now calls it a Jedi
It's f******
Soap.
It's so
Such a mess because I know I know how people work
I mean eight look if
If
Did the same thing
I'm not into it
Call themselves
Be there we go now we have a question
We have a conversation
So
You know he loved to sell gun
But it turns out there's one weapon
Any other weapon
I take issue
Correct
And I'll tell you and you talk to any of these
Super soldiers that they're the real deal and I'll tell you the same damn thing
It doesn't matter what you doing up again
All you got to do is say Jesus Christ in your dead
It's so easy sounds
Right I do that time and time again
That's it
You go up against some monster they think they're so tough
Real quick
The power of Christ
Compels you
At this point
Carrie is so checked out that he's just rambling to get like trying to end the show
You're not coming past me you're nothing you're nothing and all you guys don't even have to
I don't know what hit them
This is the saddest thing I've ever heard we all do it
We all do it
So this is not religion but that's what we do
Sure that's how it's done
Sure okay
She's so checked
She's like trying this is maybe five
Minutes into her life
Trying to end
Plug
Plugs plugs his Twitter
And we
Okay start I know you
Questions about that
Here is where we get into
Not going to
But you have a petition
What's the simple way to find this stuff
Well
If that's the thing about the White House petition patient it won't even really show up on the page until we got at least 200
50 signatures so
Best way to find a courses to
It's just to do a Google search with my name
Under 200
Destroy the demon
He just sad
I just got sad don't even Saturn
Radio show called truthcatradio
Radio show
How can you have a radio show if you can get 200
They have three.
Okay
I guess maybe we shouldn't be evil
No
It seems it seems
Bond in terms of what
You can lie about but if you actually get
Do you like you've got this fundraising
3 people who have signed up for you
He spits all this vitriolic s*** on Twitter
Right not like
It's not like he's doing much better on that front
You see like that guy that guy who was on Infowars is the example I always
Liking you starting
For wagon
Just wright
$300
Donations
4 months
Everything is so artist
Inflated
Is it easy
To get
The views on your videos
If you name them
Space proof of
Rat River
SEO you're able to drive traffic
You can have twenty thousand people watching
Your video
What is that train
Translate to s***
Maybe
Still be good but
Get better.
That's the real Jess
Unfortunately
Evil people are just better in SEO than what it is
They're better than manipulation
Stop right unfortunately
Like
Real a keystone aspect
I am so we're not good
Not bad words
You win maybe that help
For sure anyway does bring them to the end of time
Kelly
On a project
If you have a ride if you could put a laser on a knife
You would have sa Industries
As well
Sincerely wish that
Well I was talking about
Stop
Density of bums me out like when you start talking about levels of density
I get
Angry
I don't like this.
Because if you pull out dimensions
That's fine we can have a fun talk about
That's the issue
Science app with all science fiction where it's like
Dimensional like Shore Fine it doesn't actually mean it
We start talking about like 50
Density bulshit
Talking nonsense
It doesn't have a thousand year
Science fiction history behind
No but it is a
At least 20-year b******* history behind
Extra
Because it hit on.
All the words
Your wheelhouse
I could have got another couple hours honestly
Tight in terms of
6 hours later
Just all the s*** I know about this
I know I know
But the moment we got into Atlanta stuff I was like s*** Dan's going to talk first
You did you did an amazing job
If there was a Project Camelot up so that I can find where someone is like
Hey
The
Or something like that
Block off a hole
I got you
And we got to get a handle
But
2 hours
We got a weirdo hard Reese
Some stuff and one of those things as we've done a very terrible job
I'm getting back to the
Please time travel
So yeah so I'm going to go priority
Yam forward public apology to
Particular to do
Who
Time travel episode those will be coming soon
Yeah
And
Back
Everything is
Forward and wonderful
If you want to check out our website
Dollartree.com
Go to Facebook
Is right
Google just released a new podcast app probably find
I don't know how to do that
I've no idea
Anyways there I believe
Cut that out
He can absolutely go find some minor one
What are you got Tanner
No no
For all of your massive lies
Still fun
Appreciate some of them
The scope of them
We can still go fuc
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color