Alexandra Thurston color
Break up with Alex
Dance if you were to wear a jacket
Perhaps
The single most
Possibly wear
It would be
Showing up
Ferrari
With the t-shirt that says
I don't know anything about Alex
The realities of the world rehab
This is not working out I know a lot about
Good but before we do that I would like to spend that video.
Just to give away a couple
Giving them away
Refrigerator
First
I'm a policy wonk
I guess when I was like 6 years old
Name was William
What is older brother's name
Assume it's the two of them I don't know I would assume a text
Never actually listen to the show Buffet
Very common name
Common Man
Possible
What we're doing is I started listening to a little bit of modern
And I said I said goodbye
Nope
Interview with a guy named
The amazing Jason I believe
Alright I was like oh my God is that was interviewing magicians
It's not like Gallagher
Slash
Maga African American
YouTube
As I can. This isn't a bummer
No that's what I'm saying there's a lot going on I don't want none of it
I was really disappointed
Expect it's just
I don't want to do it
No I don't want to talk about his perspective on the present
Perspective is kill non-whites
Going in there are time travel
Wilma Jean
One of our
What about daughters who donated on the time travel level
We'd appreciate it
Today we are fulfilling
The Rick Ross
Prosthetic
11th 2013
Any idea why we might be going
June 11th 2013 so that's a years after Obama was re-elected
And wait wait hold on
Re-elected
I think I might be living in the alternate reality where life isn't
Here's a clue of what we're going to be
On the show
I agree
Good
You nailed it
Terms of public opinion
About him
I don't think I want to tell you why
This date was chosen
Use it you just rather let it unfold in front of me
I think I think you do
Pretty cool you're pretty quick
I'm not sure
This is a good choice
All right here's where we start
We are going to be
Wow it is good Lord willing
Austin Texas by the grace of God I was able to successfully
Adverb
Against
He is just scored the biggest refrigerator
Forever against everybody
Personal record
The interview
Into
2011 that was June 9th
Turn on BBC Sunday show
10th and then we have the 11
Just as a refresher for everyone who doesn't remember
This moment did Alex Jones
History here is a clip
Alex being a f*** her show
Yes I mean
At the time you discovered
But it leaves me with a shoot question
The New World Order
It's full of criminals
Is full of criminals at cetera
Poots
Omarosa happy to learn crusader
How come
Play don't exist
You'll part of the controls
I tried to put
The New York Times
Threatening
And you better take it serious cuz you were just talking to your dad was in the hospital
I'm here to testify that your head was not cut off
A little bit
Tell him to shut up and just
Interview.
Screaming over them as they end the show
The guy the host of the show
You are the worst gas I've ever had he have an idiot on the program
Came out and said that as soon as
Showing up
Went back to normal
Dan started
Oh that right
Alex
His feelings on it
The victory over Bilderberg
I don't know as there's not a lot more
In this episode the rear lights
I said that but he could be reference
This episode is probably you could say about TSA
Aspire
Sort of
Okay
I'd like is the TSA the transportation do you know why I got confused
You're right you're right
Add insult to injury
From
What is way back from English
Planes a lot about both of them
Bored with Snowden
He's mad that other people are
And then
Pencil
Inordinate amount of time on this episode talking about like
Waze
Do you can block
The NSA spying
On you and like try and create
Right problems right
Track really well but
By the weather today
Are traveling all this with terrorists terms online
Ladies and gentlemen
The latest patent
Tell Yukon a congressman
That will give them so many headaches talk about how you're a whistleblower
Stop at Aerotek
They're there to make sure the terrorist attack
Talk about making sure we stopped are
That's like I got two seconds left till break
Okay we're at already committed to laughing a little bit
Humans do this
Human run
I don't care about that strategy
At what point did you just start saying human laughter instead of
Human laughter or not following what he says
He's basically saying just talk about patents in front of your washing machine or your toaster
Listening to you and Alexa
Right you just say I'm going to stop a terrorist attack on the Block
So they have trackers
That is obvious
But hackers
Flooding the internet with terrorism words
That like if you could give enough. Leaves it would overwhelm the software you could just
Constantly be writing stuff about bombs or IEDs like that
They've there was a belief
But you could trick
Wild goose chase
For the NSA to make it worth their time
Or not like Finance
Actually viable to use
The system it said it was already
And that it did not work because it was already flooded with too much of
Monitoring the domestic Communications of the entire country
So much information there that you can't possibly find a needle
If you want to find something
You know where to look
Of course but like
The reasonable
Response for someone to have like I just
The first thought
Right kind of
What set off every alarm
But I don't know Alex is a toasters
We're going to stop terrorism
You're not that brave
You and me toaster
Lobotomy
Perception is a little screwy
And I think
He's doing his listeners
The disservice by misrepresent
What
I'd come out about
But
One of the reasons I believe that you've misrepresented
Is because I don't think he
Reality
As evidenced by the next clip
He talks about going through the TSA line
I would he's describing
Is a very positive encounter with some
I hear this
I hear this description and I will say that I all I hear is a TSA agent
Being polite
Courteous
Maybe even going above and beyond their responsibilities Alex feels like he's being attacked
Super thin soup
Just like our government is caught shipping in the majority of Narcotics
Four Points
I said wow you're really on power strip
Do you know who I am if she was persecuting me
Why do you think you need to get a new one
There's something wrong with this one
She just sits there staring at me was like
She's Janet Reno type
I hear there's that mean
I don't know I don't care here there is essentialism
You know
I'll get a new one
Cuz that's exactly what I heard is really nice
Aspire like once every 10 years
You might want to think about getting a new one
New one before it expires then the whole process is going to have to go through afterwards
You could say a Power Trip like Reno
Right now I don't even understand why
Even even if
Call Leanne maliciously
In the most possible way you can
Power Trip
You clearly let him use this one
Stupid
And that is that like
She said that you need
To get a new one today
Expires in a year-and-a-half
Do you know who I am
Because I thought she was
Computed wherever you go
Now here's my work
Alex Jones doesn't fly internationally all that
News very few opportunities to
To get his own /
Personal story about being harassed
TSA agent
Costumes
People make the most out of it whenever it happened something like this
Superflight he's got it like
See what I can do with it
See if I could change your tone just exactly
Every time Alex is taking an international flight I imagine about
Him it's his version of being like
Really I have to take my shoes off because one guy put a bomb in there one time during years ago like he's
He's just bitching about it
What is jealous of people who actually get singled out
And he wants his own claim to victim
He doesn't have 10 my God she was so considerate to me
It is I was a victim
I was such a
I have the worst
TSA experiment or experience I had was coming back from London
And I was almost home
I was almost home I was right to the very last
I do hair and this f****** guy it's like 8 in the morning I've been on the plane for 9 hours
I got my headphones in clearly I can
Can't see straight
And this guy was just a f****** dick to me the whole time
Would not
F****** I just wanted to try and hand him
Then the f****** ID and he's like slapping always like headphone
Get your headphones
Screaming at a little road
Worst
It was 50/50 on me
And this was a very polite and erection
Absolutely
02b
This is not the totalitarian
Popping all over you in terms of
You make a fair point
Emina pilot walks over
Add
It was incredible
This is very weak
Do people
Very vague
And like
Alright
Sure maybe they
Will be nice if they were nice
What
They need that you
Process like a thousand people every hour something about bored
Of court and some of those people are way bigger assholes than absolutely kind of customer service
Every situation you know assholes about
Let alone one
Fraught with anxiety over travel airport
Tensions were high at airport
Cuz lot of people are anxious
Just about flying a lot of it is really tight schedules
And because of
The nature of weather
And things that are completely outside of our control sometimes flights get delayed
Hey become complete disasters
Jeffy
There never was a TSA
If there never was terrorism it would still be a scary
Supply places
Yasso
DD's people
In a vacuum
It makes sense why they would be rude
Belittle route so many other route
That you can expect until
Curing here
Is 0
This is the euro
Have a great day
Like that's what I'm giving these PSAs
About the pilot stereotype
Is that a known thing that pilot do
I feel like we're also I mean I don't know but I also
We're past the point where
Pilot being drunk
Okay The Stereotype that the
Youth probably understand
You know like that used to be the thing
No I don't I don't know or I'll eat
Sitcom stereotypes
For the kids
Was that that man on fire
We've only got one reference
It was not all bad
You did end up needing one
Super woke
TSA agent
Alright
I like it I don't think
You should get
Obsessive
Compulsively
He's basically images of screenshots from
The South Park episode
About TSA
Certification
Alex
We bring back so I need a new password please please
Scary I would want to I wouldn't want to
Secret
Conspiratorial wink
Number to USAA
Just like
People forget to take away that I don't even care
Female that be fun why did it why don't more people turn the TSA
Experience
Like a fun little what
Cuz I want to get there to be more like
When you go through the line ever
I would like to psia line is where everyone knows your name
Exactly that means
This is like this is my kind of fun
So I was over at
A Bloomberg article came out
About how
Uses
Conspiracy
And feared
To sell gold
And
One of those no duh
But Alex takes
Bloomberg done very similar
Alex Alex Alex
Pretty
A serious problem
But people saying that
He's trying to sell gold
Headlines
Alex Jones sells gold on Sirius
With bombing conspiracy
Why are they shooting at me Politico
By the way we hardly
Gold is one of the smallest
Sponsorships we got
Unfortunately I wish I could
$5
Text Stuart event
That is
That is as much an advertised you could reasonably do
Without it literally being like
We're barely has resources
Which has the best sales right now they have
Gold for $300 an ounce
You couldn't beat that and it's so good that I've always held on
I'll never let it go at all I want to do is sell gold I don't want to sell
Giving gold away I want to hoard it
The others
HTC violation
Presenting
Of the
Infowars
That's right
Entirely
Vindicate
Okay
It was very different
Then just being a sponsor
They are responsible for his vindication
And for it being on radio station
Shepherd is beyond sponsor
Bambi the the nature of the
The ads
A lot of Alex Jones's adds Argenta
Network ads better run
Through the network which is owned by
Resources own
The ads that are paying Alex Jones Revenue
It's very complicated
Is f***** up
I meant it's locked up because we know we've seen
How desperately tries to
I like the idea that he saying
We barely saw
Existed Elgort
I think I got a limit for you
Baby bobcat
Around as much anymore and
Maybe Alex
Remember how shameful he was 2009
You want to Buck back at Bloomberg
Triple B
I still think it's
It's awful to hear
Do just
Do it
You sell gold
Crime in terms of
Misrepresenting
I really cry more likely that big of a deal
Considering what it what else
What does Fox News sell but like things that are for
Beer and old
Mostly old people get Mickey
Do stuff
I seen on TV type nonsense
That's as big of a crime is gold
Ellie Goulding and doesn't break down after
Easier to scam people live gold
Manipulate the Value Inn
It like that
Yeah it has Seen On TV products
So in the next five Alex Jones
Get them to another
I think it's going to be a
Throughout this up a
And that is
He wants
He wants you to know that he's
He's been nice
Scared
New York
Truth Rising
You're not allowed to have this demonstration
Windpipe
Gyros
Hollywood as a thug
Badfella
Or average fellows
Good for medium
I don't believe that I'll
You know I rejected the idea of
Every conversation that begins with
Listen
We're going to say your cameras are bought
Kabob
I need at least
I don't like people
Bounce Around the issues
Little dance
Front and honest
If you're going to say that's something I'm bringing with me
I love the pretending the guys were walking around with pipes
There's other weapon
There's a concealed carry law
New York is going around in New York
Osberg
Really in favor of
Carrying laws for
Yep
So Alex gets death
We are change
Infowars adjacent actual employee
He pops up a lot
I don't know the skulls
No one does
Mistletoe
Williston you just said this earlier
Yeah that's right
Asking Bloomberg a question
My wife
And I'm going to head up a
So we need your prayers first and foremost
Madre support because
We need to expand the face of this new world order
This is like watching a baby learn to crawl
He's really close to that address
Interested in
He's going to die and they're getting me
Cryptic phone calls the tell you what you've been saying and stuff like that
Raise your emotional state
And then mention weenie
Need your money because of the
These things I'm scaring you about
So it is the primordial ooze from which
The ad Pivot Group
Yeah this is not yet
It's where they're better
Astonished
Yeah I think I think
Recall is pretty early and
Supplement
Company offering I don't know what month
It started in Bible
Things got going with a couple
Call supplements
Into that mode yet
But I still wanted money
That you get all the time
They're like
Hey
I've been listening to
Right here's what you were talking about earlier
Experienced so many times in the past
No no no setting on a self operator
Party line
Small towns would have like a party line going maybe
I think it's something
I mean it sounds good
In terms of scary
You know
Well
Yeah
I mean
You
If you believe
All of his ideas
About
The nature of the spying
What's going on
It does track
Someone would be listening
And would be like
You were talking about earlier
It works if you're already
I think
I don't think
That's absurd
Just silly
I think that's silly
If somebody did that to me I'd be like
Are you
Are you okay
Hey man
What are you doing friend
Can't you be doing something else
The
How do you feel
About what
The British guy
Serological response
Do that
Euro f****** loud mouth guy who screams
About everything and has no filter on the radio if we threaten you you're going to
To talk about it either
Our position has been there not real
I think I'm going to stick with that one even get the idea that he has
They can't kill me I'm too publicly again
It really would not be hard to kill you because there are so many alternate explanations for why you could die
Literally any kind of like
Oh he had a heart attack and everybody be like
Can kill you for giving you a heart attack
Kenlake wave weapon
The project
Kellogg Eye his associate Vince
I was killed Biggie they gave him a
Give me the right
Walk around carrying types
It's consistent throughout
These are paranoid
Like the idea is anything that's natural causes
Is probably
It could be suspicious
So no matter how I die
I believe the worst
Wow
We saw what happened with that
Right now in terms of
People not believing
I just something
Sprite but if nothing if
There is nothing matters there is no explanation that satisfies
The paranoid mom
Exactly
So matter
They don't exist
Going to kill him first
The good way to go about things
Organization behind
Lucien's 400z
Love yourself before the invention of the telephone
They like pissing the best
You know he's not threatening
But he has buyable
So maybe we invest
Gold company
Someone would go about it
If anyone wanted to corrupt Alex it would not be through
Threats
Or anything like that it would be through
Greenback
Or just
Things about him
Flattery and money worship hours
Earlier in the show we did see
Example of a
I'm trying to explain
To try and jam
Yes he does
He goes about it
Here in the show
Just the way they spin
Is so funny
Messages about terror attack
Bombing Al-Qaeda
Yes we have photos of the defense intelligence operatives that were there with the Patxi's in command of them
On
April 15th and we're releasing that data
Central
All the computers
We don't actually have that
That part will computers
Saying that you do
Immediately following up with hieroglyphics
Like seriously
You're telling the wrong lies
You're lying wrong
I'm good at that
15th is in Redford
To the Boston butt
You talking about
The Boston bombing
Because I
I've been I've been looking into this a little bit and I think that as much as he became
Popular apps
After 9/11
His stock grew quite a bit
I think that
The post Boston
Embalming.
Would probably
The most like
The modern most organic growth
Because of the
Is what it was one of the early ones I know that I remember
The internet
A c community going Buckwild along with him
Lichen
Search
Through
Pictures
The try and find culprit
Pencils like that like the internet sleuthing community
Crazy
There was more of it even
Before this.
I've just don't realize but I know it was pretty crazy
In terms of like
Very irresponsibly
Put the blame on various TV
Yeah there was there was some pretty serious
And I know that Alex
Made a lot of hay out of
I am so
This is right in the
What would you call it
Right after
After that it's sort of in the
The evening of the honeymoon
Yeah yeah where things are still like
I think he's
He's gaining a lot of
Momentum went over to England
Absolutely
If you're from Texas you have to go to England at least once
Yeah yeah
Yeezys
Positing
Bringing up this idea that
He's going to
Revealed evidence
But he's right
Hobby People
Admittedly he doesn't have
He also did say it later that
He's already put it out
Even though he doesn't have it
He doesn't have it. I don't
I don't I've looked
I do think
Present his trip
UK
First of all the greatest victories all-time over the Bell
Absolutely
He's bent out of shape a little bit about the in
Interview I think he's in a bad head
And I
That comes up missing
I don't care
Me all you want I don't care
Whatever
Whatever happens
Whole truth
So help me God almighty
On the altar of God
Resistance and defiance
Solar eclipse
Starts with him
Makes fun of me
I think it's because a lot of people
I think the
Rational Minds
Steve at UK interview
Have you hear the guy being like I've got an idiot
Mstudio Drake you do
Sorry
Sorry had to go through that
Geico
Interrupting
What have you
I think he's probably getting a little bit of blow back about that
I'm so he's
Kind of on edge
A little bit
I don't care
Cuz all I care about is
Vigilance
I'm always
Like I don't know what it is but there is something programmed in
To humankind that that
Southern Baptist
Revivalist preacher talk
Like that that
Forum
Just so
Like there's a reason that there were there were f****** kids
Like Margie
In the twenties leading that spiritualist revivalist movement
Having 20,000 people at their at their f******
Can shows
You are lying
There's a lyrical quality to it looks like oral tradition cultures
Storytellers
Even to ascertain
Rappers
You know like
Is infection
After
You can tell 20 minutes of good jokes and then you can just ride on the Rhythm
Taking care of you like your next 20 can be boring but people are so
It's constant that's in this like reaction to the Rhythm that they'll laugh at anything
Just like you
Your Rhythm can make your
Your style Legend
Even like
The jokes
Someone like Mitch Hedberg
Wouldn't be
Revered as
He is
Or Steven Wright Interlaken just have
Perfect
If you want to you want to follow the Rhythm
Yeah what if the Headless Horseman had a headless horse that would be fun
Cooking chaos signal like that
There's nothing but the way
The Rhythm over
Come to that
But
This is
Next
Yeah
Because
The point that I think is weird
Particularly tough time for us to do this sort of thing
Make the point that
Nope have a real tough time with the Border
Hello passport
And tell me that maybe I should get a new password
Feed
Their power ego
He almost said you don't belong
Let you know
If you look like you were fervent
It was citizens it was milk cows
It was good looking women
It was border patrol
Customs
Even the TSA imperious
Imperious
I think you have the word today calendar and.
Do you know if he's using that the way that he
I don't know I don't think it always
Necessarily have the consolation of Imperial
Do fall under
Imperiousness
I didn't see that the reason that that is
Is a an incorrect usage of that word is because imperious
Suggest that there
Empower
Without
Application for it
That
They have a justification
I'm not super interested in
Because you can
You know
I could
Someone on Alex's at world
Easily make
Argument that they
Take too much power
And it the ends don't justify the me
In terms of
The other scrutiny that people are forced to go under
I agree with that argument in tires
F****** racism
That's the bigger issue Mister grammar over here
Take a step back and say
It's really f***** up that he's saying that hate anybody who looks like they're foreign
I don't have you they just get
But this citizen
Cow who don't know what they look like
I think Alex knows what the f****** look like anybody come out
This is the sort of thing
Yes
That doesn't
That doesn't match up
In terms of scale
With like
If you have Richard Spencer throwing words around
But boy howdy that is as racist as like
I thought can be it is absolutely it because you categorizing people don't look
American is
Being non-white
That's a problem which I got the entire point of America is that
Anybody here looks America
That's kind of Who We Are
You know that whole Melting Pot
I like to eat
I like to eat out
I prefer broth
I don't like to cook
Give me give me milk
Give me milk
So
Situation
And you might be surprised
Great band
The BBC situation yeah that's not bad
You might be surprised to hear Alex's take on how everything
I'm not but
This clip is jarring
Shows Italy
You're an idiot
I just broke the trance
Winter break
Stop yelling
Their treasury secretary
Ball
And
Egos
Stop yelling
He went back on and said that I was a fake and it was all an act
Real
Okay
Want YouTube
Realize you are not
I would suggest there's just a difference in definition
I would say
By definition
Someone who's real is not someone
Screams over the other person
And delights in dominating them by yelling infowars.com
Over them instead of engaging with the ideas of
Putting forth that's not dominating that's being a baby
Rima fakih child on British television
I'm looking like
Crass
And the fact that he stops as soon as the cameras off
It doesn't mean that it's fake but it just means that like
It's a show.
They think they want you to think that no one's real it's like no we think you're real but the reality for you is
This is all bulshit
Write a mixture
Aren't you know Inez in a certain sense I can actually
Respect that argument
I can't
Really worked up
As he presented himself to be
On the British
Yeah he would not stop saying you guys
You don't fucken understand what you're apart of
Do you understand that
Be the globalist
I have all these documents on my phone
He would continue trying to
His point across to them after they got off or he would scream at them and say you're part of the problem
One of those three
Or you would just check out cuz this is isn't like he would just
Performatively stop screaming
I've been hanging around
That's not what would happen
Well I'm just trying to put myself into that
Idea of like
If I am going on TV
If I am against
All Odds
Somehow
Hannity
Invite me on
Pretend that he has something to say tucker might be a better
HuHot possibility
I would absolutely because
The show
He has nothing on the inside
And he's he's a joke as well
So is when the cameras are off I'm just going to go
Just go
It's funny you should bring that up
Escorted
But I don't
2 G
Got to go
Cuz I don't I don't think it was like a getting
Thrown out
For his own protection or whatever got
Regards to take him out
Here or even just like
Dude you don't belong here anymore
You in this light you're gone your services have been rendered
There's no after-party to hangout
Something that I do
Do not believe this true
That's all they can do as well
Former police here
Sure they said what you said about the 7/7 bombings Mendes how did you know that
What
That was an assassination
I need cops one and Eminem
So sorry about 77
The bombing
What else is probably operating off
Probably most
With his awareness about
Movie called 77 ripple effect
Productive
About 77 bombing
Basically the British
77 bombing equivalent to Blue Stream
It was directed by a guy named
But that of course is a fake name
It's actually blue
From Dune
It muaddi
My friend
Do you want to go into all this all right so you have to go through
Concentrated spice
And that
Kills all men who take
But it's the same thing that Reverend mothers take
In the band
All right so when they
And they take this and they have to
Use their there
Like
Biological Powers 2
Due process
And that then liquid becomes now
The interesting thing is that Paul Atreides
Is Mom
Wasn't
Supposed to have a son
She was supposed to have another
Because the movie
To be two generations on
Crazy
So anyways
What what are we talk
I love to take name of the director Paul son and his daughter
I'm sorry I'm sorry I did it
The directors real name is John Hill
You like dude
From an article
A document from website
He is the messiah
George Lucas
Star Wars after being told telepathically what to write
By the very Force
To which the films were fur
So that's part of his world
Interesting to read living in both.
Fake I was all comes back to
To the fact that the
Is reporting that there was a
Drill
On the same day that the police were engaged
But if you'll pay attention
Alex
That's pretty much what he says every single time
As well
Now you can go case-by-case on these and I can't speak to
To every single
Supposed drill that Alex will talk about
But as it relates to the 771
BBC article about it
They point out very clearly quotes
Peter power of former Scotland Yard police officers her power
Do we have to do this with every f****** name
Sorry where do these people come from I don't know
Copp is a former Scotland Yard police officer
He says that the 7777
That was wrong the drill
Was an office base drill and involve Justice people
Republic income
Internal office
Exercise that was Ron
What would be the response
It's unfortunate
Horrible coincidence
Act did go down
Very suspicious
I want
Juneau Police Department
Girls all the time
Each day like every city and every
You know principality
Everyday there's going to be something generally
Sort of like let's pasta our response to
The laws of coincident
You know like it's broken
It's like if you've ever
If you ever like
Lifted a phone to
To call somebody
Can you find out that at that moment
Start calling you
About all the calls that are happening all the time
Every single day
It's inevitable that that happened
Irregularly
Beatles meaningful fuels like this
This is very suspicious
Yahtzee
I get it I get why people be very suspicious
About that
But I don't
It's like a dam
In the case of this where they've talked about it like it was a tie
In office
They clearly have nothing to do with the running of
Multiple
Attack
Anyway Alex belief about 77
Big fake large leaf
Comes back to this documentary
It was written by a guy who believes in
The force
The Messiah
From Dune
And a lot of his overtime
Bogus
Fun
I love the cops
I came up to you and cried
Figure line
Now
This is interesting
This next clip
Because this is
Free
The episode
We when we talked about Fergie
Alright
Alex's response was very much
People that burning stuff down cop killed a guy I think it was totally fine
We apologized
Wasn't White
But Alex has a very
John riot
About how Paula trade
Nissan Note
Merges with sand fish and actually be
Becomes a
A sandworm
Himself a power
You know a few thousand years
And Alters the entire course of human evolution which eventually leads
The great scattering
Mount was at the sequel to Highlander
Now that when they go to space for some
Alex
Expresses variant
Absolutely
Plus riots on record a year
What
So that's a good thing
Very weird
Very weird when the cops kill somebody we should have a right and Burn the City
Because they have like a Thor attarian
Totalitarian state already
Covid-19
But here's the rear
Is why
See that's why the Chinese
Can handle and at home I have the balls
Strength to Riot right somebody when you burn it
Meanwhile
Not
Six months later or whatever
And there were burned down
No
Breakfast
You know protest lied to that is up minimizing the
Situation dumb assholes
It's like I don't understand where the
I don't understand where the line
Absolutely no sense
Isn't one that I can really
Toss away really easily like
When we are looking at
Looking at 2009
Position
These have been
I don't think there's enough time
For something to have happen
Yeah I think he's just
Racist
Yeah there's no other explanation scared of black people
Having agency
Being mad
Being justifiably mad about
It's interesting to me
The
Because
Like the more we go through this
The more Alex's insanity
Dubstep DuckTales
Perfectly with just
The mental gymnastics
People require in order to justify them not
You know what I'm saying
But all of this
Worldview all of this
Sanity is
Built around the idea that
He believes all people
Equally
Did B
And yet the same time he makes all of these
These rules where it's like
Japan
We are at
Overarching we are all underneath it all of the rules that I build
Mean that
White people are under more tyranny than everybody else
Creating the tyranny
Is destroying the white
Exactly his worldview so even though it may appear that he doesn't care about all these other groups
It's really because once the lights go down
You're all neck
He says like the West
Behind hell on Earth on Earth
The exact same sort of thing it's like
Alright
When
To Native people
When they happen to black people
Shirts bad
But I don't really care
Because they're on the other side of that pork or whatever it's like
That's not going to take down the Levee
Right but the white people are the Levee
He's not realizing it make sure that they get there
Eddie's not realizing that like the water is
You are at your
Your Swiss cheese
I don't know if I mailed that metaphor but
The same type of mental gymnastics
Pixar require
A
Just like
You know it look like if you if you and so many people went to
Trump rally in Minnesota
150 years of our Republic
Show me reporters went there and they asked people are like seriously what the
If if this were happening
We would
Totally be against
We just don't believe any of it happening
I watched a bit of it it was very troubling
No it's not
Really it really
Struck me that
I watch the number these rally
Another point there were
Fu
Not white people
I don't want to judge whatever there
Motivation
For being there were
Their own choices in life
There were it wasn't
Rutledge said
And then a little bit later down the road it would be like
Just that one guy with the blacks
For Trump sign
Yep yep there's that guy and then like
He kept showing up
And that was like all right we got
This was
I was looking I couldn't
Anybody who wasn't like
I don't know cuz you know
Right I don't even know if there are anybody who
Are already
I don't know if ever been
And I was like nope
Still nobody
Everybody's like
Michaela
I didn't know if it was him or not but I saw people clowning on Twitter but that was like
Super high-resolution
Picture of this bar
Looks
You could blow it up higher
High-resolution
I was looking around
I wanted Pizza I don't know if
Kevin McHale butt
I know it's not Robert Parish
Tell you that right now
It's super weird
All of this could
Still down
Sam's
Look like
Alex is not really
Concerned about
Your contacts.
And so like
Chinese people rioting
Is great because
Because in his brain
Creates problems
Tricom
He hates so much
If it were Chinese people rioting
Here against
Dissimilar oppression
Let's say when the Chinese Exclusion Act was going on or something like that
American act like that but so like if that were Happening Here
He would be very good
Creating problems
For his
Conception of America is white
Problematic in a
Largely African-American area
If it were white people rioting probably be
He totally fine with
Especially if they were like
We're against
Chinese
Yeah I imagine that might be okay
Especially
Subway to work it in
Some b*******
You know what interests me
I don't know at this point
At this point I am not going to let you know
Dude for sure Highlander
Moderately
I love Highlander
I'm suggesting that you do a spa podcast
With you cuz you keep bringing it up
It's just you know
The Erasure of the line
That is what fascinated me most
About
The way that they when they do those stories where it's like
You know that people are
Being torn from their parents
Inputting to concentrate
How can you deal with
How can you support
And instead of saying that there's a line
Where they won't support Trump
There's no line
Now they just it just doesn't it just doesn't happen
I know but it seems like
Even if you are a republican you should have
Thought
At least before now
Is there a line
What will it take for me to stop supporting the Republican Party
Nasi but that's what I thought
Democrats want you to have and that's why they would never had that thought
It does seem strange to me that that's a thought
Nobody
Seems to have ever had
Like what's the line
What is the line for me to change my party
Have you ever like I don't
I have no Allegiance
Stupid Democrats
Because they are f****** garbage and they're going to ruin it
They're going to
But I have no choice
Because they
The alternative
And at the same time
What's My Line
No
Right because I don't
I don't have an Allegiant
So I don't have a line
I will go with
People that I think are best
The positions that are open
No that's
Really
Youth in like really early there's a lot of things that are disqualifying
L but
I think
Right yeah me neither
That's true
I guess our line is not
I'm sorry I'm sorry
I mean I mean for the politically on a Philly
The line is ultimately like
Just leaving
Right
Like at what point can you not even support the Comerica
Yeah yeah
Yeah that has to be the
The real
Like what's that what's that line feel like it should
Earlier
Cross a long time ago
I'm not afraid of planes anymore
Time to go
Time to change this up
Get back on track the show Alex
He wants to
Duplex on Obama supporters
And so he starts taking calls
From Obama supporters
Alright I want you people to come at me
Don't really like Obama that much but
These are Obama
Are your colors
Yes you know what that mean
He ran into
Wherever I'm not sure if this person is a globalist
But it's very possible
Nothing
The plane okay then the jury still out
Chinese Telecom
Welding gas wanted back with
American Airlines
I forgot Alice and Annie was like
What's going on
You use regulations
I don't think I prison
First of all he's very well-known
Vero
Somehow involved to George Bush
Famous we know these on American Airlines
Absolutely very powerful
Not a f****** chance in the world
Also this didn't happen but I do
That's exactly what
I think that part is clear
But
I just
Who's that
Stupid
Libertarian garbage
Reframe what
Regulation
That's like all the super rich
People already have all their money
Enforce
These are these regulations
Make sure no one else
Can get in their game
Trust
Monopoly
We which we have many
That regulations are supposed to break up
Problem
I don't understand idive sincerely donut
The difference
Spiritually
Between
That which would break up
Monopoly
And that which would regulate
You know like I don't understand
Like you can
Bring a spiritual difference
It's supporting one and not the other
Cuz I like seems to be very against monopolies
He hates the idea of Monopoly
Capitalism
Should I try
Regulate business
Let business be
Government to break up Monopoly
No he does he wants the people to break up
Get involved she absolutely.
Okay then how
What do you mean
Well
Okay
Do you want to go into breakup Amazon you want some breakup Google
But he doesn't want us
To do what he wants
The government to step in
Okay but how
Without regular
Laurel Leaf
Nope
To close
Can you use stipulation how about dance party
Now that's interesting
Amazon.com
How about
Tire government
Has a huge car wash
Okay better idea
We go to like your dance party
This is a better idea
Musical chairs
Okay
Everybody pays
Amazon business
Or like you get the book
Part of it okay
Go to work
Because
Musical chairs is only going to lead over Napoli
One person win
Oh okay multiple rounds
Like you guys round is 4 Prime
This is for the shipping business
This is for the warehouse in all right around if you win
Bees okay throwing the dance party
I must say I don't know it's 200 million
To get in or something like that
19 to walk away with something but you
Choose what it is
You get whatever
Right there like one of those games where you at
No because you get whatever musical chairs were found you
But there's only enough rounds for as many people are they
These are there is a dummy
Cuz it's not fun to play musical chairs
Here's my plan to break up
Monopoly
You know what that's a very big cuz I'm a big enough man to admit that Saturday
Here's my plan
Alright
Firing
All right so it's hoping to avoid this sort of thing
Right then we have like six people with guns
Nobody knows who has a live bullet
And they all shoot them
Via
I don't know
I guess regulation
Just to reinforce Alec
Terrible
About that
Very sad
We haven't covered a whole lot
What episode because there is a
The whole lot kind of
Yells about
Fantasista
But it doesn't really say anything in particular
To talk about how you been right all along and yeah
I think
He's talking about William Benning
I had a guy on from the NSA or whatever
No one talked about it a little bitter about that
LOL overall it's just a lot of zeros lot of zeros throughout
Episode
Everything is very vague it's always a guy who did nothing I was
At a place where a thing happened
Rock climb up
Being difficult
But the things that are important are they at
He thinks that yelling at the guy at the BBC is Domino
Dating him
Describing different feelings on riot
Depending on the
It's over there it's not over here
He's just making up so much s***
But he's making up what happened
The TSA agent
He's making up the top crying to him
In London
He's making up
Former cop making up this
He's just creating it like
Great Samuel Jackson movie
He probably had a really boring trip that was mostly Pleasant outside of getting dunked on on UK television
He's trying to create a mythology out of it cuz he doesn't
Away from the states very often
I can understand that
Fish and chips
But make no mistake about it
His life isn't Dane
You talk about the Boston Bomber
Release the photos by the grace of God the photos
We focused on the drill real quick
We released the photos that were already out that sentence
God
And they freaked out and be really honest with you
I know in my gut
Discussion
And some other agency or group might just I'm sick of that guy do it
Well you know what
You're not
FBI CIA
The TSA
Could be the APA the emir
American poolplayers Association Protection Agency of Bradshaw and Farooq
Could be
Kirby the CDC
Could be the TFC
What's up
TCM Turner Classic Movies
The rapper
Alright
Slater Alex Jones
Seems to care about killing him
To our great regret
I'm fine with them not dying but
It's just
It's becoming
Laborious
I still live I love doing the show and I still love learning about these things
Because he's such a perfect conduit in
Into learning about things that I would not have any access to otherwise
But it is becoming a thing where it's like
4 years
Just like that
And then you see him now and he's doing the same
He's doing the same bit
And it's really it's like
Cena comic Francisco
I don't want to see anybody in particular because I don't know the man
Someone
Like
I don't know somebody
That man you like that was amazing
Are so good there a great comic
I've been five years later you see
See them do basically the same site with
With the same crowd work
The same
Besides
To the audience name built-in shiting you like
So you got
There is a feeling of like
Is all you got
Too bad
That sucks man
Uniden
Episode
Let's go back
Allograft also apologized a little bit that there wasn't as much a
To meet there wasn't a ton of me but
The reason that I still stand by it and I can
This was a
Exactly the right episode to do
Was because
It was a reason we got sent back and we found
Alex's responds to him being on the other BBC
Mission accomplished indeed big banner on a
Absolutely
Ian and everybody who
If you'd like
You can find us
Knowledge feit.com if you would like to have us do your own time travel episode you can click the
I support the show button and I'm sure the rest probably
I have a few
The Chamber of people who have sent me messages
I don't do a good enough job planning this out but if you are on that level of you are more than welcome
Come to send me a request
Clear enough on the
Patreon page
Itself by
Please send me a message at knowledge fight at gmail.com or on the Facebook group
Are you inside the message on.
On Facebook
And I will get that date
I will
Absolutely
Or you could send this tweet
Have you even go to at knowledge underscore fights erect correct
Go to iTunes and you should actually go to f****** help in this case
You still go there
Describe
Let's do it like
Leave leave a review appreciated we've had some very nice
Street Music very very nice
Yep
Alright
Possibility of ever since meeting
In asking for notoriety is is a wonderful absolutely like
I mean
It's some form of Show Business
Performance
Same time I have a
I'm allergic to being like
We will dwell in whatever stage worried now
Hey we have important things but people need to hear it
Is a nap
Thanks for listening
Jordan Future
Well I am going to go I'm just going to stay
That there's one
Small
Tiny
Pathetic
L-shaped ear having
Balding motherfuking hunt of a man who needs to go for
F****** die
Jeff sessions go f*** yourself
Alexandra Thurston color