Alexandra Thurston color
What's up if you went to a family reunions yesterday
Yeah boy
Yeah don't talk about it
Cut through this stupid fit that we do at the beginning of human
Member of my family you don't know anything about Alex
That's exactly how it went
I've been perfectly honest with you
Adventure
For the last couple days I noticed I had but I bought Saint Austin
This is finally coming in the mail since they're too
Big to be taken on a plane
Just wanted to put that up to the universe
Despite
How do you feel about that
Arwen
I'm being attacked
Expired by now
You should have gotten it about a year-and-a-half before it expires
We have delightful show
Before we do
I feel like I want to throw a wrench into the gears
Look for ways to expand on what this show is
Is all about
Really I doubt it is driving me
I'm so I have here a habanero pepper
I'm going to eat this
Wow
I allow you to take over the show
What now throw the show into your hands those are the people who our new policy wants then I give a shout out to
I've never eaten habanero before I have no idea how I'm going to respond to that genuinely
I have no idea what's about to happen all right
Anyway he would go Jordan take over the show
Eating a habanero pepper right now
That's our new donors ladies and gentlemen
Our first new donor
We would like to give a huge shout-out to Peter welcome to the policy wonks
Don't do that right well then
Swollen
I'm a policy wonk
And our next policy wonk has actually bumped up
Her donor Shadow just came from
She came straight in at the globalist level
Thank you very much Larissa
Someone sodomites
You threw a tiny wrench into the Giants
Messer from
FernGully the first thought I had some way
I was weird
I don't know Jordan's going to enjoy this
I don't think you did and I give it a Beat
Really hurt by this yeah I expected to be like
You know I did not expect
Do you like spices things and spice like they fight
I would cry like a
Thresher in FernGully a guy and that's what I kind of like
Where did
Opening of the show's becomes do
Entrenched in this
Yeah little tiny bit
I don't think is going to work
For the curveball
We mix up a bit sound like we do the same bed every time
And now I know this is
Glycol
In Patriot mythology
Is it real
Very much out of contact
I just spoil
Call arifa
It's talking okay
That's it
Off the hook
But everything else Alex believes in
Today Jordan we're going to be going over the
February 6th
February 10th episodes of The Alex Jones Show
It's because there's a lot of dead air
There's a lot of downtime and we need to pick up the speed
We need to get to the point where the
Party really kicks off
And we really get to see how long
Take Alex
2 Chainz
From
All of those 2,000 positions into his
Much more in line with the Koch brothers
And so we need to
Need to get to do that
See how he responds to
The massive public
Tea party stuff
Tom and
Is launching a new narrative
Is really interesting it will carry through
The entirety of what we cover on
I'm going to guess
Okay
The it's about the bees are dying
Because in 2009 was whenever that first started to get like it has been happening for like 10 years before that but
People started a really notice in 2009 they were like
Where are the there's going to be no food if we don't have bees
Did Alex Jones is going to jump on the back of that
Like really
He's already said all he's going to say which is that
The bottom of the
Here's where I think he's going to go with this
You first of all let me just
Stop before you go any further never been more right
I've got to go with
Complete turnaround for him
He is going to find the most
Reasonable Acts
Chemtrails
Or the magnetic poles reversing
What he is going to say
Is
I'm going to go with man-made climate change
And it's time to regulate the oil companies
In order to keep this from
I'm continuing
3 left field turn
Christian Franklin
Play Aaron Franklin
Going to say that the globalist
Directions
Globalist
And growing
Criminal
Concentration camps
Increasing number of states declaring sovereignty
Migos over it
A lot
Not Justa
Next hour
You know
In the history of our country
Generally speaking
State legislators don't get together to say like
The law is the law federal government
But mysteriously a month or so after a black guy gets elected
A bunch of States get together and have their legislature put together
A bunch of bills
And resolutions that they put through that are directly to the president
I am the speaker of the house that just say
Hey
You know
The law law
Don't be encroaching
Wait what
Yes
Legislators got together
What
They wrote a resolution and they mailed it to the speaker the house
Don't tread on me
Revolution
In the state houses
Snogging
Actual like Federal has
Representative
They would be sent to the president if they pass
It became
Accepted resolution
But
Is this
Coordinate
These are all almost
Identical Resolute Revolution
I'm read them
Almost all identical
Things that are being operated by people who
May or may not show up on our episode today
Yeah because they're weirdo Patriot assholes
Because all of these all of these bills are like actually written by the Heritage Foundation
Are tired.
By the Heritage Foundation
Homemakers ever actually learned
It's 8 some patriots Bill Mill
And Franklin
So you can find Bill trackers
Stuff like that you can find out what happened
These resolutions
State that got introduced
Go to Sapphire nobody did it and nobody acted on it so it never got past and never got put through
The main one that Alex talks about cuz it was one that was introduced
I believe at least
But since I got four listen
I look that up and it turns out that the bill is listed as quote
Legislate
What's up Billy what is inexpedient
Arizona
VR the house resolution passed 34 224 but no black president
At the same time
Arizona
There's somebody went on record
Is it only passed because
Obama
Cologne at a black person
Yeah yeah
So it was then reintroduce as a resolution quote
Circulating Montana's rights under the US Constitution
And it once again failed
Because everyone's like
You're saying
So Michigan diversion introduced
By the committee of government operations
My home state Missouri
This one's weird
Their version HR 212 was a little bit
It declares Missouri sovereignty under the 10th Amendment
Does the United States Congress
To reject the past
Did your federal
Freedom of Choice act which prohibits regulations on abortion
So they
They were like the law is the law
But at the same time
Please don't make any more laws
About abortion please Monster the 10th Amendment
Into this HR 212
Missouri
Missouri house
Zuri was like
Because it was it was it covered too much
You know it was like
It was replaced with HR to United States
Which classifies abortion as a fundamental right
The law is the law and you got to remember that we're Missouri we are sovereign
The law is the law everybody likes
It appears that that's the case
294 does appear to have half the house
So
Alex will end up talking to the guy responsible for
Oklahoma
Crazy
I don't think you could not talk to
Any Arizona Montana all that's it boring
Oklahoma Oklahoma Oklahoma
I'm excited I want to hear this
Resolution
Which passed the house and the Senate
When was vetoed by Governor Brad because the language of the resolutions that Oklahoma
Send back federal taxes
And he was like no I don't want to do nothing no one wants to do that
I will ruin
All of our budget
Governor we would like you to sign this bill
The name of witches
Shoot Oklahoma in the dick
Oklahoma
Reduce to Bella's house
Current resolution 1028
It passed the damn house again although it's slightly diminished support probably because of the
Brought up
Because it was
Concurrent resolution it did not need to go to the governor this time
Speaker of the House
All the bill was
Was it you could really boil it down to just
The two words
Watch it
Or we got our eye on you
You better know that
It's really really hard to look at this and not see that
You know what I'm saying like it's it's
It's pretty much like
Oh you guys are shook
You should have been the moment Obama's like
Really going to happen on this 18 years trying to reach across the aisle to
Being like
We're passing a vaguely races bill
Indirect
Response to Obama being elected I know about the resolutions of this because we're years later
GameStop
Comedian stuff like that
They happen in like
March and April 2009 we're at we're still in
There's a little bit of an omniscient narrator
You know that the reason neither being introduced
Because
Anyway in the next
F****** weird I never really know what to say
Expect from him
I know him well in many ways
Right but he still surprises me a serial killer
I didn't see em.
It seems like a decent
Guy I would say that
Jarring
College
Grant
Children is bad
Panda
Ponzi scheme
Not security
Another
This is not the part.
Surprises I imagine.
Right in line with his demographic shift
We're not having a baby
Forgot
A population
Shorty got a few children hold on hold on
Hold on hold on
It was
Emeryville
Too far
Blend
Whether it was a good decision or not
What does it matter
I don't I don't care I just hate bunnies
I don't care either but I don't know and I don't care
Who's coming to bat for October
Like knowing what we know
1414 East 7th
Yeah you said it my man well
For me
Call Sue Metty
I don't know what equatorial that's what I was
What is he mean by ecuatorial
I think near the equator
Of the world is there very fertile people from near the equator
He thinks she's actually a volcano
And she's in the Ring of Fire
Notorious
Play fertile soil is incredible prone to explosions
I bought
Still very firm
All I know is
Excuse
Races
It does
Steals is racist
I don't know how
Because that's
Remember when I
Earlier said
He continues to surprise me
That's that's why
That feels
Very
Very bigoted
Know how to put my finger
No it's wrong
It seems to me like someone who talks about like fiery Latino blood
And stuff like that right
I don't know
I do like the idea of him changing his rhetoric is like the West
The middle
You go all the way around it
Center I'm going to go with the
10th to the 10th parallel
You might remember that a few years back Todd Akin
If a woman has
Raped her at
It's pregnant
I'll take care of that
Best thing for Clay Aiken to say wish you was invisible
Do that
If I were if I were invisible I would
So it is
To freising to remember that Alex wasn't like
He wasn't offended by
It's kind of like
Seems like a reasonable comment
Coronavirus
Out of it back to 2009
That's where we are
200%
Other forms of reproductive
Flash
Don't associate with breast cancer
Why don't you have the baby in adoption
Why don't you
Glock dookie
Screaming really gross things
About abortion that are just like
His normal Mooyah
This is real this is very unscientific
Is it is it like
It's got to be something like if you are near them while they're menstruating
You'll become a woman like
Doing
Self everything works out
There are no problem
50% of women used to die in childbirth until like 100 years ago
Body work that out
No Doubt
That's how much do you have in October
Exactly that's a
There's that there's a question we need to ask ourselves
Or more
If you said so
This idea of guilt
People about stuff
Utter horseshit
Literally
By his own beliefs
10 women cancer
Are you stupid it so he spends a lot of this show.
Really gross things
Fear tactic
It about abortion
It doesn't it doesn't pass the smell test
Probably
Comes from
Anti-abortion
That's probably
Information
South Broadway
The Greener more familiar pastors
Our old friend
The guy who
Millions and millions
From South Africa
The outcome
Financially
Will be all the currencies will collapse
Evaluation
Almost all of them will do directly to be a futile do okay
Which one
In the meantime every single day
Every single currency
Is the valuing against against
So
Eden Spa
If I really but it is just
It is just on to say all this stuff about how like
There's an artificial collapsed
All current
Google
Inflation's going to go ballistic
$900 at 1 $10 gold
Gold is going over $3,000
And if you don't
If you have
About having that defensive insurance position at home
You've got to get more coins
You've got to get more silver
Anything
Again
Next week is going to fly
Next week
It's going to fly
You better by shiting now
Never hit
I will say that gold was right
Around this time
It never reached
The levels that they are saying
It's going to
Gaining value
It's falling and there
Pretending
Right it did it
A little bit later up
10:00
Torso
Corrected
Pretty much sense with
With a little bit of fluctuation
Right around 11:12
Because that's evil
They're doing that maliciously
And it was still for a time a good investor
Will you call like that
You can be a liar about the big picture
Correct
About
Detail
Kermit play that is a bummer
It is to be all alive and unfortunately
It's not
Trying to scare you with isn't true
But the idea that like at that time if you'd bought gold
You could have made some money if
If you got out at the right time
You know that's not
We've never said that that's not true
No it's actually generally always been largely
A lot of cryptocurrencies
But if you are able to ride them correctly
You can make money on
A lot of people but it's just there like
More examples
All the people who go
Get the fraud
Or
End up blowing
And silver buyers resources
Is Reno from
Copious amounts of
Rip off
Reports on chat like that
They were getting screwed having nothing to do with
The price of gold
So that's that's
Anderson pops up
Zug is a spackle
Sovereigns are hot
I have a hard time realizing I don't think I've ever asked a question
What
It's so he doesn't sell golite of everytime I hear he sells gold
I imagine little bars
That's what I every time you said that
Because a proper size bar of gold
Exercised
No that's what it's called
Mostly coins
That have a certain amount of gold content
Okay so generally British sovereign
Dimes that have silver content in them
From
I don't know how much how many
Currently up printed
But you have these like you can even still find some of them in
Circulation you can find like quarters
From McKnight
Want to hear something like that they don't have
A little bit of
Silver Inn
From specific ears from back when
They had
Silver Inn
He's going solo
One of his walking liberty half dollars or whatever will have
Oz
Gold in it or whatever
What how would you know because of that they're certify
When they were printed
Those were it like that was
How
The more
Non
Historical
Coin
He has are ones that they make specific
This much gold
And then some filler
Evenflo gold coin
Reselling
At all
Whenever that was the way that it works
How could you trust that s***
Who is doing the certifying
I don't know
Currency is always been Magic
Rosie has always been a faith-based
There's so mad about with the idea
Trusting the government
Define to trust
Local
Or the
Centralized coin guy who's making
Coins for this whatever
The point of the show
Happen
I'm at is Alex Jones has
Watson
Paul Joseph Watson
Brother
What I've never heard Paul Joseph Watson on the show in 2009
And now I hear Steve Watts
And boy
He is not ready for primetime
He is boring
Has not been on the show but I haven't heard yet
So far he's not popped up
He's definitely around but he's writing
But Alex hasn't forced him on air yet
A b t w
Comes on
Man if I can't
Imagine
He's on Everett
He's so boring
He is just
Disaster
And I have a working Theory this is my dick
He looks a lot
I think you might not exist what happened with Alex introduced
As like
I think
Did Paul Joseph Watson or Steve Wilkos Olympia
D Watson yes I decided that he wanted to pay checks never come to English
Brother persona
Push them all
So Steve
The Persona comes on and it's just awful
You never comes back on
Does a little bit of like
Little bit of work
Little bit
He's training
It's a little bit better get a little snarky
Getting that glassy eye thing going through looks like he means everything you say
Stronger than ever alright never shows back up on air call Joseph
Takes the mantle out of the Watson
And now Steve Fades into the background much like Paul Joseph Watson
Appears to be in 2009
That's my theory I have nothing to base that on
Except for a picture that I saw Steve
Watson who looks very sick also
A long way to go
I'm going to be honest with you I'm leaving toward that theory more than I am that Paul has a brother I've got to amuse myself somehow I listen
Paul has a brother whose exactly is crazy as hell
Yeah probably
Score in the early days they got on the same page about we can make
The money off this
Does he have a does he have the same Posh British
Center is he like a
Does he have
Lowe's
It's low energy
Just because
What timezone
Because now I'm thinking
Paul Joseph Watson
But just hams it up with a Dick Van Dyke
Kind of
Cockney I
He doesn't do that enough voices that I believe they're from the same
In my area
So boring
And awful and we are going to go
Surprise
Nobody
Questions
How does a box
What's what's in the box
How does that work so what's in the box
Individual
Tyler I appreciate you coming on with us
Call Blue
What's it about
Tyler
Water filters
So sweet
Boring interview with one of the sponsors
Anderson
Is justice
Subsidiary arm of
Wholesale
Soap Limerick guy on all the time
Water filter
Response Iran as a guest
It's clear he has to do this it's cleared there's some sort of a brokering of like you sponsor my show and
I'll let you come on in spots
Now great this guy doesn't say anything that's like as funny as a liberal
Or anything like that
Disappointing but it is
Infomercial Alex's offering
Infomercial space
He's bucking desk
He's not doing well
Guarantee that number of
Bob Chapman coming to be like next week
Gold prices are skyrocketing. Only function of that is to be like Buy It Now
I'll do an infomercial for the water sponsor maybe you get a couple extra bucks from him whatever
Towards the end of the show Alex decides like
Transitioning
Imma take some
And they're all pretty boy
But this one caller says
I want to send send you a my thing I can't find your address anywhere on that little what is wrong with your site why is
An abortion is an abortion I cannot
Find anything because
You have all the stuff I don't mind having the advertising
But the rest of the space that you have like little blocks a little segments
So we can go to whatever segment of the site we want to do tonight
And I go berserk trying to find simple things
Your website sucks
Dude get some f****** web design going
I don't think I don't like it
I don't like to change your voice I'm still going to listen anyways
I don't know
Well you told Alex that he needs
Changes website
It's in.
Maybe you'll change
So that ends the 6th that's a Friday show
Navigate to the 8th
Nathan
Disaster
It's mostly just in reading a bulshit article by Kurt Nimmo
To really go into and then a lot of episode also is about again
Declaring their sovereignty
You've already started
Disgust
The only thing I
My ears perked
At all
Now why Wisconsin try to join them
Chicot power imaginary kontrolfreek every nobody
You can't build a business you can't run a company
They're all little uniform
On power trips Valdese roid head cops
Who been in Iraq confiscating guns killing 1.3 million
They're all coming home to America
To drink our country
Okay
So that's very is I troops
I feel I feel like
From his perspective what he's trying to
BB customer-facing
Persona
The idea of like yeah we're going down but they're getting hurt
To probably isn't
That's not good that's not like that's not in line with what he wants his listeners to think right I mean
Yeah that sounds right
Well yeah but you don't f*** that you don't want that presentation
Absolute I have a working.
His dad just would have made him feel smart
Difficult route
Fascism has a login
Alex Jones dad would have
Weird
My perception
The downfall of America
That's a good boy
That's a weird way to the beauty
February 9th
2009 is also kind of not
Much
There's not much going on on that show
Illustrate how little I think is going on
The only thing
I think it's worth mentioning
Isn't that this is the first time I've heard this
Theme music
That I think is one of the most out of
Place things ever on Alex's show this
Who's the first time
More more
The real quick will get back to the cliff but like
He's using it as a coming in from commercial where is
Always going out
So now it's
Figure this could go like
As a soft reminder that it's time for a commercial break but coming in
Is jari
Engineering
AR testing how covered up the media house
Watchdog group
What he said
Engineered mosquitoes where you
Sounds like it was from Final Fantasy
Compose that right it's so mellow
Zelda dungeon
You know it's like an underwater level in.
It's very weird
He's working off this really
Understand
Anna Gunn article that you read about settlements
Mosquitoes
Low mosquito drones being able
I like it
People is
Absurd because being able to make something
Small enough that they would be
Largely undetected and be able to fly around and
That people was actually able to have like
One person worth of adult that's a milliliter
Yes pretty big
Just like the
The energy capacity that it would need to fly around the middle of
Diculous
The people have gone on record in specified like that technology
Cost-prohibitive
It doesn't exist
No one would be motivated towards creating it
Why not
Vaccines that you need like a flu vaccine
Seeing or mmri never liked require subdermal
Injection summer subcutaneous
Didn't you
Tubi
Like specifically able to make specific injections
It's just it's
The craziest idea
Because if
I mean what you would have is you have to have someone operating
Someone flying around a little tiny mosquito with a milliliter
Worth of what do you think the Nintendo switch was invented for it that's what it's all about
Pixelmon with his ML and then you have to go back to
The HomeBase
It's just going to be lost
This little mosquito drone is going to be lost in the field which happens if mosquitoes
I thought you're out a million dollars
It doesn't really work
There's a lot of like sort of just a fundamental question
Asking about
Technologies
Arizona
Iraq
If you had that kind of a drone
Precise way about
Worried about what
Because
Almost the time
Propeller
How are you doing this
You have to worry about like
It doesn't work that way
Really
Is just putting a little robot right out of mosquito
Can't do that
Lyrics to worry about
Humidity will be just like there's so many factors
Involved
Just make us like
Bill Gates
Omnipod
This one is not
Different track
Alright you build a giant mosquito
Robot
Shrink it down
I'm nodding so you got
That's the start
No doubt about that
Possible
No
I got involved in a invention
Background
Cool that would clean BBQ Grill
Cuz there's a bunch of different things that you need like
Exhausted all right but I made a prototype of this
Mulch
Repurpose tool for cleaning BBQ grills
Entered it in this
Exchange
And I lost
And I gave you a mosquito as a reward
To this girl is hypothetical
Shrink and expand
Proof-of-concept was a Hershey
You would do it it would hit the Loray and then it would turn into that
Willy Wonka
Maybe.
She is she's just she called it to my TV
I'm still mad about this
That was a proof-of-concept
Smith
Alright well I'm still alone
How did she do
No I mean like later on in life how's your drink right well I lost track
You lost track
Mosquito Tek
Alright
Well that's good
Who's winning that contest
Held her that gave her the self-confidence necessary
To pursue a career in giant mosquito
Technology
You're trying to step in the way
Don't make me most.
Is that like I'm sure
She doesn't even remember
Not even a memory for her.
What could have been if I had just won that contest
We move on
To February 10th
Here's where
Fairly interesting
And Alex says about to release
Getting back on his bulshit a little bit
Saying gross things about abortion
Yeah I only kept
Because
I've tried to find
Pacific Ace he's talking about and I can't
Just don't
Mainstreet news story about
Abortion clinics
Partial birth
Exposure
Cockroaches chewing on it
Handle it
So I looked for this read the original article how would they find it did you linked to
I'm not disputing that there might be some sensationalize bulshit article
I haven't found it
But I did look into all this
You know there is a lot of it
To the babies in dumpster
Stuff like that
Dumpsters
Most of the time
If you look
Stories
They are not abortion
They are people who have the baby and want to keep it secret
Whether it's an abusive
Spouse
Abusive
The partner
Or just like a I don't want to deal with this
Kind of situation
Generally speaking
In the same way that when he talks about like
Kids being Captain k
I'm stopped right but like in terms of
Pedophile networks are keeping kids
When you look at
Sometimes the kids have been found in cages
It's almost always the parent
The stories that I kept finding when I looked into this and tried to
Dig it up I don't even want to talk about
Horrifying
Gross people who
Head
They didn't
Take care of it they got no I don't know why even these articles a lot of the time say
It's unclear why they didn't deal with it yeah but then they end up having the baby at home
Thrown in dumpster
Like as if that is going to deal with the issue
It was like a sorority
College student
And she had the baby
Her bathroom
And then put it in a trash bag and threw it in the dumpster
And I texted her boyfriend
No baby
So like
Wow no more baby or something like that
To the extent that I didn't find like a police report on this
Also I'm going to take this with a grain of salt
But I think it was like a new Republic
It's not like
It's not like some place that makes up
Things whole cloth
Yeah I like that but yeah
It's going to be
You have stuff like this
Do you have stuff like
You know Kermit Gosnell
That's a doctor who was cutting up babies
And stuff like that that's not a story about abortion being a problem that's a story of a
Do you have a couple of instances like this
Confine
Analysis
As best I can tell he's trying to
To turn
The
The fear of the reality of people like Gosnell
And these
People who do this
This to their own child
And apply that
Two abortions
It's it's
Problem is what
He described
Is a cartoon
2nd and the door gets locked behind
Flying out
And it's sliding around on the floor while other nurses
Anything quick
Across the room like a greased Pig and then it dies of exposure
Ladies around with billy club
Youtooz just like
That's what I'm saying it sounds like they're people with hammers like they're always just people with big phone
Mallets are at an abortion clinic like
Well it depends if the baby comes flying out of there we got to be we got to have backup for this abortion I would say
70s
Especially Horsham clinic
Pretty keenly aware
People want to kill them
I generally take today
Much more aware
Even if you wanted to
Do what we just were sarcastically discussing guys like
A possibility
I think I think of a Go Far More by the book
And that's why whenever these things come out by like
Zookies
For the Center for Medical progress
It's always
Crazy edited videos
And it's always
Outright manipulation
To try and make these people look like they're doing the thing
They want their listeners to
Afraid that they're doing
So
Long-held belief that
I like I like it because there's nothing you can do there's no amount of Purity that you can
They're going to portray you as what they want to do matter what
Like don't even is like what
Who gives a s*** like
Obama never had a chance
Would never have given him a shot
It'd be so great if you do
Just like
Suck my balls on the table
That's my issue with liberals
We don't swing Ardex on the table
Conservative swing their dicks all around I think it's fine for
I am coming around to your position a little bit more
Clarification
Like in terms of
Versus
Like what is the right
Decorum
I don't I don't
It's wrong to scream at
Anybody who's involved with Trump
I never did
Be at the line that I had for a
The longest time was like
Well we are going to have to eventually figure this out and eventually we're going to
To have to work
He's out and eventually
There are people who are
Conservative who are come from
Positioning
We should not
Abused
Persuasion
Time goes on
The last unless I hear any of those horses
Right the more it becomes
I'm very clear to me
That's our priority is the people whose
Existence is in jeopardy
You go ahead and
Go ahead and take the service of the Broad Run
Baby 6-9 months ago I kind of scared a little bit about the idea of like
Let's be fair to people
And not put them in these groups
Especially with that
TV's polls
Conservative
Like
Supporting every
Well
This
Lowe's 20% or whatever that are on board
But f*** you because the other 60% is
Kill my friend
That's not cool
Just always goes back to life
Think about who's standing around
When you're at a rally
Look around
Do you want to be at that rally
And if you are one of the 20% of conservatives is like
But I'm still calling myself a conservative
Go fuc yourself
Music classic thing of like
Like if you're cool hanging out with nausea
Because you are enough
There's not a thin line.
There's no line at all you just are
Yep
Washington Post article that was about the
That's my new my new show it'll be on a.m.
Starbucks at I mean
Walking potok
Strong
Sarah Huckabee Sanders should not have been kicked out
I agree with you is that Nazis are bad
We need to
Of all the things to care about right now
What's Sarah Huckabee Sanders is allowed to do I don't give a fuk I don't give a fuk
Even if I agreed with
In the longer sense
We'll get to that later dude
Whenever all of this s*** is behind
But
Then we can talk about decorum
Let's bail bonds
That conversation
Is even like a disservice to the reality of the world
Even the civility conversation that
Seems to be happening on
The internet
I think even that is like
We should just
Reject like we shouldn't even
You didn't even have those sorts of Articles just hard pass no thank you
It's just a
Diamond all seem to boil.
From the right
Responses to
Sarah Huckabee Sanders not being allowed to eat
Eat at this restaurant
Seem to be that like
Your actions
Are different than you being apart of
Civil Rights Act
How many
And we're not bothering anybody
And got married and would like to take for that
The jail all the time all the time
Did you see that video of George
Peterson
Being interviewed by Jim
Jim Jefferies
I heard about it though
It's basically just Peter does
Libertarian
Just brings up the idea of the Civil Rights Act is like
Okay so based on the argument
Businesses
Shouldn't be able to serve
Black people if they don't like
All day all
Basically waffle
They all just fall apart in the fact that Jim Jefferies brings this up Jordan Peterson
Have you like
I might be wrong
What the f***
How did you not think of
And the fact that it was
Disastrous
How dare you
You need to go on hiatus
Like this is the intellectual version of like
I got to go to rehab
Got to go to rehab perfect perfect
Analogy
Got in trouble got a little too
To Buckwild one night and then like alright
I don't want everyone to hate me
I'm going to rehab
Go away
Film Iron Man
That's what you got to do you got to go away to come back
You're going to be huge
With not being a homophobe
Exactly
So now
We get to the next one
On a lot of
Against his libertarian
Values
Yeah
Hydrocodone and going home and
Turn your lights out
So that's a long pause.
But I wanted
Very easy
I believe that Libertarians do believe that you have the right
And your own life
If you are in excruciating
You have the right over your own body
The of that
No one stop
Going to the dent
Justin getting a ton of hydrocodone
Is I'm pointing out okay in order for you to
Did you
Who's willing to be your accessories
In your suicide of yourself
You need to conveniently dental surgery for that in a long hydrocodone
Have you ever been to the gym already
No matter what you're going to need a sister
Somehow guaranteed to eat
Getting that hydrocodone
Or you're going to need Kevorkian
You know like you need one of
And there's no way around that
We'll get to it
During right now
People want the right to die
Then he says
Well nobody's stopping you
From finding a way to kill yourself
His whole point is that like
People who are arguing that like old
You should be able to choose to die with dignity
Which I think is probably
Believe that better way to fry
Yeah those people that
Food that's really bad
And s*** like that
Reject the premise
You shouldn't the law.
To come in
And make it okay for someone
To help you died
Because that's just going to get other people
Don't want to die killed
Where is you should just be able to go
Be able to
Specifically
Should just go to your dentist to get a bunch of pills
Rather than kill yourself
Right or what do you suggest
Close and turn the car on
You want to kill yourself go ahead
The whole point here is
Did they want to pass a law
All those things killing people
I do I RKO you
I reject the premise
Because
Documentaries about people who choose to end their own life
Assisted suicide
States that allow it
Yeah I've seen something
No no
You had to go through like that
You need a proof
Psychological
That they are deciding
I have a disease
Super painful
And is going to
To be a miserable experience to go through I would rather check out now when I can be around my loved one
And what have you is so the idea that he's like now this is a slippery slope
This cruel cruel
The anger that he is
Expressing with
You can't turn on the gas
That's really everybody else around kill blow up a house
Did you just turn on your gas
And then off yourself
It's like if you were single person and there's no one to find
Entire house with gas
Could blow up a block
And then also the
Do that that exhausted your
Your garage one
You might kill your kid
Stumble Inn
There's Auntie pass out
Possible there's a lot of
There's a lot of real serious
Problem
With that like I did like
Here's how you do it
Here's how you do it stopped
Give you a
Lethal injection that you
Ask for around your loved ones
Checkout noticeably absent
Dunce
Weather
Like his vet
Never know which is what I asked cuz I don't want to bring that up
Almost
14 lakh
Because it is far as the law goes
For me the law should just be like the f*** that noise
Where do I go for cancer and you get to press the button that says f*** that noise
Get on out
You know like that kind of thing
Go
Like if you want to go
Sleepily with drug
If you want to
I've been busy
Is weird baby I'm going to
Safari
Scenarios for us if you want to
I think you should be
Thunder Lakers
How to take drugs in
Or maybe you're weird and you're last Moana
You don't want that
Now yeah
Blacked out and safe
Like because of the drug maybe the last moment with your family is you think I would type
The Green River Killer
That I would even want to leave out the mystery you might be super high on whatever those death
Drugs are French
Then I'll tell him I got you
No I can't but in order to avoid
There's ways to do that safely
I just I disrespect this position
Hey I know that he's afraid of Obamacare and all that
I get I get why he wants to
To spread his political for your butt
The real-world impact of this
Is really really ugly
Specifically
Because that be
Denying you your choice
Absolutely he's trying to protect his ideas by saying
You can go kill yourself
We just shouldn't allow it under the law
Bright like that doesn't make
Make sense
Is
They want to steal
Give you a kiss and then it's on the floor
Then
Defense Alex on this show role plays what it's like
When a nurse
Is with a pregnant
I want to hear this
You feel safe at home
Money
Is fat
Despacito
Oh okay okay
What is good luck for everyone
You probably don't even need to pay your taxes
If you don't be surprised because they're too busy doing it to everybody else
You probably having experiences but everyone else
Please Don't Talk Amongst yourselves
About others never happens
Ridiculous
Oh you're having money troubles
Putting in the paperwork
Steal the baby
Got a little
She's got like a little bag teller secret alarm button underneath the
This is crazy
It is
It is in line with it
This song
World's you that he has about family
Like that
So I can have anybody get
There does need to be
Implement of the state
If kids are being a
Abuse
It's stuff like that like you to need
Some sort of recourse
I don't like
Tweet we get a trend
Positive
He's really talk
Here we are
We are going into the control grin and with it comes a facekini cameras the secret police
The public illegal aliens
Clean-cut good-looking police
People
Clean cuts
Good-looking picture looking
Families now they leave everyone who looks like they're foreigners alone
Right
Could be anybody
Certainly not clean-cut good-looking family
She's not even a citizen
About her
I know that this is
Repetition
To my madness too
And just remind it do we need
Reminders
Talks about positive
It does seem to
To be like
He's talking about white
And there's a differentiation
People who are weird
Indifferent
Clean-cut American
Good family
Again
This is the weakest link
It's so obvious
Terrible
You go to a place like well any
I would like all the mainstream conservative Outlet they're just running towards his side
The guy the guy who said you're out of your cotton-picking mind like
You you are running
They used to be better out of these stupid things
This is where you're like I don't even know
Something that I never predicted
I don't even think
This was the case at the Alexa
I'm not I'm not 100% sure cuz I was not a
Scholar
Fox News
Forsyth
But I never would have predicted even in
What we would end up with
Is
Fox News
Coming like our
Like I didn't think that what would happen is that we would experience
But like
That is what's happening
Like a light
Did the the overwhelming portion of right-wing media is now
Blending towards
Well they have to
Well I mean
In in
They didn't they do kind of have to in order to door
In order to continue existing as they are grounded
Run or something
And they can't do that
So
You have to because the reality is he's doing everything that you said you
That you said Obama was doing
You have to make up reasons to book disbelief
And the more reasons you make up to disbelieve thing
The best way to disbelieve something is to
Create something else to believe in
IE the global
Hugo
Deep State on Fox News
Those things in order to
Cuz they're smart enough to know like
About
The connotations of using the specific
SeaWorld
How to deal with it
Other than Alex
Yeah it's the same guy
Gabby
Show me the other day
He was on Fox and Friends
And he was talking about the
And he was the one who said they're not argue.
And there was a there was another
Confront talking about
How are
America has not had
Purity
Something like
Scandinavian countries
They marry each other but we marry other breeds and races
Yeah
Covert
Nazi Network
That work is that crazy
Although at the same time I saw a regular Fox News
Like like the news part
Fox News is
They're their opinion programming programming
Represents itself exactly like their new show
And I saw one of their regular Fox new shows
Legos cute to see them try
Is cute
What's about to happen is
On the 10th of February
Gentleman by the name of Charles key
You might remember him
Cuz I brought him up earlier
Guy from Oklahoma
Who
Is putting forth that sovereignty belt
Very funny
McAllister
He comes on his again
Charles Keith
And we find out
We find out the reason
Did Alex Jones for the last cookies
Now where the tap
One of the reasons that
He's pushing
The states
Asserting their sovereignty narrative
Just Like Heaven
This is exciting and there's a deeper reason
Sunshine
Oklahoma pass the resolution
Boxer rescue
We're not going to put up with those things you're not doing and can't
Brave
This is what you know what else
We're going to stop at stop sign
I don't know if that would have passes a house resolution would make
Alex Jones
Is that Oklahoma passed a resolution like this
Retaliatory action
In order to amend the Thunder
Right now
I
Find this
I do all right
Give several examples why
I will in a moment but before I do
Here's my here's my stated
About things like
Oklahoma City is a really big
We were going to get into it it would require
A lot of research that I've done already
And I don't give a
Not because I don't care about the people who died or anything like that
But because the burden of proof is on Alex
If he wants to say
Did Oklahoma City was that's too broad a claim
I don't know what to do with that
I need him to give me a specific
I need him to point out one thing
And then I'll look into that and we can go from there
If he says this
Did they pass this resolution
Oklahoma City
They put that.
The teacher
There's nothing I can do with
There's no
There's no amount of research
Search that I can do
Prove it
Tenuous connection
Unfortunately
In this interview Alex does bring up a
Seabreeze up Tarrant
Soccer broadcast
Now
He's a police officer in Oklahoma City
Saved a bunch
The bombing
Pulling out
Between 4 and
People from the wreck
Before falling
Through hole
Another building
He fell two floors and injured his back
And after that
He became very
Despondent
Felt an immense amount of guilt
Because
And wasn't able to save more people
Ended up committing suicide
Buddy you're after the Oklahoma
Before he was supposed
Receive
A huge honor
Before that
Started to say things like I don't
Don't deserve this
And things like that
Now imposter syndrome
I've reviewed a lot of the evidence
That conspiracy theorist was tortured and
Killed
Reveal
That it was also okay
Because
He thought he was part of the whole conspiracy
He believes
Is that underpinning
Names of the Oklahoma
Conspiracy
Is the Terrance yeakey was
A cop who was involved
He was about to go public
And
Deal with it
I was making a bunch of statement
In the heavy quote murdered
Write the suicide was Ice
Actually a murder
That's it looked over everything
The Terrance yeakey
Murdered
Looks like an all-too-common
Distance of tragedy being
Compounded
The oak Oklahoma City Bombing with a complete
Suicidal
Who by all accounts
Seems to be a good-hearted man
Just another layer of that tragedy
Circumstances of his death
Particularly outside of what you might expect
Suicide being done by someone who is not
Suicide before
Deer tattoos
Superficial cuts to his wrist
Throat
But died from a gunshot wound
This might seem strange
But in reality
Harder than you make
To flash your wrist
So
The circumstances were Vicky
It was in his car
Have you tried to slash his wrists
Conceivably his
Yeah and then
There's a bunch
Blood
The car
His car was last
You wandered about it
The mile-and-a-half
Your modern about a mile-and-a-half
He was found
In this field
Having shot himself
So the issue is
It takes an amazing
That's the right word but
That to cut yourself deeply enough to kill you
I know this sounds really
Indelicate
And awful but it does
I think we're
You think
This sucks
This sucks to talk about
Was there
I
Did the whole thing
Really hard to do
I speak from experience myself
Yeah
It's it's that you don't you don't
AAA
It's like a
Really really close to trying to
Cuz you're doing it with your own hands
It's really close to trying to strangle yourself with your own hair
Exactly
It takes
Take some
You don't you don't
Understand without having
Gone
You have to go
Super deep and you have to really mean it
I'm not saying you didn't mean it when he was trying to cut his wrist but like
There are ways that you can kill you
Overdosing
Or a gunshot that are more like a button
Bright crafts
Overdosing
In that state you hope that it does
Sprite and whiskey
You done but Lake
Cutting yourself is like
You might
Think it's deep enough but
That might have been what he found himself
I'm not
Sure
If you're walking a mile
And then you shoot
It wasn't there
So now to reframe things a little bit cuz this is very important
Believes
He was attacked in the car
And then drag
A mile-and-a-half
Batman killed
Now the problem
Never said is why the hell with the murderer is caught him up
Barely cleanly but not enough to kill him
Which likely would be impossible if you were fighting back
Particularly considering that the cuts are on his wrist
And his throat
You know like you'd be fighting and then
If you're trying to not kill him
But then you get deep enough cuz he's fighting back it would there's no way to to
Create vets
Scenario
Without going too far
Nosey Parkton
Pittsfield
Car which means that they would have had to been in
Enclosed face with
And further any of the cut
He had would clearly cause blood stains on the murderer
And more importantly do blood stains
In the car
Where the murderer would have been
That's physical evidence of a person
His car would be open and shut
Doesn't exist
Then
You have to consider that these murderers would have to think
It was a good idea to not kill him in the car where they've already done most of the work
But instead of a mile-and-a-half
To take approximately 30 minutes
Under normal average walking condition
But would probably be slow down
By the barbed wire fences in the way
And the very heavy
Human who is he was 6 ft tall 3 in
The murderer would have to be dragging
Yeah it was 66 357
Dragged him in there
Conspiracy theory of mile-and-a-half after attacking him in the car he's bleeding but not
Possibly still conscious
A mile-and-a-half
Very fair to assume that that would take 45 minutes
50 minutes
Generously
To cover that
The murderers would have had 240 reason
Risk being out in the open with their victim
For almost an hour when it any point he could scream or anyone
Accidentally stumble on there
That makes no sense from any perspective
What is the job that needs to be done
Could have been done right there in the
The car
Then
For no reason they would have to
Choose an arbitrary
Spot where I guess
They walked far enough
Where they decide to shoot
Which they very much or even back at
If car is a terrible plan
No one would have done it
It's much easier to rationalize the idea that his wrists and throat
And realized
He couldn't do it you couldn't do it to the extent that would he wanted to end the
His life
But he couldn't do it that way
Exact reason for leaving the car is anyone's guess I don't
Pretend to have any idea what it would be
But it could have been a fear that an errant shot
If you was shooting himself could have blown up the car and caused
Access damage
The field he was in
Like a wildfire
The idea that he would wander towards
His childhood hometown
El Reino which is
Clothes to wear
He ended up being his body was found
Finish the suicide makes total sense
I have no idea what the reality is but there could have been a Sentimental attachment
Place where he ended
Simple as that where he fell in ran out of enough strength
Text Carrie on
The idea
There was a downward
Trajectory
To the bullet went through his head
Okay
People bring up as a Eva
The murder is not
There are a hundred different possible explanation
For that one of the easier ones
Is better to be the safest way to
You shoot yourself if you're expecting
A possible In-N-Out shot
An upward trajectory could leave that bullet
Nothing else
Pecos popping out
Beyond kind of
Just feels natural if you put a
Fake gun to your head like this and it kind of feels like
There's a little bit of a downer
Projector
Can see that even passed that a person's head could be
Loud when they're doing this
To themselves and that would make it down to Rashad
Also much more likely
Settings Maurice
So I started to look into his life
That's just the details of the actual event
Looking into that stuff was really
Top because it's
It's ugly
Thinking about that stuff
Is never fun
Gregory
So I read an article in People magazine
The 1990
Was called up for service
Persian Gulf
They're his duties included the mass burial of civilian
Has killed in the war
Back
You could tell there was a major
Vicki he wasn't
Same
There's an incredibly High likelihood that what was happening was
Did he suffer from PTSD
Miss PTSD was re triggered Isaac
Experience in El Cajon
City bombing
Again from people
On the night before his death sheriff's deputies found him sitting
Disoriented in
Car by the roadside
Vicky's house we're exhausted
You spoke about the explosion
Inviting that he was haunted by the images
Dead children
Terrified of his own night
Call I'm afraid of what I might do
The former Canadian.
More details about this specific
The former Canadian
Sheriff
Clint Boling
At the county that El Reino is
He said okay
Doesn't concur with the analysis
Bowler said the Yankee showed up at his house in Delran on the afternoon of his death
His car stop it
Call in the middle of the road
When his girlfriend Kate Allen
The paramedic ran outside
They found a police officer
Virtually passed out
Quote he couldn't tell us his name and
Lisa Tallon
He was a real he was very anxious
His heart rate was rapid he was sweaty
He told us he'd been having constant
Problems
Slap get all the appearances
My first guest
Someone who is having emotion
No problems
And my second guess would be
Of course
Some kind of substance
Abuse problem
Basically they
Michigan is a quote
From
Bowler
Basically they are you talkin about parents
Does family
Ended up calling to pick him up
And ideally take him
Refuse to go to the hospital and family just let him leave
Course they just let him go
Said bowler
We told those people you needed help
We knew he was suicidal
He had all the classic
It appears the parents suffered from a severe combination
The PTSD from the Horrors
Experience in the Gulf
Mixed with survivor's guilt of not being able
Save more people in Oklahoma
Not to mention further PTSD
Experiencing that terrorist
Caswell
The Murrah building deep and Yankees
Distressed what other saw is
Does heroism he regarded
This failure
He'd say
How do I not fall in
I could have saved more lives
It's recalled his biological mother L Margera
Terrence fell and hurt his back
In his efforts to rescue people at the Murrah building
Something that he was deeply ashamed
And most likely led to him being prescribed opiates
To deal with the pain
It's unclear if that was the case but it's
It is said repeatedly medication
As a very common prescription
Made in cases of
Consistent app
Caught you taking medication
For his backs
The Canadian County
Sheriff
Skid 45 medication
Cinestar
Absolutely
Murrah building
Definitively say for date people that day
His ex-wife
Tony Rivera alleges that he was
Or that he said that he wasn't there
Which indicates her either not quoting him well
Or testify stand being in a very bad emotional state when he said so
Hello cuz line
Additionally in a reflection of behaviors that are unfortunately,
Returning Soldier struggling
PTSD
Appears to have had a history of making a violin
Quote in a fit of temper Yankee had once threatened
To take his life
And those of his wife
So he done
And that sort of State
That dude was fun
It makes zero sense that quote today
Would wait 13 months to kill the
Person who allegedly seen evidence
But the whole thing was a setup
Many of the arguments that are made involving his
Fall that happened rescue effort
During a during the rescue efforts
Have to do with the idea that he
He fell through some floors in the
Undetonated bomb
Which is Ray Weaver
Stuff up
In the absence of any truth
Perpetually Bass
Syndication
People say that that
Is what
This is pure fiction used using some basic
Details like the fall the tragic
Suicide at cetera
And forcing them to fit the predetermined
Conclusion that these people want
How to push forth
Iey terrorism is never real
It's always fall Flags done by the government
Meant to demonize white people
Going to take away guns
It's incredibly Des
Yep The Story Goes
How much more of this
Piper Reed
Hellboy
I am going to be honest I think we're good
No because I need to
Explain
I need to explain to you that like
The reason that people think that there is something
Conspiratorial here
Is not based on any real evidence
It's Allstate
His ex-wife
Tanya Tony Rivera
They all Trace back to
Like I've looked
Through the claims
They have no backing
There's notes
Support to them
Their nonsensical
To ascertain
This really quick
One of the one of the stories
Or the story that Alex would believe
Is it Terrance yeakey was handcuffed
Horribly beaten
In his
Experience
At the end of his life
The conspiracy sites
Allege that he had someone else's blood on
However this is not from any official report
Well dr. Larry balding Oklahoma City
Alexander quickly ruled the death a suicide
Another medical examiner's report would according to Tony Rivera
Surface
Erie press
Message from the grave
This is something
His ex-wife is a legend
Mysterious second medical examiner
Report
Even necessarily exist based on any other
I did get a hold of it and the report said that Terry balding
Great hair
Lot of hair amazing amazing
It's like a guy name
Mini
Smiles
Benny's
Medical examiner's report
University
Created
Why would it also
Just be alleged by this
Where is that guy is was he commissioned
Why would the government if they were trying to cover things up
It's better hire another guy to get the real
The other further Evidence about this goes like this
Function review
Sister had a chance encounter with a mortician who worked on Yankees body
She was discussing
Astringent
The death of someone at the party
Not knowing the woman was Rivera's sister spoke up
Quote that sounds like
Just like Apple
Police officer we worked on it Oklahoma City
But you said when asked if the
Deterrence Yankee the mortician
Freak
Murderers and those covering up his death had not counted on the
This particular morticians test
That is not a credible story anyway
This story that's being told is completely unnamed alleged mortician that Rivera is claiming that
Unspecified social
Horrible
Really remember drunk
The story of without further back
Mortician
Statement that he made him come
Means nothing it's just another
Piece of dubious
Information coming from this Rivera
Now here's a
What's Miss Rivera's
Axe to grind
She has a vested
Have not had a
Committed suicide
Insurance
And there we go
I'm not saying that's a hundred percent
The reason that
She would do this I understand also grief
I also understand
Kind of like to make stuff there's no such a thing
There's those sorts of aspect
Time there was
Allowed if it wasn't a suicide
And it she has a very strong
Financial interest
Bob maker
I just have to be clear cuz I know nothing about her
Except for that restate
She's made that most of the
Conspiracies about this
This guy revolve around don't make sense nothing behind
You can't find it
Just when you look at them
Document it that
And that doesn't
Exist and
Timesheet
So I don't know
So this is been my very long way of saying
Alex finally brought up a
Pacific about Oklahoma City
And I don't buy it
I'll buy it one bit
You got them
Somebody knocking at the door
I don't do a bus to stop there too gross cuz I do feel so bad for the guy
I totally
Like that's that's a brutal situation
If you never had a chance to any did something
Along with v like
Threatening to kill his kids
Nope
No there's no there's no there's no way we
Tyrell
Positive figure but
The idea of turning him in
To someone who was going
Unleashed this information
Again 13 months after
We could have done any of this
Told people definitively what he was going to reveal or have any of his things on a dead drop
It's just Alex Jones trying to call
Created
Charles Keith
Trying to create
A character
Story much the same way out
Been trying to do
Was Anthony Bourdain
Write the same sort of behavior
And it's pink
Credibly just
Also Charles key
Charles Kelley
Chuck
Chucky
He also
I believe the election right before this to the Oklahoma
State Legislature
F****** 531 on a technicality
Greener pastures
2018 where everyone is screaming at members of the Trump campaign
Not allowing them to
It's delightful it's wonderful
Alex is not into it
Now what is he saying about this sort of behavior 9 years ago
Yep
Interruption
Church
Talks
I mean Stephen Miller should have two black eyes so big it's tough to get around like
So high agree I agree I agree
Because I feel like I didn't
My point perfect
Clear was that Carmelo had a terrible season 2
10A should not have been
Is over they called it the big three
About that
Because it's an umbrella
The
The Narrative that he's pushing
About the states
Is very clearly and service
Those beliefs that he has but Oklahoma City
He's
Using this narrative in order to Hope
That something happens in one of those
And then he could be like it's just like Oklahoma City over again okay I just had to make that clear cuz I'm
Okay so what you're saying is immediately is like his point is immediately after Oklahoma original
Did the saying right
Then the bombing happen
To teach him a lesson
If something happens in any one of these damn I got another okay so I can make
Very clearly obvious
He's doing
Once you get a smell of him
You kind of get used to it it's so clear what he's doing
Please let someone bomb Oklahoma again
Arizona
Missouri
Come on I want to buy I need
So
Bright
I will say
That I generally hate Alex Jones
Listcrawlers
This guy enters the pantheon of people who like
I'd like you to know that a lot of us couples listen to your show all the time
And my wife made an interesting
Comment I think I'm going to pass it on to you
She would like to see you have more
Women
The rainbow
In The Patriot movement and the Second Amendment movement on your show with guest
It's just a hint she wanted to pass along
Open your website
BMW bikes
Old weird anti-communist John Birch Society
Maybe you should have some women in The Patriot auto there aren't
Any other ladies hazan
Rodger Stone first appear on Coursey died
Soon enough that's not enough
Credit First
F*** Krauthammer
I did that guy being like ladies on
F****** agree with her but I'm still going to make it
Comet weird Alex Jones
Well I'm
Down Home Country hillbilly but I think they Equal Pay Act should have been past 40 years ago
Oh that's all I'm trying
Alex I do declare you need to respect the voice of the latest
Where the women on your show Alice
Like a f****** feminist Foghorn lately I don't think they should be allowed
Not fair I bet this guy is totally totally into women voting
Such a contradiction
Totally I love it
He's just got one Progressive streaking
Otherwise he's a normal Alex Jones
Something to build on caller I don't like this next caller much
You hear about that guy's wife and what she said
Ladies
I am
Distribute
Credit Bureau
Are copies of your
Come out to people
Have you heard of anybody else
Been more less what a friend of mine called black bag
Mac
February
Go
Then we detected that somebody had
Been in the house maybe
Heather didn't
Seem to be anything missing
Her Disturbed too much and
I thought it kicked our imagination until II
Look at
Original copies of your DVDs
And every last one of them it looks like somebody took sandpaper
Went from one side to the other on
I'll tell you what's going on
Okay
Also
You need to describe
Fold-out
September 1st
New this guy inside job
He has
Maybe he's at a local bar
Now that we've got a Fed in house
So many possibilities
Caribou this is the game that you played
You try and push pay
Patriots
So I would say
Do you have any pets
Levi my first question
Are you keeping those DVDs
Is it possible that you kept them in like an unsafe place anyway
Ivan's a whole bunch I did leave them dangling precariously above my circuits yes
Collection
Garden
Magic like a philatelist he's got them all
Pins
Not most of my furniture is Cactus based
There's a hundred explanations I can come up with for Howard other than breaks in
My blankets are woven from my own
Stubble
That could be good my blankets the Beast
Alright that's a bush
I'll tell you what's going on
Can I get back to the sky
You stay right there I heard it as whites
We're black back to the rest of the show
Maybe.
Okay we are going back to Curtis Brown
Ducks to small-town
Abilene
What happened to 2004 I don't know the details of it the only information I can
Can fighter from like ronpaulforums
Right
Planet articles I don't drive
Now I have no idea is probably more to the story but I have
But yes they probably went in your house looking for something
There are no real terrorists but
Last year
They said this is wrong but we have to show
Don't like videos
Yes
Don't know why
Ballpark ballpark round 300
That's a good answer
I don't know man I don't feel like it's good to reinforce people paranoia like that feel like that's a very unhealthy
Bi did absolutely trap
People into
Terrorism
But
Wasn't
Wasn't black bag and white people
I'll tell you that right now
I don't know if you know anything about the FBI
Long history
Terrible things
Waste their time breaking it
Someone tries to scratch out
Abilene absolutely another copy
From the
Freely available internet stores
So now you got it
What you
Haha you actually just wind up getting another and car.
We've wasted 2 hours of this old dudes for the feds
I don't understand I don't understand any of this
There's such a benign explanation that his dog just so I can scratch them or something like
Who's 100 different explanations
I like the difference it's so disgraceful
Need to do is become even more radicalized to my team
Are numbers
Much better than they are now but
Well
Think of anything that's on YouTube
Weird phone call
Ex-wife 31 Moore clips
Alex wants to
The make you scared about how the military doesn't exist
Brainwashing
But job
Cool cool
It is
2009 style is that like it's not
He will give you whiplash of the present-day but it'll be like
Yeah, you caught me off-guard you got me unawares
But I like the
Security by 2009
Real tight
Yeah pretty good
The primordial ooze
From which
The modern-day at Hibbett's will eventually come
Absurd
Jordan over this
Discourse
I think is the most important is that one of Alex Jones is pillars
It is Oklahoma City narrative is b*******
Right now
Find out what kind of
States are declaring their sovereignty
Is very relevant to Modern Day stuff
Sovereignty is what he has a boner for now
It's very relevant that he's only really using that as I as the interstitial way to set
The table
To make propaganda
An attack happens
It's clear because he's not it
Dealing with the fact that
All of this resolution
All of us house resolutions that are put in biology States
They are a coordinated group of quote-unquote
He's not he's trying to present it is
Burgeoning up in August
And that's not the case at all
And he's also not dealing with the fact that
In the same way that he doesn't
Address that
Those FEMA camp bills that he's makes people so scared of
Are real
And they'd never made it out of committee
Most of these don't make it out of
Make a resolution of the Law's the law
We're not scared that a black guy's the president
And that's really what's driving
The other half
And if
How many terrible
This is just
Terrible
Yeah
We should wrap this up
Ironic it is a never-ending source of irony
That
Immediately after Obama got elect
The conservative media
Went hard into him turning into a tyrant
Putting people in Camp
Doing all of this s***
And then at their
Alexa guy
Who does all the s*** that they thought of Obama was going to
I'm really glad you brought that up because that's
Good
Cliffhanger
Faraar episode that will come out
Tomorrow
As an emerging
Call know are we going back to the present day
Okay thank God
Call Ryder
Please leave a review all that stuff
Help
People like helping us
Help in terms of growing the audience
Any help in terms of our audience
No absolutely not
We kind of don't want more of you but on the other side of that we need a whole lot more
We don't want more people good-hearted.
And so unlike most
Chose
That want to become big
Guys
Keep this real quick
I don't snitch
Tell people you know we're cool right
Let them hear about the show we want a game
One listener added
Pretend like we are people selling drugs
The terrible plan
Alright so we're going to get out of here it's my turn
And there's no way any other way
Been saying
Oklahoma
Representative
Charles Keith
Go check yourself
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color