Holding
Alex
Beverages this case of blood orange IPA
3rd Dan
Jordan
Being pressured into
Of a garlic hot sauce soft peer-pressure sauce
Continue to fight back 40 episodes of Archer
And or hot
I just wanted it
A lot about hot sauce
Weak tea I was raised on
Look
Wendy's spicy chicken sandwich spicy thing I ate until I was like 45
Spicy
Fast food items like a volcano
Very good
We're doing a little bit of a
Because this is a minisode it'll be two hours
And our last episode was
February 6th
The temp right
Alex appeared in such a way
That I could not include it in the entirety of that episode
You insisted this to me
Multiple times and I couldn't explain to you beforehand because of the premise of this show
Got to keep going
We got to get into it but just spiritually thank you everybody was supposed to show fuel exports go to knowledge
Fight.com
Show button
Now we need to get to the important issue
I wouldn't
To you it is wasn't like
A very real
Furious
Issue
I don't trust
Here is what we need to talk about
You'll be able to memorize any type of information
They fix the pronunciation
State commercial
Is it
What happened
Someone's like hey guys that's not
Also you don't have enough women on this
So let's not talk about that
Intro
Uncle
Text Jessica past 34 learning that we heretofore did not know exist absolutely
Aspiring that there's hope for everyone if you can learn that medomak
Is based on lies
So actually here's what I want
Well okay
Of course is referring to an article this morning
That is in the El Paso
Is reporting this
Going over that
Coming up
After
Don't
He's really stretching about me don't tell me about
He's really
Dan don't tell me what's going to happen
If you say it's very bad
Alex is going to say
The Disney Prime
Alex is going to say that your government
Is encroaching upon you Alex
This is the worst thing that
You should revolt and overthrow this government Alex is going to say government
But does this type of things is invalid
And it's not acceptable and that we should literally draw a line in the sand
And leave that government or perhaps
F****** Destroyer
Is that what I was going to say that
Not entirely I think there's some there's some of the undertone your
Getting correct but the reason that I need to talk about this
Is not because of
Had a realization
About Alex Jones
About why he's not a hippie
Okay this is a big this is a big deal I should just tell me on this hard
Really should have understood this sooner and I think
Naivete
Something that I
Listening to this episode from the 11
Brought into sharp Focus
That
I should have been paying much closer
Retention
Listening
He's actually talking about
Because we
So often what we do is we hear things like
I was just going
In that
Sometimes what you miss
What doesn't
Swept up into the
That's not the right one
Or whatever
Is the spirit of what he's actually talking about at this next clip
Really problem
This is your mic down clip
Because he's very prescient
About certain things
But then he also presented in a way
To all along
The big failure on our part.
We had
And they are part
Outside Austin
Portum
Grab the children
Process as well
Set the precedent
So
The part of it that the FEMA camp stuff that he's talking about
But
The part that I need
The scales dropped from my eyes looking
Originally
Was when he said it's a beta
His whole
Problem
With mystery
Of Emigrant
His whole problem with the mistreatment of people who
You don't worry about them being treated poorly
Is that it's a beta test
Because eventually there's a
Yeah they're going to do it to us
You know what
Because I had that thought
Recently
This has always been there
Like watching all of this s*** happens like
Really when you stop and think about the people that are doing
Do you think they really don't want to do the same thing to Progressive
Just like us
Communist sympathizers and
Don't specifically Target f****** Fred Hampton and Martin Luther King jr.
The only archers
Has an evil president been assassinated
Has somebody who has committed all of the evil
That could possibly be done even if I'd was Reagan actually get killed
I don't know enough about McKinley
He's just I just don't know enough about
Sure
He was
Note
I like to I like I told you before the show you were going to scream about you like I probably won't
But apparently I jumped before 9 it's fine the neighbors are cool
Oh God.
Better
That
Mentality
Is made me take a very serious pause
The idea of it like I was a beta test
That they would abuse
Immigrant
And stuff like that
It indicates to me because I I think this tracks with his
He doesn't care what happens to them
He cares that eventually it's going
Happened to good
If you put
Good
Clean-cut
Families
Who are people
Now hear me out on that note I don't agree with it now
When we have in the past you've been screaming about FEMA camps forever
And now we have these camps
Where parents are being separated from their children I would have you
The reason critical for him to be like
It's fine it's because he knows with Trump in power
The Next Step isn't going to happen
White people are safe
And that to me was a heartbreaking moment listening to this episode
Because
Back then there was a black president and it made him
Next
And now we have an overtly racist president and he's like
Ernie is fine you have a president who's legitimately saying like about
G Ching ping
View president liked that sort of stuff that his principles should have led him to be like
No this is tyranny
On any on any scale
This is how you end up in a position where you were in the tyrannical
Dictatorship authoritarian rule
But because the person is presenting themselves as so fine with white
People and sofa
With the oppression of white
He doesn't care
And what it leads
Need to understand
Is that we've done a shity job on the show
Because
This is as far back as we've gone
For the most part
The 2009
It becomes very clear to me
Then he is a
White supremacist
22 like
Crazy doesn't say the same shade as David Duke
He tries to debate David Duke
He doesn't say
Things is like a Richard Spencer
Sing like that
He is a much more
He's much better at presenting himself as being like no that's not what I'm talking to
He has a lot more Nooks to hide and looks
But
I think that we've done a really shity job and I'd like to apologize to the audience
This to me
Is revolutionary
So how I will deal with Alex moving forward
There's not a there's not a bone in my body
Did think that any of his position
About
What he's afraid of are real
Their only real inasmuch as
He thinks they're white
Person is going to be a victim
Yep
This is me calling
I think that my position especially on this show
Is not taking that leap until that leap is appropriate
And I don't think that I think that up until this point from what we've witnessed
It would be reasonable
To say
Hey you didn't mean any of this yet
But
The scales are not fallen from my eyes
Until I heard
Very clearly the idea that what they're going to do
The things that I'm afraid of so much is a beta test
Making it so clear that in the
Same
He's talking about
The idea of people having their kids taken away
It did that exact
Scenario playing out
In front of our eyes and
And him being like
The moment you started talking I was like
That connection was made instantly
Because yeah I know cuz you're a smart person but
That immediately made
Perfect f***
That's the only thing that makes
F******
Because if his position
Is essentially when they came for the Jews because they didn't come for me and then they came for me
Like that's his position and now he knows when they come for the judges comings are not coming for me
This is f******
Nail this is a coffin that just got nailed into the
F****** ground has been masquerading as having principles for
3 years
Yearsin
His only principal is white supremacy
That's what it is
Quite realistically
I mean we've always had the smell
Forgiving white Terror
Creating
Gymnastic level defenses of life
How it's possible that this isn't
This is done
Set the eclipse
It breaks my heart and soul that the f****** clip it breaks my heart
Because it makes things very simple and moving forward will have a much easier framework
To work with
Some value to that
Really bothers me is that
I want to save this
Really quick this is a diversion
Alex is ex-wife right now is on Twitter she started an initiative where she's going to
Plug Infowars
That's her new website that she's going to
She's going to unplug Infowars
Unplug Infowars
And what
Clearly is it right now in 2009
She's a big
Part of the operation
Like when we talked about it she wasn't around when he went to Trump
Part of it at this
She knows a lot more than
She's putting out there
She really wanted to unplugged
Lot of stuff.
Put out publicly
It's a lot more than she could say
But you.
The other thing I want to say
Stock
Left
It's so obvious
By no means have I not call him
For the past year-and-a-half
That is
F******
That's what it really is
You know your other conclusion
Flawed and he's not applying them equally
This is his principles are
Pacific
You know why you know why it's so damn
But you know why it's so damning is because there are moments of like
Outright White
Supremacy in white spirit
Going into the swimming
Muslim women being like this freaks me out
You don't belong in your space
You are your problem
But this is such a different level because it's
Such
It's
Inexorable
From
He's Bass
Narrative
Like the things that he has been most
Aggressive about in terms of what
Fear is
But here the Bandit now being afraid of
You know it's that it's
Yep you got that you're on Homebase now
Or more specifically
Safety event
Some of our other brethren
And the world
Airbnb
Irresponsible of us to sit here and say like
We are
Safe
Alex's married
Cuz you you're saying that he is safe now because like gun whites
We are still white and we still have a much bigger past than a lot of the other
Population
Yeah I mean
But the problem with
That
The problem with that
Veev sympathizer label
Which is going to be thrown about
If
We are
We will become sympathizers and that's loose
Like that's what it is what you think you think in Nazi Germany people who
No cuz they were why do you think we're not going to be people hiding people
Like a f****** if it look if you're illegal immigrant to my place
I will f***
F****** her s*** believe my shity look thankfully were not very
If I were there
Risotto there is a nice office in Chicago
This is the big that I wanted
To make
But there's more
Thankfully for the rest of this was could do a dance on Alex
Is racist a
About
Obama dictator
And it's interesting the specifics that he uses
F****** they're not even f****** real human being
They're dead on the f****** inside
Restaurants
Retail store right now
If
It's amazing to me
So that is all
Appears
In the Obama
Documentary
Economist
No idea
But hey
Fun fun fact
Murals of trump are at the zoo
Champs
I received
Would be a nice inscription
Sometimes losing a battle teaches you a new one
Cursive
Encouraging message
To the children or the people in those camps that might be it
As much as it is
Middle finger
To the liberals who have tried to create different ways
To make it through that declaration
Mural the Trump has
Everything with his goddamn name on probably paid some million other people now cuz I think that's that's a level of
That's a level of micromanagement
Dickies capability
I don't think
It's it's
That would be an insane amount of organization that I think he is
These two hands off
White supremacy
Mayday
Mural with Trump's face in American flag
Adidas nmd
Sometimes
Losing a battle to win a war
I think that relate
To all the years
Supremacist or bang their heads
How to
Power
That's sort of a wagging dick
Kind of
That you should be staying to immigrant
I think that is entirely
I f*** you I think that's a f*** you too liberal
Would you be autopsy after they f****** destroyed 2008 was all about becoming more glue
Was all about changing demographics was all about making sure that the Republican party was more exclusive it was more
Inclusive
Figure out a way to win and make it more
Exactly
Tea Party
F****** Christ
Dick
And here's
I don't I don't I don't know much about him and I can't I can't find much about him this clip said everything I need to
F****** know about it
After he was elected I heard the day of his inauguration I heard on the television
At least 75 times this is the first African-American ever elected see nights
Steaks
Well
His mother is Caucasian is father was 80% Arab in 20% after
And I don't care whether he's black.
But he's 10% African
African does that make him an African-American
And it is absolutely
Die die die
The sales pitch
The sales pitch Powers Allah
And
Amityville Trump
Has not gotten any of my reference
Also I think
Night last episode
That was clean
No
In this country
You're hyperventilating
Black is about Heritage in America
Black is about skin color
It doesn't f****** matter how far back
Do you have to go if you were halfway you were still not a citizen
How far back do you have to go to where you if you were halfway you still weren't allowed in the same white rice
Restaurants
Because I think what you're trying to express
Could I take a picture
Because it's time
Where whiteness was defined by exclusion
There were people who were like
You know you have a
Do you have a drop of black blood
Therefore you aren't White
Yep
Keep people out of places that was
Keep Society in order that the whites wanted order to be in your mother's grandma was black
Doesn't matter how white the rest of your family is your a quadroon
This guy coming in black enough
To be black
Your
Look there is the history of exclusion of black people because they're not white
And then now we have him being like what is the president
Black president
He is Mama's wife
Get the f*** out of here what the f*** do you want
Fremont
You heard him say
Who's the first black
You didn't hear them say he was the first
African president who was the first
President who was from Kenya
Isn't the first president that lie or mostly related to another
That was not
You heard them presents because his skin was black which meant that no matter f****** what
If he was
If his parents were white his grandparents were white
And by genetics
Everyone around him
Because they would see his skin color and they would say the n-word Direct
Could have been 98% but if his skin was touche
Then it wouldn't matter how he was
Genetically because blank
Outlook
F******
There's so much
Fitbit
Concepts of
Whiteness and non-white
That are being played with
Specifically like the way you
Each each
Version that he's trying to
Use R2
Defend whiteness
Anti authoring
That's all he's doing you saying you like
He's using a rich tradition of
Exclusion
Black
Through
Appearance
He's flipping that around uses
Let's be like
You're not black enough
Because look at your lineage
Look at your lineage you're not black enough
And that to me
So Eugenics to build up on top of that
That is also a
Dick
Of like
Well somebody who is really black could never be
He's the first black president
Well of course he could become president so as I was actually but
So fascinating about this rich
Is it like there
This is fudge this is dark chocolate
Racism
There's the garlic layer and then there's the ghost pepper underneath the garlic
Ghost pepper that are like
The other
The idea of like you what are you saying is like
Absolutely
He didn't say all that much racist
She's plenty in his interview so I just like
Let's give this guy
Also gets back to the idea of
Changing Purity level
Because it's still always about what
But it's like
Well he's
Percent
Arab
Is X or Y
Whatever the return is always
Mostly
It doesn't it doesn't even f****** matter
Nope
Always just going to whatever it is
So now there is no reason to listen to anything these people have to say
This show is
Bulaga
Gas
We've got a murderer's row
He's a cop
Alright well then he's a graper
He also has a show on
The communications Network
You f*** with
Are phony president by the way we haven't had
This is a time that we don't have a president of the United States first time in our history
And because he's a phony president
Evidence to prove that he's not our president
Because of Article 2 Section 5 is Constitution says he's not
Because he's an illegal alien
Out of Kenya
And
Anyway they think they have got it made
You know they think they've got it made they got us
And they don't realize that God is still in control
God is in
Is there anything you cannot realize
Did the other people
Yeah because that suggests that
Where is there a god I wouldn't believe you
Controller
Control everywhere
Nicely done
Stop
And he doesn't remember that George W did not actually win Florida and the Supreme Court gave him the president
Because it was a conservative f****** Supreme Court but it was a 524 majority
Is that like a question that remains
But there is a question that remains of a why was Alex
Against
The George W bush
If he is this like
Now Trump is in office and he feels
Doesn't worry about this
And I would posit
As much as
George W bush is a war criminal
He was not as clearly a white supremacist
Like he wasn't it's clearly
Like he was not somebody that if you were if you were a Nazi if you were to write
You would not hang your hat like David Duke never advocated for George W bush
And that's because even though we're of the stupid / evil continue
They were like
He might be too dumb to
And he never gave like those wings
Synod right does to the
Few but they weren't as like murder
For that I think of it when we look at the history of like
Where Alex puts
His foot down
Criticize
It's very clear that
George W bush would have been like
My date is a Nazi rally there's good people on both sides
There's a decent
Which actually makes me concerned
In 2050
We do
Rodger Stone
Mike Worthy
Driving forces for him
Joining up with
Yeah that we don't know what they said
And there's a
I think Steve is a manipulator and he was doing his
There's a counter counter-coup kind of shape
Whether or not he is a racist or not
Is irrelevant to me I don't believe that his manipulative game would have been
He's trying to Margarita
Yeah now I don't know about
Rodger Stone
There's a Rogers
Just been like a look he hates Hillary
Love's wife
You got to love
Yeah he's going to be fine with whites cuz
Is willing to tell any lie
But that wouldn't be a liar
No no
I just sent that he will do
Like that would be would be like
You love
He loves wife let's move it along is a propagandist
Manipulate
Absolutely
But I also think he has shame
You don't like from what I've been able to
Certainly
You can pretend that like Sandy Hook was a false flag
Las Vegas is a false flag
But at the same time he would not
Lower himself to being like
Please Alex
Like look he likes white people
He would try and do some high-scale manipulation as opposed to the low scale
Whereas I think there's a chance
Rodger Stone
Look on a bass level
You're afraid about white stuff
She's going to protect whites
I think this is
Possible that Rodger Stone
Ultimate Conga player
Ultimate limbo ultimate limbo champ
Glam
I'm going to read that you from the Southern Poverty Law Center
From the website
He produced a periodical called Aiden police newsletter most famous document
Operation Vampire killer 2000
Colon
American police action plan for stopping World Government rule
In parentheses
McClain was perhaps the government
So the troops serving the New World Order after martial law is declared with Noah
Do with people living in Egypt
A blue. Met that you were destined for a
FEMA camp
Pick indicated that you were to be used in
Slave labor
Shot in the head
Mcclam was also involved in the development
Almost Heaven
Located in okay that are coming before
Every word Idaho
The community
But you merely was supposed to quote New World Order
Mclambs partner in that failed venture
Conclude bogert
A decorated Vietnam veteran father of the races
Very Christian identity religion
A former Arizona
So that's
So that's sort of his
I hate he look he opposed Martin Luther King Junior having a holiday on the grounds of
We got too many bank holiday
Next
So on this day that Alex reveals to me the scales dropped from my eyes that
Just about protecting whiteness
He has now had a guy on who is
Saying that Obama isn't black enough
Right now Jack mcclam president
Country happens to be running right for trying to run a right-wing a separate
Community
With people who don't believe Martin Luther
Holiday
Christian identity
So that's cool
Is the Big Show
Gated communities
White supremacist gated communities
They're doing great
Not an Idaho dude location location location
Always
No doubt so it was next week
I'm telling you
1 Spencer it's great to have you on with us
You talk to you again
You know Alex I moved out of California down here to the Border about 7 years ago
What about the tell the truth about the border the American people
Admirable goal
Is it
Nope
Hope not
I should tell you their what sponsor does
Glenn Turner
He has
Technology
No these people can't have technology may or may not have an army of drones
Might you might have
Graph
So he can tell when they're people walking over it
At the border
People crossing the border
Now he doesn't do anything with that information
But he is a weirdo who spend too much money
He's a mess
And this isn't 2009
Yeah
This is he still doing today
I'm not sure if you was doing in 2009 he's actually doing it now
Started
But he's been trying
Develops
To f*** over people at the border
Long time
Doesn't report them
Border Authority but I think it's because
He doesn't believe
Even the Federal
I think that's part of it
So you just you just
Takes pictures of them
Take pictures of them as they crossed the border airplane
I think it would like that
It was like
Border-crossers.com
That's not all
Was about
No sir
Implies that he's two people like a celebrity couple
Glenna Spencer
Where did you go
She's going shopping
So he re started this thing called voice for
Things together also known as American Patrol
In response to what he perceived as Mexican related violence in the LA riots
Police officers
So goes all the way back
All the way back all the way back to the Rodney King riots
Troll
Involved
94 was the
Opposition
Which aims to cut Publix
For undocumented
Immigrants and their children
From attending school
Spencer's website would become a popular anti-mexican
Consistently post
Fictionalized stories
Meant to imply that latinx people had a higher propensity towards
And undermining America
Culture reflected in this next
Clip
Something is coming apart
There was no Foundation there there was no cultural strength
Are unified in their very nationalist
However they will look for any reason at any excuse
The movie cross that border
Because they want to take the Southwest back
Anyway you slice it
So I kept that after that break their just because Alex had to
Spawn like I had to make sure yet
Stupid as planned
6 a conspiracy
Believes that Mexicans are working together through their advocacy
Metro or the Raza
In order to take back the Southwest
They're coming to America
Specifically because they want to swing demographic so they can
Voted back to Mexico
This conspiracy is deeply race
I
First off
Love that
To be fair
Really land
Go to put together a Scientologist
A guerrilla operation where you infiltrate an entire government
In order to take back land
Pretty wild easier ways to do these
Also the idea of a nationalist saying that they're very nationalistic
Yeah
Baseboards
Borders and they want their land back
You're wrong I actually think the Tipping his cap to his enemy
I think there's a
Spectrum
I kind of think
I can see that
I'm too also
I don't before you go any further
Despise
The
Because I'm special
The propaganda of the status quo
Yeah which to me is that
Anti-immigrant
I just use that I just used is a feeling because either race
Right exactly
That to me is the propaganda of the status quo that idea
My framing it that way but I only did that because
I was harkening back
To what key
Probably thought he was doing that it was probably was
A kernel of it that he thought there was a
9 doors
But that might also me being that might be me Express
The same naive like you came up with anti-immigrant
No
At that phrase
Azrael a tighter that quoting some other places
I mean
Yeah then in that case
J'accuse
Was doing it all
I mean on a on a
Barebones
I do agree with the terminology cuz he is
There's a bigger picture to it
Don't get involved in anti-immigrant
Qrn races
Yes
What do you mean
Call are they anti immigrants from everywhere
I would also like to
I'm sorry sorry
Eventually we get to that
I don't which is again
Because generally anti-immigrant politics
End with
New York Times
Because there was a jerk
Those
Politics
Work
I trust you when you say that
If I ended it with
Anti-immigrant yourself
Yeah 1008
Center posted
Jew control Hollywood brainwashing Americans
That's actually
A good question it he assured readers that he had Jewish friends but added quote I fear however that this
Small handful of patriotic Americans are liberal Jews
Total control over Army
So he's branched out
At this point news on Oz Show
From just being super again
Coming from the border to
Monessen forward like concept of
The five jewbag
Late like Run the World
The 5G producers
There's always
Catch-all
Which by the way
I don't think we have enough donations
The
None dare call it conspiracy to come out
Delicious
But
Man there's so much of that
Ready for
Cages
Construction
Again all this
Propaganda
He goes back and back and back
People just ate
Hazel stuff
Misunderstanding
Communism
Like vociferous anti-communism
Was such a scourge
Cold War
It was so bad the John Birch Society stuff was
So right
One actually I want to tell you about that
My research
So amazing
A bunch of University
They did a bunch of studies
About people's
Throughout
7 Dees
The 80s
And
They found that
Of course
As time went on people had much less
Fear about communism as an ideology
Actually towards the end of it
At least
Affinity
Alex Jones
Good cop.
But the
Funniest things
Is that they did a poll
About
The government
Should be spying
So they are bunch of different groups like
Should the government spy on them
Yes or no
74 this is
The number one group that people said yes you should spy on them
Was the American Communist Party
It's 74.9
Which is pretty high very high that's pretty crazy
What you up to communist
I kind of understand in the 70s
SOB Americans
Good answer
Stuff like that phone number to its 7
34.7% vigilante groups like The
Kirkplan
The KKK comes in just under
I like that they're closed
I don't like who's number one
But I'm feeling you 74 so far we're doing 50 50 years with really fun
You came in third
The John Birch Society
47.2% of respondents to the government
Should be spying
On the John Birch
Tire ratings
The students for a Democratic Society
The Weather Underground forehead just got done
They were more suspicious to the public
50 FPS
Because the SES isn't actually going to take over the government
They were trying to change policies they weren't infiltrate
There's other
Republican Party
Society
Hahaha is what they added Fox News and it was number four is
Raising
Super weird facts
Yourself Glenn Spencer you suck we're sure you are a monster
But
This is actually really fun
So I want to see this but I couldn't
Because it's time
Pinstripe
I have started to notice that Alex says a bunch
Interesting
Pixar off
The only way you'd be able to
No this is
If you listen to all of the Ross
Right
Not to the attitude coming out of
Commercial
This
Repeatedly
Initiate
Waging War on corruption
Alex Jones commercial
Initiate
I think there's a part of his military
There's a leak coming out a commercial
Not like let's go
NACA
Whatever it is
Where is worth noting
I like it I like it
I think it's more fun
If he's like a weird closet Syfy
Call viz references or like what's real is actually what happened
No we could never love a Highlander so much you just relay that to his stupid ideas about Star Wars
In a week and everybody thinks that I loved doing it
Okay was it matter was it
Good less references to Highland Drive I'm putting a pimping you a little bit
Dude I could go get him a present
Does there are four
Have you read chapter
It's a few thousand years after the god of
Check the f*** out
I-Ready
Seventh grade
This is news to Long Walk
It's like it's like anybody tried to convert to Judaism where I'm like
No no
You don't want to go through this no it's
You don't want to go through this
Let It Go
Coming up
I told you this
This guy might be worse than all of them
Alright
30 minutes
Joined Sheriff Richard Mack
No Sheriff Richard
It's going to be a bad day for
Sheriff cuz he's never like
Help save two puppies
Today it's never that it's always a sheriff that is like
I'm the ultimate laws
The one person who I believe has new world order
His name is
York County Sheriff
Oh boy
His name is
How many counties are there
But also counties
Louisiana
Alaska doesn't have
Is very
Like the sheriff is
Too bad
Richard Mack
A board member
The Oath Keepers
Dick Mac is a board member of the oath keeper I should also tell you he is one of
If not
The main originator of the cons
Institutional stairs movement
He's been one of the guys who started this idea the sheriff is
He's the Proto Arpaio
Funny you should say that
How do you say that
Is another drop
Who has endorsed my book by the way
He's on the back of the book
Jubilee
In all of this about the autonomy of the sheriff
Look what you've done
That's a bad way to phrase it
Look what he's done
Look what you
Would like
All of you
Policy walk
To elect me president
I will have a vice president
Who is far more qualified than me
However
As president
I will spend one day in office
And that day
Will be an active executive order
To murder Joe Arpaio
Scrotal
F****** die
20 years ago
The worst god dammit that
F****** piece of s***
It's not surprising that would be super on board with Richard Max idea that is not
VR the sheriff is the ultimate law of the land because people like Joe Arpaio
Make their own little mini fiefdom yep where they are King
They like to abused their power they liked
The creates the
Systematic abuse of people who are different
And scare people about the immigrants in order to
To justify
Things like
Not
Investigating
Abuse
Things like
Creating fake bomb scares in order to get himself over this over and over again
Never Enough never enough
There's there are very few like
Summary
Execution
Candidates
Anthony
Yeah
Like for real
Legitimately
White supremacist
And as done
Irrevocable damage
Countless
Like the people who had to live in his f****** 10
Kansas City
I can't imagine what
PTSD some of them had to go through and
The lingering effects
That that is caused
Do people in their lives
I can't imagine
The people who dreamed up
What happened to them
Like the ripples
That he's responsible for Jeff because of his love
Power
And just because of his desire to be the king share
Richard
His advocate
He is no he's at a level where I like
I understand six Roman overlords put people
And lit it on fire
About about
Yes like absolute
Because
White people are not
The people who are going to be hurt
Exactly
Pattern
Is so f****** clear
Over and over and over
So now I'll tell you about Richard McEvoy
Why wouldn't you be
Why would
Why would Mac be there
Richard Mack former Sheriff
I was part of the Bundy standoff because of that he ended up a guest on Fox News
Appearing on Fox News has the real story on Monday former Sheriff Richard Mack said he and other protesters quote
We're already strategizing to put all the women up at the
Front if they're going to start shooting it's going to be women that are going to be televised
Federal officers
So that to me takes away from the brutality of what the officers would have done if you are
Open up front door
Create some sort of monster image
Oh isn't it terrible
Put them up front daughter for them to be
Be killed
What the f*** is going on what game are you playing
Like he's pretending or first of all that never happened
Second of all
That are not worth you getting your wife killed
What the f*** is going on you he cared more about the Optics
Pretending that the oppressive government that was going to kill them
His wife
In Mortal Danger
What are you doing is he saying you know all those organic
Locations where the cops
The government
Have murdered young women
Children everybody
You know all those situations where white supremacist have wound up doing that
Well we're going to manufacture the
That's what he saying
And let's not talk at all
Is there white supremacist
Sip killed tons of
Minorities
Tintagel would never
Do that their monuments to doing that in the United States was definitely not doing
Getting Burger King
I would say go Wendy's
The place where the world is so f***** up
How do you what are you even f******
Literally the definition of gallows humor
No s*** in 2014 Richard
Navajo County Arizona
We're going to make it a constitutional County
Show everybody the bloop
Blueprints of freedom
There's a lot more people running another offices
I'd say I'd run for Sheriff
We're going to give this one more try the elections 2016
I'm going to be moving there in the spring 2015 so I can
Get ready for this
Your buddy year-and-a-half
To decide I'm dead serious about this
PostScript
He lost that election to democratic Market
So now here
Jordan I wrote this paragraph and I'm super proud of it
Richard Mack was a hostile opponent of Obamacare
And then
If you had a heart attack while his wife was very sick
They were self-employed could not afford
Insurance
With mounting medical bills they started a GoFundMe to pay for their Healthcare
Jordan will be thrilled to learn
That they did not read
Yes yes I am
Yes I am
I mean like that there are a classic example of
No it's bad when everybody else does it it's
Yeah absolutely
$60,000 goal
For there a GoFundMe
And they reached
53 South
Still too much
And Subway
You know still somewhere like
Go fuc his
There's the real issue is they had a miscalculation by 10 grand
Like that's the
If I had $50,000
Never really happened
I think that if your
If you have this principle
You go through life like this
F*** people being able
Afford insurance when they're self-employed go f*** yourself
You stupid piles of s***
Look at this
Affordable Care Act
I hate it
Oh s*** I had art
Please give me
Yep
The idea that you don't at that point realize why it's a problem and why this
This is very important for people
Security benefit
Caused him to be like
I get
On the other side
I don't
I refuse to understand that I'm accepting
What amount
Charity could just be done
Automatically
For everyone
We could all do this
In a bigger way and take care of everyone
And GoFundMe getting a 8% cut or whatever
Private ism
Capitalism that doesn't leave
And everyone knows it
Security benefit
And yet
Pass that massive text cut right and what are they doing now Dan
That I have ever said this before
Written about it extensively
For those tax cuts
I'll be God damned if it isn't to cut Medicare and Social Security
Oh they said they would never touch it they said it would
We got it we got it
3 trillion-dollar deficit
That's a terrible idea
Too bad there aren't other ways
Reason
Voted against his own interest it's bananas
Be subversive
The height
Are going to
To be punished
Long
Immigrants
The minorities
Lgbtq community
It goes back to reconstruction-era South
Poor white people or black people
They're going to
So you divide poor white people in
Which is why everyone is so mad at the
In terms of the broken Coalition together
Exactly the same time the ID of like shifting
More right in order to be more appealing towards
But that is a problem but that idea of
Together all of the
All the disenfranchised group
I'll take care of you
If you followed with all of that
That was reading strategy
We have the worst president in history and somehow the opposition parties going to f*** it up
It actually is very clear why
No one knows
Like
Why would
Who's been in
Government for 10 years
15 years old has assholes for like 20-30 years
Why would they know how to deal with
Why would they understand
The situation
That is
Unfolding Lex Luthor Superman
The Democratic Party
The Democratic caucus
Leadership
On the
In the same breath
How could they not
Give him a pass
Yeah of course years of like
Things being different
And now things
And you'd hoped
I got to wake up call
Get better not going
Because I mean I mean to
Spoiler alert
Because out is that a couple of House Representatives
The show as guest
I looked at their salary
House represent
Not even in the Federal
House representative
In most States
Have a
2070 thousand-dollar year
Salaries
How the f*** would they give a s*** about
I'm in this posting
I'm good right
Right
I don't know
Can you imagine being
Ada government for
30 years
20 years were
There's a very little chance you'll ever be voted out because
Sometimes you don't have anyone even
There is in that government job
Because it is so pretty
Lifetime Health Insurance
Billion percent of money corrupt
Like the arguments for paying representative
Politician is because if you say if they were already rich maybe they won't
Averse to corruption as we already know better version
Oversight
Regulation
Crazy
Everybody hates that word
Soap dirt back back back on track
I'd say that Richard Max sucks
Dickie Max and here is one level
Very very very
Give misrepresent
Beloved
Yeah
Election
I think it's very
Set the hopelessness that people felt during especially this last campaign
The presidential election 90
That's so many people with a bad taste in their mouths of hopelessness and right now I've given the message that there is hope
And it is your County Sheriff
I would say
That I never saw more
I never sought more people
I never saw more
In my lifetime
Optimism
Who otherwise
People who are very scary
Do you mean
That everybody was dancing in the street
Because that day
So many great
County Sheriff
So many grapes the greats of County Sheriff
You've got Kareem Abdul-Jabbar Gregerson
Right
Absolutely you got love it
Is that in Camden is that a place I don't know
I don't know
That took all the way out of myself I was going to try and come for a name
I'm so sorry I wanted to hear like 30
McGregor
Jerk tungsten shout-out to Mystery Science Theater
That was an iPhone
Hardest name ever
No he wasn't Coolio
Alright
Listen here's one thing
We got we got a couple more clips and they're all fun
From here on out
Alright
Very queer
Line of white supremacy
Read ideology
Like all of these
There is
Not a quitter
Since they're all on the show
Now I should tell you
Over the years
And that is italics
Killing dog
So
I find it hard not to think of naught
When I hear music
I think he f****** shot knocking the head I'm not sure if I'm just hearing this
He is
Singularly obsessed with this like
Verbal picture of killing a dog
You don't want to kill
Yeah but you got to kill this dog you got to kill this f****** dog
What is
Circumstances
But you don't know what the government is going to do with that remains
Kill it yeah
Jaguar
But also
I got that I actually got that a letter was
I didn't see any reason to kill that.
Joyless to a kid looking up to you with those puppy dog eyes work
Any reason to kill this dog
Portland
Trusting person there's no reason to kill that dog
You're just murdering a dog
He's looking at you up at you hungry
Like a dog
Elizabeth
7 years old so you know you've built a long relationship with it you love that dog Kenosha
Well
Single benefit of the doubt and then it's just
Anyways
Free dog
Video of Obama talking to
Open house
I'm having a real tough time I'm homeless now
Well I hope I hope
Can help you
You see if we can talk
After I don't know if
This forum
In that speech
And then I also do
Presented
If he'd been like
Your dog is
Is going to die anyway
Is murder a woman who's hungry
Edwards home
And
It is exactly like when you murder your dog because you
Nobama didn't murder that lady
Not quite like Alex murdered
Probably
I can't even remember the other.
He's brought up
Sandra Bullock
Call Bae.
We were in Austin and we almost went to
I don't want to go
Nazi iconography
We're going to we're going to end this on a Cota
Much like the end of Layla
That is where we get to like
Episode where
Revealed Alex Jones
Long stand
Cannot get away
This will be a
From now on I can't stress that enough
Like this is
Payson pool to scales
For my eyes
You clearly now
They are eventually going to be
Be applied to White
Yep
Champs
All of that
Only about like
They will do this two white people eventually
Scared of that.
Because
Yeah so now
You really
Years
He doesn't have it.
He's got Anderson
Who selling gold
But it's clearly not enough
He's not a millionaire
He's not done with
The film
Pre-sales
Please
Yeah give
Give me money
Zombie dance
Yeah this is
Spell through
ICBM
More powerful
We are focused now
Gold was $200 an ounce
Now it's
Doesn't make money
He doesn't make money man
Skyview
Your finances
That's the worst salesman
Course
But it works
So I'm at the end of it like
Is
Lowe's
Of whites
Jack Nicklaus
Don't know enough about George Humphrey but
Is like
Obama's black
She hump Richard Mack
Call
Sucking dick
Monsters
And same show that Alex
True colors
I mean the reason we end the way we
It's cuz that's how he
Generally
Trying to get some money
Cuz all of this
The end of the day
Isabel
But it's also
About Khan
It's about the
Except valyria effective
He believes in the white supremacy first
Totally
Titanic built around
Effective
That's why Jim Bakker will never be
God we be such great white supremacist
Be tough for me got all the skill
What if we made a harsh turd let's not do that look
Policy wonks email knowledge fight at gmail.com
That joke is flown around the Facebook group
But it would be it would require like us not being friends
Like if we if we faked that
You could not
Would not allowed
I could make a pivot
Things or something
Be the end of our
Friendship
And then how do I do this
The show after that
I thought about
Possibly like
Controlling
Like what
Our friendship
Could be over I could not handle that
F***
You got to start from Square One
Supremacists
Generous
I'm not ready to make that game today
Not ready
Because I
If you like to find more about our
Your knowledge
If you are a white supremacist you are not allowed to collect support no
I-90 is right.com
Absolutely
Are looking at iTunes if you want to leave a review
Jordan
It's your turn
And what's funny is I've left you with
Characters
In front of you
Call Butch
You just
The constitutional
John my Richard
Doesn't get worse than the idea of some a******
Who wants to turn his f******
How
Not not like a
Bravo
He wants to turn a place filled with
10000 people
Is own personal f****** Kingdom the goddamn world
There is no idea of the middle manager
Who gets a little bit too much power
And abuses it to the
Point that it is untenable
There is nobody
Worse than that
F****** guy the manager at your office who's a dick
F*** yourself dick Mack
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color