Alexandra Thurston color
We are careful to sit around big novelty beverages
No
Not stay safe today
What do we say to the god of B
Not today
Today sucks alright
The shift
I don't want to talk about it
Yeah we aren't a political Affairs and I feel like
Anytime we train drift too deeply into those Waters
We sound like idiots
So let's not do that that's not what this shows about the shows about
I'm still calling for a civil war I'm not sure about it
But something's got to happen
I saw your tweet from earlier about stacking the Supreme Court
Might be
Probably going to retire
You better not
Is the wizard awful Supreme Court Judge replacing him with another awful worse
Now he's not going to be positive now
It's bananas
Sceptre all such a mess
Because of the I do know one thing I want
How to say thank you to our new donors
That is a tasteless transition on my part but got to get out of it somehow
I'm a policy wonk
Refrigerator
We'd appreciate it if you'd like to support the things that we do
Support the show button
We would appreciate it very much
And every policy wonk will be a
Commissioned officer
Or absolute
Nonsensical
The political landscape is immoral
I decided maybe it's time for us
To do something that I've been wanting to do for a long time message
And suggested
That we do this
Notified the heart to explain to him that I've been kicking it around for awhile
Alex Jones
A little bit
Conversations
The folks
I don't know if I said it on the show or whatever but I might have
The theme of this show is
Alex Jones
Everybody is running a con
These are all running a con and they're doing it the same way
Stop lockjaw
Our listeners need to be
He told don't listen to these people
Put it
To look at how very very similar all of these
Who are the old people by pushing whites
Supremacy
In such a way
It's a really successful blooper
It is it's fascinating indeed
It's being done to the body politic now we're feeling it
The stuff that we're talking about right now is beginning of this show it's the end result of these
The conman
Cool
Destroyed everything is allowed people
With Bill weld
The people like this
Stephen Miller's of the world
To game the sea
The power that they are in without the huckster con man
It really just want to take old people's money
Probably our biggest
They're all monsters people but at the same time they motivated by wanting to
The grip Granny's
Biggest on the local level they don't want they don't want to be the Arbiter
How long the Nationals
Bright
You have people who get whipped up into a frenzy don't trust people who
Because we're genuinely confused anybody's listening to us
The first place you have
I apologize for not responding to a lot of emails
Is overwhelmingly emotionally
Especially nice one
Please
Give me fuel very
Scared but a good one make me feel
Invalid
Yeah
We are imposter syndrome
About my friend
Is Jim
Snow
Oh yeah we don't want to know
Stupid crazy
And all I want to do is watch more Jim Bakker
Okay we're doing Jim Bakker and I'll be honest
Towards the end of this
I got the
Spirit got good to me
No I'm not as I get it I understand
See the tricks that he's doing to rev people off
Yeah yeah whatever
To switch it on you to sell like a
Survival radio
Jim Bakker sucks
Is a televangelist
Who's done some time in prison
We're going to get into why he's the worst person
Someone who's gone to prison
Various various
Things that will learn
I don't even have a contact job for this episode what I was going to do is I was going to start with that song
That made the rounds that went viral that guy singing about end time
Here's the issue then now
I'm going to have to pull it up because I decided it was
Because I
I thought it was a key they like it
The one thing that most people have seen
End of Jim Bakker
They went around it was a meme that got that got sent around
I'll give you a little bit of set up here and then I'll play it
For the good people cuz for the past
Year 2 to avoid any and all social
Media still sucking tweet every now and again cuz I'm
Same person
It for me I actually like once every couple of weeks just whenever I'm so angry and there's no one to Yellow
Flat around me long as we're doing the show
Couple of days
I totally understand
This was a this is a guy is a rather large gentleman and a Hawaiian
I'm shirt
Is either a part of Jim Baker's praise band
Orgasm doing guest vocals
And he's going to sing a song
The guy that guy
But also like
This guy's going to
Sing a song
About
Jim's various
Survival Products
And I'm not sure if Jim Bakker actually speaks
Behind the guy finally
Well a little.
Let's get a little death
Over here again
Kevin I love this song
Courage YouTube
I think when you get
Calvary Hill from Woodbury
El marketon
Text Mark
Mark's doing good
Oh my God
That's right that's what I f****** looks like
And this is set to my girl
Alright
Your house
I can't
Your face
Reserve to get to the koreso they we could cut bait
Dude
Got the most racist people always want to steal black music
I'm going to go I'm just going to go see this
Yeah
Absolutely biblical to prepare for the end times
That is against the rules
I did pick up
F*** aren't allowed to You're supposed
To just shut the fuk up and be a not shity person response was going to beat now.
Is the kind of bulshit we can get behind
Now that is what I call music
Volume eight
That's hilarious like the diversion
Does not involve
A man that was so bad that is
So terrible that made the rounds nobody's planning on Jim Bakker for a bit that's
Always fun to see
There's a part of me that like one of the other things that makes
Be very
I'm pretty
You sure
That he didn't think that like
I'm going to do this embarrassing my girl cover and then everyone will give me free press
Like the way Alex
Sincerely like
This will really be fun for the Congress and we'll sell some of these
That
The never fried
Nope
We're going to learn a bit about his food here in a little bit
Alright we're going we're going to get real deep on a lot of stuff into Baker's to help
Alright alright
There is nothing more christ-like
Where were the bread and fish
Target
You said it my man
So I went like I don't know Jim Baker's been around for f****** ever
I was like man it would be really convenient if someone who's on Alex Jones Show a lot is also a
Would it be snowing now in that total
Michael Snyder
Is a guest on there is actually going to be on in like a week or so and another episode
But we literally we've already talked about Michael Snyder all that much on this show
He shows up a bit but he's usually fairly boring on Alex
The shop
Get that
Treatment from us
But then
Guess who I found
As a guest
On Jim Bakker Show multiple times
Steve Quayle
The moment you said Steve has like
Who's Christine
Saturday the two of them again
Come together he is a guy who's been around
Thanks
Long time
He's a longtime Alex Jones
Death
Yeah he's written a bunch of books about
Number
I killed you
Steve Quayle is a bit of a lunatic
Rice
Alex
See the prophet
A witch
Should leave you two
At least
On many levels
That
With some of Alex
Narrative
And I think we're going to
To see some examples
That very clearly
Thanks to Jim Bakker
Conspiracy
Jim actually died
In jail
Jubilee in for life
5 years
You say
Just removed all of her makeup
And now
The bull
What's the time
That's what I said
Here is at the first clip that we get
Like
There's it impossible
How to make a clip
Of the Jim Bakker Show without some
Some sales being involved
Does he talk
Telling all the
What time into this clip starts
I'm trying to sell
Sell Steve quayle's book
Genesis 6
Giant
The book
You wrote
And then
This one here what's the difference in this one this is true with all the myths and legends
Around the world in addition to Giants but it talks about why this subject is covered up by the powers-that-be
Arizona
It's a Ballroom Blitz
Do you know about this
Well let's see if he says
Everything
Set is at the Giant
They bought them up they've had to buy museums just to get them
Absolutely why would they want to do that
Because they don't want they don't don't want
The word of God substantiated in any way shape or form
What they're going to
Play ladies and gentlemen
Is that the
Aliens Breathe by way more people been one for the Lord
By finally answering their Quest we got they'll give you good example when God said
YouTube
Go in and Jack and Caleb
Jack and Kayla going in the Promised Land
Woman child people say how could a holy God do that
How could a loving God do that that wanted to protect the genetic creation of Adam
It was about the promise and 315 Genesis
The Redeemer Jesus coming through the truth
That's why Jesus called the second Adam
There's a lot of stuff there
Reckzo
Correct
Giants are real
Smithsonian is covering them up
In order to keep people from knowing that God is real
Is entirely accurate
When you ask
Why did God murder every man woman and child
The answer is
Cuz of course dummies
Do you want the pickle idiot
Little bit of Adam
God loves Justin
What from Justin Sullivan Kelly
So what do you know about the Smithsonian cover up my dude well the Smithsonian is a museum
And it has a lot of interesting things
Great website
Pretty sure that's the end of the story
In December
They bought all the top location published an article titled quote
Smithsonian admits to
The destruction of thousands
Giant
In the early
From this article
Quotes
A US Supreme Court ruling is forced
The Smithsonian
Petition to release classified papers dating from the early 1900's
That proves the organization was involved in major historic
Local cover-up of evidence
Showing giant
Human
Remain
Poorly written
In the tens of thousands
Have been uncovered all across America
And were ordered to be destroyed by high-level administrators
Stream chronology of human evolution
Another time
10000 giant skeletons
Ons of a bit seems like
You might just find him and get
It almost seems too low it almost seems like
Any of the people who had those
Skeletons could have said no I don't know
How much is a giant skeleton run
Probably a lot
You think
Lake part of the cover-up
Yeah absolutely
You gonna go to the National Enquirer
I've always said that National Enquirer is a wasted shot though because like they would pay you that much
I know that everyone's going
Bulshit like 50 bucks
You can give you 75
That's why there's a good one
Alright
I thought they were
I assume that they had
Destroyed all those bones
In the
Because
That was during the
Be great
The bone thing
Strong indications of this being complete bulshit as a stories that it repurpose old
Father's Day
Pictures of the skulls of people like Eduardo pair of obopry
Gigantism
Who died in 1904
The article lies about the context of
The picture pictures
Text believe
First up a little bit more
Difficult
Also all Spring Court decisions are a matter of public record at this one does not exist
That stuff
This came out on the site called worldnewsdailyreport they must
Remember if this is a great recipe starting on with
Steve Quayle
Steve Quayle is a religious zealot
To the point of believing
Music Giants because it fulfills his weird belief about Christianity
A biblical literalism
Even though
The website that he got this from worldnewsdailyreport
Includes this as out disclaimer
Quotes
Worldnewsdailyreport is a news and political satire web publication
Which may or may not use real names
My real or mostly fictitious ways all news articles contained within worlds has dandruff
And presumably fake news
Well that's essentially what we're dealing with
Books about Giants
For like before this
Fake article right
Using it as
Proof
He's not on such solid footing Willie Mays
The Smithsonian
I would lose my s*** I would love it
I need a Supreme Court ruling on that
A lot of stuff about
About to
Gadabout they wanting to stop the lineage of the 12
True God rabiou
And here is where he gets
Real
What is work conserved
What is politics
I'm not sure if he's ever going to actually touch on that part of it
The smugness here's the other thing the Scion
You see I believe that the silence in the abortion
The world of abortion
Let the silence in the most
No one since the Middle Ages even more so
Date somebody posted on YouTube
There's no there's no sorrow there's no Brokenness
What time is reading the Bible where all men are one body
That's the thing that
Crazy but you know what
All that stuff is taking place and I guarantee I can
Fruit
Because of the total contempt for life
Every single one of those babies that's aborted every single one of those
Brother or sister and women are being just
Rutilated
Rutilated that's brutally murdered and mutilated you know
It works
New word
Cocaine
They've just jumping around from topic to topic
Newark
He's bald eagles jumping around and yet he's a bit laconic
Little bit lethargic as well
Football is just a measurement
No it's it's a mix
No that's okay
Cheese ball like heroin and cocaine
8 Ball
If you're not
If you're not like understand
Exactly what
He's getting at with this
He's talking about this
Sort of a fundamentalist Christian idea of
Every time that a baby is aborted that might have been the new savior
Kind of s***
Okay he's on that tip to the point where later on he will actually Express
That it's a
Effort
On the part of people who are pro-abortion
To make sure the next Jesus
This doesn't come
To which I would argue
That's
Text bad
As a lake
Your
It seems like your religion is
But control of the universe
Did you think it is it seems like you
See that coming
Your God
Easily Blind Side
He missed every
Like the whole Noah thing he should have seen that
Coming along time ago
Redo the whole thing
Omniscient
The world
Anyway that's troubling
How come he gets
To tell people to go and kill every man woman and child at a place
But we can't afford our baby
That's just
That's fair game
You could just say God loves everyone every good turn deserves
You can just say Godzilla
Something like that
Give the same credibility as he's trying
Golden tablets
Zoe
We get
What I would call disgraceful
Native
Very few Ministries will even address the subject
Okay
Charts in the Grafton this means this this means that okay
And everybody's worried about this seventh seal seventh Prophet you know
And I said you know the only thing you need to worry about you better check with the Lord make sure your name is written in the Lamb's Book of Life you know
Work work work
Christian culture and because we got I wish delivers that were in the numbers lottery
Who knows who knows
Cancel gym the true legend
Hold up that picture right there it's hard for people to understand
That that that's one of the
Famous Native American legends
Delivery of the Giants being so big they could carry a buffalo or a B
Under each arm
And listen that's like having a meal on the run for these guys
And Tom came on I don't know if he talked about it
And the Anasazi
Indians which we lived in Mesa Verde they were the little ones
They literally got wiped out overnight they were eaten by the Giant
It's okay so are we Native American Legend
When you spend the time I've spent
Going through the stuff that's why the bags are under my eyes but I don't sleep much
Probably from the 8-ball
Speedball
Ribault
I would say if you
You spend a lot of time with him
One of the first
Things you should have come up with his
Is that honest
You're not supposed to use that term
Oh really the appropriate term for the population
Ancestral Lorraine
Pueblo
The reason for this is
The word that comes from the Navajo
Which meaning anime ancestors
For obvious reasons
Sabado de Puebla
Do not walk
Primarily referred to as
The descendants of enemies
Yeah
Is it cuz like the first
People who went
Through that like
The first white folk who went
Through those areas were along with a Navajo they were like these as bizware
So there's that you had a Navajo translator with you you didn't have a translator with you
You got that
Yeah yeah
So I mean that you should have figured that out with
Anytime
Fast food
Now here's another question
If there are current
Poplin
How is it that the
Ancient ones
We're all eating up
Because they weren't
But there's like
Dispersal from
Population that went out
Well when the giant eats him he throws the other one away
Right right
Appeal to Legend
In terms
The factual stuff exist because Native American legends
I'd like to ask you what about a Hooter
The Aztecs water monster
It looks something like a large
Stylized
I'm only with panda eat their eyes
I would rather that
Real the giant any day of the week if it Smithsonian is hiding that s***
Absolutely
Every public record
I'm just a huge fan of the gullibility
Inherent
Gullibility that you can
Heater perfectly
Whenever a dumb person on TV goes
Wow
Ray Ray
That that was it that was all she needed she heard that she was like wow that must be
Be true he said it
Who is along for the ride and making a lot of money
I thought you might
Who viewed the coyote is a trickster figure are we going to assume that the government is covering up that coyotes love to do pranks that's actually true
Oh what about rabbit tology
Which is broccoli name
I was born from a clot of blood and raised by rabbits
What about the spirit form
Die if you commit various things on earth
What about
The monster that killed people
Begin the origin of ordinary skunks
Elster
Like what
I mean like
There's only one explanation
France exact
Play YouTube
So what I'm getting at is like Legend
And is full of
Really
Modern
Real real
It's almost like you should
Put your faith
Hey it just
Old myths
Ripped from a time before science you shouldn't
Your face
Into things
Like a wendigo
A Jesus
You shouldn't put your faith into those pigs
Jesus is closer
There's Supernatural aspects two-story and stuff like that but like
Look at the end of the game is up then I'm closer to that then
To go though or rabbit boy
Besides the part about being born from
Blood clot
The part about being raised by rabbits that just
Like a feral child that's not really all that
Anyway
Steve Quayle
And that would be reinforced as we go along but
The specific reasons
He's being an idiot
Some of the specific ways he tries to funnel that it is
The message
He's incredibly important
And it's important
Remember that he is someone who Alex Jones
Reviews as a
A prophet basically as a is a like
The guy's a genius
So before we go any further
We can say with confidence
Jim is
Conning people
He doesn't believe in f******
Now
He's already
Specifics about Jim Bakker but
But he's a con man
Listen to this is the first of his commercial break
Woodmore of the Jim Bakker Show right after this work
We're sitting outside of our general store here at Morningside
Real quick Morningside
Pleasant Valley
It's a
Religious community
General Store
Probably more action here than any place at Morningside I would guess because it never closes
24-hour store
I'm going to suggest
How much did General of the General stores that happened
Underselling Morningside by food and
Probably I don't know if you haven't
But you know the thing that I've been saying over and over again
We need to be prepared for what's going to come on Earth so what we need to do
Is read the word be prepared so that we can be a part of this
That's going to be so Wayne time amen and so if you're not prepared
Be prepared
Why we have this special going on
Now if you order a year of food
Bonus food can they get today
Are dogs the ministry
You getting a bonus of a rice bucket and a bonus of sliced potatoes and just with the bonus
1/2 months of food
Bulldog what is it what measurement is a year of
It's in a big can you go to his website you can find the breakdown
Serving
So you have like 500 servings of potatoes
Whatever in this bucket
It's not
It's crazy
Gyro food
Yeah yeah yeah
Variety to it there's like a powder
Food like bread
Powdered eggs and chip
Dammit I am hating
All of the Doomsday Preppers so much right now cuz I'm leaning towards them
Like really realistically right now
In ten years I think
I might want some powdered bread I don't understand what powder bread ever but there wasn't
Since we started the show at
Standard position
Water in the house
Listen listen
I had to pause it to let you know because
This goes much further
Super donation of $600 in one year plus five and a half months of food for 2 years
Sears in a year for two people or two years of food
A double bonus 10 right yes that's right you're going to get two buckets of the rice and two buck
11 months
A donation of $1,100 to the ministry and what I want to emphasize
This the food is the best but then we're adding to it extenders we like to call him food extenders
Take the rice and add it to almost any of the things here let me have
This is kind of a recipe list of stuff we have
Is oatmeal you could you could add what could you do to help me out you could literally
Put
On top of that a lot of people have
What is WhatsApp
It goes out so much longer giving you recipes for food that cost them
What $0.45
Talkative
What is there sending you
And I can only send it by Freight but
That's just
If there's okay
Tonnage
It also
If you order a Year's worth of
You get a bonus
Right of one bucket of rice
Potatoes
You get a bonus of
Pics of rice
And two buckets
Two potatoes
Standard Home Shopping Network I don't know
Commercial for you
Another couple minutes
These two people that he has
His to salespeople
The creamy chicken and rice
They're doing the Forrest Gump Shrimp
Memorial escapan anti-love that he's like
Let's call it extenders
You put this racing but then he brings up the oatmeal other night there's no way you're putting rice in that oatmeal
Look if you chose the exact wrong thing
Cuz he's old he looks old crazy a*******
So
I'll tell you a little bit more about Jim Bakker but
Before we get back in
The
The festivity
Alright
I should tell you
That
A secretary of another
Another Telegram
Did accuse him
Allure her to Hotel Andra
Do you believe
Because he was serving God she
Rosetta Bakery
A lady named Jessica
Jim's version of what happened when he was called to answer for it is less than satisfying
Quote I saw a fully acknowledged that 7 years ago in an isolated incident I was wickedly manipulated by treacherous
Former friends have been colleagues who victimize me with the aid of the female Confederate
They conspired to betray me into a sexual
Counter at a time of great stress in my marital life
Vulnerable as I was at the time
I was set up as a part of it
Team 2 co-optimus
Name some advantages
For themselves
In connection with their hope
4 position
It sounds like b*******
So do you set them up
Hahn and Baker
Did say
No on record he said that Jim had asked for him to
To get somebody to help make
How do you say jealous
So that was something that came out before
And you just look into the details of this
It's pretty horrifying
Angus pretty f***** up
Jessica side of the story which I believe far more
Certainly
In terms of I don't believe him at all
I believe her
She was under the impression that you was going to go to this
Convention
And babysitting
His children
Call showed up at a hotel room
And you know
One of those things
Really f***** up
$279,000 in hushmo
Apparently money coming from the funds of his then Ministry
PTL Dentistry
Now that's an score
Praise the Lord
Answer the cover-up of this hush money came out Baker was forced
What's the step down
His ministry Jerry Falwell
Gavin cancer on the face of Christianity
The church history coming from The Great Escape Ministries it's whatever
Call you a little over-the-top
Either
So in 1988 Baker was indicted on a
Play counts of mail fraud 15 counts of wire fraud and one count of
Conspiracy
He served about five years of his time and for part of his cellmate was Notorious railings Buckhead
Infrequent Alex Jones
Who baker said was convinced that their cell was tapped
Quote to say that Linda was slightly paranoid Baker wrote in his autobiography would be like saying the Titanic
I had a bit of a week
On December
88 Lyndon larouche was convicted of
Conspiracy to commit mail fraud
Involving more than thirty billion dollars into faulted loan
11 counts of actual mail fraud involving 200
Defaulted loan
And one count
Conspiring to defraud the United States Internal Revenue
Did not file the tax return in 10 years and when asked about it
Flames have no income
Just a little bit of context at the time you lived on a 100
72 acre estate I like that argument Ball Z
Jim Bakker was in trouble and ended up in prison because he'd sold tens of thousands of $1,000 lifetime membership
Which entitled people to assert
Free Hotel he was built
Basically was like a timeshare type of
Never built that hotel thousands of these members only ever did end up
Building 15 hundred room hotel but represented
Massive overselling
I was intentionally very clearly fraud
Baker sold exclusive Partnerships which
Exceeded capacity raising more than twice the amount of money needed to build the hotel
Much of the money
Heritage USA is operating expenses
And Baker campus
4 million
Everybody's got over
3.4 million overhead
So now he runs this Jim Bakker Show with his new wife Lori
Hello peoples of the world is about to end
He sells literally everything I can get his little Hands-On with the help of Lori
Reminds me quite a bit of Tammy Faye
Pleasant Valley
Includes
The Morningside community
Which
It's it's f****** insane
If you go to Jim Bakker show.com
You can see all of the stuff
City cell
There's cozy cottages
Oh that's that you can rent a vacation stay in
That would be weird I would totally do that he has condos
But they sell
Yes they snow that's for they rent out condos
I watch other videos
Gesticulating when he
He's giving the sermon
He's just tickling around that the condos
Are the same room as the key at the open
Door
Your front door you're in the church
Basically worst thing I've ever heard
Terrified the s*** out of that on top of this
We have court the General Store where everything is rocking
Everything is a lot action that we have an RV park
Camping
I don't actually think that one's too bad selling property though is f***** up to make the idea
Prefab actually if he's selling them
Literally
In the church yeah yeah yeah
Boys boys really strong on that
Yeah it's it's pretty crazy Jesus was pissed
Yeah yeah
Agro that was one of the few like I am the Son of God and I'm going to f*** s*** up
So then also
The place called borries house
Which
Is crazy
They showed a picture of it and one of the videos I like
4-story chip
What is the UK
It's if you go to the website and you look it up the exterior of it is
It's pornographic
Inside it's so big you look through the pictures of it there's like
Ornate staircases
Within every picture of room
Every picture of rooms that they have Arts
Astraphobic they feel so small weird like there's a chapel
Haha
Looks like now
If it's so tight
It reminded me of like rooms where you'd have
Surprise meetings at work unplanned movie
Lori's house is place
Open healing providing a christ-centered home in
Support the pregnant women during their pivotal time of an
If you want to follow after me give up your world
No
Plus I mean
You know on the one level you have the idea that maybe she is
Doing a service
Isn't helping some pregnant women who are in
Doubt it but from the other side of it is
You know that this is
Deployed
To like
The anti-abortion
I don't I don't believe many people are saying
Literal house
Contract
Could be there's a floor with very large rooms
Give me there's a space where
Giant skeletons
So now it's interesting Seuss we've gotten a little bit into Jim Baker's con history and what have you and look at any rate
What he's doing now is
Yeah this is brutally sad
Is pretty pretty crazy but it is super important
Is to listen to him breakdown
Some headlines
Kind of breakdown
Familiar at all
But the thing is is that we're seeing
Now the literal fulfillment of all the event
Corruption we see genetic corrupt
You can read you see it. It's okay
You see it in the Highwood called the Midas
Dispatch of the Illuminati
Real quick
What do you think
Headlines
Corrupt
That's not
Suggested
It's not
We're going to get the weather
But just to be clear he's just
Drudge
Here on Jim Bakker Show
Philosophically inclined
Entirely
There
They're releasing information that will ultimately enslave us okay
Us scientist creating human-animal hybrids
Growing human organs inside
That's literally
That's literally the exact same headline that Alex Jones brings
Look up all the time
GMOs
Cyborg Cris Cyborg true
Fox News
CNN he's our mainstream media
Kind of gives up the game tiny bit inasmuch as
Is he saying like
These are from our crazy stuff stream crazyshit anytime anybody says they're from the mains
Extreme Newton
Betrays that they know that their position is kind of crazy
Yep so I like that a little bit
Exactly
This is the same message to Alex Jones in the world
To tell you
In order for their Victory to be complete or whatever that's part of it misrepresent
Chimera narrative
The Chimera narrative is now being repackaged
Into a morse
Specifically
Anti-christian
Message
To scare this particular audio
It's pretty crazy
Chicken Little
Suigetsu
Here comes more Giants baby
Alright
Situation
Relative
The Giants
What this is a whole lot to do about the Bible
Okay
It's over and over in the Bible it's many many places in the Bible in different words used for different Giants
The Giants
Are children of who
The Giants of the children of the Fallen Angel
Translate a giant
Two places and numbers 1333
After that every
Giant boar
Land of the Giants store
Whatever is refer to the land of the rephaim's
Okay Nephilim or fallen angels
Demons are the disembodied spirit
Of the Giant
The demons have app
Appetite okay fallen angels Don't inhabit people
And then they're all Springs
They had relationships
With
Paper people
Angels
Look and people say well why would
Famous quotes scripture the misunderstanding
Undertaker marriage that's in heaven
Came to corrupt
The seed
And the whole thing was they were trying to prevent the birth of Jesus Christ
And now why it's so important and that that's
That's the bottom line and everything
The reason it's important
Is because science
Wants to do away
What the last
Vestige of Adam
What
Volume
Okay
Alright
That was a jump
That was the leap that was a leap dad I'm going to I'm going to use my new catch phrase
I reject the premise
Obviously
Fallen angels
I have an appetite
And that means
Is trying to destroy the line of Adam
That makes perfect sense
First is that anytime anybody is going through a laundry list of b*******
And then intersperses okay that means that they are wrong
May 2nd
I know
We're Clowning Around
But can we take a second
Give around
Applause
How great of an interviewer Jim Bakker is
Like
He is asking leading questions Cameron
Great work
You getting one word at a time to
What
Although if you say it's in the Bible
Flights
It's in the Bible
IRead
Especially
Super Define
If someone says that to me I say I got to go thank you it's been real gif
I'm so
This next web starts with a
Starting out a question
When you say your kids grandkids and others coming after us and history
That somebody wants you dead
Don't scare the f****** kids
Black children in America
I'm sorry
But they want to annihilate you
So the word cyborg literally means in Central Command that the military wants to be able to plug into everybody's brains
And run them literally he won't be able to think you know
General Lee
The one that will probably running this program
He's going to be
Sitting there on his keyboard or wiping his hand on screen
And all the soldiers will respond to what
He commands them to do
This is also further in line with Alex
Right now we're getting like the idea of the cyborg troops
Like Alex talks about the
Vaccines with
Nanotechnology that soldiers are given and stuff like that
He's talked about the Chimera stuff
Like it's pretty
Clear
Steve is responsible for a lot of Alex
Whose beliefs
Is this a show about
Questions
Whatever whatever
Man that's a great question it's supposed to be
It's mostly about selling food
Food cyborg
Bright
So
You might think
If you buy a giant
You get
A giant bonus They Might Be Giants
And bucket
America was named after Amerigo Vespucci
You probably don't
You don't
To think everything works in pocket
Like that but
Steve doesn't think that either
Just one thing
America America
Land of the
Boom Serpa
An interesting Lee as word land of the plumed serpent
Inca Amaya and practitioners the human sacrifice
Donnelly babies everybody
Went on the sacrificial
But they knew that the Giant
Who ha
From the East
Had built their Citadel
It's pretty tough to get an Aztec and Inca to build the Great Pyramid
Sickly shells
And Ward
For the technology
So important
Jesus said you know we're going to know the truth
The prince is going to set us free
And this is a good work.
It's coming out
In the press to do away with
Humanity
He's so often and Alex project Bluffs diminishing of
Civilization
Bugs with shells
They could never do that
Giants needs to be there to build the pyramids
Are they were pyramids they were
What are they called
What do you mean in Central America
Whatever it is there
Most people just call the
There's a different technical name for it
Also
Of the people that I've ever met in my life
That is a strong word
I bet Steve is
Is probably the most likely to believe in like Eldorado
Let's
Do giants
Is actually made of their bones
Destroyed
Mysteries solved
No that's the
Just a classic sort of whites
Supremacist world
You know just a lately white
Before couldn't do s***
Everything else
Must be proof of alien
Or Giant
Because these dumb people
Figure out
Anyway
That's such like Marco Polo's description like
You know the the old drawings that he had whenever he came back of people who didn't have heads or hands or feet but they had
Add spaces in there
Chaste life
It was all pretty much b*******
He's making up most of it
I've never been there you must be right like this is also where the guys like
You don't know anything about the native text about
I think we would still be susceptible to that
Mentality
Even nowadays it's like one person went to
Tamar's or something like that
Legitimately
Prove they went to Mars
I never liked that a bunch of
Ruby like well
He was there he was on Mars
That's true huh but it'll be the same
Scrupulous
Sing
Think you're telling
The truth
Brenda Morris
Here
Steve says something
Really fun
And it actually
One of my
Respond to login
And you know what the biggest rat
The world at this point is Persia
A okay
They just announced that they have the electronic warfare any military guys to know what this mean
Taking shut down everything the US
Possesses and the Russians did it the other day again
The Donald Cook the most sophisticated billion-dollar
And they basically flipped the switch that sucker went dead in the water not the soccer the chief went dead in the water
Probably suckers really more accurate because
If you're got a billion dollars
Someone can throw the switch on you
And your multiple weapons platform just goes dead in the water
I would guess you're adept.
Furnace base adapter
What's the name of the ships
Michael the Archangel Gabriel
The fighting
Against the Prince of Persia
And it's at the Prince of Persia
Iran now
It's nothing you have have that will work against
Nothing that's not an idle boast
That's not an idle boast
What I do I go God
One more day
For people to repent one more day for people cuz we talked about the end time Harvest
And you were that position now and somebody was telling me that there's a scene Angels around
This whole area ghetto meaning your you're
Perimeter Institute
I'm going to send my angel
Compel
People to come in
Compel them and those that are quote religious alt-right
Justin don't need Jesus
Well they've got their reward
I mean that
I hope not liberate
Come later that's the point that I'm really trying to make is this
We are in we're not in
We are in the last days
Okay
Well then I don't think I'm going to need a Year's worth
I don't think I will
Depends if you post a pre-trib rapture
If your post
As we all know we all know
Pre-trib
Bulshit
Oh yeah
So the Archangel Michael fought against
Jake Gyllenhaal
I don't care about that
The USS Donald Cook
Very interesting
Right
In American history
Situation
What's happened
Sort of
But
That's not at all
USS Donald Cook with making Anna
Excursion into the blacks
Speed when it was buzzed overhead by multiple Russian su-24
They made a number of passes
Absolutely not appropriate.
Combat Behavior
In hindsight is pretty clear this was an attack
Provoca the ship-to-ship
Do down there
24th
And create
This point the US European Alliance
There was standing
At the time between Putin
Full-scale gravity
So
That is what happened
This ID
Dia of the
Electronic shutdown
Of the ship
This is so interesting tell me about that
That's so a group called the digital forensic research lab
I checked them out they did a deep dive in
Well forensic
Examinations of where
Things come
So they did some research
Claims about Donald Cook having a
Elektra
Electronics
Disabled because
The story was going around but it also didn't
So where
The story come from
The dfr alphabet a number of the almost
Identical post on Facebook to be in the form of a letter
Around the time in April of 2014
I think I can see where this ends on the ship
To his beloved
Mary they're all clearly machine-translated as they reflect very
Types of Miss translation of English
And includes
Suspicious details that leads you to a pretty
Gases to who's writing
Like quote
We Thrice cried Hip Hop Hooray
I'm prepared to show the Russians that what awaits them if they raise their hand for the second half of Ukraine
Are we all screamed out
Hip Hop
But you catch at 2 p.m.
Scream to threaten the Russians if they touch more of the Ukraine
What's going on
Yeah
So all these posts linked back to the entire letter which was posted as a Russian language
Opinion piece by a guy named Dimitri set
I would appear to have been written
Satirizing
U.s. Navy
Quote
Mary you can't imagine how we were
We've never been so ashamed in our lives other beat their heads against the equipment that wasn't working
The first officer dragged down a whole bottle of whiskey in front of everyone and shouted
Those freaking Russian
Repeat those freaking Russian kid beanie
Which is B I like technology
Empi
I had to ride the captain was green with rage
In this condition we were barely able to lower the roommate at the Romanian Shore and right after luring three dozen of our guys wrote
Their resignation letter
They couldn't bear the thought that a decisive moment in our equipment could turn into crap
Which state have to go to the bottom of
So this story was picked up by the Russian
State-controlled Channel
The show with it was Eric on it
It is called Vespa
Based
Based on
This haha
Report
The peace it was covered
Hold on covered by tons of foreign media
Not realize they were either directly amplifying Russian propaganda
Panda or at least covering a satire article to know and realize was
But
He was on Jim Bakker Show in 20
So we couldn't have learned of this version
End of the story from
The Sun or the times are any of the articles
Came out 27
So he is learning this
Straight from the dec
Has to have
Wow hard to say for sure
Exactly where it came
In front but Sputnik
Put on article on their German site
Claiming that they crippled the Donald Cook
In April 24th
And this is from the DF
Dfr l2040
Russian State newspaper
Rusty's Kia Gazeta ran along
Gloating article claiming
That the su-24 at Target
Did the cook with the
Kabini system
Knocking the entire agency
System out of action
And the shipping quote hurry to a Romanian porch
Historic nerves
By November Infowars reported on it with the headline
Russians disable us guided-missile
Destroyer
Incident skipped over by Pentagon friendly corporate media
Of course the article is pretty soon
Sympathetic to the rush
Oceanside quotes
Russia has condemned the placement of NATO by NATO of a radar on the Czech Republic
Attend interceptors in Poland
Russia is also sending a message in the wake of the United States
Tomato decision
Confronted over
In the crisis in
So that was my November could have been regarded from Infowars was getting it from all of these
Yeah Russian
But the only way for that narrative existed before
Like the sign of the times
And picked up on the story of 2017
Ramsey's
Foreign
Propaganda sources
So
Who's at the door
Steve Quayle you are a
Disgusting
I got a bunch of them in the car
Uno
Call Jonathan cloud
The glove box
Go fuc yourself
Stupid ass off
It's fascinating at the layers of it like
If you read the stone article and just didn't you know didn't yet to it and thought it was true
But then the timeline no no no Steve
Propaganda Outlet
In Russia like Sputnik
Rufus kayak Gazeta they tried to push it but no one picked up
If so
They didn't work
Then here
When they did it
It again
The same story when they
They tried to do it again
You can see the forensic fingerprint
Prince being exactly
The song
And the Daily Mail
The other ones but other kind of publication
Picked it up
It's no bolts
From there right
Crazy
That's fantastic
I love it
I don't understand
Why
If you are doing this
And if you know that it's propaganda
You don't
Mix up the letter
And just just rewrite it in into life
Just like
For real just turned it into a civil war
Dearest
No
We stood upon the deck of the
John Cook
Most of these Donald Tucker whatever
So like a lot of it is just like
You don't have someone on that yet
Automate
I feel like you got to have somebody
You should have
Why are we still giving advice to propaganda this just goes to show the realest I mean
Of course information Warfare asthma going on
On forever
This sort of
Targeted
Approach
From Russia
And
The figures
The people like
Steve Quayle
Who's big influence on Alex Jones
They are clearly on board with Russia already
You can see from Alex
Carburetor
Yeah they're already been holding two or tricks by
Manipulation
Better being done
So it's like
I don't know whoever talked about that the like
What were they doing in 2016
Marriage
They were already done
They'd already done a lot
I'm so now let's get another commercial just
Get this out of our hair a little bit
Heirloom seeds
20 different types of vegetables
There are Luminate they just they come back every year and it is
It's a great
A double blessing it is if you get the 7 years of food then
You have the seeds you can just keep adding all this food and mixing together you have all this
Outside and pick from the garden add that in and add the rice and the multiplier
As someone who eats mostly eggs and rice and vegetables
And if
If enzymes were coming
Dial be like
Great
Whoopty
I'm not be excited about it like I don't know what it is
Something about the way he says food makes me
Food food
Seven years of food
To talk about it
It's a double
Got you also other things and silver solution
Like you probably a colloidal silver of some kind God.
Also he at least shares one sponsor
Literally
Alexapure air filters
Alex Jones
That was one of the sponsors
There's a sponsor
Of
Jim Bakker
Who Alexa
Probably sign on them
Probably just sell through them there's like wholesalers
You know we just mark down a little bit
Right reason we still filters
We haven't heard
Like the Alexa fiehrer person
Come on out the show and do limericks yet
Bulgaria map
Another similarity with Alex
Of the rhetoric
At all of these things are happening
I was so shocked
When Tom Horn told me
Dadant Everett
Single state
They are experimenting
Wolf hybrid human being
Don't worry about who Tom Horn
He's at another time
Okay
Absolutely
Human
How do I say sacrifice
You can't
Put Christmas tree in Town Square
It's not as government property
Doing experiment on
It's because the people that are making
A war on Chris
Want them absolutely
Destroyed
This is something that the Christians understand we've been given
Power through the Holy Spirit
Anymore very few okay there is no way to deal with the stuff in the nap
So you don't
You've got you've got a left-handed right now
And let me know you got to prep you got to have your power your food you know your water critical
Okay the ability to defend yourself and I'm by the way I'm a guy that preaches on the radio every woman that every woman
Concealed weapons permit
Because I'm going to make sure that the last
Breath out of my mouth no woman is brutalized by the people that are being
Brutalized
Rape murder in Europe okay and no says anything
He was doing so good for you
No I don't want
He was doing great and then he said that you're a partner like that you're on that site
Hey
The similarity to the Alex always going on and on about how we need to arm women
Is
Also
Women want Guns automatic
But I'm not going to jack off about it
We're going to let them have the choice to have gone
I'm pro-choice
With women having gun
The other
Then there was
You know you need that you're right in your left hand
You have your last name
We have your prepping
Engineer
By the way
Double bonus
Most people aren't ambidextrous
You got the other hand is kind of a waste
For the most part. Okay
You know all that prepping
What is largely away
I get it
I see what you doing now
You hate left-handed people
Why did you do that
But why did
Did you force people
Locust
I would argue
If your left hand
You everyone should have one hand
That's what I'm saying
I'm sites
And it should be attached to the water
Imagine whatever day of the week it is
The power goes down
Call bank
What if he 8:30 p.m. car do not work they go to pump gas
There's no gas
Cuz you can't f*** with no power
You could be Virgie broadcast
Nation comes on
Do do
Unforeseen circumstances us Cyber attack on Iran
Structure
They're going
To generate
The Prof
That they will provide the solution for
Call Becky Italian dialect
And then we will be brought under
The control remember that it's all about control it's all about
Hell yeah
Hellyeah Hellyeah
Man all the messages being put out
Synchronized essentially throughout all of this world
Magic for the horrible Christianity that I was raised in
Oh well at least they f****** talked about the Bible or some s*** whenever I was growing up this is about cyborg
But I feel like a piece of that is actually what kind of got me a little bit but I was
And I like about it watching this exactly what happened
This is a clip that
Play Ventura
Harken back
Like my religious deism
There's some things were easier
I was a kid
Watching this evoke
Wildly prefer people believing weird s*** and then holding snakes instead of them being like
You know the government's making chimera
Alright alright
Snakes theme song
Exactly exactly like you're crazy but I think you mean it you mean it
It's toast
See through
Lake speed
I think it's
Is not that smart
No I'm very much now
And couldn't
Cut it as a
Scholar
Can Rider I don't know if I could either so I'm not like I'm not criticizing
I probably could make it as dollar needed
He decided to take a little bit of a shortcut which is
Reading up on mythologies and stuff like that and trying to find ways to
Used to gather things
Pretentious real
Put out a bunch of
Stupid ass box
A man starts screaming about government
Depression and what-have-you
Link yourself up with the right-wing real hard and
Start selling gold
Does the other gold
Sale operation
Diversify
Her does though
I bet he does
Say
So
Hey man
I know that I know that you think I'm Arizona belong
Church but
A man who's dead now
Heard me on the radio years ago
I want you to know he verified who he was
And he
I have
Seen human being
Animal hybrid
In cages
Crying out
Help me I'm a human
Puppyspot I was against the death penalty for a long time
Against the death penalty for a long time but there are a lot of people that need to die
That's f***** up f***** up wife
Cages right now
That's fair physical plant
Babers
I don't know what to tell you but
F****** guide
Tupac All these places
A app
People being engaged
And then watch people going to f******
These are people in
Who are saying maybe they are and maybe they aren't
You should trust them they apparently his I could make the argument that their ID Missouri
He's like
Look how terrible approach to the camera
Alright I'm sorry I'm right on board with you and I appreciate your passion and I agree with your sentiment
Compartmentalize
No he's very clearly expressing something
Claims someone told him
Story
Is the Genesee
Of that
That story about fish
Facebook Chimera beans
And he confirmed who it was
Though he won't tell you or confirm to you
What is very credit
This is by no means considered hearsay in a court of law
Worldnewsdailyreport at nautical but others
Supreme Court Acts
They needed to reveal the
Spirit quartz
Start back at the beginning of it cuz he got so mad
I'm sorry I was
Turn me on the radio years ago
He said I want you to know he verified who he was
And he
I have seen
Human being
Animal hybrid
In cages
Crying out
Help me I'm a human
And he said
He said
Suck in this guy made the
Okay you made it to me I've talked about on the radio
I am
An assassin
I get that
And by the way he sent his son to Bibles
Even though he was the most profane man I've ever met
But he said even as hard as my heart was
When you see
Human-animal High
That was once
Strictly humor
And people do that
If you see in the headline
In all
States in our country are
Beat to the rebuttal you can't do that
And in every country
Angola
Doing it
Burkina Faso
I don't even know where that is but they're doing it
Capitals of Ouagadougou
Madagascar
Okay Madagascar actually they are
Madagascar is a study on Evolution and island nations and how you can see the flower
Species that would go on the Instinct and otherwise places everything
Fantastic
Play Chris Rock David Schwimmer movie was actually a documentary all those animals in Madagascar were chimeras
Chris Rock has been in
All time
Of course
Bigger and more chimeran
What all right
I can't
You know
It's one of those things you know
Alright you on the show there's another guy who's a guest is name is David like
He's a preacher but he is mostly silent wow Steve Quayle Steve rolls over everybody
God intend
But he gets to say a little bit here
I'm at this
F******
So laughing
It's telling you to get prepared
It's all about Jesus
Folks
Antonyms of former pastor Pastor 27 years
I'm so tired
Alex pantywaist pastor
We won't preach anything
Politically correct
All they want is your money
The denominations got done with them
He brought us out of the Harlot
But I just want to warn both
Images laughing
I love I love a guy is a baker shows your money
Preachers just want your money
You find it within Infowars
That's where you find
Does mega mega churches ask
Skin for your money by the way
You can get a
Only $600 when you talk about megachurch
You don't get more Mega than this guy who has built a city around who
Lake is community Ozarks
Look in the middle of Missouri
Write as a p.o. box in Branson
Because
Is churches too far away
Doubt it is essentially an apocalyptic cult that's funny
Yeah I don't know one of those
Prosperity Gospel
Yes they told me it's a matter of
Actual
Poundage of money
Antimatter
Well certainly we're going to get to that
But it's more about like
He's created a world
Megachurch people they get in and get out and then go about their lavish lifestyles
Living mansions
Like God's
Extravagant lifestyle that their megachurch affords them but
I don't I think
From everything I can tell Jim Bakker seems to like
Have a comment
Yeah I don't know if he lives there all the time but it would be stupid if he didn't because
Like I said
Lori's house
Is Giant
Buildings are art
Giant
Huge
It's crazy
If you have the money to do this and live in a mansion somewhere else
I don't even want to
Considerate also why would he live anywhere else
You live in the only place where he's worshipped regular lamps
If he went anywhere else people be like
Or kick his ass
There's a lot of people who probably a really mad at him
He probably
It's probably a situation where the Ozarks are where you can hide
Yeah
To some extent
Senescence
I told you were going to get to poundage of food
How much pound
Flesh this out but that last the guys talking about
The
These other piece
Preachers they just want your money in that stuff back to another of Alex's
Rhetorical
You people of what you're doing
Very good strategy in order to
Deflect
Criticism of yourself
When you're very obviously running
Scammed
Accuse people
Especially people who have nothing to do with what you're doing
Other preacher
It's preemptively saying I'm Rubber and you're glue that's that's what it is
Pound of haddock
In this clip
Jim Bakker
Sort of insinuate that you don't buy his food you'll be forced to take the mark
That sounds right
Ship gets
Weird
Yelp reviews for
Princeton
I've got a granddaughter who's
I've got a grandson
Who's
About three months
Nieces and nephews here now
But I would check it again
Define
And they're crying what am I going to do
What am I going to do
Who is
The joy of my heart
You all say well I'm strong
Alright
I'll believe that when I see it
Batman
But why
For years and years
Panda
Amiel's here
Morningside
About coming
Distill
Weird
That's where I go
Because I couldn't I couldn't quite tell what the guy said
But it wasn't good
There was something I come on man
Don't even
Try
Think about coming to steal my food
Why would I
It was the last thing on them if I was hungry
Well
Preach that again
Please
If
ER
So I found a review of the food
Apocalypse Chow where they try that.
Blind
Hear it in PR we tried the
The creamy potato soup
Macaroni elbows in
Powder and the chicken noodle soup
And of course we had to test
The chocolate pudding
For dessert
Extremely salty and had odd lingering aftertaste
We couldn't agree on which was worse the thick potato soup that felt like eating wet cement
The strong chemical overtones of the chocolate pudding or the
Disturbing radioactive orange of the macaroni and cheese
Pro-tip did not make a mistake we made of adding more
Portuguese.
Because work
I feel like that's on NPR
Liberals run
It's awful
It's trash Greg lauro of Brooklyn New York tells basalt
November video for sploid Loro Cooks
Taste test several dishes
From baker's revivalist Buck Italian marinara the potato soup
Black bean burger stroganoff and chocolate pudding they taste
He says like cooked paper mache a bathroom at a bar at the end of the night in the college
I'm simply one of the worst things I've ever eaten in my life
Frank Davis is the founder of food for health International one of the two companies
The manufacturer the food for the
Jim Bakker
Show
He takes issue with Laura brutal critique of throttle
40 Years War
When stored and ideal basement lights
Conditioned hunger is the best
It's not crucial to you not
To use anything
Mickey go rancid like
Even though animals
Make a cheaper more flavorful
There's no way that will work
Korean baseball
Not all products are vegetarian
Many like the answer
The potatoes have rendered
Creamy stroganoff ingredients list a vegetarian
Bass
Bubba Bubba
It's all Quote this is the chef
Loro
It's off-putting Baker is trying to sell this stuff on its
It doesn't look or taste
Anything like he advertise
So there's that
I don't know if your years worth of food
It's not
No
That's just
I mean if you're already predisposed to buying a Year's worth of food
I don't think taste is big on your on your list
Priority
Probably not because the point of this food is you haven't been able to eat
Just looking for a calorie
Go for it
But at the same time
Food as food
Write using these pricks
Fear in order to
To sell the food
Clip from one of his commercial
On this episode
That I found jarring and it was because
So indicative of
Every
Telemark
Televangelist
So do it today we know we don't know what
The future brings
But
We can be ready for the future
That I believe you haven't done it
But I believe that God is really speaking to someone someone be prepared and if you
You haven't even started
Maybe today is the day you need to order that seven years of food
You'll not
Be disappointed
If you prepare
Wait we have to get back to our program right now
Yeah I got to go
I will
Commercial for a product that I was like
I mean that's out of my price range
But that's pretty cool
Generator look at fuelless generator that they sell for like $3,000
Oh yeah but it looks really cool like
Cuz you eat we can do is you
You can hook it up to solar panels
They comes with a couple solar panels you can hook up
Come to the back
Apparently
Allegedly
2 hours
With the solar panel
You know there's other ways to power it like
You can find Outlet you can
But his like USB ports
It has like gopher
4 phones
It's got a bunch
I want one of those what I'm saying
Smaller version of that would be amazing for like Tampa
You know what I'd forgotten the generators and probably come a long way since I've ever consider
Wasn't even the product they're selling it's like
USB
So now I really want to generate
Feeder
And then we will power outage
Wrap up with
In the last
We want to live in the city
Sunnyside
Yea or
Or something
Morningside
I want to tell you
1 minutes
Something
What they want
Holding
A roast turkey in her hand
Then they want it on it
Grandma
Head off
Yep
Turkey
What people are hungry and then there's
Converted
They're going to take what they want
Jesus allows you to not feel
Also
I'm not so I made sure certainly get a hypothetical gang members that are certainly using racist
Beer to deport in prison
Yes
Highway
I was in a prison cell with prison cell
You're too rich old con man in a minimum-security prison gangs were you in
Stupid credibility
Now the idea do Demi he's just using classic racer
We are basically the marauding minorities
Everyone leaves everyone
I don't think it's great of a game wants to behead your grandma for a turkey
Or chicken or whatever you're saying roast chicken
Probably
Better taste
I will say actively what Jim Bakker does as a
The career
Is talking that old woman into giving away her turkey
Or chicken
He is just using a different tactic in order to get the exact same thing
The Gangs do
He uses emotional manipulation
Fear of religious s*** that's all made up and apparently Giants
In order to trick grandma in
What she can't afford
Violence
To take your grandmother
And I will only use the 300 Violin fridge
I am a good man that actually make sense
Don't buy my food
Buy a home in my community
Where I have millions of
Right that's the only way that makes sense
Because you're safe in his
Apparently everyone has guns
Well-armed.
I don't know
I hate this guy I am feeling so
Terrible
Like legitimately
I am offended
As the 10-year old Christian boy that I was
Come on
Christianity is the f****** worse in organized religion is killing all of us but for some reason like there's that
Like no matter how old you grow or how your opinion change like there's that ten-year-old
Part of you that was raised that you're never going to be able to scratch
Completely away
And 10 year old me is like
This is a terrible interpretation of the Bible are spitting on Jesus's face
You should be ashamed of yourself and when I come
You will burn in hell for eternity Jim Bakker and the only reason that you would do this
Is if you knew
100%
God wasn't real
The way he behaves is Sosa
Brutal
I don't understand how you get to that moral play
I'd like
It sucks because
A lot of the victims are probably well mean
People who aren't
That cynical
But like there
I know that my grandma buys a lot
All the stuff off at QVC
I'm not sure if she still does but like I would get these horrible
Stupid Christian
Some gift
But you would sound like
Two years in a row for Christmas
For my birthday
She sent me a book that was a tour guide to heaven
I was just about like
Yeah like in the structure of like
Is it was a hotel that you were going to
Gold
Even bother to disabuse you of your boat
Cool cool
The same thing
To being religious.
Volvo misguided there's like
I believe we're going to go to hell if you don't do these rights
Achieved
No acted out on it poorly
But
The people on the next level people selling the books that are used as
Unfortunately
Araucana
People below them
And I think that's actually the case with almost every
Church
I think you get the more sincere thing probably are the higher up people kind of realize that is a business
Because it is
Something that they themselves
I don't know I don't know what I don't know
Enough about
Play Church
That had the that had
In my small town
Growing up
I had to
World rocking events
In the Christian
1 Nugent
Woman pastor
Everybody
Talking about
Is quite a everybody
5 years later
Holetown
This is cultural Marxism slippery slope of subjectivism
But that's
That's the thing to me
Christianity exemplifies
The worst
Thing and that's the thing that they argue and they bitching about all the time which is
The idea that it is the Smart versus
Does the dumb
Like that's what Christians always fight against like that the idea
You can't go to college
You can't don't go to the colleges
Because they're fighting against you
And they're using the fact that you're not
Capable
Really
Of looking
Cuz you're dumb
Your
That's what it is
And that lesbian pastor
Exemplifies to me
Believing
I'd like actually believing
Because if you are a lesbian and you believe in
Christianity
F*** you gotta believe it
You got to believe that it's real true otherwise
Otherwise damn you are aligning yourself with the entire organ is trying to murder you
Yeah you know that's a good point
That's cuz that's what this is It's the smart versus
The dumb knowing
That you're too stupid to see through this s***
And if you had even though
The slightest modicum
Critical thinking skills
You would look at this and go
Wow is that dumb then it's the same thing with Alex Jones
Which is why he always says
They think you're stupid
Knows he's playing on
Securities
And those same
Speeded feeling
The people have is not one
The dumps
And most people aren't as dumb
A lot of people thing
I guess I don't know
I have no idea how to make a broad generalization Uno
Another employee
Jim Bakker
No I wish the song
Someone I got to say looks like she
She's 14
I don't think
She is a really important question
Before you can
I know you're trying to get a clap and I'm doing that thing where I interrupted light clips
Premier I'm sorry
Is the music any good
I know I did you know why
Here's the thing the video that they put out don't often have
The band
Playing in it
What the f***
Well you just need to hear
Steve talk about giant
What the f***
What is the time song
You have different perspectives on
Not true
My youth group
Guitar bass
All that stuff I was just a vehicle for the
I guess
Probably like
Funny something-year-old music leader to be the frontman of a band
And so they did covers of like me
Meet Virginia
You just described every youth pastor in this entire f****** c***
Also except you didn't add him that he was guilty of sexually abusing children
Music leader
He was beating like a second-in-command actual youth pastor
Name
Well function
I don't know
Wish you would step back from that ledge my friend
Big youth group
It seems like there might have been like some sort of a worldwide religious
Yes I got together and they're like these are the songs that are okay to cover and like time of your life
Everywhere everywhere
Didn't do that
The music guy but I think he probably thought that
Day was too hard
Something like that
Cricket
Sing song
I do but if you do do that then you run the risk
The kids fine
And then maybe
They'll find out what the word Duke
Right
But then totally fine.
Train
Third Eye Blind
Which song was trained
Drops of Jupiter
Drops of Jupiter that yeah yeah
So now we meet this employee
Lori's favorite employee
Would you take care of her
Would you say
If you are up there with your mom and dad
No matter what happened
You'd Survive
I know they wouldn't
Specific
I just I just like her response which is which might as well have been like
I'm not playing your game this is no.
Yeah I'm telling you she looks like she's 14
She's not
I know that
For another
Isn't that I'll explain tomorrow
But the
So the parents are there
All right I wasn't that boost
Not as many pounds is the potatoes not really but he's risen around with this guy about killing moose and living in Alaska
Different
Idea of meeting
Right so now the reason that she is there and they talked
Lori's favorite employee
Her parents are there
Kind of raping now
Or because the show ends
A video package
About her
Wait
Mike.
I think the exciting thing
About my daughter being in this program is really the personalities
Is really the people that have connected with her
Have invested into her
Have really given the time and the effort and the experience and
And so
I went anywhere else
Would it be fulfilling for calling
With some experience behind the camera some desire and info
Christian the net and found out that really her niches audio
So this goes on for a long time that music swells and at the end man is kicking in really got me
That swelling music over like the dad and the daughter talking about like having a good time in life
No this is an ESPN 30 for 30 of a tennis player whatever it is
Do you understand what's going on here
Jim Bakker is straight-up charging people to indoctrinate their children
Teach them how to use specific technology that his show uses then turn them into employees
Under the guise of something he calls Morningside School of media
What
Yeah buddy
The moment I Heard a Voice
You can look at my notes
The first thing I wrote was
F***** up
Udon and now I am
Furious
I think he's she looks like she's 14 15 16
It's tough for me to tell but I do know that from the website he doesn't allow anyone under age
Into the morning School
I'm at so at morning
This is
This is from their description
At Morningside School of media receive Hands-On training
Some of the best and brightest Minds in broadcasting
Dalmatian pointer
As you work alongside
Them to produce a National Leasing
Indicated television show you'll be learning how to use high-definition cameras
State-of-the-art audio equipment and
Professional editing software
Create content that airs
On the PTL television network in the Jim Bakker Show
This Hands-On approach will
Will will boy
The cut and paste ear and it said will you you a one-of-a-kind experience that cannot be found
You can't respond to book
Real schools
Also
I find I find it not to be an education when it's just send your kids here will give him a bed and then you can watch
They can watch us create the show and then eventually become the people who create the show
That actually less of a scam that a lot of
Reggae
It's not accredited
No I'm not saying it's accredited but but I
Spent my first semester in college was an audio production
If if it were that
It would be less of a scab that it was
I'm not with a scam
You can't learn some skills from
You'll have no degree
Know what you should do is just go to a audio production facility and jdola
Exactly
It's very clear to me that we have here the Peter Pan
Situation
Where does the Lost Children
Is there the one making the show
You will see that there's a cutaway
The go to the booth
When he's talking to her as like Laurie's favorite employee
Has a child Army that's running the show
Exaggeration
Peter Pan
No it's Peter Pan cuz she looks 14 and clearly 20
$5,500 a year to year program
A student becomes through his door
The FAQ
The school specifically state
Went
Discuss discuss
I think you specifically says this when discussing why they don't offer grants or scholarships at all
Quote what is the FAQ
Is Dan I am very curious almost will come to Morningside School
Prince story about God providing
Many of the support stories of Miracles and for that reason we agree with you in prayer
God has called you
He will support the finances for the school year
Also as a general rule do not offer payment plans
Also tuition is not
Tuition is not tax-deductible also if you're looking if you're looking for a fun car
College experience
You can get kicked out for swearing smoking or yep quotes non-refundable
Completely forbidden non-refundable not allowed to have a job while you're there
Quotes
Also also also big things to consider
Unless you're on Verizon you probably won't be able to contact the outside world because
Do not read
Yes
If there's a Verizon tower nearby so if you're on Verizon you probably be okay
But if you're on the other ones people have had
Problems getting a signal do not allow to print
Even customers to join this group
Being able to contact the outside world is this
Featuring not a buck
This is indoctrination
I was really really scared of it is really really really scared of it when I saw
Sure
Cuz I thought you was a
Yeah and knowing
Little different but it's still super f***** up
Is it the boys and girls that
I don't think separately
I already assumed
Now we find out what Lori's house
It's for housing music
It's not really about the abortion
Crisis pregnancy
Girls who code
So they don't end up
Open coed situation
Cuz if you f*** you figure out the God's not real bright
Black Square
Heirloom seeds
Investigation
For sure the Waters of
Now that we've come
To the company cuz I know why I did this
Yeah but I'm wondering what you're coming away with it
The same as
I intended that the sort of thing I am coming away with it with a
Newfound knowledge of my
F***** up upbringing and how it feels
But most importantly
I am
Thinking about how
Built-in like if we were to talk about Alec
In the present day
The thing that
Is getting
To me is that there's only one
Reaction
To turn it off
Exactly
It's just like
There's there's only one way to respond to that
You we can no longer
Like I'm not saying that we can never do a present-day Al except
Episode
To be not true or whatever but
I loved her right well that's
Not giving me many options up top
I love spicy
I love really spicy pepper sauce
What most people don't
Most people do not enjoy them and they find them intolerable switch
Alex Jones before
I find it tolerable most
People can't listen to it but I think there's some
Experiencing it
I can do it
I can tell you about what the sauce is like
And you can experience it on the second hand
Level and together we can make it entertaining
But there are other things
That are like
Their sauces that are gross
Are there two
6 million Scoville units or whatever
What's the f******
Point of this don't eat that right
Rubbing them around until you're blind in the present he is like putting Scotch bonnet up your butthole
There's no reason to engage with it at all
But now there's really the only response at this point is like
And thank God for the heroes who keep doing it but the only response to these people now is
Get the f*** out
If you're it's Sarah Huckabee Sanders is in your restaurant tell her to get the f*** out
If Alex is anywhere near you tell them to get the f*** out
Maybe we can talk later
After all this s*** is over but for now
Absolutely
Listen to this so now I'm back on the like
Let's
I have fun talking about con men
These people are evil
Jim Bakker is dumb dumb dumb dumb dumb but then there's also the
Do you like lust for money over power to not make it obvious
Trying to con you into buying potatoes
Because he doesn't mean to most of the time
It's a calculus that people do and I think Alex has done it with white
Jim Bakker doesn't
I'm sure they're not him but some employee
Alright
80% of the people who watch these are going to watch if you like
Percent of people
Maybe 5% of that 20%
Are going to end up buying stuff
So who cares if you make it over
If you make it over
You're not going to even if you're subtle about it you're not going to trick that 80% anyway
Focus on that 5% of the 20%
Except the 20
Percent
Does a hole
Text to 20% versus the community will only make the 5% more likely
Guilt about the other place
We need to keep this going for
Done that more with bigotry
Sales
Does any good sales are on
F****** much lower level than gyms
It's 8
Need to con people into doing the right thing
It's not it's somehow
Somehow they're trying though
To come people into not doing the right
That's a weird thing about the Democratic party right
Right now they're really trying hard
I'm actually in now I'm now I'm interest
Did you see how I
Or Taz did in the
Especially in the primary for the 14th
Church of New York
Well I'm glad
This was fun
Jim Bakker is
My sort of radar
But there aren't as many people who have
I like
Frequent
Contact
Yeah you know like everyday to make without a couple things a week
People give
You got to give him that you got it
Big Mike cernovich does
Tons of stuff on Periscope and
I'm sure you can find those audio video streams
Go over
That doesn't seem as fun but if anybody out there if you have other ideas of people who might have overlooked
Send emails
Send a message to us
Give it a look
But for now I'm I'm excited
Talk
Yeah
Jim Bakker
Pathetic
It's just such money-grubbing
Crazy like there's nothing like it
That's what
Like that's what really fascinates me about the
Is Prosperity Gospel guys
Is envy
Please add Jim Bakker
Is the world
Where it's like
Wow
You have
Nothing
You believe
If you take
Religion
And you take the
Like ultimately kind-hearted believe that
Life is about
Being kind to others life is about
Serving AAA
Power that asked
Steel to do what's best
And you turn that into
I'm a billionaire
What and if you do that and then you commit
Massive fraud prison for 5 years
Write a book called I was wrong
About specifically how you got a lust for money
And that got you off track from the love of God
On a bigger scale it's like she's alright not to build Hotel
Fine you just have Cottages now Cottages in Condominiums
Great
Proud of them
Marlboro.com
We are
Facebook you can go to iTunes Kylie review do all that stuff
Is the algorithm
Vince work
Do whatever they do
So who's going to f******
Themselves today sir
Call boy
Call Jim Bakker
But that's not right
No no no I cuz I think there's been
Dark Matter book
Are you
I don't like where I think
I think you know exactly
Does she look like Tammy Faye you better Goddamn believe
You don't remember
She's the one who's behind.
Jim is an old f****** man who doesn't know how to do anything else daughter in mb
Like this is like a former baseball player a former major league baseball player in the minors at like 5th
Doesn't know what else to do with I will tell you who does know what's going on
And that's f****** Lori Bakker you can go f*** your
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work