Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
Hello sir
How do you do
If you were at a let's just call it like a regular party like one of those
Because you my friend
Have already been displayed and you are fat
Thank you very much
So you're talking about like maybe a gender reveal party
Specifically
Baby shower baby shower
Mother-to-be
You don't know the gender yet
She asked
View
What should my fetus
Eventually listen to
And could you describe whether or not or perhaps the relative knowledge of Alex Jones
Appropriate to your coming baby
The world will be long over I am so it is irrelevant
If your child
Is taken up by the aliens
Much like the children at the end of
Nicolas Cage movies
What
Nicolas Cage has been Nicolas Cage
Movie 2012
Taking up by the aliens
Repopulate the new planet
The world is that it is
Aliens come down
There's just a random out of the blue alien let me be clear
My phone is
Mobile nearby
Your child is one of those children maybe there'll be archives at the alien
I have aboard the ship
I'm making listen back to what was happening in the culture
Little about movie
Is a torturous
Although
How to feel like
But also I'd like to thank
EXO
Broadcast on an empty stomach
Really possible I'd like to give a shout out
And I thank you 200 looks like
I thought I had lost.
Say thank you so much for joining up with the team Destin
I'm a policy wonk
We are appreciated
Who came in at a little bit of very much Michael you are
Someone sodomite sent me a bucket of poop
You can go to our website
Appreciate it it means a lot and we're getting really
Dangerously close to the point where
I can literally
That's nice it's really appreciated that
I've got a lot of big work in the in the oven
Of things that everyone is going to really enjoy but it's very working
Intensive anime
Take a while
Info baby is born
Play I Don't Like
Any of the words that you just use very hungry
Baby coming out across the boards
So
It's called go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
A lot of folks sometimes
Sometimes post memes
Never a bad idea so delightful time
I was noticing a little bit of a trend
And that is a long time
I'm doing a bit of work
On digging into the beginning of a party of course
And then we introduced
Jim Bakker into our fold
Revisit in the future
I found
Including him in our show
Like that we are talking about him sounded amazing
Episode
Place entirely at the general
I wish that there is General Store commercial actions
So
I admit and I accept the criticism covering the present
Alex Jones
Also
That most of the stuff you saying it's stupid and distraction
It doesn't mean anything he's
Just yelling Into The Ether
I don't want to cover it
If I watch it it makes for a boring show
Anybody else
But I think that our skills and what we can bring to the table is not best used
In terms of like
Just doing an entire episode about him screaming about something
We have done a couple of those in the past when they have come up and Lord knows there
Family fun
But ultimately it's so much candy
You know if there's no nutritional value to it and we're just what's going on
I'm just I'm just your spirit of giving people Health advice
While at the same time you're bringing out info babies right your China
I don't know
So I just
To cover a couple things that were not really going
Talkin about
I'm sure you want to talk about
Little bit the New York 14 race
IVF
You have any thoughts about that
Amazing she is doing everything right
She's got all the right position
And
The only the only observation you can take away from her
Brilliant and inspiring campaign
Chicopee shook
She should just quit
Like the moment she won that right Nancy Pelosi should have been like oh I'm old
I forgot that I am eight million years older than Alexandria okay
Amazing winning
Harbinger things
To come but it is a super
Liberal District
So there's reasons why a lot of people
Could under playset
And have a pretty
To do with it
Approached
Primary campaign
Coming encroachment of communism
Which the Russians don't want anymore
Cuz of God or whatever
Play Everybody
Number videos better
This is like going to bring about Civil War
Define I'm cool with that so she is a Democratic Socialist
I believe in our group misunderstand this
Fundamental piece of Alex's
Cosmology so I feel like it might be
You're good
Virginity to explain it
He's arguing with this
To Communism
So this is democratic
And the reason for that
Come from none dare call it
Conspiracy
The John Birch Society
Socialism that makes perfect cells for the people to lead into communism because you like
All this free stuff socialism and then
Before you know it it's communism which is really
Totalitarianism in Disguise and it's all run by corporate in
Which is a classic brought about
Especially in the thirties like immediately following the
We hate the Russians there communist
Realize that everybody's and
Railroad Barons are still a thing so we can't be having that how do we make it to that all this works out well
Socialism
It's the end of that sounds like communism under one call it a game
If you if you look at where a lot of these beliefs come from most of it comes from
Rampant
Communist
Fear propaganda
Years and years ago
I meant
Also just rum
Flimsiest Oracle
I promise
I'll do a much better job of
Explaining all of what's wrong with my near future
We be here for 6 hour
So we're not going
Do that that always
Most Anti socialism propaganda comes from the people who are threat
Teton Volkswagen
Be of the people who are best served by these narratives
Want to retain
Corporate capital
Exploitation Brothers control
So my biggest point that I wanted to make with people who are saying that like
He's just calling to see if there's a reason for it
Piece of his worldview
I don't really watch the video don't particularly want to go over that
So we're not talking about that and not because I don't like a half hour of the show
Cologne
Emergency reporting
I just don't find it all that interesting and I don't
I don't know I mean it's just
Fear fear being repackaged with
But
You put out a special report on Saturday
Which is yesterday as we're recording us
Sunday
Fourth of July is the last
Fourth of July
Okay
Now then
He just wants to sell
Stop
Bill Pullman
When you mean
Put out an 11-minute video and I really thought it was going to be his Bill Pullman speech like
Bill Pullman
Alex came to the studio.
He's just like this will be
The beginning of
He's just redoing all this stuff and that we're under attack
I want you
To get 50% off
Closest Vystar
July 3rd
Prices 205
I don't know I'm trying to repackage I don't know okay
Rehab
Rodger Stone taping
I haven't been forced to come before a grand jury
We have Rodger Stone admitting that
He met with a guy about getting dirt from Hillary to steps
Is it a Russian guy
We have
Indication
They're coming out now that North Korea is actually ramping up nuclear testing
The other day
Homeland Security
Came out
It started with we must
Secure
And the title was 14 hours long
We have all this stuff
Coming I like
I think that Alex
Is realizing
All these marches around the country
29th and
All these marches were people were coming
Together again
Family separation policy
How we treat immigrants
That turned into a lot of abolish ice protest
You know what have you
S***
Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Who's won
In New York as a Democratic Socialist
Enunciated the first
Who was everyone keep saying was
Inline
For possible house speaker
He's not dumb.
See the writing on the wall to put up
The front of like
Havis super-powerful Democrat lost
Mary Ray
Alex
He has to realize.
Socialist
A very popular entrenched
The Democrat
That means more to him
So I think he's
He's just really scared
He's going to be lashing out
What about you
I do
Is the 28th
June 28th
We got that Thursday episode
We talkin about because
Alex Jones might be trolling me
And Rodger Stone might also be trolling
Are there specifically targeting
Text drop
Alex that beard is looking really good
No
Going to stop
I think
I've heard about the studiously avoided looking at it
Get the beer
Atrocious
It's it's gross he looks like a disaster
I believe he's been referred to as chubby
Wolverine couple times
Background research on me
To know that I very strong opinions about
You do have a lot of beer
Not you trying to trigger me
Alex is what it is
It is making fun of Alex in the most
Obtuse way possible
Perhaps
So this Thursday
You think there's one sort of main line that goes throughout it and then that we get a weirdo gas
Here is what I would say is Alex's main thrust
On the Thursday show this is the game he wants to play
Shamanism
The thread that runs through out of the
First
Bobbitt of the show
We have the globalist in total connection fits over
Justice
Rockstone would be waving
When they released
Giving the lepus the biggest defensive fear they had yet where we going
For some of that
Rogers get on airplane right now
President-elect
About needs Trump's main Piqua
Most conservative
Well you know what he wants to do
Alexandria
Ocasio-cortez
Supreme Court Justices going to be
Boy I remember reading through the oldest
The Judge Jeanine Pirro
Yeah
Is it really
OK Google
Aripiprazole list
That originally put out instead of
Neil Gorsuch there is the whole like 17 possible one or serve
Murderers Row of awful
I don't think we passed the bar I really don't think you didn't think they're all required
Wasn't wasn't Garfield both the Supreme Court Justice and president
I still Betty passed the bar I didn't couldn't read requirement that was a time before the Gutenberg Bible
Requirements Army releases
Exact
You are correct
So no other thoughts and other ideas
I will invade for my TV
I don't know if they'll
David Naughton play
But before he gets
You got to keep up
Which eye is that
Interesting
Sort of standard
Play Metallica
And I read an article
Foreign Affairs and others thought you were so stupid
World
That ABC CBS NBC
Reminder CNN MSNBC
You're crazy I don't want
Obamacare
I got bad news man
This is because I f****** newsletter he pulled out
It's probably because of all the races
Probably cuz it's super racist newsletter racist newsletter
Right but
In the first person
We called the Ron Paul report
Yeah no s*** so there's that
I bet example for him to bring up
And then also if you want to say that that's the talking point
This is your talk
Because I don't
I've never accused of being racist cuz he doesn't like Obamacare
I would say that might be a piece of why she doesn't like Obamacare but my arguments are much deeper than that
In terms of what makes him
Would we got over right nausea
Medic is the Reliance on auntie
Dometic tropes
And the idea of it
Still believe
These archaic versions of anti-Semitism and applies them to the modern-day it has nothing to do with his idea about the Federal Reserve
Being a privately-run organization
That is a
Bernard he's using
Strawman
To get himself off the hook of racism
December Temecula
Brett just boring
Hate the modern day
Because so much of it is I say this they say I'm going to say this
I didn't say that they said that
This is what they said
Too much it's bickering
As a as a ring
Is bickering with fake versions of arguments against
Himself to respond to
Which is fun
I mean
But even in cheers in like season 7 they got together like you can only pick her for so long before you got to f***
Will they won't they
Is if you are going to bicker back and forth with the mainstream media
Sooner or later
You got a you guys got to come together and figure out a medium ground and then you date for a couple of seasons
There's a big wedding
Incredible just describing scrubs it like house
Where are you
Cuddy get together but then it might have been him having a opioid
Hallucinate great
And had a complete opposite day show
I think he has been
4 years
Another I mean for him
He just said he's read a bunch of stuff
Just gives it all the way honest
I think Alexandria is the best
Sitcom from the millennials
Would be lovely except we're all going to die before we can X
We solve this b******* that the Baby Boomers left us
So I think what we should do is
Working towards a better future for our kids for the kids
Anthony Anthony
In this
What you're really afraid of
All the time
I don't think there's a ton of value
All of these products are marked out to the point where the discount isn't even real so this is like
This is really just a mess RPG that you're playing that you're paying for these
The auto-ship discount is b*******.
Anyway
It could happen at any point
It's not very
Does the next couple clips
I really want a big reasons why I decided
This is episode we got to go over
Alex gets into an allegory
Might be a little misguided for a number of reasons
No but it is something
Now I have not studied
IMovie
It right but I did study classics
In college I studied
Greek through that I read a lot of Mythology
Alex Jones
Did they predict 2012
Hillary America
Here's why you got to let him have the allegory baby
Part of this
You can say that
You could
Are you staying with the whole step
In the mythical
Story of
Head
Severed
Forgot that I forgot her name but yes
Event at the defeat globalist Kraken with
Do you know what
I as much as I know you know way more and I don't want to embarrass myself so please
Yet Clips deconstruct with wrong
Presented
The first thing that needs to
To be done is cut off Medusa the Gorgons head
Much like in mythology
But before that will let Alex
Flesh out his ID
As the symbol of the dominoes falling to bring down globalism will be complete
Archetype
Has the Medusa head of the global network.com
Hollywood all of it
Hollywood
He was involved in all of it
And her head
Is a blueprint
To defeat them
I don't like that freezing at the end there this early it seems a lot like maybe so
Second Amendment people can take care of her
Although he does later say that rather should go follow
In a grave
Politico
Okay well that's nice to say that cuz of what happened this week with Milo that.
Everything I've been able to tell about that case
I don't think that guy was necessarily inspired by Milo saying
Not to say that Milo is okay or off the hook but it doesn't appear that that guy
Seems like you had a long-standing
Put that paper
And had a hold
I don't doubt that Milo specific
I don't I don't doubt that effect at all and then you also have these remember
They put out a piece
Peace where there is like
Are two bunch of their hate mail
And stuff like that posted a bunch of things
The people that sent them of course
Whether or not this guy was motivated
From
Specific
Received grievance
Or generalize it doesn't matter
It's symptomatic of something that
All journalists are
Racist
Sexist
Android
Just overall violent threats on their existence
And all that.
Are we indeed
Just the the concept of it
You should not be in the mainstream as a
What is is permeated throughout by Trump and by Milo and all of this stuff is
It's open season
Right right
Exact response
Does lot of people have to the shooting on
Do you like
Gab
CB posted were like good journalist
Should live in
That's a really
Cancerous
Oh yeah
Cuz even like I think Alex is one of the biggest
Problems
We have
In the public rhetoric
And discourse but I don't think
People should hurt him
Like I think we've gone out of our way to
To be very but you might
You might want to beat up view my email
Political
No
A little baby got back to the analogy
Gentleman
Persis
Medusa
Is ready
The Vanquish
There's one more thing
Really not using the word
Trump doesn't have the air
Needs a horse
On the horse
In the sky
Winter hat
Analogy of
Trump and Morgan and the Kraken
The blooming day are releasing the Kraken
So tell me about Perseus slaying Medusa begins with his mother Danny being
Situation where she was going to be married
To polydectes
Perseus viewed as a bad man
In order to do away with Perseus
Because he was always standing
In between the marriage the other polydektes wanted to have
Inflamed throat
To bring a specific gift
In this case he chose a horse
To honor hippodamia
The god or goddess of horse
He did this because he knew the Perseus didn't have a horse
Right since that was the case Perseus offered call the dictys an option
And then attempt to get rid of him polydektes chose the head of Medusa
Knowing that I would probably give her
Perseus was he have some
Jesus he got some help from the gods
In terms of gear
But you got the Helm of invisibility from Hades rats flying
I like it like that
Yeah yeah yeah
So with all that gear until he went off and killed Medusa
He returned with Medusa's head
I mean
Based on the story yes but if you look at it actually it's not great
Heroic Lee
Murdered her while she slept
If I remember her as well correctly
She was f***** over
And then okay
So he returned with Medusa's head only to find a polydektes of made his mother
Since she would not marry him even with Percy
She is gone
Perseus call Angie Alda all all of our friends don't look
Something like along those lines
Everyone married to Stone
With Medusa's head
Mercy killed Atlas
The guy who has to push the world uphill and goatee
To keep doing this
Of course he's a dick
How long is Prometheus
Call Ty
Credit
So long to Battle Creek
That is because Krakens are not part of Greek mythology
Century Icelandic tales about Seabourn monsters mythical creatures
Real living cephalopod
Carl Linnaeus even included is original taxonomy of biological
Creatures
Animator Edition
Took it out
The original
I did not know that
This stuff is not real
Pudding
Finer points
What Hillary did and didn't do in the campaign
Not the painter is any kind of heroics a better comparison
A Hillary Clinton Medusa would be the following
Medusa
Eraser in Athena's Temple
Athena blame
Medusa
It made her face horrifying as so as to turn
Who looked upon her into stone
From that point forward
Because of something that happened to her
She ceased to be human
But instead became a grotesque Nvidia symbol
You might say
But Alex Jones has done that with Hillary
Poseidon I guess in this case will be Larry Nichols
Alright alright
Alright
I don't know
Issue is like
This stuff that I want to talk about it
A mythology
It's from that class of the tie
Exactly
Architect
I don't remember a f****** Kraken
I don't remember I remember I remember a lot of
Mythology I don't remember
A some story.
Like a Minotaur
To go with
Theseus
Military refund
The stories too but he's so much better than most other religion
It's so good I love mythology
To like you know like
Native American culture
I love mythology
Too seriously
Dump when you pretend that movies that came out in the 2010s
Represent actual archetypes
Rhombus ology what you're doing is
Very stupid
And that's what happens when you drop out of junior college and think you're really smart
I really don't think he's using the word archetype
Correctly I think ever
You trying to this 60/40 relationship
Noemi is batting average
Wailord
Turn music music correctly before
Kraken rambling
Stand-alone
That like rant about the problem
Is that the idea
Now that
You slayed Medusa and has to fight the Kraken
Because Pegasus is what's going to get him up and fly him to the place where he needs to be
Look if you go back to
The Perseus myth
If you slayed Medusa he already has Pegasus Baker
Came out of Medusa but he killed her
That's part of the whole myth it's not like
If you have killed the Gorgon
You are friends with Pegasus I remember
The Disney movie Hercules Zeus and Hera and they had
The Great
A pair of loving parent if I recall correctly
Pegasus
Actually the result of the original rape of Poseidon
Library
You know it is The Offspring of
Poseidon and
Medusa
I think
If I was going to grade his paper
When I say
You can't have a paragraph As a paper that doesn't count
You're going to have to go back and rewrite it
At the very least
Hamburger recipe
At the very least ambergris
Did you drop out of chicken
Do I graduated from
It's like a basic you know intro all 3.3 paragraph suppose dragons like lettuce Burger
I've never heard it called that
I just assumed
Formulaic
Exactly
Did not know
Burger Time
Excited
Video game
Avis no Leisure Suit Larry
I said I was at
It's really fun
From a historical
His favorite villain
Almost
And the UN
But most of the nutritions in Bloomberg
Most of the
Workers comp and an ambulance chaser
Exploding Tire
Stop in the country
Financed by George Soros
Most of it
What
Think about what you think about that
What do I say
I mean why is it used
Just once
Zeus wants people to do
GM up the courts with his b*******
Most most most every amulet if you ever seen a commercial that's like have you ever had
Meet me there filho
Back of the Yellow Pages back in the day that was also Rose baby
He's not
I was curious about this one
That doesn't make any sense
Blue burger that means I have a thread
Call Fletcher
Alex is reading and chocolate is actually probably this opinion piece it was on the Rockwell's website
Play xanarchy article
But in that article also mentions the Bloomberg
But I think Alex just
Use that to give himself
Veneer of credibility because the Bloomberg
Not at all sport the assertions that
Arete you from the Bloomberg article
Soros fund management is pushing into the branch of litigation
Finance
That's a few head sponsor
His family office is bankrolling a company that
It's creating investment portfolios out of lawsuit
According to a regulatory sign
The Firm Soros is backing
Bundles cash advances
Fitzmall shops
The plaintiffs in personal injury suits in return
Supercut future events
Wall Street has been bedding for a while on commercial litigation
Which provides corporate suits
Millions or even billions of dollars at
Cirrhosis focused on the consumer side
For plaintiff
Adventures of $2,000 on average for legal claim
To Auto and construction
To cover personal expenses
Such as medical bills
Increase frivolous lawsuit that argument is made and
I don't know necessarily if that's true
Certainly there's no data to support that at this point
Led to an increase in
What's lawsuit
What are the important
One of the more important
Consider is
Industry proponents say the funding helps people win appropriate payouts instead of settling
Pennies on the dollar
Under the pressure of medical bills
We're missed income from work right
Pay back the advances if they lose their case
So as opposed to cash advances people could get me situations lateral like cars and houses yet
Just a piece of paper
If the case goes south
There's nothing
The funding group
Group can reclaim
We're take away 4
I think
Wild weed
Keep an eye on the idea that frivolous lawsuits could go up
This sort of thing isn't
Incredibly powerful be helpful
Do people who are square
They have a righteous suit
Against somebody
Can't pay their medical bills or let's say it has something to do with their car and the car is totaled they can't get
Transportation
Without
Some sort of like $2,000
In order to get by as they proceed through this
Then they get their settlement of like
$15,000 or whatever payback for 2000
Even walk away with a 13
In the fair
Should have gotten from
As opposed to settling for like
$3,000
In the meantime while the case is going on
Racking up like eight grand in debt or something like that
A really positive very helpful
Soros funds all of the ambulance chasing in America
Horseshit
I don't know how I don't know exactly
I feel like it's a good thing at the same time I don't
Know if I like an investment Bank
Bankrolling
Lawsuit no idea how I feel about that.
For decades already
It's been going on for decades are largely it's only the
I'm Avenue of large firms
Big corporate
The higher Stakes a reward
You get like a much bigger
Have a bigger Spot the Difference
Supplying it Mighty group
Which he has put some funding is applying it
Two people who
Don't have tons of resources behind them
You know it's one of those things
It seems like
There are parts of it that I don't know if I feel
But the bigger
If
Done well this is great
Yes that's what I feel about it
Goes
Great
Bye
Think that
It is a good concept that should not have been privatized
That's what I think cuz I think ultimately this is like
Yeah this is ultimately a pro-labor kind of situation
Exactly
They should absolutely be allowed to because if you're fighting up against a multibillion-dollar corporation
And you can't afford food
You're much more likely to settle and they're much more likely to get away with
I've got like a we're going to Asian flush
I'm all for this
At the same time I don't like they're being like an investment firm
I just don't like the words investment firm I don't know I don't know
I don't know I don't think
I don't know I don't I don't feel like all we're doing is saying like
I would need to look into this
Figure out whether or not I
Been around this little button on the end
I would say
Kudos also
Not what I want to say
So I don't know if you remember this
Michelle Alex
Court Piqua
All In
Why'd you keep saying all in
Secret f****** show up
Show
Is all in
He's running the back
We Are One
Who is the person about to be nominated
To replace the outgoing Justice Kennedy
Pathetic the time
They are looking to put
A better person
Very very very very very
Call your neighbors or friends or family Thumbkin infowars.com
Driving
Yes it is
That was my first reaction but I do
This level of doing it all the time
Rarely does he like
The f****** call people
You only pull that out occasionally that's level does only come out
Like I know we experienced during this fake FEMA camp s*** 2009
Yeah generally generally speaking
It's just the tease is there
Keeps going forever do you like stop people in traffic
That's where the thing is like
That's pretty special
Any idea who the pic is Neil Gorsuch is kid like
Maybe it's
No there's not a Drudge
I don't know
I don't know judges you think of any judges
I can't think of any judges except for Joe Brown
Mills Lane
Bill's latest judge from Celebrity Deathmatch
Your your level of weird
Good life
We're ready for it.
To break
Emily comes back
He's clearly talked to Rodger Stone
Rogers like
Shut the fuk up
That it's really fun okay cuz we get a very clear picture
Of where Alex is getting
Permission to say things
From
Homophone
Trump Supreme Court
About this on air before
Let's just say this in the front run
You're the next one
About that
In the next
But this is big
So he is a little bit like you being told to shut up.
You're you're going to
Going to blow up a spot here
Because obviously what he's about to say
Is
Man I hope it's not true
I don't think it's true
He's about to reveal at that lucky will I will day.
He doesn't reveal what the name is
It man I really don't think there's any
I will head
He's someone who I have joked
It's going to be alright
Whether it's socially on this show or on Twitter I have made the joke that this is going to
To be our next Supreme Court.
Okay
You allow for the possibility that this is part of the teas
That this is the work now
You wouldn't allow for that because of this
So this will be
Information is
Direct
From El Presidente
Phone calls
Enterprise
The calculus
Whatever
So the reason I don't
Because he's spinning out on Airline
What does Buckeyes
Don't put it that way don't talk like that
Because Rodger Stone probably knows
Can s*** like he's doing his like back of cigar shop talk
Look look
Stupid or something like that
I imagine that they'll buy that
That's the only explanation I can come
Love watching Alex look stupid
Bridgestone
In that way of like I'm giving you a compliment and yet at the same time
The biggest Joy
His professional career right now
This is you
Projecting onto Rodger
You're too much what that's what you want Rodger
To be doing I think a lot of times he's not
Steve
Subway
For his own
And I don't think the Alex saying that Rodger has told him
That this is going to be the next Supreme Court Justice
And it turns out he's not
I don't think that works
Mister Rogers been
That might be the game that's being played out behind this
So far
This weird spot
So that he gets that you shift over
He doesn't lie plays like a video of Rod Rosa
Being being
I interviewed by
Jim Jordan
Trey Gowdy
They're giving him the business is not providing documents
Undercover stuff
Rod Rosenstein the whole time is like
When
Something is redacted
That doesn't mean I did it
He's just trying to explain that like
Sizzle large organization that we have here
Doesn't mean that I did I crossed out everything
I have 50
2018 super whatever
There's a whole organizational structure I'm not withholding information from you at the gym Jordan opencl item
So you're telling me
That these redacted document
Not just black panther
Crosses out the stuff he doesn't want to see it's not like he's a grade school teacher being like
You're going to need to get rid of this sentence we got a
Remove some wording around
It's not that
Miss hearing
Clips of
You know
It's not a thing where I rule over
This department
It's a thing where
Iva head of it
But there is a lot of organizational structure to it and I don't oversee literally every single thing
Micromanage
Is it really worked out well
Doj is clearly
Smooth
Jordan's argument seems to be
You run everything
Which is not
I don't
Tri-County pardon
Trey Gowdy saying
This investigation is hurting America
Too much of the clip
Starts with like
Russia attacking America
But they're not being hurt by this
We are our processes being hurt
We need to wrap this up as wrong about the idea that we need to
You even presented as like this is a real thing where Russia
Anyway it's a hot mess
And there's no real point
Phyllis Denny
If you want to go listen to the hearings
You're welcome to
You know exactly what our two
Point on it is he's lying under oath we taught him
He's not
It's ridiculous
The Hill New York
More crap but
This is quite a spectacle
Trump son
Murder everyone kill me
Kilmore members of Congress
Show host
Router
Certainly
And physically
Lynch Mob me on the street
Simulation
Taking it back
Get back
With the 14-year words
We must secure
Yeah that's really the vibe of what
You know the people who are taking
Things back
A point where
Lot of people didn't
Like a lot of those
Lot of things exciting as like a
Horrible things
The Liberals are doing
You're talkin about like people who did
And I'll maybe
Maybe
Maybe a little out there tweet
About like hey
People's families are being taken apart
You know like that sort of thing
I'm fine with that I understand if I don't really care
I think that you went
Do you open up the possibility of Alex saying that
No matter what I'm not saying don't say stuff like that cuz the intent is to highlight how horse
Find
Are being separated from them
I don't think I've course hours
The whole thing about the restraining your language and stuff like that
Which I've been very much on the side
Now I'm here for you
Well that's it but that's one thing that you can draw from Alexandria
Who gives a f***
They're going to hear if you're the most middle-of-the-road neoliberal Obama all over
Repulsive
If I was running for president right now
What states are guns
Why not
Dax Style
D-Generation X Style
Call promo
It would always end
If you don't you're not down with me
Suck it all right
Like that we kick in with the theme song of the other Run DMC
C version of the DX theme song
A boy you realized chop is the primary
Never had a chance to get lytical suicide
Sonofabitch
I was just DMX and say
Say it
WhatsApp
Socialized Healthcare
Jordan go give it to you
I'm slipping
I'm falling
Get up
Right
Flipping
I'm falling
I can't get up
Give me back on my feet
So I can test you
What's DMX
DMX lyrics
I was just letting you know
I knew you were going to give it to me
Stream Court thing
And I
In the process
To clear that
It's Rogers
I know you are my next nominee
And
Then it becomes well don't
We look mad on here
About that's because Rodger has
None of these people can actually still
Ian Rodger
I just called him pretending to be a senator
You could talk to him
Thought we might find out a way here in a little bit
So
Who cares about all that
You said nothing
Having a fight with Rodger
A lovers quarrel
Indeed
So in 2009
2009 episode we covered that February 11th episode
Where became never forget crystal clear to me especially
I think I was late
To the party
I got to run out to jumped on it
Who's already been Alex's principles were largely based in fear of things that eventually could be done to
The idea of you no minorities being put in camps
Didn't bother him
He just was bothered about the idea that eventually they're going to do it
To us good people
Present
American
Western
People once the slippery slope became a plateau he was like
I'm fine with that
Scales falling from my eyes
I hear Clips like this from the present day
Quite differently
I was against the left and blameless in the Ford Foundation
Center
When the training manuals
American Bill of Rights
Free market is down
Gun owners are going to have to be put
In Fremont
I don't want that all of those things that you talkin about are all misrepresent a
Is all of this idea
These people are being trained by the Southern Poverty Law Center the George Washington is bad and
And stuff like that
That is all misrepresentation of
People
Realizing
That
White
Terrorism is a real thing
And it is very active
I told law enforcement is trained
To deal with that or
To look at it as a
The priority
To Alex's
Major threat
Which
It shouldn't
What terrorists are Alex
Hand
Largely his guest list
He's just mad
Because he's not on broadcast stations in prisons if he was on broadcast stations in prison
He would be fine with white terrorists being caught
Cuz any till I've listened no cuz they can't get like super blue through the commissary
For-profit prisons
Everything contract with the prison
Industry like for his product
Depressive state is great
Someone else we will end up in a police bait Hallelujah
Prison where his act like a market that he could suck off
Oh yeah
It's one hundred percent
So
I'm not entirely sure what
To say about this next clip other than I know that
I mislabeled this
It's very vaguely
Did you just label it not accurate
Labeled Trump is actually the nice one
And I don't exactly remember
I thought that would trigger in my brain like what he was talking about but it's so
It's too vague I don't really remember so let's enjoy it
He doesn't roll over when you attacking you
You're so mean.
Proving
You had us under suppression
Surface
Trump
Oxygen has been trapped underwater
I just kept that black part in there
I don't know I just
Real
We want to cause depression
What I hear out of
Love me
Well there's that there's that there's
Deerwood
Makes me kind of can
Convinced
It's it's like
Come down
To a civil war
You been talkin like this a little bit lately and
Makes me a little
And this isn't like
Afraid of is opposed to something
The precipitate know I don't even think I'm afraid of it I think I'm
I think it's more like I feel like
Because
Here's how I hear
This is what convinces me
That
A civil war or even just like not necessarily A warlike
Break up the f****** country
Communicate
Like there's no
You want the nullification
Finally realizing that there's no Reaching Across the aisle
Disorders like impune Barack Obama back in
That you would always talk about how
Comparing him to Lincoln
How many go to Lincoln
Beaches that are like
If I could save the Union
What would be required is
Accepting
People have slaves or whatever
We probably do that
Preserving the Union
Geography
If we could if if
If Chicago and New York and l.a.
Just those three cities were like
And we all live near each other we would create a like it would just be
We're done we can flip flop like a
I don't want to say this
Who's going to be like
People in Wyoming
Put New York and Wyoming
Are we are we playing
Arizona
Now we got the West
You know your Eastern seaboard
The issue is
It's just like we don't have it it split correctly
Urban vs rural the problem becomes
Imaginary
Chicago and New York move to the West Coast
Chunk of the West Coast
We can't imagine we could have
All of the culture
Put all of the relevant pieces of
Spell amazing
People in like Arkansas sucker anything like that
Those are both
Those are so often over
The rest of Austin Cantrell Austin area just like left Alec the other income
Buckley
Geographically it
It's 16
The country
Used to be
This liberal
Sliver
AB free
Minorities
Control over their own bodies and
People are celebrated as
People
You have the other
Parched
I'm certain it is within
Years I would imagine Manifest Destiny would pop back up
Right the right
Problem which is that Liberals are pussies and they get run over
Become cyclical all over again
The desire to compromise
I would always come up with that
That's why
Vertically architect
I hate to say Wyoming
Is gorgeous
Natural Vista
New York Lottery
This water
Do you mean need to be a port
Lakes or Rivers
But that's not very far west
Great
Push it over to
The world should look like
This is what I think this is our new this is our new game
I feel
Tag teams of wrestlers greatest metropolitan area
Over into Michigan looking to have this Midwest Alliance
And then we absorb into Canada cuz we're close enough
Now that's your liberal Manifest Destiny right there we just take over Canada
Or just like
Valletta
My joint
All the stuff is real
Sucking hard to figure out
I don't really know what
I don't know what direction
Point when the left realize
There's no communication
There's no way for us to say
Because anything you say is going to be turned into your trying to destroy the
Destroy America
Destroy the market
Yeah we can't say that
Even though that's what they're
The only way to do it is to create a more
Appealing
And that would be really tough without the
The edgelords and weirdo meme makers
Exactly her already
Is there
The highwomen
I mean I guess there's really no way for liberalism to really March
Forward
Guns
Mad about that
Sojourn
It is time to reveal
The Supreme Court who is going
On the roster
Do you want to give any last predictions
It's not Michael Jordan
Call Larry Bird
Judge Reinhold
I was hoping you would resist that joke cuz it's way too easy
Very few people
Empresa de gallo and there was a supreme court vacancy
I remember
It was just in the news
I learned from inside sources
Not just Rodger Stone
The big computer program
Record
Conservative judge
Front right now live
And that
You said okay I'll do that
Person on the bench currently
Neocon
Weather bigger Longer record
He is going to be the running
Andrew Napolitano my dude
That should be against the law about it
Stuff like that
It's crazy
Fox News
Frequent contributor Andrew Napolitano
Steven says that out loud we should have rights
Rights in the f****** Street
I did get this from Rodger Stone
If you hadn't just got it from Rodger Stone you don't need to say it if it's not something that you're
Preemptively defensive about because it's already
Positive about politano
Is it good is it good
I'm tried it
Connect
That's what all deposit
Civil War guy the guy who
All that stuff
Lincoln could have free
Replace bypass
Are slaveholders all that stuff
I bet everybody would have been fine with that
Cuz I believe that the Supreme Court
Oh man
Good
When
He's
Friends with
Get it back
It's not good for the president to be
Friends with someone he's like I'm going to put on the Supreme Court
Technically legal for him to appoint himself as this
Supreme Court Justice
I mean
Still need the law degree
Does anyone know what's going on
Does anybody f****** know what's going on
This is going to have
I don't think it's going to happen
That's a good point
Year-and-a-half
Two years that I've been wrong almost
Pruitt
It doesn't mean
Nothing
Doll just going to
Luba
Slide downward whatever name he says is going to be the worst possible f******
You get you've got a million awful people to choose from and it's not even like Kennedy with some kind of
Swing Vote it and he was like the 10th most conservative
History
They were fairly important but that's just because he was the Fall Guy
Like it like that everybody kind of got together and we're like
For real though
Like we all say we believe this s*** but none of us actually believe this s*** stop it
10-year the Fall Guy
I mean I don't I
I hope
You don't live in such a world where
This could be treated
But who f****** nose
It will be revealed his big piece of news and now Rodger
Gaston
You might want to keep your pen handy for this
Might be something
You need to write down
What's Roger's got what's right
Reality
Judge Andrew Napolitano is currently how do we make sure he stays at the top
Well if you're a Believer as I am that ended Apollo China would be a great Supreme Court Justice you should
Call the White House switchboard where they're set up to take messages from the American people
456 1414 202
456 1414
White House switchboard with supportive calls would be
Very helpful
Keep a respectful
Okay well Jordan is pulled out his phone
As I imagine you might have done it much like when Larry Nichols gave out his phone number I think it's
Switchboard
Is a telemarketer
And they hung up on me
Great switch will give another ring
You just hang up on me
What do both
Search for the White House
As for the president
Avenue clothes
Let me leave a f****** message
Come on
Call back and ask for Trump
Ron Paul
Quality Inn
Dirty Boyz
Which is the worst government we've ever marry
Larry Nichols
I actually do it later
About the cat
Come on guy
Come on
Rubino payoff
Representative
Trey Gowdy I apologize
He doesn't work at the White House
I feel like he does
Yeah but he kind
Where can you go
Prank call
I didn't want to prank call the White House
Put upon that's not her fault
Why would I ask for
Maybe I'm talking dirty it's a fantasy house
I've had sex with 45
I am very gay
Mike Pence
I mean pasa
I'm kind of hoping that
You kind of hope
Who would you even talk to
Trump would be up
Manning the switchboard
Himself never remember that I forgot he was Manning the switchboard
Awful close to that
Call Alex
Breathe
Tries to do like a really like
Pump-up speech
Does this really cool
Coming in from break
See if you can find the biggest lie
In this
Give me large
Global satellite transmission
Getting close to the 200
Albert Speer
Happy time
You know what I didn't realize everybody contenders a bigger fly
444 on the biggest lie there's ever been 200 something radio station
Commissioned by Justice absolute
It's vague enough
You know it means nothing
So that might not be alive
Blackjack on that one
For sure
It's a happy man
I don't think anybody's ever said that ever
Didn't
In German
He's Hungarian butt
About time
In the time of the Holocaust
And he's discussing
Support
Senior Old Navy
Free because of the heroics
His father
Saving a bunch of
People from going
Somehow that was at
Invigorated like nothing could touch
Even though the world is crumbling all around
Re-watch those videos and found a couple new things
Cuz he's also
Man the 200 radio station so that's a number
That's not true
Sure you did lie about whatever you want
Are we all of them
FM
Knowledge fight
You can find it everywhere on the dial everywhere 24/7 on every radio station
Do those plugs because you can not find knowledge fight
We're stupid
We are
Crazy everywhere
So
Mount Jordan we get to
Guest guest
Is wild
There's been a lot of bulshit
Episode so far whether it's
Misrepresenting mythology
Whether it
Really teasing out the entire episode that
Which I know we're laughing about now but unfortunately
I do foresee a world where
Far beyond the pale on Fortune
But now we get a guest
Is real weird
Real strange cast for Alex to have on
Are we got surprised
A while but
Books by Brian cam.com
5 high
Then I saw him
Tool Cover the Waterfront
Where is this the world we are right now
The best
Smell bad to an Alex Jones call I think we've ever had
Do you know who hotep Jesus
Who
He's the guy who went into Starbucks
Is reparation coffee
That's pretty funny
And all that happened was
Someone was really nice to him
Starbucks coffee
There was no real
The real Point made by it I don't
Starbucks was expressing
Commence Wakefield
If I remember correctly by opinion
Just go
I understand that but there was a certain
There's a certain level of like
Alright
Starbucks hours
The policy of
Did they want a cup of coffee you supposed to give it to him
Because that's good
PR more lies are good for the community
Coffee cost
$0
So he went viral video
He's so obsessed with being viral
Thrilled to have someone who is not white
Right is he still living with his
Did he go
There's a
Put out a video
Catching back up
With Mike Rotondo
VH1
Now living with
A lady who allows them to live there
Exchange for doing like yard work
I don't know
I don't want to disparage anybody seems like she's very nice lady
The reasons I think I will never have him
Turn back on
Because in these vices video
The lady is being interviewed in front of her
House
And she has a blessed Ramadan sign
So now Mike Rotondo has been taken in by a very generous Muslim
So
It's very mysterious what happened to that $3,000
He was going to do was going to move in with that guy
Well of course
So better
That was gross this is where my interested in Mike Rotondo
Saga has
Far exceeded its expiration date Islam that would be the best
Comes back on
Salaam alaikum
Kalevala
Hotep Jesus
To get into and then we'll get into
But we got to do one thing for the internet today
Need to see me and you
Side by side
Screaming and raging at the globalist man can you do that for me man
Sure
How is my voice
I love you
You owe me to come
Yeah that's how I feel when I come off my parents cuz I got that Ali's jewelry
We need that that movement lacks passion did you bring passion and I love you
Super siah
Dragon Ball Z
Goku and Super Saiyan in his first fight again
Frieza
Is very important then is the series went on there were different levels of Super Saiyan
Dragon Ball super witch
Is the new version of that there was a two
God level
It's a really
Convoluted
Situation
Fantastic
Just go out there
Sonic
What does -1 Super Sonic and Super Shadow
Also I'm installing a tiny bit because it's really funny that all this comes up be
Because on
Hotep Jesus is website
He has an article
May 18th of this year
Title policy is liberal bulshit
No Dragon Ball series teaches valuable life lesson
Watching Dragon Ball series Life Lesson Nostalgia every episode of inside a hidden esoteric
Jim's
Allow me to provide a high-level overview of what's
Gohan
Yes that's
Goku Son
Luxury of being homeschooled until he's of high-school age
What's the condition of the public school systems
Thanks to his mother chichi
Father Goku
After proving his power and his victory over self he finds it important to me education
He actually didn't win against al he went Super Saiyan level 2 but it was once again
A Spirit Bomb that defeated
Now it's talk about Vegeta
Yes let's talk about
This guy is my favorite
Inspire
This guy trains Non-Stop
Before the Android so I got bloomer
Yeah
Best way to Rue Morgue
Yeah but you would not be able to stand up in this room let alone train with a machine
300 * gravity
He was doing push-ups
This is important in the context of his own
Because the only reason that Vegeta did this
Was because Goku
Did the same thing on his spaceship flight over to the planet
Alright
When he was going to fight and that is
The Virginia was just trying to catch up
Jealous little b**** that's what's going on there
Is the series protagonist in Japan's Mickey Mouse
He's not there yet I think
Pikachu is still
By the way
Relentlessly positive character
Naive idiot
Oh no
A little
That beer was a little loaded there I
You dropped this door too easily and he is a naive idiot
But you have to respect his gangster comes to fighting
He wants to fight anyone and everyone to prove his Supremacy as a fighter
After Krillin dies for the second time but the hands
The freezer
We see Goku turn Super Saiyan Goku has the unique drive to consistently reach New Heights
He's always pushing the envelope
You're only as good as your last fight
Parenthetically accomplishment
Sometimes
Today
What is the next
Achievement what height are you reach
How do you feel about that
Rosetta track with your understanding
Piccolo's very interesting
Because he's trying to save the universe
We wish back
Doesn't have a mask
Piccolo steps
I'm going to read this entire helping
But it's
Let's go home
The plan to work as a team
Foreign concept for Goku and Vegeta
You have the energy and the elders have the experiences
Whether you create an Unstoppable Force
Set bad example for the Next Generation
Especially on social media
Which is very real
Dragonball irrelevant
We need to Holy Ship has nothing to do with Piccolo
There's six more paragraphs
Alright he's going to knock on her
She is like a stereotypic she's like that
Ideal
Of all the characters cheese probably the most growl
Well others are distracted with training
Aliens
Other bills that to be paid and kids have an education
She's what's missing from so many families in America today
With feminism pulling women out of the home and into the workforce there's no one at home to attend to the
Naked photo
The care and attention they need
It's gender roles that hold the family together is a solid
Chichi was no pushover
The only person
Can intimidate Goku
Jenna salt rifles and submachine guns
Parenthetical
I don't think I'm going to Merica
I know I just realized I know
She was no slouch and could fight with Beth
They never got the waiver
Is a woman
Skip Goku checked
In grounded
A vital role
Creating
How is this
What do you think about
Freezer
Frieza literally wanted to destroy the world for his own power there's no way
Itsfunneh
Sometimes I write a book
Not be allowed to transition off his rambling about Dragon Ball
So you've written a book
His real name
He's written a book called quote Twitter marketing
How to build a cult-like following
A promises to teach you how to quote every time
How to network with influencers for your benefit
How to manipulate Twitter algorithm
Although he misspelled algorithms in the
For the buck
This is the same as like Dave Seaman vlogger turn Bitcoin hack who had previously written a book all that had
Create a news Buzz
These people at their core Allstate
You buy that
Maybe we could get the better quit attraction I think we would end up losing a bunch
Marcel's in it
I like that diversion because it's fun to yell about his
Rambling about Dragon Ball but
What's more important
Look at this guy as a as a
So I will
The Navy wants to go by his hotep Jesus
Even though his name is Brian Sharp soil refer to
Website hotep Jesus
Hotep lifestyle memes
To him as best I can tell
It's pretty much just about black nationalist working together with whitener
You know it's bad when I'd rather align with erasers
Crybaby black
This is not really new
David Duke and Louis Farrakhan respect each other's desire for their respective races to live
It's not really a new
Like it's not a novel perspective to have
But he's just trying to merge black nationalism with white
Right because they would be a lot more powerful
Forced together
I'm going to go with
I will say inconclusive as to whether or not they would be far more powerful force
Working together
There was a way for them that's their leader
It would distract a lot of people
Running Fred Hampton was the last person to try and do that and he got murdered
But I don't think it was necessarily strict black nationalism and white Nash
He was trying to bring together
I mean he was trying to do that but under the Aegis of hey let's not do that right
Another post to find hotep which is a term for a license
Regrouping hotep is not
Just like I
Like I thought it was
Another place to find totep is being all about strength
Nuclear black family
Specifically defined as a
Child
It's really strange just like just like what he says
Hey
I didn't get this from Rodger Stone
A caveat
An argument against you
All we care about is the black nuclear family
Man woman child
You know there are about
Why would you I just don't understand how those two things match up whatever you want to say
Also the hotel
Denotes a black nationalist new religious movement
Emerged
Basically
About
Afrocentric version of the
Pharaohs were black
So it goes back to it
Africa
But all this is a spiritualist
This is like an esoteric movement
It involves a lot of
Alex isn't taking into account like all of the other things
His name being hotep Jesus
And what he's involved in
Outside of politics
Looks like the religiosity of the key potatoes
What Alex
Isn't it
This guy is close to like the Lost Children of Babylon
The nuwaubian
Like those shorts
First off give me the 5%
But it's not exactly
Second
I don't think that Jarvis
Much with Alex
Really
Because it because
It just like we just like we were just like you
All of his fears were about what if this happened to White
Right
Fall of hotep's ideas are like
You do you
Leave us the f*** alone
Let's do let's do that
Yeah like he's only afraid of black people
If there's the idea that there's an encroachment
Upon his
Whatever it
And if they're fine with his
If you're fine with me being a white nationalist and you just don't like like don't live near me
Then you can believe whatever the f*** you want
And he's sitting
Tony said it over and over again doesn't want to be made to feel bad
You don't want to feel bad about the bigotry that lives within the car
I want to be a big
Distance
I don't want to see those Muslim women at the pool
Eggplant
Exactly hate them
Steady
Hotep Jesus does not seem like a great guy
Do you have any interest
Call the United right rally in Charlottesville
Is there was no anti-protest there
Are there would have been no class
DeAndre Harris wouldn't be hurt and Heather hair wouldn't have been murder
Fat
I mean
0 contacts
Factual individuals who were killed
Antiproton
But they would
All be heard
More protests
Generali's happen
What you just said was if the Jews live in Germany
They wouldn't have been holic
There's something there's there's some similarities
So he's also appeared on the show called Red Ice
TV
Does the show run by Henrik palmgren
Is a Swedish whiteness
National League
Palmgren
Denying vlogger
Red Ice in the last month has put out videos with titles like quote do they want you
You dead white man
Interracial relationships are pushed on white women
Weirdly tutorial on how to make beef jerky that is still somehow race
I watched it very weird
This is the white whale
It's very weird
I just don't pull it look if you pull this Jamaican jerk chicken
That's not even jerky
I didn't tell you the right now that's like a combination of spices of like
Cooking tutorials
This one was like
Coolest dresses
I recommend everyone go watch it I think you'll agree with me
Feels backed up
So nice
She isn't real
Actually a plot of the
Quote
Is it always comes back
The only thing that makes white supremacy I thought people mind
Is the media and the media is controlled by who
Should've been home
The only thing that makes his music
That's controlled by who should've been home
The movies Hollywood who controls that
We talked about people got sold out
Well who controls these Banks
It's off-limits.
It's already know that my country United States
America is going to become an Islamic judelle.
Dominick's steak
School
I don't think
Islam that he's
Afraid of
Is Cool Whip
The LGB
That he's also afraid of
He's afraid of a lot guys just kind of like
Set down
Like really worked out
The fears that they have are the Venn diagrams that they exist
You know
Like I'm cool if you're I'm not cool I'm just saying like
Ideologically afraid of Muslims I don't like because
No that doesn't happen
For a very specific
These people aren't interested
First aid in reality
That's very interested in spreading a fee
Look as if they'd if it is okay
You sit down and think about
What am I advocating
Does this make sense
Does
Does does a b and c of the things I'm afraid of could we possibly coexist interstate I should be
Be afraid
He would have to sit back and be like
I got to get a better Rock You
Nek not happening
It's about
Brandon's about getting a cult-like Twitter following it's about what he wrote a f****** book
We should read that book
Did write a book
About culture
You didn't write a book about how it's important
To free yourself from the shackles of
The globalist
Or whatever
You wrote a book
Bryant.com
Bryan
To look for books by Brian fell braai
Just a
Different Brian brain brain
No Brian
You said
If you go to that it's a Amazon books
But like the book that he's selling that he's trying
To push is about getting attention
It's not about the
The substantiv issues
That leaves
That's what he's more interested
Time spreading
Very deeply bigoted
Or
If you are a
You get that
Attention of the cult-like
Well yes he's credited all the time he was on Laura Ingraham show use credit as a comedian
Stand-up comedy
We should find the check
To that point
If you are
Black
Looking to get as much viral attention as you
You possibly can
For taking the position
That people who have
Power
In order to take advantage of the fact that you are black saying all of them
Discredit the actual voices who are working
For the people the workers of the world
You working class
Alexandra
Anacortes
Alexandria Alexandria
Alexandria Cortez
Okay zi Cortez
They took her winning
This race
In order for people to ask
We talked about her in the media
The intercept
It was like in the rest of the world was like
We don't need the actual winning of the primary race in order for it to become a voice that
But if
You go this route
Very easy
Still get attention
Make millions of dollars
If you're running scam you can find your niche
You know like you can find it Jesus wrote a blog post called anti-racism is worse than racism
Why Dragon Ball Z
Are you says quote what's the wrong with white people saying White lives matter
If you say black lives matter doesn't that open the door for its antithesis
Now this is dumb
Because it's pretty amazing that you can't understand
Spider with a that is not the lives matter
Right right
No way was better argument
GoNoodle
White people scream white power White lives matter black people get offended I don't
I'm proud of these whites
It's self-determination and I'll gladly applied any group that
Xzibit self-determination
My Counterpoint
Is the historically people who yell white power or also the ones who are really black
So it doesn't usually mean like I love being white and I like to celebrate eat a brat
It's not
It's usually
Power against you
Usually the people who are throwing in
Which
To that point
Griezmann
Just introduced maybe lynching should be a hate crime bill
Already been on that one a long time ago
This group
Didn't show up in Charlottesville
The truth is none of us would
We'll be talkin about Charlotte
If you picture white nationalist
Sapphire anti-protest group
My Counterpoint to that is
Nope
Or you could say if you picture of
As a fire
Then white supremacist are the people who are
Before the Charlottesville rally there was a talking Nazis yelling blood and soil and Randy
Tiki torches and what-have-you what are the gator shirts
Crocs
God
This really doesn't take him too
The consideration that what happens
With
Movement
Like
Fascism
Is that when it's unopposed
Escape Routes
And when is embolden
It it gets
The foothold
And when that happened
Everyone gets hurt
Why people get hurt
Black people get hurt
Days get hard
Spectrum guitar
And the historically
Yeah I should say robot
This thing about that
That is
Really really important
In terms of like that
Don't feed the
Controls Naruto
Is
It is
Tiny part of America
Out-and-out White
But because they have gained such a foothold
The Republican
Block them
But because they're associated with that
Are playing the teams
Like my parents are not
Really
Because they don't even understand
But they're on the team their de facto so they're like
Well yeah of course we support all these white supremacist because we're not on your team
Your team has to be wrong
So I mean yeah. Now we're ourselves into
Supporting this thing
And we can't get away from exactly
Jumped a foothold and the foothold was all it took
NAU
Situation that's why the anti-protest like the protesting
Rap groups
Arson
Are crucial because they are the people who are there were saying
No this isn't okay
Those people need to be
Rebuke
Did every turn
And overtake our entire country dialogue with
That allows us to communicate and
Sherp
Who hotep Jesus is
Twitter
Buzz Market
Scam
Kind of guy who sells a book about that stuff
Which is
It tells you how you can use
Influencers for your advantage
Being like hey wouldn't be great if we yelled together is exactly him doing that
Oh yeah in a way that's probably spelled out in his book
And use it as a selling point for his book
Hustle
Pitching list
Black nationalism and white nationalism
Should merge and then we can all live separately hating each other
Which I find very unkind
Pleasanton
That's a unattractive future
I did I am going to go with
He's being disingenuous
Stupid
Is the
If you look at what they provide for women.
The only thing they provide for women are prenatal vitamins
The rent is abortion
They should just call it the abortion clinic
They're not planning any Parenthood
That's what they do with the baby
Body parts
Black babies and black people do I'm short back
I don't know how I don't know how you can make money
I don't know what the black community would like to make all black baby is I don't understand
I don't know
Six fingers like what are you hoping to make off of your life baby
About the idea that there are like theirs
Research that
She's done using
Endometriosis
Prenatal vitamin
To be really work with
Thankfully
Hotep Jesus
Drop this
Real quick before we go
Check this out right
This is according to Planned Parenthood
They have seven 17400 19
Versus
33.5 million STD test and 323
Thousand abortions right
Prenatal care services
5% of their services
Only 5% of your services
YouTube Planned Parenthood
And black people are backing
This isn't a story about this is called
Planned Parenthood wants to kill black people in hotep nation.com
What do you think
Broad question
Interesting
I suppose I suppose it is the
Do you like
Feather in the cap
White races
Trying to be racist
While supporting races
Like
Did you know the Planned Parenthood
Yeah
Like
Care
Your career calling
Giving
Black women Healthcare
Charter
In some way
The people are forced into it
Ludacris and that's brilliant
Dumb thing to say because that it's wages the
Am I racist I think I am
That white racist have
What's a cat
Package of believe that you already have because you're mad and hey
Which is now your repackage
Also I'm Pro black
What is the god saying that
That's what it is
It's all over again. Like
That like you don't understand
It makes them happier
If there's already isn't God's will
Don't don't fall into this trap of like
Oh yeah
It's racist
And it's all couched in this language of like you're being neither of those well that's an interesting approach
Because the truth of this
Hotep Jesus
They publicized
Statistics
Specifically to attack Library.
Well it's true that our report came out covering the time 2014-2015
The reported from 8
Planned Parenthood location
That were surveyed
17419 in
Prenatal Services were reported
However
It does take into account of that
Not all the locations
This country are equipped to provide prenatal care
That is not really the primary function
Planned Parenthood offers
And it is never claimed
To be thought what they offer
Is only thing is available at certain Planned Parenthood locations
But have these
Pacific doctors and the resources
In order to afford prenatal care
Further these statistics are classic case of
Assuming that the 7419 number does cover all the prenatal care the plant paradox
The report was only covering a
Some of the
Location
It was like
8 out of the 56
Survey survey
I said they're probably more than that in the
The country but it wasn't
Caught up in there yeah yeah
A height of approximately
324,000 abortions
Reported in that timeframe
Which
To assert the prenatal care Zone
Only 5%
Are the services offered by Planned Parenthood
What you trying to do is get the listener to assume that abortion must
Be most of what they are
Is not true
He even admits when he's talking about that the report was like the Planned Parenthood offer.
3.5 million
To point out
Different
680 2000 cancer
It almost
3 million individual cases
Contraception
These people
Like Alex Jones
Like hotep Jesus
Who make these attacks on Planned Parenthood f****** know this
They know damn well what abortion
What plant what plant
I did not because they say
Sincerely want to get rid of abortion because Planned Parenthood offers
Essential resource
Whereby control their bodies
Investor-owned life
They use images of fetuses
Sentara stories about Kermit Gosnell
Purposeful
Purely to further their real goal which is
Depriving women of Asian
So all this information that hotep Jesus
Does using
From a group called live
Abortion group started by
Ginger old lilah-rose
Who got her start posing as a prank
Teenager
Posing
She pretended to be pregnant she was just half of it was true
She was pregnant
I bet she would be on the other side
I bet you wouldn't be going on with Jim's Okies both it
Fascinating
Yes probably
Keith made a couple of videos and then she met a guy named David
We talked about before
Completely tricks
Fake nails
Director of r
That's not good
The work of these involved parties occasion
The finished product
Is always
Complete
Presentation of the raw food
As
Many people also
Beyond courts even like some of this is just people who
All the Raw
Footage
Yeah they're like this is
We not the case you're misrepresenting everything
Yeah that's the case with with lights
With that James O'Keefe
Project Veritas
Education
Center for Medical progress
It's all the same
So misrepresented even if he wasn't getting
Information very clearly from
Anti-abortion
Outlet
He's still misrepresenting it
In terms of like
The main thing that Planned Parenthood is about
Is preventive care
They're not that they offer prenatal services in some places where they can
But that's
Not their main
Like doctor
That's for OBGYNs where they practice
It's about preventative
Care and when you look at the
Almost
3 million cases
Is of contrast
Septic services
Is the offer
When you look at it
Via reproductive aspect of its 6
T2000
They're crucial for
For cervical cancer
Like the idea that you would
He wants to talk about all this.
What percent is the abortions when you have three hundred thousand or so abortion
And it's three million contracept
Give services
3.5 million St
680,000
You don't want to talk about that
Because that's not what you care about
It's not what they care about
Care about disenfranchising women
And I know why
It's because this mess
Straight white men
Straight black men
Are under attack we have become
Call Public Enemy Number One in the eyes of bee
Protect people from the globalist
Block out the paint
ASAP
And they're using to do this
Okay
AR
They're using
Nobody's at
Evercade
Super Bowl of acknowledging that women
Condescending just like
Like it you could
I mean here we are obvious
Is like
Well we don't want heaven we don't want women to have it
You say that
And that's exactly what their base wants to hear
AA meeting would be interesting
Cassie like what kind of
Sport it would get into wooden pole grape
Well I was
Whatever it is B
Regrettably
You have just made me realize that
Probably if you pulled
A bunch of really painful thing like
They would have 50% whatever whatever Jones got in his election what was it
Is it like 57% of white women that's exactly how many women not being allowed to choose
Who's on the good side
Okay you talkin about that
My bad
Terra Vista
I don't really f***** up
See that I don't have anybody pulling
Stop like the idea of like
We should all live separately otherwise
Seems like
Pools
Yeah because I imagine the numbers
Pizza Hut
Blue
We wouldn't want to look at it
Yeah can we
Like let's not pull dog whistle questions
Let's just pull the questions like why are we why are they
Okay fine but they still killer
I think he's dog whistle
He's a little on Alex's show cuz he knows he's
There's more people listening
Is actual steps
I think he's very clear
I hate
They're behind everything
Merge
So I don't think he's dog whistling at all
Except again
Being good
Alex
Existence
Just just stop it
And everybody's proven that there
Gohan
What is Atlantis real
Because I guarantee that
Yeah just like it just like I'm saying
50 / 7% of white women are like I'm against white women being able to choose
We should be in the home barefoot and pregnant
I mean what else do you say
Because you can't
You can't possibly believe that women should have the right to choose anything
If you're voting for the people you're voting
It just seemed
Consider Lakers
The willful
You know like
You take it all away from it a little bit
Hot-button
Right
Sprite
It's a f******
Something
There's just no communicate
Do you can't do it
You can't f****** do it
Let's bail
What's
You and I you and I are officially seceding from the Union
Knowledge fight
Mileage
Independent republics
Apartment
How do I register
No idea
Too late
I don't want to call
I want to know what he don't want to talk
I just don't want to talk
If we're going to do this we have to plan in advance I have to call him and hate that up a bully here
Just call him out of the blue
We set up a time we did the whole thing
Look Dan
You don't know how
I have that first I have to call all the Jews
Together
They have to get into a meeting room
Netanyahu's wife is there the corrupt mod
So we have to do that whole thing then
So
This episode has been mostly Alex doing
Is Edge play about the
Supreme Court
Microwave
And we've ended up with the orgasm that is
Tano
Certainly hope that is not what
I think it'll probably be floated but
Really hope everyone smart enough
To be like
La shutdown
Not anymore that sucks
GameStop not anymore
I don't know everybody the coward underneath
Nancy Pelosi
I mean
I say the world
Can't get darker but
Dan the world gets dark
And that Dawn
Surprisingly climate
So the world will get very dark and then we will all be burned alive
By the Light
You brought up earlier the Central Park five
Because
Alehouse combat positive
To hotep G
Boy this is
Wings Over
And that and that and that
Everybody does know Trump knows that's not true
He knows it's not true
For the most part
Oh boy black
I'd like to
Call the black community that they were not allowed to live in his building
I'd like to pull the black community that certainly
Who are aware of the situation
The first time the Trump ever was in the newspaper was
Because the government
Because Nixon's Department of Justice was like
Well your
Belmont housing
Nixon
Godfathers of red line she's gone too far
But his whole career
Over the years
Over and over again
Eugenics over about his dad being Superior in
Stuff like that like the idea
30 years ago black everybody just night
Apartments Hayward Haven
Hey
You know what it is that it's that mentality that Alex
Like it does complicate
This is another point where I think
We're going to have to just suck it up
And swallow a brutal pill
That is this hypocritical
Because this still follows Alex Jones is belief in
Free association
So like I think
He would say
It's not racist that Trump doesn't want black people living in his building
The right of free association
If you're okay with them
Snowbigdeal devil doesn't exist
Cool Ellijay was terrible
He did Kill
And then I believe that
Attempt to talk about modern-day Alex Jones I feel like
None of us enjoy this all that much
Mythology
I will send
I love it when he brings
Sink your teeth into
Not not just with research but with like
Yearslong indep
Breakdown
He talks about Diageo
He talks about how he was going around asking
Looking for one
Which is the myth
About the origin
It's so much fun whenever people pull that out because I know
Translate
Vet
Absolutely not
Weirdo
Complete weirdo
Masturbated the marketplace
And like screaming people he was in
Cannibalism you didn't believe in private property rights
Right
Say f*** it out there weird
And when he did the line that everyone missed
Lea I'm going around looking for one honest man
Would it really
Translate
Something that I would describe as what a crazy person
He's walking around at night
With a lantern
Looking for a
That's it
The word for honest and just
Is diakos
It is not
In that sense it is just entrepot which is
I'm looking for a man
Which is what you would pay like if you're caught out somewhere where you're not supposed to be what are you doing
Angry man
I am looking for a man
I just love all the time
Like father
Thrift
F*** all this plan
I don't care like I don't
There's nothing for me to bunk
To talk about inter
Napolitano
Supreme Court judge
Other than Mustang
Yeah because I don't know I don't know what steps or says he's going for obvious he's just talking to Rodger Stone
Conversations with Rodger Stone
Useless
All I can do that it's like him saying that Arpaio is up
Supreme Court judge
Right there's no
There's no
We don't have a bottom
Know you of the past
Can we go over the Paw
The value of it is
That we get
To have
Distance
We get to have time
From his married
So we can
How things have
Play doubt
Is this
Was he completely full of s***
We can find the things
He was referencing
We can see how it all worked out we can
There is that like
Respective week
You can take on it where is modern day stuff
Like
We run into an issue where he's lying all the time
We know it's what he does
No
What are you saying all this stuff that we can
Prove or disprove
Prove
It's this mid-ground on
Where was like alright he's
It is
Sharon the contrast
Like every like if you are if you are preemptively
Or perhaps even defensively saying that
We are doing a disservice by covering
The present because we're not
I'm not at no you're not no you're not you're not saying that
I mean just more like
This is why we're not covering
The present
Ivy like it is still important for us as a show to go back into the past
Which provides context for the Press
And then we can come back to the present what once a week
Never end
See what the difference is because you can just
Hear it if you listen to this episode versus our last 2009 episode
You will instantly know
There's a huge difference
And yet
And here is where and that only gives you more ammunition
There's some there's there is value to it
Should never do it
It is just a
It's a situation where
I'm a human being
It's not like
Pains me to listen to
Yeah I think that a lot of people on the the Facebook group
Have the impression in their head that it's
I get
Like
All up in like I can't handle
It bothers me to listen to modern-day Alex
And it doesn't
You know like I eat that's it I just feel like I listen to an episode like this
And I have
This this takes
3 hours to listen
Edit
Makes even more time
The only value
Really
Is like
We met hotep Jesus
Alex misrepresent
Mythology
Like beyond all the other stuff is just
Yelling into the void nonsense
It's just
Sound and Fury signifying nothing
No totally
Why can't we yell into the void with the guy was yelling at the boys like f****** Goku
Here's why
Because it's repetitive
About over and over
Still trying to do a show
And what it's like
He says
Like
The globalists are
Central Banking cartel's blah blah blah
We could we've already talked about this
Yeah we can we can
Do it again
If you want I want novel
I want to learn and I want more like
Content for the show right
Joy as much
I don't mind what
Covering it from X
The time
But like
Hours of my day
F****** waste
When I look into
Like the other episodes that I listen to the cover
That's a that's a three-hour waste of my time I totally get it
I I can I'm not mad about that
Embarrassing that's with Alyssa
I'm not
Is long enough that I know
Feel the same way about
The right-wing
Outrage
Like anytime I read the news where it's like
Fox News said I'm out I don't give a s***
If they're boring
They're boring to me because they're just going to say if you if you
If you were like what's your Fox news headline I'll be like
Is evil because blank
And liberals backlight
I understand that, exactly
Here's a further
You really taken
Federation
Alex Jones
In his world
What is marketing
Izzy has to be under
Really great way of putting it
He has to be understood
There always has to be a threat
Can't sell his ship
In the same way that like
Disaster supplies
And stuff like that
If the end actually sell a Year's worth of food though
Yes he does
Billy Salyers where the food
You asked for it on the show anymore
Not the same shape
Jim Bakker remix
I Choose You Baker
This is Jim Bakker episode
Special
The Khan of
Disaster prepared
Only works
Until the disaster
Like once it happens you no longer have a cash
So
V8 your disaster is shared the same way everybody else
Like if you sell
Survival radios and
Jim Baker's big old
Potato buckets and stuff like that
If she goes down
Your supply chain is bus
Everything is destroyed
Make money
The gig is up and now you are left
Billion
Survival food rations you have at your Pleasant Valley
Okay so the game
You know these are fuc
Acting awful reality or truth
Vino not in their best in
For disaster
To actually happen
It's only in their best interest
People scared
Is about to happen right
Is that the game that I was just playing
He's marketing paradigm
Which I'm going to replace
Perfect for real that is the perfect phrase to replace world
Great Wave
What
Because he shifted his entire operation
Trump is the king of the auntie globalist
Isis
He said he was a globalist
Model
To do now
Is a mating
But he has to do is
A where you can
But eight
Maintenance
He plays this like gift get afraid of Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Get get scared of that because
Casinos
Like on one level he knows
The Democratic Socialist
Membership
Like that
Torino's B like
You know what a little bit down the road if there's more
Democratic
Yeah so he knows like let's get a little B
Scared about Facebook
Find get her killed
Then that's going to
-2 our address
When I watch I've watched
3 shows from this week
Like trying to make this up
Episode away from it with
Is that he isn't
Pathetic holding
He's just
Worse
Then I've seen in here
From him there is just a like
In the past you said he doesn't know how to
And that's
That's probably
In the fact that he's on
In terms of
Control
You don't know how
He's
It's real
I'm having a very difficult time expressing this because
What it comes down to is
You have a conspiracy
Propaganda
Who's now
His job is
Keep the base
Riled but maintain the status quo
And it's
Boring it's boring apathetic
When I watch it I don't know I don't
Do you know what
Do you know it's fast
Look
If he wanted to live his
Principles
As we pretend we have over and over again
He should be saying
Kill Alexandria
Ocasio-cortez
The cheese the biggest threat to democracy
It's a bunch of
Take her out she's a globalist communist who is trying to come after your guns
Globalists aren't necessarily
Even
Socialist
Communist Folk
You know what you
Like
I don't know
Everything
Everything about the modern-day
Apathetic
It's so pathetic
It's not like I want him to advocate for people
You should
He should be up
Calling for blood
I agree and he's not because he knows
That's not how I make money
As we see all this in
Michelle like
Kim Jeong Hoon
Making more nuclear tests
Rodger stone that the walls are closing
Things are happening at 8
Information just
Seeping out
Pictures
Becoming clear
Unclear of what really happened
Not just in between
16 election
But four years before that
Yeah
I was kind of nose and it
This is a conversation that you don't want to have and you really don't want me to start
Maybe so let's find out
Yes
Calling for blood
What realistically
Put it put it all together
All right we have any free have an illegitimate government that was assisted by
IV by a foreign power not least of which
Was put in by a minoriti
Of the country that was
It legitimately stolen by how much
F****** b******* out all of this
Gerrymandering all of this should never have been there because
It was a f****** destroyed
Exactly
It's important to remember that the American Revolution happened because people had
To pay like $0.02 more
Intex
Like that
No
It's literally all the time
Like I'd like legitimately protest
F****** incredible
Millions of people
Walk
Throughout this entire country
Supporting
Immigrants rights
But we saw the same thing at the women's March
We saw the same thing at however f****** many March we thought we saw
Maybe world record
Flash forward to the present we are most likely
Supreme Court Justice
Access to abortion
Like in the computer American history from
Perspective
Cuz that's illegal
That's technically True Blood
I mean there is that
But it's probably
We're on the wrong side of the law
If we advocate
Violence again
Anybody before were already on the wrong side of the law just for
News about Trump
Probably
Here's the only
I know I'm a f****** middle guy
The old
When the guy to the left of you is saying
Murder people
The middle
I have this
Hesitant about what you're saying is that
Like I know that there's a lot of people who listen to
To our show
I don't think anyone would hurt anybody but
I do want I worry
About
The rhetoric
But you're
Presenting
Only because
I don't
Think that
Target's would be
That makes sense
I don't think that innocent people should be hurt and that is what would end up happening
If any organization not just
Ralix
If Alex did it end up in the situation where very innocent people
Are collateral damage of some b******* which is
Probably right
For the situation that we have on our hands
Now it's believes there should be Blood on the streets cuz the globalist
719 13th
But jacket
The wrong people get hurt in both
Equation
I don't like that that's why I'm in the middle in terms of this stuff
In my defense
I know I know I know
We're both so polite at
I have never
Advocated for wholesale
And in fact
Consistently
The difference
Between a nation and a
Government
I don't believe so I don't think that
I don't think
That there should be blood in the streets
In that f******
Whatever because I'll be goddamn
Scott Pruitt find a tall oak tree
Yes
The Koch brothers
Should have their homes burn down
They would not be allowed to go outside while at the same time their house would have burned down
With them inside of it
That is the reality of the situation
And the fact that every day
We get f****** people murdering journalist
Stinks
Which is that one side has been
Fighting a war against us
For the past
20 of
Whatever America
All of America
And we have never ever fought back
Against the Real Enemy
We're not in versus the Warriors
Patrician the two sides
And we can't play different games
It's time for the long arm of the law
But few of them down
Cymbalta maker
He'll settle down
Not ever.
Here's a general
Genuinely what I would prefer to
I would prefer an Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Become an attorney general
F****** New York State
Do you think that the Koch brothers haven't committed f****** crime
In New York City
How long did it take
Don't
Don't you dare do it
I'm going to give you plus one
And then I'm going to take it away
But I didn't
How long did it take you
How long does it take us
To find out that Alex was committing a
Like a concrete crime it's probably likes
It took some investigation
Investigate
Figure it out in the first month
If you've been anointed I didn't I wasn't that wasn't what I was trying
If you if you really I'm in I'm not going to lie
If you really wanted to take Soros down f****** start investigating because if you're really
Billionaire
There's a crime
East valinda satisfying
All the crimes that
Alex and his ilk commenters on our website about it
Allege
Are real
Like I'm sure there are things that he's done
He's accused
I don't give a s***
F****** p****
I'm not I'm not here to defend him
Exactly Hillary to
If you find a Chrysler
These people should be in jail
This is a team effort
By the rich
Overall our thing
This has gone way off the rail
I think
We should do
However
Chicken alfredo
Here's what we can't do ever
Another song
And that's what we need
I'd like to bring up so long because I think he's the best ruler of all time
I can't happen
I know I know that it
But
It is the thing that we need
Never
Going to
It's weird that the way that you present yourself
Your hypothetical
Very similar
In the terms of
He was like I'm going to make these rules and then I'm leaving
I'm out so you have that paralleled at
Another ask Azek
Syria
The shaking off of bird
We need
Forgiving of
Dirty deck
We needed that.
That that sort of thing needs to happen because back in the days of ain't
Engine grease it was
People who sold them
Resolves into slavery
And now we have modern equivalent
Absolutely modern Google
Parking short-term
Car loans
Like what else is that underwater because of ground
There's
But the reason they have someone is because Trump
Is
He sold himself as so on exactly in the same way that we
Can't be like
They're coming for your guns and buy and all that should because the hard-right has taken that
In the same way Trump
Pretended to be that Solon he pretended to be that
I am the guy who is going to
Fix every
Because that's
Really what you want
Because you know
Ultimately
No I was like I don't want to do this was selling himself
Which is better at
History WhatsApp have
The Kraken
In Iceland in Atherton
Yep
With Liam Neeson
I don't know I don't know I don't know how to put a button on
But
I think
Where we spawn off way too far was the idea that you want blood on the
Don't want it's not
Very least I'm going to go through it I feel like Pruitt should be murdered in front of everybody
The most corrupt person I think
Incredible
Is really killing it on the guy I almost admire him movie come back to now
We're talking about is
Entire thing is
2 years
The normalization of corruption
Status quo
Yeah I think we'll get away with stuff
Is more OK Google get away with Stephanie
And it just keeps going
Just keep going and that's what I think that's the
We're going to
No unfortunately
This is the part that sucks
Because
If you had a situation where you had just a
F******
Business
Like a trump who was just like
I want to
Corruptus f****** make
Ton of money
Kleptocracy where
You have like a family businesses
Expensive
All of the contract making billions of dollars and sense
To be in
The problem is the merging of that with people like the Stephen Miller
The world of that like
Corruption is cool
Mentality
With
Overt
White nationalism White
Separatism
Bright
Voodoo sorcerer
And you know what f*** I do
Give a s***
Let's just lay it
Everyone was afraid of Barack Obama being a black
Good evening
They were right
It wouldn't have mattered in the same way that it would matter
The Trump is a white
Agree
Because
Barack Obama even if
President
Tough row to hoe
You know like huge
A really hard time
In terms of getting that blacks
Supremacy up the hill
Pushing a boulder up the hill and the reason that it's so scary
To have whites
Merged with
Power is
Because it's
So
Already
Search already the State of Affairs
Lakewood University
White supremacy merge with
You know what it is
Everybody knows what it is
And we just are afraid to say it because
We feel like we
All of us
Not all of us I mean obviously there is there's you and me in the pot
So many other brilliant people the people who
Marching
But
The status quo is terrified
Acknowledge
Because if you acknowledge
If your Nancy Pelosi
And you go out and you say
We are seeing white supremacy merge with power
We've seen this before
Then all the sudden everything that she is ever believed it behooves you to
Act in a much more severe way than
Then you're willing to act exactly
People are weird
With not just power but monetary power
And that monetary power also supports
Central
Terrible
Surveillance
Over the years
And terrible and that's why
Rodger Stone
Alex
Made fun of your beard.
I think it's really what I wanted and on
Now that's a button
Look I've been I've never
Over the course of time who done this show I've never
That's not fair
I want
Set a private match
Bray Wyatt
Yeah
Yeah I haven't really
Like made any contact
Try to f***
Quatama doll
But I've been really resisting like just meeting at him
Your beard sucks
Just cuz it sucks
Really
I've never been more triggered like
Base level
I know that I hate his rhetoric
I hate what he stands for
When I see that beard
That's what really gets me
I've never wanted
Punch him more
Because I know the beard exist
I get to go look
It's such a bad beard
Google
Andis beard
Call Sophie
Dollartree.com
Do you know where else you can find your beautiful baby picture on Twitter
Acknowledge
We're also on Facebook
Indeed
Also on iTunes
Please rate reviews describe all that good stuff short helps
It helps people find us
Yeah will there be cool if more people
I just want to go on
Want to be invited on Fox News
As the liberal angry guy
I want to be that guy
Your turn
I always
Because I never ending Cavalcade of people that I want to tell the
I feel like it really is more like relevant
To you then
Sometimes I feel like a real
Someone gets in my craw
But generally speaking I feel like telling people to f***
Themselves
You just can't tap into that primordial anger
I can feel it
More sincere when you do
I see within you
The Super Saiyan
Yourself
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color