Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
You were somebody who had let's say lost
Faith Betty's country
Entry would ever possibly work
Is a functioning democracy
See you again
And would stay
Instead
Descend into a corrupt kleptocracy
Till the end of time
To celebrate the holiday
That most
Exemplifies the worthlessness
Brave
What podcast would you recommend you want to listen to something
Rome burn
Check out knowledge
We haven't we bring to you
Happy Fourth of July 5th when this comes out
The fourth is generally we have an episode on
Most people probably aren't in the office
Second Civil War
I heard about that
I don't know someone died I guess
Clowning on Alex
Twitter and doing
I'm second Civil War letters
Oh I like that
It's fine but sausages
Buzz Marketing for Alex
People don't realize
Like I really want to be clear about cuz I got a couple questions
People who were like
Hey you guys that you know
You guys think about that
I want to spend much time on this second Civil War nonsense
We've already seen him do this over and over again
That last time I had that big March
Another women's March the other one
I can't remember what it was
I think it was the March for our lives
Right after the Parkland shooting
Alex's rhetoric was that that was when Democrats were going to launch their Civil War
Moved
To take out Trump
They're going to kill him
Perhaps
Like all this stuff
Recycling
Stuff over and over again
People getting excited about it it's like
You just
You're getting into the rerun
Already a little bit
Celebrating
Some freedoms
And maybe personal freedom but also the other thing is that like
I get why it's really fun
Clown on Alex
We do it a lot
In
In various ways and I understand that I'm probably make
Looking to find a line that most
Really appreciate her under
When it becomes
The number one
Trending hashtag
Go the second Civil War hashtag
To making fun of Alex people don't recognize
A lot of the time is that like you don't give a s*** if people are making fun of him
It doesn't matter
Because most of the people making fun of him
Are people who would ever
Consider him
To begin with
They don't he doesn't care about that
Already
So they might as well be May
Is Bucking name out there
And gives a better chance
The 20%
Why is everyone making fun of them
He says
Whatever people on Twitter
Whatever it is it
Exactly
And then the flip side of it to is that like
The idea that somehow he's going to be humiliated when they
This doesn't happen
Never was
But beware
It doesn't matter
Because he has built-in narrative
And place it doesn't
When it doesn't happen to be like yeah because I
They're playing
I stopped
The second Civil War by publicizing it
You can play that card if you want
What's 2
Is not over there could be
Terrible firework
That way
Oceans 8
That 20
Percent that he's not as
Engaging
In this stuff is really only giving
Free marketing
Happy 4th
Distracting those who would start
They were too busy clowning I'm busy
Yeah right
Never going to have
I hate it and I understand
The impulse and I appreciate it.
I live in this weird
Space where it's
I know the best thing to do with
Betake norham accepted
Very specific
Pick contacts
Ways that are good to
Take care of him and
And deal with him
Everyone live your lives
You just did it you just talked
Pictures of out of your own position it's the same position are they go ahead and do it but just recognize the
You're not scoring a point on him
You're just
You're sort of playing into his hands a little bit
This is the only PR strategy
Because no one will take
Good morning
Advertising
Same people who work
Defending the daily
Stormer is his
Neo-Nazi
Lawyers
His lawyers
Well lawyers who were also like
It also to me is like another thing people are clowning on that
That doesn't mean the lawyers are neo-nazis
Some deal nephews are protected by
I get the urge
To be like haha this is
The link to him
I got a lot of
I'm telling you
One thing that we never
Affected when we wrote all those laws was the necessity of adding a
Except for not
First Amendment
We just got to rewrite all that
We added
Bad breath
Even consider Nazis of protector
Class
You wouldn't think so
Before interior
But we'll never get there
Because government
But like I said
It's time to celebrate our freedom
And so I decided I don't want to talk about Alex
Here's what we're talkin about
Hi everyone I'm sure Cassidy from Project Camelot and very happy to be here today
We're going to be talking to Eddie page and this is my second interview with him
Should be a lot of fun he's also been putting out some videos of his own
In his own words his life story and he does that on his YouTube channel
He does do anybody page
I'm going to go with the
Bastard
Jimmy Page and Eddie Vedder
No Eddie Money
Incorrect
Coleman Jr
No absolutes
Story is dealt with in another interview that you did with Terry
Within a week or so
I will
As a beginning
Syllabus
Animal get into
Two more as we go along
He's a guy
Who claims to be a pleiadian
Alien being
Who is doing the interview with Harry
I got to say most of his backstory
Not super important
This isn't we do it
Flashback format
We can just do small chunks of it we don't have to
To deal with the entire back
Do as we go along
Detail as you need
What's important
This is one of the weirdest Project Camelot interviews I've ever heard my life it goes so far off the rails
Go off the rails like the one with Courtney Brown
Where you talk about his remote
I'm talking over this
You disrespected Mark Richards even though
The Camelot
Also the one with the guy who was like under that museum there's a demon
Bright right
Her loyalty
Really weird
Amazing liar
But this goes
Even further off the rails
Disrespecting Mark Mark Richard
It just has to do with Eddie page
Being
A chief weirdo
Aza
And then he was his name Junior because of that or was his play again
And then I don't know
The page part of it I don't know
I don't know the etymology of his name but I do know that his
Something some sort of like
Angelic being
Human neck
Let's say
Like Michael
Yes it's okay
Toronto
Something like alright
So you may not know this
But it's
Until he was much older in
Oh yeah
This is that is just a little bit about his dad
As a young child I remember meeting
My father
I've never met this man until I was four years old but
Looking in his eyes and knowing
And magnetism that I knew
This is very special
It is
He I like her
Have you couches this
The beginning
I think a lot of people be able to identify like this I was for
He was a special
When I looked into his eyes
So in terms of identifying
Both
Large junk
The population away
Yeah I think I mean I know that a lot there's a lot of
Single parents out there and s*** like that I understand
You don't know your dad is beginning of your life
But that's.
That's not everybody
Usher
Find out
Age of 30
This man that I admit 1957
Was my father
It was our father I just like saying I don't want to seem greedy but
Very proud to find out
This man
Okay now
You found out when you're 30 aren't you mean you went through 30 years without knowing that you're pleiadian
Well
So
This introduces the first problem
You know we we
Who painted
Kerry Cassidy
Perhaps the worst
Interviewer of all time
The most credulous at the very
Stripes
At this point like in this interview haha
To the fire about
That I think are pretty impressive
Being a good interviewer but I realized
Usually far more nefarious
I'll explain as we get to it there's a remarkable thing happening here
Dominance
It's going to be fascinating the way this plays out
Scary cats
Ifucking Alpha
She could tell that this dude is
The chop
Play do we find out here that Kerry Cassidy
Is
It went what we end up finding out I'm probably showing way too many cards way too early
She might be
With
Trucking
Guy in prison
She's she's now screwing with my crutches she might be Puppet Master and Margarita
Alright
Usual Suspects that I have always wanted
But we'll see what you think as we as we go along
All the sudden her voice
Get lower by.
I've known
Do the s*** all along you assholes
F*** you
Also I think that's the backstory of Star-Lord from Guardians of the Galaxy
Metastatic forwarded know until the 30th at 7 a.m.
Pretty sure that was the one
Didn't know that he was different
Here's how you would describe it
You remember
I knew there was something very unique going on here
Where did you go did you see
And what did they say to you first I didn't say I saw anybody
So where you get to speculation what did they say to me
I would say all fairly standard
You might ask a kid that was missing for a little while
Like a kid that wandered off down the street is like where were you
Baby panda
Current behavior but
I don't know Alexa
See if there's more to this
The man in the dark
They were searching for answers and
Even today
I wouldn't I don't want to say anything all the answers but
Weis Markets
Are you
And compared them to the my other 32
Special
Kiara is the third of that 30
3 pleiadian children that were alone
To Earth or whatever
I guess I don't know through the government's fully aware of it the Vatican
Nose
Getting play in a little bit
Children born on to Earth
The Coleman family is taken care of them
Right there you says when I came into the age
That is
Here's his story
Broad stroke
Works for the CIA
When he was 18
He went off to the military
Vietnam
Quite a fighter pilot
In helicopters in Vietnam
Course
Laser helicopter got shot down
And then he lost 11 days
So
411 days
He was on an alien
Right so they took him
I thought you lost
Does he not remember them
I'm sorry I'm sorry
Will be answered in
He pops back up on a field
Uniform that he was wearing
To begin with which is important because as
Describe the key
Vietnam in a special issue black
Infrared uniform with a special Elite
Secret Service
This group They Carried high-tech equipment
Special
Issue Colt 45 pistol machine gun
To assassinate the Vietnamese
I don't think
Even back then
He did not succeed
The only reason I bring that up
Specifically is because he had to explain why when he was found
I have his black Nani
Infrared
I suppose I'm guessing that's why it's a piece of a narrative
Even a different uniform when they find him
But it wasn't 11 days later it was like
Minutes later
You have crashed
Or something along those lines
Well
Okay
These are things that I can confirm or deny
So I'm choosing
Believe it
As much as I think
Stolen Valor is
Super ugly
I also think the idea of me saying no you weren't
I have no idea
Is Ron
Right until someone can
Can show me that you wasn't
I'll go ahead and take his word for it tentatively
But I will not allow that he was
Right
So what are you going to UFO that he told him they put them in like this yellow liquid that he can breathe in which
Super weird everything gets better
Gets back
Which is yours
He ends up getting recruited by the CIA
In his term
Either reality
He got
Simple regression
There was a guy named
And I believe
Charles Hamilton
Do you got a regression by a guy named Giles
Yes
I think you just went to
Regression therapist
In around
Before 1980
85 that was right around when the satanic panic
My uncle was doing a multiple
Went a lot of
Psychologist
We're doing some really
Irresponsible
Regression therapy
Repressed memory therapy where a lot of people ended up with
Completely bogus
Spell memories
But end up causing a whole lot of trouble
It's like going to see a psychic
You don't want to if you go see a regression therapist if there is no there's a 0% chance
Figure someone
You wanted
Do you want to be space
You want to be you are going to be different
And I certainly think
You come up with
Sort of thing where
Like I was
Magically
11 days on a spaceship again so important
Replay ATM baby
Vatican knew about me
There's a whole lot of other stuff that's very
Dubious along the way like you was in a car accident
Brokaw
Kind of bone but
Is magically healed the next
Flabbergasted
I was hoping that he broke bones but no other human being had
No but there is a
He is going to save this part
I think that this
Worth noting
Brings up that he has like
Blood
Dave the doctor say
Be determined is human
In human blood
Okay this comes from this comes from a memory that
He has underrate the regression
He's getting regressed by this Giles
Individual
Except for in relation to him
From his memory
There were 20 people staring
Do the glass enclosure
This is after
He is gone
Vietnam
Magical experience
People staring at me through glass
Enclosure as if they were studying
I can overhear what they're saying
Beside me or three people
The head of the CIA Robert Brooks
Chief assistant George Bush
Vice President Gerald Ford
They're all showing a picture of a flying saucer
I recognize that photo I seen it
Before
The DNA cannot be labeled
The blood type cannot be labeled but does contain some human blood
So
Visit this idea is something that comes from his regression to all of this
Just like
All right you seem like maybe a suggest
Purple guy
So-so
He had the head of the CIA
And George h.w.
Event also Gerald Ford
So-so
One future president
1 current president
Current vice president
Okay
Because
Because they showed him a picture of a flying saucer
Well no because
According to what he believed
He crashed his helicopter and then miraculously
Healed and so they're like whoa what happened here you're in a totally different uniform
A miracle it was 11 days ago
So that's most of his story
We got the broad Strokes
Events and future president head of the CIA they showed him a picture would you know me
Actually remember
The doctor absolutely they were all watching him
So he could be shown a single photo
And he will be like
Oh yeah I know that one
You don't need to feed your friends
Isn't there for a blood
Certainly don't
Email address
Yep
More or less all you really need to know about his experience I'm sure he would tell you that there's a lot more details
And I respect that but we have a lot to get to
I respect that
And that is the Carrie is
Really hung up on this idea
Like weight
No n
Any of this until you
Yeah why is she hung up on that
Okay but
Just to ask you to question a little bit more clearly
Realize
Priest from the agency
Assassination and so on
Used to being interrogated
Zen
You grew up
You're telling me that you and your host family
Did you know you were adopted during that time cuz I thought you did know after certain age and then also
So did you go through school
And did you know that you were that you were not human or did you not find out until the 8th
Age of 30
Relevant
Necessarily
Probably
Although some of it
So he doesn't know
He didn't know until he was 30
Gary has clearly
Lestat you heard her question
I was good at school
I don't know what he talked about now
And I told her I said actually I'm bored
And I explained it to her
3 days later
My people who I called Mom and Dad
Alien
He gave me
I had sound
Sounds
Weather in about 40 minutes I answered all quick all the questions like 300 in there
Hoover Dam
So you was bored this year
And I said no ma'am she says you have not missed one
Well I bypass the ninth grade
Nn
Special ed
I was the only one in there I would take him
Outlook
This is an old man telling a boring story
Telugu
This is what
Because of the generational differences maybe there wasn't one already established
At the school
Maybe they had to make one for him
And that created real feelings of like soup
Superiority and different method
From a very young age and those have been transmuted into
I'm an alien kind of feeling
Put into the special advancing
Through
If any of this is true through classes your social group behind
Current it at this time
Was he also fighting NBA
Little bit later
A little bit late
Graduated 12th grade
You should have been in 9th grade
That would been like what
15 16 years old he's graduating
High School
Two or three years before he
Vietnam
Oh okay
What is bumming around
I don't know
Sound barrier
Just put a button on that
I just wanted to show like
I don't feel like people get a really good sense of how boring a lot of these episodes are
Like we talked about a lot of the fun stuff with the
Crazy
They're also sometimes
Two-minute stories about the gifted program
Where there's just old lonely people who want to talk
Did not realize that I was in a
Didn't know that but now I kind of think
I was in Tripoli the
To program at our school but I
I did not skip any
Well that's not alien
Easy to prove
If I had any
Special skills
Is wondering about Eddie Reddit
Also find out about
Your ears up a little bit when he said that
He predicted the JFK assassination
We're going to learn about the details on that
I did this and then I went
10th grade but I skipped
Super advanced
Not at all of these people have that sort of like
It's the intellectual version
Stolen Valor
Let's just put it this way
Growing up
I was much different than the kids
The Coleman family My adoptive parents
Visions
This man didn't
23rd 1963
Looking good are you
Good morning
No I couldn't
Watching back
I think my skills
We're having to be recharged
Call me the process
That's probably the process that's what he thinks happened when he was in Vietnam I got there
But I would say
Harsh materialist perhaps
Futureworld little bit
Alright
I would say
That the most likely explanation
Here is it as a child imagine
Someone getting their head shot
Apple X maybe you saw it in a movie
JFK was assassinated
10 years old
And he can
Conflated
Precise memory of a tan
TV with the earlier feelings.
You had and decided that
He had predicted it all along
Because
VIP
Vivid picture in his head
Someone getting shot in the head no it was the president
Not a b not a prediction
No that's just a mental image
He's kind of what we call a dream as well would also function is
Probably had.
That thought
Probably thought about it
Visualize and attack
That's fundamental
This is not impressive
Psychic work
Now that's a bet
Call Dad
Off the glass
No but I know when you know you need
Need to get yourself some sort of credibility
In this world and by this world I mean
This world
Right right
Cuz how you going to prove it
How's it going good just proved that he called it when he was 8 or whatever you know
F****** know
I promise you
Weird
It is weird
To hear somebody
Tell a very humble version of the I'm a psycho
I got the I got the
Yeah I had a vague
Wheeling
I had like two out of five is dodging was ahead
It was weird
Seems like
It's kind of boring
A little bit
Because we we have his bag back story that I've had to fill him
He went to a gifted program at this
There's not a lot
He thought about
Someone getting shot in the head for JFK
Alien none of this is Nessa
Sincerely all that good I promise you
Is it going to go places
That are
Unbelievable really what this sounds like right now is like a guy who's just
Instead of being like just turned it into a very low-key like
Also I'm an alien
Like it's not even he's not even bragging really or like telling interesting stories or like
Oreo
Making up of mass
Battle that he is the only solution for he's just kind of like
Alien siblings I was in a gifted program
Some of the self-important Slater out of this this
Spit there walking through
That is
Cleary clearly doesn't believe
Gary really as a problem
With no any of this s*** before you
Pikachu
There's there's a big issue
The Carrie is going to flash out here in a second
Important and that is that
He went on this
Alien craft for 11 days
When he was 19
Then he found out about all this when he was 30
There's 10 years in between there
What the f***
It's not want to answer that question
Cascade around for awhile.
Through the next few clips
Perch fry
Desperately to be like
I don't really believe you week
Got to get through this somehow
Weird
Okay now
You
Usually like to talk about how old I am but
I could say that I'm not that far
Different from UA
So real quick earlier in the episode
He admitted
Got it
Anyway when I was a kid I was very aware of
Other dimension
Communication with other beings
Premonition that I was aware of
Actually I was being abducted at that time. Kind of memories as well and
And in my sort of ability and interest in in sort of
My Savior called the psychic realm Etc just expanded
And so that it was very very active when I was in my team
And in my twenties
And so on so
What I'm wondering is
You when I forget how old you were when you enlisted and then you have that
Experience in which you you know we've described that
Fire video for those of you that
Story in your tuning in now
You had 11 missing days
Are you your whole body was put back together you met your father excetera but when you came after they wifey
Your mind see you then
Remember that
And it is strange you know
In other words I guess when I'm kind of getting at here is
Guess you sound Advanced but you don't actually sound spiritually like you were very hit
Up until age of 30 is that cuz you grew up in a fairly conservative restrictive
Area I grew up in California which is very open to all kinds of things and
I was raised absolutely
Mount Shasta
And you
You
You pathetic
Corn eating what are you ready to go go f****** go back
Cornfield
Field of Dreams
Your dreams are boring what is that goes the hell out of here there's a there's a touch of that
Hold on
Your other societies that are as well like Great Britain excetera
You know
Weirdest Dimensions other beings you know of all kinds UFOs
I don't remember when close encounters
Came out what year but you know that was coming we're just normal after that
And as a family we even saw UFO so
What I'm wondering is
Where was you know when they did these actually do you think
Dumb Jew down on purpose
So that you
You know on certain areas
Can you explain that
Focus
I would I would say that's not a fair question
That's no fair question to ask anybody did they dump you
That seems like unfair
Cuz she's given him an out for why she doesn't believe this right
Well I can look down on you
Your story is
But
If you give me this now I've got a foothold now we can start blaming her parents for elevation
Dump him down on purpose
When they wiped
Or something
Or maybe the government did it who knows
But I would say like just human-to-human or human to half
That's never that's never an okay question
Because like if I if you ask me
Bets you always look bad no matter what your answer is
I think you say
Regardless of which direction you feel you
Do you say yes
You put yourself on a lower you know
Give your give yourself some humility
That's a relatable quality people like you more
Mary's going to be like
You know what
Don't like how dumb you are but I like
Picture in August
Maybe from the dump down person that's a good angle but like from an interviewer
Very least
Route
So at this point Carrie realizes
What I just brought up
Missing decade
And she's got to try him
Clamp onto it like a
Like a bulldog just
She will not let this go
And you just been in Vietnam you've been shot down
Almost died in a helicopter crash in a whole battle went off you you
Amazed Everyone by shooting all these people but you had no memory whatsoever at that point right when you were with
In other words into
Langley
You still did not have your memories in my crap
Will my memories had been less a I still have a memory but it has been suppressed
You got to understand
Vietnam habits 1973
Boneheads
Greg Watson
Highways night
In 1973
They recruited me from
Uni Japan
Let me get this straight cuz I'm I've read your book I'm almost completely done with it I have like a few pages
Fascinating
Serrano's
You had it we had a
All he'll answer is I turn night
Vietnam and then in 1982 I got recruited
Explain a little bit that he was still like
Working in the
Paperwork
Service
Or something like that
His his his explanation
For like how the
The timeline works
With all this stuff
Really doesn't it doesn't make any sense
Doesn't really flush it out
Delete scary to have
Keep bringing it up
Especially for a guy
Has absolutely no problem telling a long
Year-by-year High School Story
However many three
3 years from Vietnam to Langley
What was he doing at Langley
How long was it
Only four days in Langley the FBI didn't he say he was in CIA
Oh okay
I don't know
You mean you never got your memory back about the
The Experience on the left of those 11 days
Even then what did you just do go back to work
I'm at now
What did you do what did you do in the Marine Corps after that
Don't tell me it's classified
He needs
Just f****** around with her
If that's where he goes on to say like
As flying helicopters Ranch
Give me something
He's a skating like crazy
There's like nothing there's no holds like grab onto
Took your time to climb up this mountain
I am so Carrie has to
To try and offer him
Suggestion
I just love that
So what did you do
Go back to work
Sending you would been in Space by now this story
You you
Yeah
If you're on Project Camelot you should be in
45 minutes
She's going to try and help
She's going to try and be like well maybe this is
During those do stores in Japan
Were you
Were you kind of like in a state of
I don't know sounds like maybe suspended animation or
Very confused
Because you
Did not recover yes and M
What happened into you in Vietnam so you had to be in some kind of state
Emotional state
What would you say about that
New Bern North Carolina
To get this to keep my earrings
And already knew
About Vietnam
The reason that I kept that there at the end
Because that's not
Answering request
Turn it off
But let's make this make sense
You just goes off
Into another vaguely
A related or unrelated story entirely
It's
Really frustrating for Carrie
Piss every
Every question she asked wines of having an answer like
But I really
I was working on getting my
Recertification papers
The most
That's super interesting story
Needed to be recertified
Well I had a quite a
Continuing education hours at the
FaceTime
I went and got a degree
What's a bartending College
Like the issue is
This is what you have done
Understand is they carry knows that her listeners
Are going to be like
Confused by the
Problem
And she knows that in order to get to
To the juiciest
He probably wants to say right they need to fix it
Because otherwise it's going to be a glaring hole
It just doesn't make sense
Fixing this
And at the same time
It exceeded like it's
Frustrating
For her because
She wants nothing more than to believe all of it
She wants to believe it
But you can't believe it
No I did too
Because there's a bigger issue even than that
Is a problem
Certainly
You could you could make
Like if he was willing to
To give anything
Get away from it
Like with the
Magical thinking that they always in
Project X clip
Then I think
I think this one is really this is really tough
Were you a pilot
I think it was yeah it was a Tuesday
Are you sure
This part in but she's talking about like his exploits in Vietnam
A great pilot or flying sideways
So at this point
This to me isn't it
Essential problem
And I admire Carrie for bringing it up because
I'm going to call her swearing Carrie from
No faith that he's going to have an answer for them
Bring up a hard
Question for him to answer
Is Bolt
Butter bark is this
Destroy the interview
But I think that she knows if there's another option
Little strange to me that that
There must have been you know they never do anything well it was don't-ask-don't-tell
South and they
Modus operandi of way of operating that they would have had you
From my understanding I'd like white on rice after that experience in Vietnam
Clearly demonstrated some kind of
Very different
Approach to life ability
He also had some some great skills as a helicopter pilot parently slide sideways into all kind of crazy s***
They would already has had their eye on you
And plus
In theory they knew exactly who you were
They knew that you were played in
Before you knew
Correct
I wouldn't say they knew I was going
I would unique I was different
Know when did the Vatican write that letter I wish when you were a child
That's ti8 the Vatican
Sort of notified the CIA the CIA took complete control of the 33 children and place you and family
Do you work now
Maybe not every level CIA but certainly the top-level
Oh
Girl that sound is
That's a sound of a TV look like
That's good
Point
I really like her
You know damn
Everything about it
Everybody knows
Can't keep track
To compartmentalize
So
Because she has a
Started this.
They're at the end of that bird
Carrie
Herself
To solve the problem
That he is unwilling to solve his own narrative
They the CIA and the NSA and the way they developed
During those
Years is to become more and more
Into surveilling kids of all types
Cuz they were very aware after Eisenhower dealt with the
Gray
The great human hybrid program objecting of human use of Art
Cereals excetera excetera so you were part of a different group and they must have known that you were part of a
Treat you with
Kid gloves
You know you are even if they didn't know you know know which ones you were
They had a real close eye on you
So okay
So here we have a downtime and and they send you they let you kind of rest
To where
Nothing unusual at least
Nothing too unusual went on in Japan
Suddenly they play pop up in your life when you're 30 years old and they want to recruit
Why
This is collaborative writing
Exactly exactly
He can come up with like
Easiest explanation
She is now you can hear it in her voice she's not asking that she's saying okay so now what is going on
We're keeping an eye on you but they knew that you needed
Some Kind of Rescue right part of the
Greg
You were someone who they could give
And here's the rest
Doing paperwork in Japan or whatever credit get back to you
So now he's been completely
Is not going anymore
Dairy Square
We'll get to why
But
Is 3 minutes long as longer than a lot of eclipse
Baby usually have
But it's
Important to keep as a whole week interrupted if we know
But it is
What we saw on that last clip
Carrie taking over and it becoming a writers room as opposed to an interview
But like
Cute to a rampant
Fix that and at the end of this you will just
He ready give up
Eddie just signals is complete submission I like at the end of this is completely.
This is like
This is alien
Okay
Actually wondered if they the CIA and
Alveolar how do you say your name
And the fact that you're supposed to be some kind of
Guess you're saying it's written in the Bible that you're supposed to be some kind of avenging angel
Real quick he's also apparently a name
Supposed to bring
I don't know I don't know I don't I don't I don't fully understand what this
Also an angel whose come to bring
Destruction of some
Alright
The destruction or something along those lines
Flights
You know some crazy lady
You're not supposed to fly sideways
Sideways in a helicopter you're going to go left
Angel
Although it's me
Seems like a major revelation
Kind of minor
In the story
In other words not such a
Anais
Kind of in the future
Supposedly
Now
Demonstrated that really in this life so far
Assuming that your father
Call him what you were capable of
I'm so and so forth
You didn't exhibit any like
What we have now you know superpowers soda
At least you're not telling us that you did
Conversation is being curtailed in certain way
Dating here and I completely agree your
I think it's possible that your mother was a hoe
Real quick
But it's not like
You were born in
You've already seen here
Now
Beyonce angel
You've seen her insults him twice
And then also imply that like you're not telling me everything
You know
Which is the way that they get around all this
Obvious b*******
Sometimes you can't answer a question
Eyebrows lightly
Smile which means it's not allowed to tell me
Alright
She's implying that
And then also being like
It's disappointing to talk to a plea ATM
Not have any
Real information and then also
You certainly don't seem like you had superpowers
During your life
So he's already even but she even preamps that by saying like
But I totally believe you're pleiadian
It's because what she's doing is she subtly threatening to expose him
I believe that what's going on here is like
Hurt
Express
Listen to him
I see you
And I know that
What I'm saying now
Should get to you
And when I don't say you're full of s***
I'm doing you a favor so now do me a favor
And go along with his narrative that I'm building for you
There's sort of a given
Intake going on here
In terms of a con
I really think that's what's going on
It's fascinating to me
To watch this happen
Look what I was watching this
Dynamic sir
Henry 8th
Like she is working with
A first year of Second City
She's like I'm an expert in this b*******
Chirp you need to
You need to step up
Your games on
I can't be doing this
I need you to bring the heat
You're just a pleiadian right now I can turn you into f***
Nothing if you have Aiden
You better have beer
You need to have beat absolutely that path or else people really like I don't
Also are you for real
It's level of
Like I've never seen that much
Sculpting narratives
Cuz she's
This goes on
It is crazy
This is coming from her
Suggested multiple things
These last two clips
So maybe this was the first time she just didn't do a pre-show like like she didn't do the
Nothing seriously Wonder Lake
If maybe she is allowed
I have a tape recorder with Mark Richards
But she doesn't
So she can
Depict at the way she
Possible
I don't know cuz it'll be the perfect
Fraud
I mean Ethan freezer
There's nothing you could do about it
Releaf
Is my bolshit possible to come to me with this
I like that a lot it would also explain why like so many of these people that are on her show are like
Legitimate
Broad
Like Sean ride that Sean David Morton
Patrick Martin
The dude was like doing time
Time for fraud
Other people have had
Juno similar
Patterns and their lives
You know like yeah
They would explain why there's all these tan man around all the time
Because she's like your f****** around I'm talking around 2
Do you have a convention
Multiple songs
Call Dick
Conspiracy
Cruise
Sea love it
Spiders like a conspiracy theory Cruise
I love that
He went on it and Main speaker
And there's like a
Advise that someone out
To cover it
A videos of him like dancing around being a real blow hard
Stuff like that
She got arrested
The second.
We're going to go on my lap
These Bernard project
That I'd like to
That's it that's a man who's a f****** a lie
Right there
So you don't actually have necessarily
Human DNA or your amount of DNA that you have from a human is quite limited that you're mostly
You know pleiadian
I looked closely the way you wrote your answers the way you wrote your book
And my impression
Is that your
Probably
I don't know if you say 90% gladion or when you know what your DNA kind of
That's what I'm getting I'm getting She carries you the woman
Cherry juice
For a certain. Of time and then gave birth to you but in reality you weren't really
First
For genetic line necessarily now you can correct me I want to just
This is where I'm going
What's the CIA motivated
To attract you to get you into the Marines
So you would be shot down eliminate you because you were the most dangerous of the 30
If you want to look at it like that
Hyundai
Semi
Step sort of you seeing red
Just because I want to pause
Before we
She is just
Creating
An entire Theory
This whole thing this episode this is like okay so really what's going on
Your potential as a dangerous
Knew that if you went to Vietnam you would be shot down in this helicopter
Engineered the whole thing to try and get you killed
You're an angel being
Some sort
She spits
2 spelling
Prophesying whatever you want to call it so
They could have set that up
And obviously Pleiadians to be watching over you your entire time
It doesn't make any sense that they would just ignore you so so
They actually rescued you from a life death situation and anybody else would have been killed
God knows
I still carry the scars today from that battle
The real quick that's another trademark
Eddie page
It's not answering the
Almost immediate
Talkin about
Bullets
It doesn't bother me
So if you hear what I'm saying right
So do you think that they they were hoping maybe you would die
I really truly think so
No I don't think so
I know so
Find happy when I appreciate that I appreciate
Sounds like the end
Thank you
You makeup
Absolutely
That is
Me reshaping your your myth
Because I have
I am so thoroughly.
Destroyed you in Euclid
Alright now we can
Now we can proceed now that the dominance
A hierarchy is very clear
Cherries on top
Eddie is
And you know why.
Cookie Queen B
She's she's no slouch
Doing this for how many years now
That's all
Novice this is the big time
This is a big league pickup basketball game Ophelia live
Bears Eli
No
Carrie's going to
Spell it out
YG
I'm not your usual interviewer and I have very sophisticated Witnesses
Such as Captain Mark Richards who was in the secret space program
Around the same time as you
Maybe even love you
He's in the six
So anyway and he and his father were the secret space program so we had
We have
We have a Ryan vehicles that that they built
All of this was going on we were not just some
Earth
Civilization
Going to stop
You were already you have you said above
President
Level
Then
And you were when you were from another planet for God's sake
Planet politics
Dealing with there
Faces on the moon and Mars
I think
New recovered memories
Efforts to establish civilizations on other planets
This is the real kind of way that I would think that you would be useful
Is it is in educating them
Capacity
Tell me tell me
There's a window you crawl out of
They don't control me
Alright don't
Did they use me in a weapon or night
Cassidy
Exactly what I was
Pull up doing
Inaugurated the education
Catholic Church
Inaugurated them into education
Into education
Interesting way of saying
Cold
I don't man look at a note to me is just another like I'm not answer
Your question
But also like I said that's the window you
You can get out of its above-top-secret I can't tell you about this
She's offering him the window out like the you-know-what like
Detective does or whatever is
That's what's going on here
And he reject that f****** window he's like no one controls me
This isn't like she's not trying
For a crime so you should have taken my window
There's no consequences to going out that window
It actually helps your story
To punch up your dumpster
Controls we stuff
You worked for the agency
It said that they were controlling you
Do you want to do or what you can
Redo the whole thing's ridiculous
I want to ask you a question
Do you think
The Eddy page
Which has been to area
I think
He had a dream
Interest vision
Here is what he
I want to give you a lot more credit
A lot more than you're letting on here
Well in the book you said you hadn't been that yeah
So he pulls out a lanyard shouldn't carrier ID
Basically if you're the Comedy Festival the passes
Indeterminate writing on it it doesn't
Carry it around with you everywhere you go now Area 51 people are totally cool with you just wondering around
Well about Area 51
But he's been there
Also if he is an archangel
I'm sort and half
It's going on underneath that museum about
You got to help out with the Getty nobody
That's an old rule
See that's what's so fun about these like
These people is imagining that they're all not like
Because they're all like imagine that they're all not lying it's
Crazy that they don't team up
It's crazy that they don't all make make a Super Friends event
Look Project Camelot cinematic
Exactly you can't have them for every movie
For Carrie to have around
See what's going on with you
The Reptilian
Boy
Even if he had at least
Maybe didn't get those memories back
Have you come back
She might have
She might as well that one under the rug
Maybe I don't trust that one
Still I still recall I think the spider leadership was
In Plan B at
The giant beetles
I think are just
That one guy right now
Think I was struggling
Yeah that wasn't a good one
I hate to say that
But
It really
We can't do that up
Episode will never happen
There Beatles
So
You might be wondering what
Like specific information
Eddie wants to
To get out here on the
Michelle
Control that part is definitely
A piece of
Messages
He's not God
I should tell you that one of the reasons I gravitated towards this video
It's cuz it was the new newest one
Okay that she's done
And also it had to do with his
Prophecy
Yes in Prophecy
Alright I'm interested to hear that
Challenges week ago
Getting ready to happen
Vague
Facebook
And I told people what was about to happen
I was awoken and I was given to court
Identification need to give those on my show
Literally the same day that we did the show happened to be later in the morning on the same day that you gave that
Mothership
So there they must be coming obviously and you also talk about this I'm going to get my
Forget we call it but it's a black
Craft and it's very diabolical you said there's seven of them other than positioned around our planet for a very
It doesn't surprise me
These are new Ships coming in that you're talking about so it sounds like they're getting ready for some
Something big
Alright
Okay that's very cool so that's the one that you were describing the black
There is 78 around the world
I still don't believe it
But also don't worry about him different
Okay good
So like one over Denver ice
And then
Buenos Aires
Right
The seven continents
Scott eurasia's one but you can get rid of
Aliens in Antarctica
Yeah oh yeah oh yeah Berlin
That's right
Chiropractor in New Berlin
You know what an artery
You know what the one thing that we don't hear about this
Nobody's ever mention Australia
No
No ever mention
Left alone in the
Please revive a lot on
Let's
As you can see when you don't have it flushed out you going this is what happened
In the lab late at night with pain
Was going to work Saturday open mics around the room
So
There's a there's a bunch
Pleiadian mother ships that are coming
Courseplus these robot weapons
Better like spaceships
Plus all the other Alyssa ever get every other person also has
Alien robots coming around and hanging out in our airspace
Alliance
Pro small has been retook Courtney Brown remote viewer
These things are possible
We make peace with our enemies
I'm seeing all that scary if we
Discount all the other guy
Are we just think about pleiadian ships
Friendly robot weapon only
It's not so bad now that's
But
Not all good news
Oh no
Alright so your your people are coming here in ships and mother ships
Nlr dealerships
And
They're getting ready for what appears to be a kind of a standoff
Or an out-and-out war and this war has happened on Earth before
As you say
We know that you say Sodom and Gomorrah
Real quick he is argumentative
Sodom and Gomorrah got new
Okay I thought you was talking about the World Cup
We have a war every four years or so.
Obviously
Obvious
Volkswagen
Call Who's real name
Egypt
I've been to Egypt quite a bit and
About it
So there's a place called amarna and it looks like a nuclear bomb hit it
Because it's been
Instead of the you know the remains of you know these temples and so on
There's virtually nothing on the desert floor it's clean
So you know the only thing that would do this to a civilization that used to be there
Is a new
Not the area also and I know so the signs
The nuke is very clear
I think you know a person doesn't
I didn't have to have some CIA guy tell me that it was just obvious
That's kind of a day
Still probably have an expert
That's kind of a dick
Addictive
Something else that I don't understand
It seems very out of place
The way she said that I love
Reveal the limits of
They're imagine a
Like it like with l.ron Hubbard alien still
B-52 bomber
And of course it's a new can either Interstellar traveling and all the best
Smarter idea to just throw one of those ships into the ground
It's
Yeah I am
Don't think about that
Also she also later
Says that the Raptors are working with the Air Force
Let me think about Rafters and B-52 bombers
Which is a really funny thought
So this is real and and usually have worn the CIA about this in your prophecies the fit when you were regressed
That there's going to be another
Nuclear confrontation
With off-planet race
Instead of the Middle East
If I understand you correctly you're saying is going to happen in America
Well you dare ever again okay well then
Is Retin-A happen in this Armageddon thing
It's not a new that they're paranoid over
May I call you my sister
Whoa come from a very source
He doesn't want to answer the question
He just went Whole Hog that. That's how we escape so much
Therefore I know that
How did I not
Q only invited
Apparently they don't like my bad language
Mariah Carey
Gary levox
Like
Catch this the first time I listen
When I was cutting clips
Kind of got it like I thought he was just
Lili dodging
Oh yeah
I thought that was for sure what he was doing but
Immediately says this
And I didn't realize that this was him
Sword of answering
The question
But you need to stall a little bit so you did that you're pleiadian thing
But then he said this and I thought this was just
I didn't realize that this was
Tired of answering the question of
What is the threat
If it's not a nuke what is
Yeah
In this place
Dragon
It is going to be a very very traumatic
Experience
Everybody
And everybody around the world
If we were not here to help
The creation
Man and I don't care what color you are
That's weird there at the end
No I really didn't mean to throw and race
Ego doesn't matter what color you are or my personal feelings
Towards you
Call
Hold on hold on
You could have got
I don't know when you put that one in if you're going to go with the race stuff that one
Dragon world's going to be able to
Whole world
Big dragon
To where the dragon is currently
Questions will be answered but did you have any other questions
Not dragon or Ray
Race-related
Don't understand what the difference
Between loving sign
And regular sign
Currently
Non loving scientist their ones that would create things that are
Okay I don't know I need loving scientists are all about the red dress
Traditionally thought of
The lightbringer
Alien race
Yes they're the ones who give us are happy
Supposed to nightmare
I'm sure that are helpful as opposed to
To kidnap us in our sleep like the grey has four chocolate bars
Right
Doodle
Texas forever
This is this is the moment
See there's going to be a space War dragons
In the middle of a little bit of a war
Got to worry about it
The fire breathing dragon
Which will learn about in a minute
No homegrown fire-breathing dragon
Prepared
Sadistic draft picks
Situation that's what I need to know
Do you really know who you're
Ambulance
Well I think I do
What are you just saying
What do you mean
Play that one more time
You really know who your
Interviewing
Well I think
Alright
You just threatened the Killer
It's
It is a threat
It was generally
Of all the people I've ever seen her interview no one's been like
With right now
Arrest
From the absolute Beatdown he had in the first half of the
I think he's trying but unfortunately
Carrie immediately smacks him back down with this
Issue with some of the language you use which seems to swear that you are not
Favorable towards
People of color
And I and that goes against my grain
Carolina collision
Brody Jenner I'm from a race of benevolent aliens or just turn out to hate
Black people who got is that a weird alien
Living in North Carolina
Oh dear
Credit on his book
She's referring to stuff that she's right in his book I believe
She's referring to
They give the inside any of this
Episode
Perhaps he's had some
Disparaging stuff in Atlanta
What you talkin about the language of you
I think that means
Facebook
Disparaging things about
Either
Caught that s***
Which which I don't care what race you are probably
You know we've uncovered some
Pretty lady
Sandwiches Amman
I'm curious party
But the fact that she's just going for it being like look
To tell you I don't
I'm not okay with the racism b u
Which
Hypocritical bulshit
It is hypocritical bulshit on her part
His wife if she actually believes in all of these aliens
Hugely rapist
To so many
Everybody with a broad brush these people are all evil
Tasmanian devil
Are good mongoose
Cassowaries out there
They will f*** you up
Birds are evil
I kind of agree with you but at the same time we live in
Right so it's funny that she's calling one of
Just a f****** racist
So here's his response
But send me your comments are are really difficult
Text
The dresser
Call the races
I studied the Civil War intently and College
PetSmart
Race relations with white people and black people
That's a good
Learn
Paperwork
Accused of
Real quick will get back to that in a second when did you go to college
Funeral
Years between
16 + 18
I don't care what are you studying race relations
Most of the time most of the time you can't even if you graduate early from high school you can go to college in
Until your class would have graduated
Usually have to take correspondence classes and I don't think that would be a way you could have gotten an a
Degree by the time
He would have enlisted in gone off to Vietnam
By the way is also segregated
Maybe he went to college during that
Not explain
Natalie on the GI Bill perhaps
Just curious.
We're going to be
Franklin
From creation
Has the label things today
Oh God
One time
Embrace
And then help these less fortunate
Weird is weird
Well he doesn't mean that stuff at the end
I don't understand how we went from
There's Dragon coming to like
Standard old racist in North Carolina fair with other drugs
Drunk old white bunnies like
Well you know the problem is with it the way they live
We were not even
I'm close to done with how bad this one
Can't imagine how we could buy this one off the rails
And here we have hit the penny
But it's still on it
Still upright
Bakersfield classifieds
Decent thought I guess
He had at the end of like
This country didn't
We do a better job of helping
People Express
There's existed in this country since the beginning and all day
He could do that and maybe save it but unfortunately
How can you even
Creating sense of mine
How can you even focus
Sun color of skin
Why does that even factor into your kind of view of so-called Armageddon
Attitude
Tidy color
Mini mini
Genetics
Andy creation
Creation story
Can I look weird
The creation story
Actually began
Can I say
Evolve
That is not true
Who are the black people
Oh no
What
You know what the machine gave him the other like
Hey you're an alien
The f*** are you so petty and talking about
Pleiadian benevolent wonderful
You still think of this
Lotto benevolent
Turns out no
You know what just what I want
I forgot to say stuff like this if profit
Stroke
I would gather if we talked to most of them
Epsom salt
Well the Bible called them the cursed race
I've always thought of the black people as well the Bible calls
Lock them out of my beautiful country that I mean alien but I'm still in America
Also that's the amazing part about this country
Is if you're white
Even if you're an alien but like an actual layout
Define also I specifically think that that's
In the Mormon bible
I'm not sure if that's in the Christian
I'm not a hundred percent sure
I think I agree with you
I know for sure it's in the Mormon Buy
No no
India what I don't either
Memorize the Bible and it's been a long time
Pick one up but I don't recall
Necessarily
Black people are cursed
Felix judeo-christian Bible
I feel like I've been many times that I've read the Bible I would at least have seen that
Once and been like four people would constantly bring it up
And if that's the case then he's operate
Hillbilly more
Hillbilly Mormon angel
TV show
Stars Nathan Fillion weed plucking
So now Carrie tries to save a little bit by using
Really faulty etymology
Okay and Humanity are is are a race of
Warriors and a Rainbow Warriors
And they are of multiple colors
And has a r a
Also called
Many colors
WhatsApp
So you're not descended from Wrecking 8
This is like so stupid
Wait what
What's the weather
No discussion of it except for Eddie to laugh and yellow mango
Okay at least they found their middle ground
Alright
The language works.
Achoo as in Grant
And man as in
Man Hugh Grant is very attract
That Rick's just
Absolutely
I believe the etymology of
Hugo's
I had the specifics pulled up about it just
Just to be really fat
But who cares
Obviously
So you kind of thinking
You know like where he'll take the word and
Conversion yet that's not how this works
I'm out of that
In the language on her like
Calendar like inspirational calendar those quotes more likely she just wants out
Of this
Stretch of the conversation
And chooses like all right look at that
What would you know about English
Do that sort of thing Carolina and he's only been to college
Incel and help
He's got to go he's like
That could have been the moment where Carrie takes us out of the muck right
Greener pastures but unfortunately
Kicking lucky
Just keep taking
Self till he falls over
He was responsible for
Oh God
Eddie
Hitler
A bad rap
What are you doing
Which apparently is a lot of racist stuff we have to call it out
But he does not claim to be a half-alien
Not where I expected this to go
Chevrolet of all the things that we've
I never expected it to descend into weird old racist who grabs you after a comedy doesn't that
You know what you're really funny let me tell you about all the races
Just things that I have to say
I'm not racist
Per se
What are you hate look
Are you cool if I tell you a joke
It gets a little razor
Little you might want to anyways
F****** idiot
Hardcore
Holocaust
Denying well
But that's how most holocaust-denying statements
Start
He doesn't actually end up like
Talking
Too much
Details about what
Hitler gets blamed for that he didn't do
Which is maybe good for Carrie
But like
That was all just $2
Oh God so we take a break
From this vicious race
Hey Matthew Savages about Holocaust denial
How is it this is somehow going to come down
Trans people shouldn't use the
Same bathroom as their gender is weird old man
The world is right here in America
It's called Yellowstone
Real quick
Many movies have been made about Yellowstone
He's talking about the supervolcano
Which is something that Hollywood could never have imagined
Even though there's been a ton of boogers
At least 50
Even though he's also called Hollywood
Bright
It is
Rumbling
I don't care what the scientists say 08 the last reference 670
I dream the future
And I've seen this so I agree with you absolutely
Example of explicit
Revolve
Not defected like
He's dreamed it so it's also true
If this is the History Channel
Normal scientist
Stephen warned about the
Possibility
Clearly on people's radar
And because of that people studied it very closely
And there's literally no indication that we need to be worried about that at present
Maybe it's sometime in the next Thousand Years
That episode from 2009
Figured I have to worry about there's really no indications that there's a threat here
Hundreds
Poster
Be able to tell any kind of
Preliminary
Does go off it is a potential Extinction event for not just us but like all life on the planet so
But we figured it would be a smart idea to keep it
Can I on it
Decades and decades studying volcanoes
Just say
Fully know what the warning signs are in that conference
It's not like the 1800's were things really
Makeup on us
Probably
Navigate back to
When you put gas come out
Read every word in there and yeah
Read the book
And see that
Well
Is because
Sometimes hard to swallow
Holyshit
That's not even
Nope
Cuz the truth sucks sometimes
Sometimes
According to Mead
Wooboi
I love it I'm on
Wow
Facebook
Doctors in there
It's not everything
About his whole life
It's about the
The Palladium
About how
Nobody
Text Big MB more by black
Then he has
Absolutely there's no black person who's been victimized by The Red Dragon
There's probably something
Think about how Martin Luther King
Easy
Almost there
Some of these nice racist things that Alex's
Oh yeah
We have two more Clips ones racist ones not
We'll deal with it not racist
It's about how I
World
Got countdown
It's actually a prayer
It's mentioned in the Bible
Story
Carrie
The Sixth Seal was open
At midnight
Very complete record of things that happen
Within
Dallas actors
You're knocking Chan
Amadeus
What a Sally
It started meal Farm
That dragon
Wake up
Swine
Yellowstone
Is starting to become very very little not starting it's getting more and more
It's not fan
Me at all
Did someone said a prayer to Amadeus and then woke up this morning
Convince me
That the scientists are wrong
Yellowstone
Of all the stuff that's happened
Bible and the prophecies that he himself is fat
Because he is an alien
However aliens all Jesus died
For their students
Even though there are millions upon millions of years old
Which means that all of them prior to
To Jesus
Who is still only a couple thousand years ago
I don't understand
Because they all reconcile the Bible with Drake I can actually
Play mat
Okay I wish I could throw
I wish I could
Because a lot of the people who take on these like alien ideas kind of Blended bitten off
Exorcism into their their view of Christianity
There's like that esoteric Christianity
Describe another weird connection between
The better answer is
No you cannot
You cannot reconcile those two
Some holidays
Pepper in whatever they feel
Feel like we just talked a little bit like
Everybody has their own recipe like he throws in racism I'm sure that's going to work well
That's a long with his consistent
Extra
Use that
There's bigger issues
Himym throwing aliens
Christ in together is not as important
Tamiya necessarily as like
Hey you're trying to Trojan Horse racism
Into your intriguing
Dragon metaphor about us volcano
Do you think Holly
Piggyback
Some sort of authority in that you
Came back from
From the dead and 11
Missing days in Vietnam
Angel / 380
Curse
So are we
Episode
How he sort of Watch
She probably
Should use
Is closing
He defends himself about race
Once again
Holy crap
Yeah he said some things about
Righteous
It's true
I'm not going to tell you nothing that I cannot
Is Dismount going to go out to break
This book now and you're going to hear some
Flagrantly racist things about minority
And then you're going to say oh my God
I doubt it
It's a surprise to me as well I did not expect
To say that
But before this before this
Episode was
It taped on the 4th of July which
Horses when we
Declare our independence
I believe every word there is nothing that he said that he cannot back
We just found out the Jordans
Hold the f****** phone you bigger
Supposed
Most willing
See that's why I didn't want to tip my hand about the races
Some stuff at the beginning of the episode
But I wonder how much of that was coloring her like
I'm going to take over the ship here
I don't know if it was though
I think that was just
Incompetent
Question
Is Rambo
But it's interesting to see
Carrie like really take over an interview
And then it's also really enjoy
To have that box open
But I'm sure she usually wants to stay close
Because I think
I don't know if I had
In the clips that I played
But when she was broken
Subjective
She does stay like
There's some comments that you've made and people are going to
To find them eventually
Do we got to talk about that that's everything so it could have been like
Sincerely her trying to allow him to do damage
Control
Punted just botched the s*** out of the damage control
You got a safety that was
That was a disaster
If you said that then that means she's not even talkin about the book
There's some other
She said
She said that there were some comments he's made me and they're going to come out
You will come out being the book is going to
All right side chica
So I think that's what he's talking about
This is not
The Project Camelot world is just
The tree you just
Keeps giving weird fruit
You know like it
It's like you
You get
You put your hand into the bag
And you don't know what you're going to get
Are you going to get a murderer in prison line to a lady
Pulling from the bag
Are you going to get a gun
A guy who believes
The Thursday
City under the museum
Are you going to get it
To be an elected official in now do you
Who believes
Has sex with an alien every now and again
Once again
The best
Got that we've ever had
South Park
He seems like a really nice guy
I don't remember his particulars I I don't think you're right
I think he might have been that f******
Alright
Who could have
When you pull your hand out this time which org
Going to get it
Like
This guy saying super racist s***
Disney broadcasting from a rocking chair if it's on the front of a goddamn Plantation
He is very rarely looking up at the camera
Start talking like this
Very
Cassidy and Project Camelot
Happy Fourth of July actually 24in listener
Hope you had a good one
Dogs
Is a bad idea we never should
I'm regretting it
Oh well
You can check us out
Four more over at knowledge fight.com
We are on Facebook I ain't go to iTunes
You can download
You could leave a review for the pie
You could give us
Some number of stars
Number number of stars
It would support the show by going to knowledge fight.com cooking sport the show
Help me survive
And it's your turn
Bora Bora
Well I mean we did is George h.w. Bush
I got to say no matter how I slice this
You are a huge racist
Please go fuc yourself
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color