Alex
Is that
Nice weekend
Chicago Improv
Doing some stand-up comedy
Compact
In order to get the studio and recorded episode
Thrilled to welcome back
I know a few things about
One of them
He loves right
That's about it
Oh you're from Indiana
Obsession with treehouses as a child
Did you always want to break into people's houses or climb up to
Flashlight on
Wrestling
Hurricanrana achiever
Each one better than the last
Interesting
Dover
Those kids
That's big of you
I respect that a whole bunch
Oh you a week before we started recording
When he first started
It he had one of those if I have a little like if I have to shave
5-day growth or something
He is the one he has that face that it looks like if
Dead an old-timey like
Hobo
Like he's like a little cigar
Sure canal
He just looks like
Trainwreck
Go home and tell your mother you're brilliant
Someone on their mate a good comment
Detransition
Into being a bald guy with a goatee
Like a cool ball
At least I have
I think I probably actually like high school cuz I used to shave my head and I School
The widow's peak
Thursday stuff in the back of my head
It don't matter
Bam Bam Bigelow rentals release little weird bump
I got a little bump but a single Bob
From taking
Hair transplant
What's good
Alex
I love you I love you
Best front like
You love out on the
Yeah yeah that was pathetic
For that you could bring up
Everyone suck.
Anyway it's about Alex Jones talking about qanon steps
But anyway anybody
Alex
My friend
I love you you love Alex Jones
I probably loves a comic
I can't think of a specific example and if I could name the but like
I probably met comedians at festivals
That I haven't seen in years but I think
I love that person
XYZ they have a show where there
Racist
Isn't cool to me that's my favorite
Isaac comedy turned is probably in every
Every branch of life
They've all been cool to me
Alex that's how we
I hate that
It's so bad
So, that person has
I don't know
Other people's experiences are secondhand
Rick was friends with the Toby
Pennywise
Oktoba always
No no
It's something that is almost not to be believed
Quite frankly
A little bit to talk to you
Because
Not like
Medicine
Not not like rake but like the nature of the heel
AMV how it be harder story to tell
Is a face you can correct me if I'm wrong
Relies on sort of natural charisma
Amplifying natural Charisma to get people to like you
To get them like the crowd to want to see
This person defeat the heel
Really specific buttons
That they wouldn't probably make people feel
People who played goals in order to
Right trigger the audience
I meant also the other aspect of it
Playing against
And then also I think it's a more
Compelling narrative thing
Because it allows for Redemption narrative
Heroic can only be like
Well I don't like them as much as I used to wear is coming out of the whole being
Coming up to like
Now we like you
Yeah I think it's I think it's much more interesting a much more difficult I don't know
I've never seen you take notes on this box
It's it's
Very hard
To have
As healed
The bad guys
Or
So
Back in the day
It was Hulk Hogan was
The good guy
Chirp
Sergeant Slaughter
Or the chic
So that was
Well Define
But
Somewhere along the way
We started getting it
The attitude
You had what was kind of called
Right
Yeah but not this happened back in the day because
With the four horsemen
Safid watch old NWA old school world
Wrestling
There would be guys
Four Horsemen symbol
Dusty Rhodes start getting
Hogan
What are the things that led to it was
The good guy
I'll be your partner insurance
Think you're a dummy for any extended period of time you got
Team up with the
Yeah
But with the cool heal
The bad guys
And
They
Would come out go you here to see
Debussy
This hillbilly company
Nobody would go crazy
Also the big thing of wrestling just real quick
Amex or just not having good
Faces for them to
Ellsworth
Good looking
People like Deadpool
Anymore
You know dick head
Yeah
Emma
But like guys
In-N-Out
Smart that's what we
So we know
You're pushing
Like Roman Reigns
If you don't know where I'm at
Always has
Number one
This is my number one face of the company guy
Hulk Hogan Warrior
Stone Cold The Rock
This is the guy who
When you
This is the guy
Who I want Morning America
Absolutely
A ton of different
Reasons
It's been like the perfect storm of bad reason
Or bad
Happenstance
This guy is kind of like Murphy's Law Office
Anytime
Here we go
Yeah but this
Stop wearing diapers
Won't stop wearing the vest kept the music of The Shield
Brian
That works
But they're just
Nope he's the guy
I do like
I always do whatever I want whenever I want
Like he's cocky
I like actually told you some bread
Opposed to
Turned out to be
The correct on which I really like John Cena back
Shouldn't like him
Everyone was Elias when he first showed up this is awesome
There's some guys who just for the main roster and alliances one
Nope this guy sucks I like
You shut your mouth I can be
Turn on my decisions the right way
Eliason
Directions
I got to get better in the rain but otherwise he
He is a guy
True deal
Bush Lake
Exactly
And it to be a good heel
A lot of times
You eventually have to
Get your come up
It's a lot of people.
Stephanie McMahon
She's a heel
But she never gets her
But then she was on TV couple weeks later than
Broken broken
Need the window dressing
Yeah
I'm sorry I'm just one of those things
Hero long enough
Villain
There are
Like tanahashi in Japan
Everwild
Okada was the
It just happened
I can see that
I think a lot of people
For life to be a lot like wrestling so that like you know the bad guy having a reception like
A lot of people ask me about
Do you think there was any point where it's possible for Alex
Teturn face
Window
I don't I think from what I've gleaned from studying 2009 Isaac use white supremacy
I think there's a lot of things that people miss
How is language
His his relationship
Black people
Clearly oh boy
There's been some
I bet anymore like I'm the victim of that when I was a kid
Cup
Maybe it was covid-19
Bye-bye
Black eye
Beat up like Alex
Three or two of his friend
And they ran away
If possible
Rockwall Texas
I looked it up now
But he grew up there in the 70s
1970 census population was 3100 people
Small suburb that probably was
You know formulaic houses mcmansion type
Sure people didn't want to leave
Because the population was too high to Urban that's my guess
Punch the walls
Fabulous Motley Crue
That privilege with listen to Oliver episode that is a real status a real talk about showing how tough they are
Adult
Drunk we chop each other
Who are your top five
Of all time
Emma WWE era
I was going to say Rodger Stone number one always talk about this
The Ric Flair Starbucks
Thanks
If Iran
MSNBC
CNN
Olive Garden
I would set them down
They would shut down for one day
We would watch that Rodger Stone documentary
And we would just
This is the place
You guys are not playing by The Playbook some guys are
Saint Peter's dude
Michael Brooks that's the dude that
All these other people
Okay top 5 heels
Alright
Now
If you're a great deal you shouldn't get cheer
Sure you should be
Sincerely hate Asher
So right now
Tommaso ciampa
One of the best
Aleister black my boy cell
He is
Awesome for so many reasons
Unfollowed everybody on Twitter
Performer depression guest very sad
Very very nice guy but
I don't know this I don't know this version of tomorrow
Edith Orchard my head in a show when he was next about so
Just a dick on Twitter
He wears a T-shirt and goes by bet you want this t-shirt
Guess what for sale
That's awesome for going
The T-shirt sale
No music no music
He would fit in the just so good so good
Austin back
When he was a bad guy
He
Became a chickenshit you can't be
Don't call I whip everybody's ass
He was a chickenshit he would
Complain one of my favorite promos he ever cut
He just after just a rough day
He just got in the Rings by everybody's got the ring
My name is
Call Steve Austin
Former four-time WWE Champion and I don't deserve
It was the best
So I've all-time Flair
There was another of those guys where he would piss you off
Rodger Stone everything codes
At the end of the day in wrestling what you want
You want
People to want to pay money
To see you
Forbes
So
I paid multiple times
Liquor store
I'm going to get them in the rack
You know Brian are going to win
Wait
So flare
Just make a Rodger Stone comparison
And for sure one of the
Organs glass
Another four horsemen
Okay Charlie Blanchard
Was one of the four horsemen
Most known
Protein partners with Arn Anderson
This was a guy
People
King Haiti
There's some guys in wrestling
Where
I forgot who
There was
Landstar Missouri
Note 4
Great trainer
Adam
He was telling Dolph Ziggler
Which is a move that the good guys
He even told me go
Don't worry about
Cuz people are going to
Always hate
Get out
F****** faces
People can hate
Tully Blanchard
Tango
No one ever was like
One day we want to really cheer him like
No redeeming qualities total piece of garbage
Heroes of wrestling
Yeah he was
They
Ted Turner
Meeting
Haven't interviewed
Nobody will know your
I know I'm telling
What's what needs to
Get Dusty Rhodes
The f*** out of booking is f****** guy all the other foot
Tully Ric Flair
Tully Blanchard
Then there's like
The heels that are
Red hot
Because of life
The political climate so the Russians back in the day my God
Like Nikita Koloff back
Russian nightmare
This guy came out of nowhere
Is big as he can hang with the Road Warriors
He was a monster
T was awesome
What's the
Let's go modern
Brighton
It's tough now cuz everyone's soul
Who cares about the last like let's play 10 years
Oakhurst
I thought
There's been there's also
We have to talk about like
Yoshi
And then there's the light
Go away
I want you here
Yeah Jared back in the day
Winnetka I would win there's if there's a
But at any pay-per-view
Where you at like hang the
Belt and such a
Russo
Tell people what are convoluted
Title from the state
Europa
That's me
Best simple this one you had to like peneguy
How to put the title
Eric 1110
Raven ECW had a real
Mama where he was awesome
Perfect
Tastic
Nowadays to it's like you'll heal wrestler
Nowadays
They don't want that
Ryan
When people didn't know it
Was real
Predetermined whatever you wanna call it
They thought it was real
And you know somebody would do something
They're making a lot of noise
When you know you're being a real bad
You're nothing
That's what
Yeah I can see the gears turning in your head because you can tell that there's an answer I hope you say
If you aren't coming out like your I tell you then was one of the worst
Man
To I was hoping
The greatest heel to you
Your fan
Wrestling
Taliban
What's up cell
Add to the list of a black guy beating up Alex
Alex was also beaten up by a wrestler
Probably about span of the Von Erichs back-in-the-day extended does he does bring up watching
Devon Erickson he was younger this was taken from episode where he
Because Zeb Colter
A piece of their character
Yuri about that Republicans
Running for Senate May I was a member of a member of the cabinet
That was one piece
But
I want
He talked about a bunch of other stuff mixed and noses like
This is
That was super exciting
Full force
I would love to say good luck but I know that you're a f****** stupid
Unfortunate
Glam doll
Jokerland
Jack Swagger being sort of
And he's like
I remember when that was going on in wrestling and like Jack Swagger was not
Like the main event the big bad guy of the
Have you eaten
Most of his character is about liking Alex
Sure he was top of the middle
Every night he goes out and get beat by a Mexican
What all delrio Nevada join them together with rice
So Deb
The managers at Coulter
Who is Dirty Dutch mantell
Old Navy
That dude
Used to wrestle in Puerto Rico that was a bad guy Rico
Bad timing
I remember the WWE put out a video
Or maybe it was just
Swagger and Colter put out a video where they're like
We are playing character
You know what I mean like
Cuz you could you could invite shirt so
The most
Recent guy
Who is out there today
He's in the independency wrestle for a WYD
He's an impact wrestling is all over
Another name is a guy
Realtor
Stop there was a match
In Impact rest
Where you put a chair
On Eddie Edwards
Put a chair on it
Chest opened up chat
Open up is fair and you supposed to hit the chair with
And that would
It would make a great big noise
For whatever reason
He didn't sign it outright and said he just hit him in the
Blue and busted his orbital real bad
And Sammy
Safari
Just
Tuff Shed sorry
Like I hit a big deal what do you do about it
And people are like
Now
That is not cool
Be back
Good things for the
Like hey man I'm playing
Like recently
Grey Worm
Were they came out
Promos
Neuron
Character
I mean no harm
So
That's the deal
Back in the day was like
Yeah man like there was a moment where
Jesse Ventura
Apparently so
Let's light landfill
Sergeant Slaughter light the flag on fire
And they thought about it and then they ended up fighting Hulk
Post 9/11
Later
The bad timing
There was a cool one back in the day with
Again tovarisch and Avari
Was the manager of Muhammad
Yeah they
Interesting C
It's like a bad guy
It's like I see you should
He's right
And he was like
I didn't change
You guys change the way you
This is an army
It's all it's all things I recall was that like
He was a he was a bad guy because of everyone
But now I go to airport
This is not you not me
And then
But then there's
A big trophy
Foreign wrestler
Pizza American
Takes their flag
Puts it over them
At The Show Goes On
Yeah
Shroud
What
Was the end of the Muhammad ahsan character
Was
They had filmed
Smackdown used to be taped
Tuesday
So they
Had an angle
The Undertaker
An
Choke him out
Terrorist
Came in the rain
All covered in
Balaclava
They had like black hood
Black
Fully covered
And then after they choked out
The Undertaker
Carried his body
You know
Call in the middle
I don't know if it is a thing I don't know
I mean it's just a funeral procession I imagine
And this was right after the
Right after it happened
Not repackage a
Rapper that sucks
5 minutes
Secular talk
Things I've ever found
Am I driving into Infowars
Wrestling
Was a surprise guest on Infowars
And I'll let you deal with it
Super exciting to have
Rowdy Roddy Piper on weathers today
Los Angeles
Formerly of course
Borno Roderick Georgetown
Charmed
Probably Rowdy Roddy Piper
Documentary they live
Oh yeah
Like you know one of the great one.
God dammit
But like if I like that
Sure sure but some of the racial
That's cuz
Haircut
That's terrible introduction
All he does is say his real name and he's friends with Jesse Ventura
Wikipedia page on a very happy
Is there
Who's that is fun is Oliver Stone's kid
I don't know man I don't know what he's up to
Historical accuracy
Is worse I watched
W
I watch the last
30 minutes of w at hotel a couple weekends ago
It's like watching a message
Sketch with no comedy
It's so in love
Yeah the woman playing
It's so over the
I will say
I watched Any Given Sunday
That's still hell.
This was just
Yeah it was
I want
I've never watched that it never never appear
I've seen Any Given Sunday
Have not seen
I could see that
I don't
I don't I wanted to though
There was that scene in there where where w
Like lovable
President
Dufault turnout hides under the under the raincoat with Michelle Obama and stuff
Responsible for millions of deaths
Reveal some news
Like he's going to unleash all the technology and healing machines
But I got a bridge
Had he died on the pretzel had choked on the Press
Imagine
Like who do you like Selena
But it would have been like one of those things that just the reverse
Superbikes
No
A joke
Where
President
The worst
I think the president of Selena
Which rest in peace
Because I remember him is kind of like a boozer
Alright maybe that's not a good guy
Is it the guy he's a guy who
Wow
Icing
Annie's a wrestler
So he's going to he's going to put himself out there for commotion
He was had a podcast
Okay
Podcast 2013
Minnie died in 25th
There were comics in La who was bloodied up to him and he
He was like I'm open do it like
The word Outlets do it
You do some stand-up
He was like
What what
Let's do it
Could have been cooler
The Young Bucks talk about how
Who are the most popular
Independent
Tag team
Or wrestlers
They talked about
Him
Call Mandy
He was just like
Hi
Here
He was like you
Change their
I was one of the things I was really weird I always had an image of him is kind of like maybe being a s*** head
Maybe like someone was arrested a bunch of times
No
Maybe a hard life but a pretty good life like treated people pretty well
I mean it's not super rare wrestling terms
You always get surprised by things like I just learned recently that Kurt Angle had a bunch of DUI
Was that
Able to leave
The first time
You got to go
They're like
And they're like
Wantable
Control
Oh yeah
Matches with
Eddie would get
Nepal
Touch me
It was in Spain
Like just like just so hurt and 50
Don and all the stuff
So five
Yo Kurt Angle you got to go
No I'm fine really
Organelle
Guerrero passed away
I don't know a lot of these people personalized but the one here about General ER
That's when you hear the
Weather good or bad about that
The fight with Piper
Around the around the Border
Sinusitis
Stood up for the wrestlers
When you watch there's like a
Heated wind turbines
Ric Flair
Now
And I
You can tell Piper wife
Kimberly likes to swing by the Rodger Stone parallel
But
Yeah that kind of bums me out that he was on Infowars cuz you know you always kind of want to
Yeah
That's why I think so that Alex
Infowars
Has
A weird thing where they can
Or enough Ringo it looks legitimate enough
It's big enough big enough
You know you can
What would people do how many followers
Okay
Play me
Do the whole life
You know
Well he's wrong about everything
You need to talk to you
If you just ignore if you only go on
The Stephanie Miller Show
Big deal you're not right
Interesting and I wish
Ladybug
Interview
100 *
The documentary
3 of that film
I think it's actually kind of
Cuz it gives a perspective italics
Anniversary
Live
Inside really interesting
Reaganomics
Pause the music
3 conspiracies
The movie is Dunn's it's taken on a life of its own
Never gets old
What's going on
I think that's fair I think it would be interesting perspectives like I didn't necessarily ever
Put two and two together that I haven't watched
Collagen Stoned Out of My Mind
I never put the pieces together
Statement on consumerism artificial messages through
Advertising and never really put the pieces together as like a statement about Reaganomics
I think a lot of those I think this is going to be another era like
B8es
Where
A lot of stuff was about Reagan
And there was that
Reagan's America
Like that movie there's a lot of movies kind of like that
Where
Now cuz I was like
Watching
Do you mean movies or video
Doughboy
What are the things to do that I did hear guys
From the UK
Yeah America's McMahon your movies
Really
You can tell like
All about Trump
I'm sucking General
There's a lot of political
Are movies are real
Are you receiving those like I mean there's no genre videos that is just people react
Someone in our f****** Facebook group and I'm sounding angry only because of the time I've wasted
Someone posted videos
Posted was Irish people watching Alex Jones
And I was how quickly they saw through like what is going on here
Them people outside of our primary culture are able to be like
My God this is
We don't we don't
Recognized as easily
I think you're totally right
Holyshit
Can be about
Like I think art can reflect
What's going on in
Society
Set timer
But then there is people over the head with it
That would be the case of like
That Snoop Dogg video where he puts a gun to
Come on in Austin and Vince already did that but yeah there are those
So that's a thing where it's like when it's 2
Yeah it's like I like
Maybe
Reading later or watching later
Supposed to be
This person
Like get it
I'm Trump
Yeah I know
So far so good Piper
That's like
The first planet
Which is about
Then
In the second Planet of the Apes
Yeah I guess they don't really get to what happened until right
Is where they have like the ape hippies getting rounded up and it's like
Now we're getting a little too the first was so subtle
And cool racism stuff like that
Ahead with it
The third one
Which is where they go
Back in time
0 in Cornelius
Time to the beginning of a monkey beginning of it all
They had this Bay riot and everything
There's a documentary the documentary
About
All the time
Is Wendy's
Happy anniversary
Of the original
Was so good
And
Caesars
Is like the new leader
Now we
Planet
They said when they test
They tested it in a
Black
Neighborhood and black
Parade near me
And they're like oh no this is
House right
So they recut it
And of course they were denied a lot of money
A close-up of
Caesars eyes
And they got the guy at the exit.
Comeback Migos
We're at
But
We can do this with humans also
Together
And we will share this planet
Am I Batman that falls apart
Clock yeah but it's like that thing of the difference of the first one
Perfect prey
Ape hippies like
That's the same thing as like
I still like all of them
Mark Wahlberg
I hope you're happy
I walked I worked at a movie theater when they came out at the time it was our tradition
We're underage
It was one of the only ways we really have life
Screen all of the movies
Before they came out
Get belt getting built
If
There was open theater anyone could sign up to watch it
To make sure
Directions to put it through where all of us
Some of our managers were over 21 and so they buy us food and we just have parties
Publix 1718 at the time
Just getting drunk
Pre-screening these movies about some bad
Oh s*** the worst was Mark Wahlberg
With Arnold Schwarzenegger
We all almost like left
But one of our managers Rick
Watched
Because he loved the old man video
She was a little older
Late 20's
At that time
A-Team
Who are all the girl drinking having a great time and then at the end
When Mark Wahlberg comes back
Back to Monument Memorial
I'd like if it's an ape's head of the building
As soon as you see
30 40 seconds until you get inside and
Call Mike f
Bucky was a f*** a WCW show
Represent
We already hated it but that was a bridge too far
But
Alright
So
Monday Night Raw
Lincare in costumes
Yeah
Do they put someone over to help somebody
God
I feel like there's no way that couldn't have been defensive somehow whoever they choose to have the 8
Oh God don't Vincent and Andrew Sobek
Nation of David Mark Henry
No don't make the storyline
No Limit soldiers were in the wcws
Was hanging around that was a fun thing where
The bad guys
Turn up
What does Rey Mysterio in Conan without piano
Animals
Master
I thought
I didn't think he was
The world
I don't think he was either
They signed
Some guys that were in his
Brutalx
Big money
Is 1 black
Mike's
Swole
If that was a recording artist
And then
The opposition
Was this group called The
The west Texas rednecks
It's a great song If
If you want to find
Call.
Rap is crap
Barry Windham
Junior
They got a song
Cuz rap rap song is a part of their Feud with no limit soldiers
Got over and the crowd loved
Ended up being crazy
Water park
People are not
Russell get paid
Cheese
So all this is to say that
Rowdy Roddy Piper this is like my favorite and my worst topics
Because then we just go
I think that's when they hire
Respective
Hot rod
I think you can retain it because of like probably got tricked but
He's kind of like
Hey however I can get the word out I think you should save those judgments I think he's kind of stupid but at the same time
Because he's on Infowars
It kind of does highlight how like he is kind of stupid he's not as bad as the world's used
He also
Claimed that when he
He painted half
His body black
Tell Russell bad news Brown at Wrestlemania
Sure
I believe it
He was moonwalking and doing those
Stayin Alive
So at this point you said that they live is about Reaganomics
Based on
When
We shot the scene
Respect
Oh really
That's interesting because you made a film about Reaganomics
So I'd like to talk a little bit about that
Quite frankly one of the reasons that homelessness is such a big issue and it's so devastating
Husband is because of Reagan
His policies
Directly the situation that we have on our hands
John Carpenter and Rowdy Roddy Piper made a movie about Reaganomics
I think maybe he doesn't understand all that too well
I thought
It was interesting growing up
Cuz I'm
When I grow up
Reagan was
The man trike right
Funny and cool
Cute jacket the movie with a bunch of garbage
Idiot
Stop
Speeches and everything
And then
Rock music
Batteries
Good man you read a few things I don't know
A 1981 on the heels of economic downturn unemployment was super high
Rockford Illinois had a real unemployment rate of 25%
Three states had unemployment rates / 14
At the depths of the
The number was still just around 10% Nash
It was bad it was really bad people were out of work
Having a bad time
Noticing that there were tons of unemployed people becoming homeless solution that was not a solution
He didn't want the government to do anything but instead suggested the quote every church and synagogue would take in 10 welfare
The problem
Because he was stupid
And thought the entire idea of homeless people existing was a temporary notion it would go away with the economy got better
This is a stupid plan
For one reason because churches and synagogues are not magical entity
If you just required to take intense which could easily be 5:45
People that's going to cause a bump to their overhead
In times in homelessness Rose churches getting bankrupted like crazy
Just trying to provide the health of the government should be providing its citizens
Reagan solution is not Solutions pathetic attempt we shouldn't help that person it's someone else's job
To make matters worse
Reagan would slash the budget for the Department of Housing and Urban Development Department most likely to help
Reagan's entire platform to boil down to
Insisting that this isn't my job
Cutting funding for programs that are desperately needed in order to lower taxes
All the rich
Cuz I was the primary motivation
And then the final step blame the victims of his policies for the policies affect
He famously popularized the idea of a Welfare Queen
Based on a complete lie
I recommend everyone go listen to the episode of the dollop
Is that a character
The episode of the doubt they did live in Chicago
The me and Jordan are actually at
Great time they lay out the history of the idea of The Welfare Queen
F****** outfits
It's outrageous
How much deceit was behind it
Respect up
Good Morning America and said the people sleeping on Grayson
Mistreat we're doing it by choice
That homeless guy
Get the numbers
I was a kid I remembered that sort of
They're making a figures out there
Right
Airtight bag
If you worked at Captain D's
All your clothes smell like fish
Do you think you want that
Yeah it's the same uniform
Cheap clothes
America everywhere homeless person sleep should have Ronald Reagan
Peter dreier in urban policy analyst
And the director of the urban Environmental Policy Department at Occidental College in Los
I saw medication how little Reagan gave a s*** about this stuff
Article in the nation
Quotes early in his presidency at the White House reception the only black member of his cabinet
Housing and Urban Development secretary Samuel
Pierce saying quote
How are you mr. mayor I'm glad to meet you how are things in your city
Holyshit
There's my African-American right there there he is
Salsa
Wrestling
Vincent Vincent trumpet
They were having
Meeting
With all the
And
What they were talking about
House heater change
Michael Tarver
He raised his hand to ask
Question
But raises
Excellent question shelter
No longer with the company
Also the reason I thought I recognized that name is cuz of
That's why I thought
Tarver is not a common name
I also this is from San Francisco
Run decoration in 1966 the international Covenant on economic social and cultural rights
At the UN member nations including the United States permanent member of the UN Security Council
Agreement that recognize the right of everyone to an adequate standard of living for himself and his family
Including housing
Go to us-92 3D to send it never ratified it making America Wanted only to UN member states to fail to ratify
Along with Tyler
The u.s. is either failed to sign
Or failed to ratify at least six other International treaties
In which housing was declared a human right
To come out very clearly and clear I believe it it
Yeah I believe it's
A bus stop bench
The little loud
Forward
Pigs everywhere
There's a lot of places.
Spiky thing
The under passes
They got the
Down
Thought it's crazy but it's someone's job to argue for that
City planner
Park bench
Razor blades
Megaman comfortable
And when we were down there in the downtown area
There is a lot of
I've ever seen in my life
Walking down the street
There's an area where there was
Luca is clearly place around
Wasn't that
Weird to me those kind of like this is very sad and I feel bad about
We should be doing better
That was sort of like I seen
Stuff like that before
Yeah we walked a little bit further
And there's a huge company
Modern ornate building
And then if you got the look
Right in front of you
On the planter does it someone passed out
Almost
Naked
Did the juxtaposition of this giant
Billion dollar building
Someone
Sleeping in their planter just made me so f******
Depressed maybe so sad
Empathy knowledge that we
Can fix
Everybody's problem
But the idea that people are sleeping on the street it's something we
We absolutely can't fix our priority
This was a thing where
DC
And then like
Two blocks away
Nightmare
Episode
Hear about that you care about his
Lack of a response to
Hy-Vee
Not like a response
This cruel
For how was it
Pitch to you that
They all grown up I heard a lot of
I always like people who live in the
They all have
Giant TV I'll have cable
$500 a week
Just like you hear all this
And I'm just
A documentary
Oh that's a nightmare
Oh no
I think you know
I don't know I haven't thought this out too much to stop
Come up weirdly
I think that's the comfortable illusion that people have to have in order to not
Have to fix the
You know because of everybody was really aware of how people
Undercover Boss
Sure so did the people who want
To like
Cut taxes on corporations and the rich
Strip welfare program
Write your writing in the same way that right now we have the two versions of like
What's going on with these people immigrants
At the border with Mexico you have one version which is like
They're all
Which doesn't take into account the idea that a lot of them are people seeking
Sure
Which is not illegal in any way coming illegally or whatever
That is a
Not a not a crime really that's why a lot of our families came here
Wait there's that to the other version which is even crazier version which
Much closer.
Is that like
They're actually human traffickers
Yeah how to create these illusions
Do false realities Justified
In both cases
Is a function of white supremacy
Suck on the welfare cheat
Vantablack
They're coming here not working
Which which one is it
It's got to be one
Like you'll go on I kind of like I told you
Taking a little bit of
Media diet
I'm not really
But
Either you'd watch those videos of like
Republicans talking about
Supreme Court judges
You know it's like horseshit
The idea of telling a Republican or someone on the right there being hypocritical is pointless
Could Rogers
No I'm not
And you're wrong he never never never show your ass
Fart on somebody
Crazy
You're you're you're you're lying about my ass being asses don't exist
Doll
Battle singing
Dick Cheney
How much money
Is enough
You're like
People are dying
But this Halliburton
How much is enough
Money
You want to be like the
King
Where have all the money
If I was
It at one of these like Elites in the United
I would
I would be liked
Like what you want
Instead of me having
4 billion
Maybe I'm Leo
YouTube then
People around me are living
Let's go.
Stages
Far off
Reality
I think she recognized I think Alex is really clunky job of expressing
Expresses in a little bit
We can't possibly understand the motivations of people on high or low
For you and I you don't know what it's like
Fracture making those two
Decisions in A Few Good Men
The truth
Tough decision
Although I do think there's something to that
What I mean Boris and I
In terms of money we just want
Where are the game that we're playing
We want to get by
You get married and have kids
Hey you never know
Level which is like I need to have a house yet
Becomes like
Can I help them through college whatever
Version it is in your head
And then there's another level above that which is like business ownership probably
And then there's a level above that which is Dynasty build
I want
No one that ever comes from my loin
To have to work
Hell I want Rockefeller money
Right that'll last for Generations
Great-great-grandfather Mart
If some of that comes from money so it comes from great
Big
So like I said there's a decent chance that even with
Predict ain't much of a monster as he is
As much damages he caused
I think there's a possibility that somewhere deep within his dark
Robotic replaced
I think there's a possibility that he believed that by doing really really terrible thing
He could reach a positive outcome
Which might be breaking some eggs to make an omelet
Maybe
I don't want it I don't want to say that excuse is right
And then
You come out the other side you forgive all of the Innocents that I killed in order to have this
As I was watching
Documentary
Want to do
Thursday
You just like
She was
The ark
True Arc
You understand
They're all just sit on it
Imma throw this out there
What if
That was a
So I had a friend
Right
BB cream
How did Freddie Prinze jr.
Freddie Prinze
They're all sit Round Table
Ideas
I won't say who the
No need to put people's business on the streets
Imma throw this
I might
What if
Mark Henry anime
Hit in the head
We find out later
Great weekend
Does Michael Symon say this
Your delivery on that was strong
Whoa
Yeah that's
That would probably
Big Ben fine
At some point though
Oh you probably gave birth to a hand
98 but I am
Getting back to what we were talking
I think there is sort of this this
Fang of like
The feel powerful the elites
Fairlife
Ron Reagan Jr
You know
He's he's at Becky
Commercial from about 8
These are you sick of people talking about God
Groceries
He's obviously liberal
But
Especially to
You're growing up here
I've been the coolest dude
Love you let's go through that
We're going through with Rowdy Roddy Piper
I'm so sorry
This relapse faith in the hot rod you probably will as well
Nexlab
It was where I was
Maybe he doesn't know what show he's on
Unfortunately this clip
Cuz I feel like this all the time
Left control going on
The signal broadcast 24 hours a day
Lunch
Taking care of America
Husband was going on
That hurt while what was going on
Doing
Concussions while that also
Yeah I blame
People turning
Radeon
To Alex
Oh yeah
You and I are even examples of people without like
Close examination of Alex we're like this
Like we didn't think he was too big of a problem as we tonight and I think Rowdy probably
Identify
Or feels a bit of a kinship with them in the sense of like he's a showman just like me
You know
And back in the 90s Roddy Piper did extensive battles
Ric Flair got together Powers over nobody
Who's that when he had tried to get a family together
Piper try and fight the nwosu
And then head to I get the player right
That worked a very very
Group together
Got the No Limit soldiers
A lot of faction Warfare back in the day
Here
I was really bummed out
Alex
I love you
Friend
He's been he's known Alex for like 20 years they went back
Broken because Rogan
Joe also is like
This is
Really stupid with Alex's about Anthony Bourdain suicide
Like
Pedophile ring news about to come out
Say all this f****** awful
F****** cowardly
Is B Rogan is now being like I love this guy but you need to calm down
Like your rhetoric is terrible your rhetoric is irresponsible and it's
Eating lots of people program you like
I'm sorry
I love this guy he's my friend I'm sorry that I had him on my show
Milo
Thing of like
I'll give anybody talk and it's like
We're going to have a conversation
You should have all of the clips of Ted Nugent
Stuck on his gun yeah yeah
This is crazy for saying about Trump videos of Ted Nugent
Bear bear bear
I'm I'm an observer I'm also tired
Responsibility
Eddie Bravo
Probably
Yes
You keep your crazy in a box you don't allow these horrible horrible people
To be exposed and not like his audience doesn't know who Ted Nugent
When you have a 2-hour conversation with a person
Humanizes them and allows you to be
Like surrogates
I love Joe Rogan
And I don't know what who a lot about Ted Nugent
Amicably cartoon have 3 hours I'm going to come away from it like
Here's a here's an example of it
When I used to listen to Loveline all the time
Yeah first of all I thought Adam Carolla there was a
Lie about that
He trains
But also
John Mayer
And if for some reason I liked John Mayer's because he was on love
That you have when you are a charismatic popular figure who interviews people for long periods of time
Like long as it says
Take a short
Super edited interview
It's really really dangerous to not
Respect and understand your responsibilities you have
And the fact that Joe Rogan just like
I love Alex Jones he's got a calm down
I think he's not dealing with the idea that like
I am a part of this
I didn't have to be I have introduced
Millions
The people to Alex
Mega Million but yet
Those people probably already knew who he was but he's doing that thing
But also
He allowed Alex sound like he was talking about
Anyway
You should have pushed back all this
To expose the Alex
You're lying to me again
Yeah because he loves him
Really really f****** dangerous
No unfortunately
Rowdy Roddy Piper
Also
Matt Bomer
The next
Rowdy Roddy Piper says something
This is a kind of tell you that needs to be
Rowdy
So Alex is smiling like the cat just ate the canary like he is over the moon when he says that
Rowdy Roddy Piper man is he's rebellious by Nature
What Alex thinks he meant is that he thinks that the South was right
In the Civil War
Because that's what Alex thinks when he talks about being a rebel
That is without Alex
Oh s***
Rowdy right on.
I don't think Rowdy Roddy Piper
I'm rebellious okay
The system Allen
I believe in the South will rise again
F****** Piper is from Canada
Okay
But like that to me was like a moment or like oh no
Oh no Alex
I think you should have asked a follow-up question there
You ear your moron Alex
Galaxy
Does a guy who I know this 100
For surviving Alex of the guy who can
Fit whatever you say
Hyperbole
That's
Because otherwise there would be no reason to be like
Can you believe he's born Rebel
Cuz of course he is
Anybody walk the beaten path in life
Iconoclast in many ways
Surprise me
I know
Hundred percent
I'm certain that definitely isn't
A mind control
Society
Putting stuff
Major conspiracy for a new world order
Myhumboldt
Rowdy
So couple things really quick Piper is trying to become something is important
Thought
Back to it later
But
The most important hyperboles in the New World Order
Second
Alex just displayed there
Is
Trademark Alex Jones
Whenever his guest says he cuts them off that one
Be like what I mean is reframes exactly the same questions
They were about to answer in order to cut off their thoughts and make be like
All the f****** time
He wasn't going tonight it's not like master
One of those like
Some YouTube
And one was that
Ted Turner
Created the end
Distraction
Real
Sure austerity mention his son
Colton
A cabana one time
Colton Colton
What cult was just what Piper calls her son
Piper texted
I love you and I'm so proud of you
I wish you was sitting at for real to me but he just wrote him back
Oh man anybody who's named
Close to me
Configure your other comedy cohort Don Friesen
Now I've only gotten prank messages
But I do agree
I tell you what I was on a website
Information
Oh yeah
It was really close to having him on the podcast
Is this close
Our friend worked with him a couple times
Tell him
I think John Friesen B of emails
The one I remember to is
What like
Family
Here on the Pike
Alex
Buckley his cousin no no no it was a
Who's one of the big
Do the yeah
Yeah
Malicious the interview Tacker
It's not what you need exactly whenever you're cutting them off you have a clean enough
Right battles the NWO
So most people don't catch on to it cuz if I were that I would get
. well you know there was going to WrestleMania
Morton Downey jr.
Kept interrupting Rowdy Roddy Piper
Rowdy
Had enough of it in like that he said don't blow no smoke in my face
And then he got a fire
Piper
I respect you and what you doing in Sean
Educated
I don't want to
Have to go someplace
So he keeps
Roddy Piper
Sir themes themes
To Beaver like the world
Yeah
I completely agree with
Sort of nefarious
Forces behind I would agree with that but I would refrain
Capitalism regulation
Business
But those sorts of things
Crushing
In about like
What they are
But we could agree on the concept that like yes
Nothing is static the world is constantly
Sort of a picture
What he and Alex
I think they want one
Governmental Force
In the world
If everybody's got their own
You can get that unless he's around
Natural
I don't I'm not very sure I would have been able to create a 1/2 government
But that
We can get everybody on the same page another ideas
Rowdy Roddy Piper loves brush
First point
Yeah the people that people are
Papa
Pop-up is in charge over there
Iris
He's talking about going to Russia
For his career and life
I would say
Send send
Has been
Power and he's a bad dude
Love the strongman
You think I would
Question
Do you think
People in foreign countries
Like do you think people in Bulgaria really love Russo
What do you think that the Russians back then actually like
Nick Hood
Nikita, I'm sorry
Nikita Koloff
Colog whatever
Look I don't like wrestling as much as you do
I know a bit of stuff but I don't know everything
Wait
I have no idea why they were so popular in Israel the people
Do they like these fake version I even Bulgarian about title T-shirt with a story
The Bulgarian Brute
The fake version Lake do people in Mexico like
Alberto Del Rio when he was in WWE
Mexico
Wrightwood
Russian Felix
Yeah
Me
You know it wasn't me
What is is bad
Irish people love
He's a legend
Absolute
I meant some of them probably
What is well-loved
Citizen X when I was picking up but like
Line between Lexington
Rotten who used to do a British
Character accent everything.
Over there
Do countries hang their hat on
Maybe inoffensive portrayal of them just to see representation I don't know
Russia almost never Italian Muhammad Hassan
He's Italian
Mark copani
That was his name
But you know
Or elected
Like when
At 8
The robot Johnny 5
Yeah I know you're talking about
Yeah short-circuit at 2
Then you came up with
Congratulations. It's like
Black people enjoy
I don't think so
I would imagine it we're getting to it
But
Getting white women appreciate
Do you think babies enjoy the little man
Don't cry
White Chicks
Anderson
At no point
Had to be the guy doing a bit
I don't know I don't know if I trust
Garbage
Try to make them
The white women that they're supposed
Make the white women
Makeup look more like these
Guys look
See now that's an interesting that's an interesting ideas for them to have done it
But I don't believe that if music movie critic would do that kind of a review without
Most of it being an existential crisis
Greater movie
George
YouTube YouTube Red
No
But I'm in man
Every
Your savable
I accidentally watched I knew the names written
How are they
They put it out there
I have nope there's there are
Certain people and I it's not a jealous thing
I'm not
I wish them all the best in the world
But there's certain people
Who I'm just like
How are you how like what is happening
How was he selling out the Chicago Theater like
Like five nights in a row I don't understand
Much more than written
Rihanna
Twitter logo to the news
It's turning whatever they'll be like
You know what YouTuber
Tabitha Smith
Shutdown
50000 people showed up
Who are you
Children
I don't know what I want to complain
No I'm not saying he's not funny
Yeah I'm just saying
How is it like we're more your thought is like the Chicago Theatre is cute that's my retina
I never watched a couple of them as their personalities to be
Not like I hated the flashlight
Anybody would watch these boring a bunch of different types of like sodas
I get that format
Sure I get it
How it has 8 million
Viewers
Even make it
1million I don't understand
Tableau's whereupon you can paint whatever you'd like to be there so you can just imagine whatever character is there you are
All that stuff is fine I get I get that
What I don't understand
Is
They
Have
A f****** laugh
Track
The people who are making that show
The people behind the scene
Are literally standing around while they're recording it and there's a gas leak in that f****** Studio
Talk Soup
Yeah
It's so uncomfortable I was watching one of my
What the f*** are these laugh like they're saying things that aren't really that funny and
Laugh track
Yeah it's even like
I haven't watched
Sitcoms that comes in a long time and I love old shows
Are there a bunch of shows that I love you
Suck
It might hurt my possibilities with career advancement
Who cares we're not on YouTube
I don't know man very very weird
The world shirt circuit tester
Good things on YouTube
Kidtastic Lovett
Will be watching that bud
Piper was complaining about the language
The currency part which is
To the next one
Where do I bleed
Real quick something
He's presenting that is a
Bad thing
What is trying to happen
The world is trying to change into
I believe
Government
Govern the entire world
Absolutely because you can have the Star Trek idea
The problem is the people running
Control
What
Alex's Alex's
I agree but here's why that can't happen
Version that's like
What
I feel like
Alex
I think that would be cool but
But no matter who was trying to make that sort of centralized power structure you be like
The idea that he's open to the idea of One World Government just not this one world government
Is like
What
That's so different than what he normally says
B a b
Ludacris
Piper sing a one world government structure
Contextualize thing in the first clip he did
Is trying to grow
But it lasts maybe a One World Government
What are they talking about
About everything
Probably at 8
Probably used
You're right
One world order
What's a good one Alex
White
Graphic colonel
There's a lot of examples over the years that I've been able to completely and validating his own principles
Do you think when
This is so fun
Fired or resigned
Who is the Breitbart
If
Everybody
Call Alex
If Alice
There's no way he was going to Special Report immediately
That would be a
He's dumb as the day is long but he's a good kid
David Knight I'll keep them in order
Yeah I think you cared
Everyone else
I think if you could dummy the
Sending number you know like make it look like it's coming from d.c.
Alright
Someone to do like a Steve pieczenik
Compression
The president
What's up I think
Scouts knows what Jared Kushner or Steve Miller sound like
She could have someone doing impression of either of them it could sound like you were I would really matter
Refresca
It's me Jared Kushner
My father-in-law in a minute
My father-in-law really like that
Propagate.
Dad is always impressed
Dad's always
No Daddy
Daddy
Always thought your
Smartass
Alonzo you're trying to rehabilitate
Career of Milo yiannopoulos
Love that you love white people so much
What happened
But are you
Willing to shave
Even if you would have been like are you willing to grow
Ground a bed for a while
I only know that threat because I
You literally hated link
Yep he has zero personality
And I want to put him in a walker
Crazy people triggered like my boobies
Two big dogs
I'm not really but like
I'm glad I know who they are and
And I've also wondered
How there I have a good research I like
Was like how or why did Google acquire
Popular
It's one of those
Cuz we were in on the ground floor did it everyday I guess I meant their stuff like hot ones that I think is really great
2 million View
I understand why people watch this
And there's other things that I don't
I get it
Yeah
There's also a lots of boring
Holyshit
Maybe you don't want to hear about lizard people
Absolutely
So next clip
Man
So at this point Piper is just been stupid in the sense that like he respects out
I was so excited
Either she was going to have Vince Russo and
For a long time
You're a cancer in the wrestling business right
Because of you own heart died
Heavy duty shed
I thought about it you're a daddy
You're trying to provide for
You're just trying to provide for your children and I got no beef
Sounds like
It was his baby built it up and everything
Your daddy
The same time it's kind of adult
No
Ducksters
The only thing is that he respects our
Sure unfortunately he's going to say something
That is a vegetable
It all it all stars
For the kids
Piece of music that made
Early 60s
The people that bought it
Got to go to work and come back home
TV
Commercial came on and made you buy
Early sixties
How sophisticated they are now
Holyshit
Oh man
What do you think about that
I think
I think the hot rod
The Conspiracy to
Do you know what the Brunswick Affair is
Is the television show
That was
It was like the Twilight Zone
Okay this episode is a mockumentary types
Style TV program
It came out that talks about TV sets that were put out in the 60 okay
That is not true so he's talking about this mockumentary
For real
It's like a Twilight Zone episode
Reality interesting ideas during something before
1/4
Message
Sure
Advertising is an ethical practice
But what specifically what he's talking about
And it's nonsense because the dates don't match up
In order to avoid getting sued they change the name
From the like of the Brunswick
Radio and TV
Creative license
I don't know but that's actually really famous example of absolutely
Brunswick but what the f*** you talking about
Popstar
He said these new pop stars come out and say dirty things
What did you do for professional wrestling
But I think I think Rod is a guy who probably saw
Some
Pop star Illuminati videos
Anime I think they probably I think he's a guy who is the one eye covered devil horns
Baby goes to vigilantcitizen.com guys who were so
While back in the day or now what
Except that you did
Forever
Maybe not Rowdy Roddy Piper
Hellboy
The map
Alex Andrade talk about like
They've gotten into like a bit of a conversation where they're like
But nothing's really been said
What do you mean
Put this dinner
The same page all is like Alex
So amazing about
No
I didn't know that
She's right by Pacific
What did she say
Because she didn't want to fight that Transit
I believe she said she wasn't
I don't want to get this wrong
So
But besides that she's
Fantastic professional wrestler
She's really I'm not sure she walked some of that back that I think it's some of the same thing except she's
She seems like she's very dumb like unfortunately
I think
Enzo and big Cass
Both big trumper's
Well for other reason reasons
Shut the door
Previous tax in Outlook
This picture big Cass with these giant fake titties
I love that
I have to go out there who don't have access to a text chain
And I sent him a photo of pecans
Diane Twitter would always do
Gigantic
Nipples
Breast
Very gross which is why I didn't respond anyway
It's very weird necessarily I don't I don't know all of Rousey's issues fight
Kind of like when you
Here like an act
Or musician
Yeah I had that with Jason when I was like 9 or so
Texas
They change it
Pilot inspektor
We get that there's a chance
To allow that on the direct
In with all the
DirecTV
Tremendous
Overlook brokers
Keto slim waist in 30 days
Hobby works
Yeah they could broadcast on
For free
Cuz we nice
Sign up for a minute or something I don't know
Portland
Was that mean
Michelle
Police Department
24-hour there live on the
Cops but like
That's like
That is an
Marty that's the evolution of weirdo sitting around listening to police scanner
I knew a bunch of those guys my first house that I lived in
Not I didn't have one but
My neighbor my first house
Dad said one of them was a Vietnam vet the other had stolen valor all day long
Yeah it so I would go over to their house
Lost his arm
Made me think of a really long time
Talk about how bad it wasn't told me how he lost his arm until like 6
They crashed his car and lost his arm
So you got a Purple Heart
Ed was a disaster
So I would go over their house
Like it was
Just like a lot of the time my friends were in school jobs
Edina dad wherever they're hanging out
Edema be like 81
Bring over some
Alright
I got you so I bring up some blunts and we sit around and smoke tell me about
And also he always
Police scanner
And I f****** enjoyed the s*** out of it although it was Columbia Missouri where there were no crimes happening
Missouri
They're all over the place
But watching it live Police Department
The country in their check
Go back to that
Man who was pulled over for
It's all black people
We are watching
They clearly are
Crazy white people
Is it 24 hours
Hibbett was
Here today
First of all
We get we need to find you somebody goes to sling
Sling TV
I actually auditioning for a commercial
Isaac why do I know that name
With the rat with the rats
I put life
Right there's a
A life
Live PD
Another one
Armenia's going slow internet
I honestly feel like
To overcome baggage
As Lakers
It's so much
So Friday and Saturday night I need to come over
Apparently
People.
They just don't have ID
Well that becomes probable cause
Continue mccoppin
Yeah
Okay what's your name
It took you awhile
That took you a little bit too long I belittled what's your last name
Why do you need my last name is Marty your Christian or the guy goes when's your birthday
When's your birthday
How old would that make you
And they always do.
You be honest with me
Goes a long way
You got anything in the car they like
No
And there's a Tornado Launcher guns in the car
Stop
Lightish
It's live-to-tape or whatever but it's not like
The show is happening
It can't be so boring for me
They know how to jump around
And some of it is boring that's why you watch the rewind that's
There was this guy who was evading the cops
This guy
Was such a good driver it was like Dukes of Hazzard like
Like this f****** guy
Of course.
It's like the cop version and the guy passengers got his hands on
I just got the wrong car
Squaring the situation
Just say
IForce
Just put your hands out the car window another charge
And this guy was
Just like
The back bumper
Flipper
Couldn't do it now bump this guy tracks out the tracks out and just
Maven
I notice a lot of people that I follow unfollow
That was sweet about it
This is like
Interesting thing that I'm experiencing now is like someone who is just like
Completely out of it
There are shows like that is exactly what I want to watch
Wait for you baby
There are times where I feel bad cuz it's all mostly poor
And most cops ever
I think there's kind of a gross
Voyeurism
Almost all of those shows are like My Strange Addiction
Water
Is Trainwreck O's
Was there an iWatch
Borders for a little bit
Apple watch
And then it just got sad
And then they just
Couch and pulled out a day
Oh no that was like
As hard as a book
Hey we got a dead cat
Dislike how do people live
Sort of world
I meant
With the cop stuff at
The horror is
Presumably the protagonist of the show
Are the characters of the show
So you're watching it and you're like oh my God
You're seeing all these people get arrested really f***** up situations
An awesome life is usually
Pretty good PR
Cops
It shines
Pretty positive light
But every wants to make every once in awhile
What what
This one I'm still bad
But there's so many people who aren't like pull this guy over
Republic sky over there in Durham
So
Lakefront from like Indiana Illinois
Do not like
So
Can I grab Indiana
Illinois
Oh yeah
They pulled the sky over hypothetically
Demon in Illinois
I need an Indiana plate
Play
And he's like I live in Indiana
In Illinois
Play
How do you search them if on a bunch of drugs
Wow that's
I just saw
In Minnesota
Hundreds of pounds
But the judge threw it out
No
That's what b******* about it you should still have that
We're going to get back to you
Yeah 10 minutes to get out of here
I think that's exactly what they should do
We could we pulled you over under false pretenses that eyebrow we have to create exact
You were in before we stopped you I love a good fun
Boston life
PD like when they
That's my wife and they separate
Harmless
Hey Google turn a
Shotgun wedding
I don't know
Alright maybe
I feel like there's a lot of harm the alarm
Good clean fun
Real life
I'm so happy you're going to
We're going to set a date I'm coming over to watch
Friday's record
Well it's Saturday
Recorded
Watch Friday
When do next week
I don't know
That's why I love it
Cancel your gigs coming over on Saturday
I'll deputize
Alright sounds good
Our next episode
Thorough review
Watch this
It's terrible as a problem but like
The idea of watching it live does trigger that like I said listen to the police scanners when you're younger
But the only thing
Against
Is the
Sort of the excitement and fetishizing
The cops doing
I think I think entertainment value is fine
Product
For five years
Parked
Ostomy
But poor black
What's not working I'm going to walk away
And then
TV
And then they would grab it
In the back of the
Charges would never stick
That's absolutely never fly in court
If I were in that neighborhood
I probably wouldn't if I saw a semi with it
F****** well wouldn't look inside Fair
Realized
Stuff you can get away with
And like stuff
Walking down the
There's no crime
Or like if they're in their house
How's your husband
Just real drunk
Can you please just
What you doing
Lick man
Got to go to bed
And it's like so fun at like sometimes a cop's job is it to go to a house
Go to Vatican what time is work tomorrow
7:30 in the morning
You're never going to make it
I guarantee I make it to work I guarantee it
Kanal D I'd love to watch that
But not
Not because that guy is drunk right now is hilarious
Terrible
Your job is to try and give good advice
And she swore her boyfriend was
Under the floor
Her ex who cheated on her
Who's under the
People are in the floorboard of their in the wall very common delusion
Now the only thing I would say
Important
Is that most of these people were having these like drunk delightful experiences with the tub
Are white
And people who
A charismatic black
I would say that the number of times black people get jacked up insurance
It's not going to be on live PD
I would hope you would not be shot
But
You do sometime from watching life
Some of the
Distress
Pressure that job
Come on
No dude I'm serious
They're just like
Freight
There's no way you don't think that's what you're signing up for a zygote for sure I know if you can do that with
Then don't f****** but I'm not saying that I'm just saying there are times when you're like
And look man
If
I was a different cop you might have gotten shot here
Like I do
20 years
I know I know
What to do
But s*** man like dude I almost had to shoot you
Look at you keep running after gun shoot
Probably should shoot
You can't do that
Like what are you doing
A postgame after I saw you running at me
I love
Dog Bounty Hunter all the time
How are you doing
I like
Yeah I thought of
Those caught in a career
All right so far
So it's interesting actually that talkin about
Cop show for as long as
Because
Alex like I said
Alex and Piper have been having conversation about like
Why does why does everybody else not feed
Glasses
Alex
Something
Live PD
Taking my shower
Can I think you just answered my question there that I said at the beginning of the break
Who makes those of us that are immune or resistance
The program
We grew up as individual
Grew up in had a brush with the streets
It was a lot of fights a lot of corrupt police government drug dealing
A lot of police running hookers you name it and I grew up
Watching this going on in my neighborhood
I put the sunglasses on because I saw the other side
And saw how naive everybody
They want to get to use them down
Take it all a bunch of political correctness
Bulshit
You know how to make sandwiches
A cop pulled out
A cop busted Alex and his friends
Let's talk about that he started talking about I never seen white racism
I haven't felt like how human bodies were underage with beer in the car driving
Back from like a party at the beach like that
You kids have a good night
I'm like I was here just a few just described
Very clear white racism
Just because it didn't hurt a black guy cop again
No he's
Back then he's talking about the corruption.
They threatened to kill
Again Rockwall Texas
30/30 150
A bunch of research into his Dad recently
Was ever involved in any
He's been a dentist
Simpsons I like 1980 Something About no longer than that
He he claims that he was a dentist to some CIA agent
And that's sort of the closest
You can get to anything substantial but
Man there was this there's his dad his dad
We know that because two employees of sued him for EEOC
And his dad had to go on record as the person who runs resource department
How do you say
Hey look
The locker room here tirement
F*** you lock her up
Sometimes Rob do says she knows now I don't know
This is Robby Rob baby Rob
I just think I don't believe any of this
That's just stuff that the internet keeps repeating narrative
Alex Jones Mossad Israel
Or the government or something like that much simpler he's a two-bit also whites
He explains his entire career you don't need the intelligence
Who's being used by
For now the Press
The president of Russia also
I think that connection is much looser I think that what is Rodger Stone
Rodger Stone
You thinks he's very stupid
Yeah totally Isaac 2013
I know they met at JFK convention
I think that
A Rodger Stone probably immediately recognized
Very
Competent person
The stupid and compromisable
Rodger left Trump campaign
Propaganda outside realize Alex's perfect
And who knows if it was money or just being like nationalist
Further the goals that you
It's very clear that's what you're about
Do you think that stone white nationalist
I figured he doesn't have principles
Evan Gattis
I think it's a Chaos Agent like to the very definition
Nihilist
I didn't even care based on the people he buddies up
I don't think that
I think it'd be impossible to do that without being sympathetic to White nationalism and white Superman
But I don't know
From
There's such a trend of like
It seems like he's f****** around that like
I feel like he just like I'm certain he's got a deal
Are you just doing this
Well yes of course I did talk to that guy like that sort of stuff
That there's that there's a feeling of invulnerability
Did I don't get from a lot of other people
Want me
F*** the Democrats the f*** everybody
That's what that's what I get for
Chaos chaos chaos
I don't think he has any like hard-and-fast alliances to nationalism
The Russia to
Absolutely
In the same boat
So he's very competent
Like much of the Plains Indians
Does anyone in our boat hates to admit like that sort of thing but like I was an amazing podcaster
Sky
He's really good at propaganda
He finally
Ghost
You know again
Trump
What do you want to know
They could be using to be like the guy
You can wear
Lucky Luciano
Where was the first flip
I don't think it'll ever come to that
Cuz I don't think you need that kind of information
Rodger prison
Now
I think it's got a deal
I'm almost certain he's got a deal
Part of the deal
I'm going to cut this
Is deal part of the deal
I cut this deal to Argentina
I'm going to
Be doing a podcast
Not just someone who keeps hot
Rodger ends up showing up on Infowars like in Indio
Might wanna be close to the Border
He seems like the kind of guy looking at movies
White suit
Indoor crowd
Like the end of that
But sounds
You can't you can't be like
He was known as a f****** s*** head
Potster
30 years ago
You can't survive this long without being like
Having EX
Exit strategies without having like an idea of what's going to happen
He's never been this much of a marquis
Key player in the things that are happening
Politically
I don't
Think that he wouldn't have an exit strategy in that power
Hey man
Looks like I'm going to go down for some of the stuff
So
You politician
Good word for me
Otherwise I'd hate
Let people know that me and my wife f*** you and your wife
Anyways
So at this point they got a call
Alright
Real Piper
Got Alex Jones
Friday big fan
Johnstone has been silent most of the time just sitting there a camera
Hey I'm friends
First Call
Is interesting because like I said most of the time that oxygen
Geeking out about they live
About they
And this caller
Alex is coming from
Phone calls Rowdy reputation calls
What kind of will in Georgia
Also really quick I want to just be clear Alex
Keeps calling him rowdy rowdy rowdy as his first name
It's very much like
Ahead
Thanks. That's a Great Movie Ride he did a good job true Ministry
I married into the Vape part of they live the control the New York la
Sodom and Gomorrah Access Hollywood Babylon
I need something my kids every morning on Saturday during worship service was that everybody wasn't part of their tribe
What's up giving animals cattle just like it said in the movie that that
Preacher
Your job brought up birthday for the message that's cheap fly to
Robin slavin kill
Call the Gentiles
America is our Focus has to be on the Creator
Name The Sovereign of the United States the creative universe
Questions or comments for our guest
Call
Like that is just a guy who's regurgitating the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Children work
Taught that in some sort of synagogue or Sunday school because
They are the Jews
That is big
Pharrell is to pretend like this is
Exactly
Someone listen to my show
It was a Alex's at a bar
I want to make rap I want to do like rat and go pee
People who you've been helping
I think that was right thing to do
Get out of there
No these are your
Like
Listen man that's think of trump when he's at those rallies
Yeah yeah
You have people who are just like I've created a thing
Yeah I will deny, the consequences are three possible
I mean
I think that I think that some of that is unavoidable sure no matter what
Some people in it that are like
But I think it's probably 8%
Rarely
Yeah well he needs somebody
Oh my God
I'm such a huge fan of yours
Crazy
Airport bar
I mean we've met a couple people like a couple listeners
Chicago
I've gone and got some
Drinks with that other folks
Heather Mike Chris
All these people in like
I didn't think anybody was a
Yeah real monster anything
Sure I've met a bunch of people
Very happy to have drinks with them and hang a an instance where
Alex
Most of them
Partymarty was just writing on a piece of paper
The code name of someone
Possible problematic
Hey an apostle of Alex
But I will say watching it video
Was just like
Yes this is
What you
Creative
This kid and you're unwilling to
What reporter pointless question
If someone Works coming to me like that
Word like accurate representation
Thanks for opening my eyes to
Jews taking over
Talk to them for a bit and hope that I could correct some of those perception
You listen to Alex so I don't have to thanks for cutting out and just
Get to know is Messi
Sincerely try to like
See where the disconnect was yeah yeah
Federal out of this stuff there's nothing I can do maybe you should stop listening to my or something like that
Figured you might not get it
Yeah
But
The first one clearly
But Rowdy Roddy Piper
Piper has a slightly different
Take on it
Johnstone help thing
Dominatrix know where that story came from
Who they really are and it does he really believe
Who is this
They was the propaganda
Again I don't think the only
I don't think we're the only living
Universe
Big committees right now getting together and staying talking about
People bar excuse me
That detailed weather
Would not see that far
Maybe
It's literally
Alright
Go to
I don't know man like
So one caller is like it's of the Jews
Stone is like trying to fix a little bit
Who are they
Literal aliens
Blueface
What did you just drystar there
Just doodling a little
I thought that was some
For the first move
Perfect
Sure second one
That's terrible
Commercial
Pressure
Perfect
The main event
Maybe I don't know I think the opening just be like the revelation
Roddy Piper was on Infowars
Over and over again Gore Vidal was on Infowars
Henry Rollins
Not so much of a disappointment to any of us that Billy Corgan
Argues with Alex
I just great
Nah that's not
Alex
Here's why you're wrong
Also I've noticed
If you listen carefully to a lot of the piper
Yeah there's a number of like
Sound that he makes that are very Ventura
Don't have some similar vocalpad
Anyway
Probably
Serially from Scotland
Course
Rowdy Roddy Piper
Has an interesting response
Missouri
A gentleman and they lived at the underground tunnel system underground base system my question is
Some people think the Denver International is like the super secret
A Spaceport whatever you guys going to call her
Yes I mean I guess my question is do you think it's you don't like the movie they say it's almost like alien
Does that mean against Rowdy Oriental that's what does he think that you know so he put two and two together like that
You need to stand up against
Yesterday
After meeting
Variety
12 Rodney
Alrighty this is so disappointing
He watches a lot
It seems like maybe a lot of YouTube and machines and
Getting all the information medicinal marijuana
Blue horse
Also it's interesting that
Is that right
Blucifer
I think I saw
The time is up
Whatever the least was
Faulty Construction
Have you and I know because we didn't episode about this
That lead from a horrible situation into
A+ you for the future
The whole backstory
Elvis you can find
Donating to our podcast
Dollartree.com
2A
Secret secret underground portal that you can go where are
Conspiracy Charles locker room talk
It's such b******* man it's really disappointing
Like
You
For someone who's not a monster
Like Rowdy Roddy Piper
You hope that they would be the sort of person who wouldn't offer these things up without
To be sitting there and then like unprompted be like
There's not see things Denver Airport
Also did the Brunswick Affair is real New World Order is it is happening all this
Man that sucks
I mean Silva's Nino presumably very decent guy and it said
Wrestlers
Husband
Travel the world
These people travel the world
People who talk to them
Liquid coming back from Austin next to a lady on the plane was a sweet lady
Conversation through most of the flight
Like it was only like
40 minutes late to Houston about how her brother
I sent you a bunch of
Conspiracy stop and they have bonfires where he doesn't like
There's some sort of like maybe a little druidic acting out and stuff like that
Sort of like I met someone
Conversation
We've covered it repeatedly with Alex like
He's in a hot tub with a globalist globalist
I wish I was sitting next to Alex on a plane
Aldi's
And that we all had those stories
You know that's like your like f****** like
Stanhope whatever
He told me
Okay dude sure
Not you
F***** up
I don't believe that anybody we might like
Pakistan Hope Airport
Severely f***** up and also a magnet for other f*****-up people just like Alex wasn't video with that weird
Coming up to him being my guide
It doesn't exist in a vacuum
Attract
Euro sign
And if you are someone who's just like maybe a little bit
Maybe one impressum a little bit
There are so many possibilities I heard
The sky
I know the
Instead of I heard
Dentist
This guy
I'll just say I know
Hundred percent
Alex talks about
Having first-hand knowledge that they are our fish people in tanks with human faces
And stuff like that who heard it from somebody else
So it's a third-hand story to Alex
Third first-hand
Who knows who that person is
Steve Quayle ran into an airport or whatever
He's f******
Hours of the drunk
And from what I've heard
He's dumb
Joe Rogan's lovable little
From whatever to
Alex
Maybe less now but has been someone who
Is really into people approve of him
I am so like he would tell like
Lotto
Fish story the bars
And stuff like that
Number
A party of exactly everyone is like
We know like ever and rolling your eyes and
Party is been so fun I'm sorry to ruin or slightly tweaked your version of rowdy rowdy
Piper I have learned a long time ago
Weather FC
Hulk Hogan
Ric Flair
Boston's are
Call Jared ladies
I take these or not
People to People
At their job
You're able to separate art some artists
God
Stopwatch
Chris Benoit wrestler
You kind of have to to some extent I don't know where the line is necessarily but there is a line
There's a line
I think there's a line Benoit
Just recently I watch
You know what you know what if you murdered his family before
He was so great
Then you could never enjoy how Brady was
But because you already had washer and you had all those feelings
You never going to be able to get rid of those feelings
I don't know if that helps
And you know it
The wrestling business
It's a lot of
Trickery
Korean
You watch a lot of
Are you here a lot of these guys
Pieces this
That
You think this for twenty years that that's there that's the case
Just by virtue of
Doing the job so
Sobriety pepper the performer love them for the actor
They live
Worthy
Jesse Ventura
ABC pilot tag team on where they are
Pro wrestlers and
Undercover cops drop a reference to it at some point in an interview
I didn't know that him and Jesse Ventura would have ever actually been attacked
Indy wrestling
What does the timeline
Bodyslam
Is a great movie
Unfortunately
He's also kind of soup
NFL experts
Like he's a big like for everything
That's a couple hours ago when we were talking
I was like
You seem stupid
But in the world he's in the Infowars pool that he's in
It makes him. He doesn't seem like
He hates people he doesn't seems like
If you come in for Wars like looking like you're not a monster then
Tabassum
Not an educated man
Oakville High School no College
Prime
Prime for Alex to
You know
Knowledge
Why patient male of a certain age
Not educated
Owner of Infowars records
Bad guys
He's not Spider-Man
Hell yeah you know that
Nada.
80 Mansions at in the at the bar with alligator Spider-Man
This guy dresses up like Spider-Man on 63
Before
IParty with some like college friends
A certain point on the weekend and his horse cop 280
Years and when we were down there
He was actually really depressing
Because we had our show that started at like
Started
Whatever baby nine
Until we went down there early World 667
Grabbing a bite and like four people
Really drunk I was in New Orleans
That Bourbon Street I'm just like
I think like being day drunk is awesome it's fun don't get me wrong I'm not judging
Party Street
F***** up
Like sun's out
I don't know how
Are weak whatever and died
We're just like
Drinking
All day all night
Steak
Cococay
I guess they can back up go see some guys throw some graphs
You are
Little more cocaine
You know the magic drug
Facebook what I want to get to at the end of this is cocaine's wonderful
I guess
No it's alright already thank you thank you
Hey buddy surla wrestling.com
I also also
When is the you geyser
So good
You're amazing and I are
But at the same time
The reason I want to get a couple that is I'm the worst at it
For your listeners who are in need
Yes you do so many like help boost
Peoples
Can odors medical bills and stuff like that and I think that is so f****** cool
I I think you are about hilarious
Awesome performers and
Creative types
But it's so cool that you make a priority to
Be such a
Like that
Maybe you don't get enough compliments for that
I saw me all right.
Problems
I appreciate that
Turn off that
United States
Better to give than to receive
What else
Did you stand up nami.org if you need to talk
But if you're not
Is that a
What is
Nami
Nami.org
Like I thought it would be nahenahe. Org
Michelle
Toy Galaxy
Stephanie
Rhett and Link if you like bad stuff
Get on Madden
Go see the menzingers in November
In Chicago
Aew wrestling promotion commentary for the
Chris Jericho Cruise that's right
You're all in I'm all in baby
Did they post a picture of you to a shirt all-in be there all weekend
There's one show where Alex kept saying that he's all in against the globalist
I'm all into Photoshop of Alex
A shirt off
Defraud
Our pleasure as always
Soham
Hell yeah gotonight.com quicksupport the show
Appreciate it I feel very
Depressed because
Their donation
Slow to feel better please feel free
And as is tradition
Someone needs to be told to go f*** themselves
And the guests
Yahoo Jordan here is the person who's got it
Because
That's very happy but at the same time
If you say Rowdy Roddy Piper
That feels really shity so you got to choose someone else
And I don't think you want to say Sean Stone cuz you don't know anything about that guy how about someone else
About I guess we've gone on
I'm going to say
You just you almost at that.
Mentioned
Mention Kevin Nash
In your notes
You say it is a complete
Vince Russo
Alexandra Thurston color