Alexandra Thurston color
Alex Jones
Hey welcome back
If you were a prospective
Supreme Court Justice
Does nominate
And I was actually
Jeanine Pirro Wapner and everything that you thought ever was wrong
At like from the moment you were born
To present day
You are the dumbest motherfuking pile of garbage in the history of the world
Right
You needed a podcast
To bring you back
To the correct form of
Follow-up question how would you describe it
You should listen to start my Bethel
F****** a rap
Very funny shows
Good musical gas barely maybe I would say Elizabeth knowledge fight that's our show
Where I know a lot about Alex Jones
Call you back I was listening back to the episode that
Marty DeRosa
Nothing wrong with that hanging out with him and haven't
Somebody some fun talking about
Maybe dumb
Rowdy Roddy Piper is
I was
Do you know it's just because Marty
Don't know as much
About this world
It departs where there's like
Something funny and I would have screamed about and they just didn't get to
Like when he had his collar who was like I married into the buffet live family that's right if we
Weird if we heard that clip would have been outrageous
Glad you're back
I don't think there's a wonder One there but they're correlation definitely suggests that there's something
He doesn't see fit to subject himself to this b******* so constantly to the point where you're at
Where things are funny
Oh yeah
Thought I guess
Simultaneously
Dismal
What I wanted to do was I wanted to I didn't know what I wanted to
Be honest
We haven't put out any new work on the Project Camelot
Right I thought that it was
You know
I do like we do have an obligation
To talk about present-day stuff
Until I wanted to cover present day
But I got sidetracked listening to Mondays up haha
Honda on Sunday you put Alex Jones without a special report
Where he responded to Joe Rogan responding to him
Sounds just like
Hibiscus already
Beauty
Joe Rogan's trying
Escape from the back-and-forth of it
But Alex
I think
Alien Predator situation no matter who we all lose
It's all I listen to that and I was
Like
I was overwhelmed by how little I care
We can't go over
Monday's episode he had a Gaston called a Yo Mama's chest hair
Until I listen to I was like
He's just like his
Blogger
Like Trump
It was going to be
Something crazy
Taking her name from line-in
Girls with
Take my medication that she
Point that move
That's wrong
Yeah it's bad
Do I get to the beginning of this
If you're naming yourself after I mean girls character
Something that said in Mean Girls and you're a trump supporter
I need to reconsider the messages that movies are trying to
To get through
Holocaust denial ISM of reviewing me
That's what that is that's rewriting the Civil War to make Mean Girls it was actually about female empowerment
That's what I understand
Lincoln how to diet
About Monday the
It's worth a damn
Are worth us talking about
So this would be Monday the 9th
July
And I just have two clips that I'm going to play from this
Because these are f****** like these are really scary
Who's the guy who I guess he has on a lot
Before
To be on to talk about the volcanoes in Hawaii
Explode volcanologist
Cuz everytime I look
How to talk to a real
This guy seems more like a Christian Fundamentalist
That really it's a tough combo combo
Fuel open and then Hawaii family pray for Trump
Twice-a-day and stuff
No I believe this guy is a grade-a number-one
Piece of s***
Destiny the Juan de Fuca plate
And it is like 55 years now overdue
49-point plus earthquake
Creating highways and a lot of damage of the shore
So yes it is overdue
I got to tell you California
Got to devote I wouldn't mind losing their their political votes at the moment
Surviving if it won't be able to
I was just saying my disappeared
Believe in the plot of escape from l.a. right now
Is California breaks off
We will have a fundamentalist Christian lunatic running I mean he doesn't
Believe it but a collection of them running the f****** country turn it into a f****** nightmare
You clearly I'm going to have to remove your eyes cuz your skin all over them
You've got this covered
Across and
Take your pick
I would say
The pile of s***
For wishing a 9-point earthquake to hit
California in order to
Get them to stop voting
Isn't it funny
Isn't Larry the most our enemy of the one that
Right now
Minority
He's there
Nice Melting Pot going on
But like the things that I really want to drive home this is the most important thing is
Is it this is on the same
Constantly talks about
How shity it is but Rob Reiner wants to punch Trump
Or something like that creating these images of violence
Against their enemies
He's having a guy on who says he wants a 9-point earthquake to hit California because they didn't like how they vote
Scale version
Robert De Niro
Which is what you is responsible to
To do in this situation
He wants any intellectual credibility
But you know only his political enemies
The
The Nook the level of death
That would happen if earthquake hit
California
In the billions
Five figures probably I would say probably in the five figures
Another reason he is not a real volcanologist
People do not use the Richter scale
Actual
I don't know if I can help you with that
9.5 is the highest
Been rated
Ears ears
Advocate violence
I do but it's targeted at people
Who are causing the problem
Are you in the same way in the same way over
Them it's just everybody
You get rid of California is liberal
The whole country
Think so
Inhumanity out of it
I think we would at least
Call call like delay the vote
If we were still trying to repair cats it's not like California would be left on its own to fix it.
Tire country
Would also
Waterport, California is what the largest economy in the world
I remember the number the number to the California
You don't get to eat
So go f*** yourself out there
Just gone
And found the garden
Which Alex is going to have him
Biblical literalism
Garden of Eden f****** roll the dice on that
A very large
Scale project that I can
I can't really get into all this
Tails up
Research on some of the individuals involved
Alex Jones
His world and I just recently did a deep dive on Doctor group
No
But he is a member of a group called these
Society for scientific exploration
Which I don't like them using the word scientific
It's not
Pictures of fake
You can't have scientific anywhere near your name
Doctor is no doubt
Can I bring this up
That they put out
The scientific
Society
Found their archive
And I've read a bunch of them
Scholarly written articles
Frazee leaps of logic work in undergraduate
With the form of an abstract up top
Format down
Hold on what the f*** are you talking about
Kinesis really fun to read a review paper about the magic and a hairy
Potter Universe being real absolutely
The five different
Poets works
To discern the identity
Of William Shake
I thought you could use them to enhance your sword in The Witcher
That is 1/4, all right
So the reason I bring this up is it's another
Parallel
Between swery Kerry Project Camelot
You know who's one of the associate editors of the Society of scientific exploration
Extraordinaire
Absolutely
I don't know I think they are
I found out it was at the
The farsight Institute Courtney Brown run not-for-profit
Music slightly different for the Incorporated
Just funnels a bunch of stuff to the for-profit and non-profit
Businesses like
No big deal
Prophet
You can do that for when your whole thing is about like
I'm going to trick people into thinking I was
In Hitler's mind and Ike
I can tell you what he thought
The oversight
Is a
For-profit
Talking about oversee which is the non-for-profit
Happens all the time the same organization Courtney Brown
One of the associate editors of the
The journal
Which is an interesting parallel between
And we have this damn Deo dickhole cuz on also is
Making a documentary or writing a book about finding the Garden of Eden
On Project Camelot 95 earthquake
Turn on Monday I think it's very scary Alex Jones
Dan Lyman
Is not
7UP
Who was it
Advertisement
Ernest was in
All the time that's the one
All right you always
Yeah
Limon is the European editor of
Infowars
Is the website
So I don't know why I don't know why
We're already over there
I forgot about Steve PJ Watson
It could be him he's already in Europe is now you got the damn alignment
Who's the European editor
I don't I don't give a s*** all right because
It seems like a little bit of a crazy dude
Here is Alex
Some real f*****-up stuff about what
Culture
Atlanta
Mother
Scary s*** about Europe
Great I know why you're such a cultural
Islamic invasion
And then
Crossword
No
Understand
What's happened before
Hollywood movies
Show that
Ridley Scott
Turn the tide
Victor Von matteosalvini the true history once they had the platform and add the support of the people
Folks
And now in Austria now have a break Everman theranos do they have their work cut out for them but
He's going to start buying all these movements together he wants to kind of be the figurehead of that it's going to create huge problem for Brussels
I think it's starting to basically fracture the entire
Political Spectrum in Europe
Unfortunately agree with that last time
It is
Doing a real number
Political Unity?
Nationalist country
You want to have a nationalism little head in
Also a little bit
This Dan Lyman starts talking about how I even
Sweden Democrats
Are starting
To make some
Main road
I mean I just like to read you here this little piece
Swedish parliamentary party
Had the largest share of elected
Spell representative
Resign since
420 Channel X
27 point
Many of these resignations were brought on by racist statements or actions by these representative
They November 2012 party spokesman Eric almquist
Resigned after
We've been caught on tape bacon grease
Austin Texas statements
Another video later surfaced showing
Party spokesman
Berkeley
And Party official Christian westling
We're among themselves are arming themselves with aluminum pipes
Before they sought out a confrontation with Sauron Ismail
A Swedish
Comedian of Kurdish
I wonder why they didn't like him in March 2013 12 individuals were thrown out of the party for therein
Neo-Nazi and other extremist movements
Like it's just crazy like they Democrats
That the party has its roots in
Swedish fascism
Evo Nazi movie
Through the early 90
So I mean like
Get the sense of like what they're talkin about I mean like
In that quip
That the sort of found a vision of Western identity in the
European countries
Is the repulsion of Muslims
Netflix that's what gives them their cultural identity that's
F****** scary thing to think
Here's what I
You think immediately upon listening to this
When you look back at the history of the United States
Around
What
1937 through 9
Where is Zur
But you see people act
Actively saying like no Hitler great that bad
As a shameful part of America
I look at
The other countries now not invading us as a shameful part of their hair
Like in all honesty because
What it what else was that little rant
I'm saying
That
All of European history has been wiped
And they have been invaded
Buy brown paper
You nailed it
For the first time
Everybody everybody
Is invading their aggressors
Everybody who lives there now
Because
How do you feel about the government in Austria right now Dan Italia I'll tell you how you feel
They want
All white people
We're fighting literal Nazi
I don't understand
We know what they're doing we know what they're going to do
We can we can bring up the end
Why can't we just skip to the part where everybody
Pretend it's not happening
Skip to the end
We're already in a civil war let's just f****** do it let's get it over with
Snap snap
Yeah it sounded like Alec
We're already in the Civil War
We're the ones who are living in the Civil existence they're the ones who were fighting the war
And they've been winning for the past 15 years
It's pretty wild
Viacom anymore
It is a little insufferable that's kind of why I like the past more
Do the Henry Rollins end
Interview
That was a wild
You know we have a responsibility is a lot going on in the world now and
I think we do have a responsibility to check in with a monitor
Lucy on Monday
Stan deyo being wild piece
We see Dan Lyman and Alex
Commiserating celebrating the idea of fascist movement
Politically they work
Spiritually wearing hoods
So now we're going to talk about Tuesday the 10th
Of July I will talk to you about where I was like
It's stupid
We can hit the main topic without like
Turn it off like an hour and those
We're going to listen to clips and all that but like
Cut out I think I texted you about this
So much of it is just like we talked about this before
Blustery nonsense
About how great he is
And all this
All this art of Nursing
Statistic weird talk
And so I will start the show on July 10th
You think
That he would start by talking about the Supreme Court
It seems like the obvious thing to talk to Brett Kavanaugh
Being
Nominated for the Supreme Court
Maybe he would talk about the fact that he interrupted The Bachelorette and it really screwed up his DV
No
Interruption
The last 10 minutes were cut off his recording
That's culture-war on the libs
He doesn't start any of that stuff
Exactly in line with what is
Ago in the Chicago
Trump pictures
Start 2016 occupation National Wildlife Refuge in Oregon
Amazing also set to go to England
Hourly islamists
IPhone 4
Trump be blocked from the country
So that
Is how he starts
Rich
As I said
Very in line with his principal
Exploded all over my table
You know everybody paper towels
Edit
So
The Hammond
You know what's fun
We always talk about how it is
Terrible
Think of jailing your political enemies
You know like when when everybody was screaming walk around healthy as an impulse
Seems like
That's
Road
Is right for a crimes
That's that's gobbledygook and you are a dumb libtard I would like
The directions
Stupid
No no
You need to stop
You're Maui's claptrap
Socialism
Is going to
Inform you about what the hell
And what the situation is
I say this was great Trump is Akira the crimes they committed
And then say that they shouldn't really have been crimes right
Controlled Burns
Everybody Gadget New York
Georgia to Florida
The mexico-texas Border Illinois
Real quick his trouble trouble with the law predates over
Just just just for fun
And she'll line
Brothers Brothers
As a firebreak
Because the
Little bit of it
Beggars having a controlled burn
Forest
Mexican
Smoke in the sky sometimes
All the Mexicans
I caught
Chase
F******
Close man
That is Big Bird
Amanda little bit of everybody doesn't there's a
Mexican bakery
I always side with the people
Okay there is a Uber in the
The crops and stuff like that
Standard
Stop but
How right
Alex's
I'm I'm being office
We'll get to the reality of your own.
Situation here in a second
Hobbit first Alex husband
Stupid
Stupid phone
A small amount of
Gratiot and
Undercover of foliage
Outrageous
They weren't really all that
To argue that a pardon of the Bundys would always have
Armed confrontations
You can't argue with this was a very important
These people are obviously political prisoners
Prison for their strongly held beliefs they were fighting
Entrenched power in order to represent the oppressed
And so for them to
Is just like if time in jail in Alabama
Exactly what this is
You could never convince me otherwise no matter what you say next which I assume is going to be very well-researched and
I really want to do a controlled burn they can do so it's absolutely
Need a permit Martin Luther King tires is always dangerous
Potential for widespread damage is always there
Pretty consistently
As was definitely the case in the Artie Hammond fire of 2001 way before Barack Obama was President
The Hammonds illegally slaughtering Wild game
So they were killing animals
My God is pretty consistently been located
F****** God they're all have been witnesses to this
Another specific hold on
It's from the government documents
August 22nd and 23rd 2005 Stephen Hammond said fires to brush and other flammable material
Causing fires to burn
Ion public and private land
And as a result of the fires of rocks
Smitley 1,342 Acres
The BLM manage land were burned
As a result of the fircreek area fires
The US and kreutzer
Austin resource
To BLM land
In the total of 188
8000 to $20
How many acres again
42a
Alright also before Barack Obama
About August 22nd 2016 Hammond Set Fire To Brush and other flammable material causing fire
Where's the burn on public and private land
As a result of the fire approximately 804 Acres
Blmn
68 Acres of private land Woodburn
As a result of the
Fire
Do u.s. encourage suppression cost
What's the amount of $15,000
$677
And resource damages to
BLM in the amount of 30000
$400
This fire also almost trapped and killed for BLM fire
Because they were unaware of the fires that have been satinwear there
Trying to work on another fire
Call Noor about August 22nd and 23rd 2016
Set fire
Toothbrush and other flammable material causing fires to burn on public and private land
As a result of 523 Acres of dlm manage land
12344 Acres of private land were burned
As a result of the Great
Depression cost
$79,809 in resource damages to the BLM land
Amount of 580c
$6
Murdered a man for selling us
Cigarettes
Incidentally throughout all of this Steven blight
Threatening to
To kill and frame BLM employees
Repeatedly tell them I want them I want that out of jail we can kill them
Let's burn them oh my God we have to burn them alive
No no no this is where you you come in with your
Extrapolation that.
Is no good man you got to you got to stop threatening to kill people
I'm saying that you're not advocating this is a perfect
Twilight Zone opportunity
So they commit all of these terrible crimes through the use of Art
Send a boy
Surprise twist
Bigot
Pardon
Mental invalid
Right
And then they get burned alive that is
Twilight Zone the guys license
Getting bro they finally got time now to make more controlled Burns
And one of them gets burned alive and then the other one
Have to watch it and then we
Is icing I mean whatever you're saying
Has the TV show I don't like in real life
I would say the TV version be a little bit boring
I'm more interested in the fact that what
But this park
Does
Just specifically indicate that like
There's no other real message behind
Story of
Of arson
Stop the ship for
20 fukkit
Here is even more than
Perhaps
I get that their history goes so far back in terms
So just not
Not playing by the rules
Burning
To cover up crimes and stuff like that
I get it you don't understand your argument like Alex's argument hinges most
Leon like
Do a sovereign citizen freeman-on-the-land beliefs there
Anything Goes
I'm sorry that
If it was even make the argument that the problem is illegal for
For them to hunt
In that situation cuz if it wasn't illegal they wouldn't have let those fires that opens up too much of a can of worms
She can't admit that even the first
Stefan struve
Cuz that it truly becomes a conversation
The primary
Ignore the primary issue
Focus on the 2nd
You know it's fast
What interest me about this
And what
More Insidious
This is a life
America has a long history of corrupt president pardoning people
Political race
Regardless a Democrat
The the thing that isn't serious about this
Petty
How small
This is just random
Small
Dumbshit
To signal
Hey guys it's all good
It's all good cuz I'm going to ignore you for that fits within my power I'll probably
And we got
Conservation
Of like
Sacred site
Father were desecrated and things like that
Respond out of the Bundys
Stand up for
The the Hammonds with Hammonton already cut a deal
Like they already
Plead down
Yeah all their arson
To get like five years with time served or whatever like it's not yet
Not even a big
Quite frankly
And they're cool man
That's the worst part about it
It's now it's not even their second straight or their 45th strike
Number one crime again
Indiana
Another 48
In 2006
The Grandad fire like
Cost of it was over $1000000
In terms of
Do like me
Suppression cost
And I'm sure they had to pay that back
No I don't think so
Well what about the fireman they almost murdered
Because that's really what it is today was it was arson
Commuter all the sentences
If you want to take away V like a malicious really f***** up Sovereign citizen
Believes that are being emboldened
Through the sort of thing
I mean you just got to deal with like the
Hundreds and
Thousands of dollars of damage they've caused by setting
Fires over and over again
When they want to cover stuff up or it's more convenient to them
And I don't believe in getting
So like the fact that
They just
Are this capricious and it ends up
Comes from
The comes from the Bureau of Land
Management resource
Comes out
It's money really concerned about where my tax dollars go
These two dudes
I'm specifically caused over $1000000 or way more
How damaged
We are paying for
I cannot allow my tax dollars
To go to something like Planned Parenthood promotes
And and
Funds abortion
Help people even when they don't even need them
But I want your hat
To go towards
Fixing the mistakes of to dumbfucks in the middle of goddamn nowhere that's where my tax money
To go
The cover-up
Let's move on
He's pretty thrilled about this park
Very much so
You're like
I know they were not quite
Proving
Wait till a little bit later in the episode
For now
Fortaleza
To the haters
Infowars.com
Meet
Newswars.com
Blog
Successful
Right I mean
What are we doing
The tenth one like frankly do you need really any amendments has
Second for
Right
Yeah
Because you're the one who don't want to quarter soldiers
I think they do though
Soldier
48th Amendment no more reenactors
Contacts I'm worried about
Emeritus
Stolen Valor a crime I really bothered by all those
Guy was nice
I never actually
Alex protecting Madea's Family
You guys just f****** LARPing with magic like normal
Who comes on Alex's show
Have you held a press conference
About the Seth Rich murder
Murder
Somebody still there
Anniversary
Whistleblower
I was going to call in
Batman tell the press conference
For a whistleblower
Call wifey
Initially started with
He promised that he was going to come
Showing you how to do the tricks
Can a call in
Did the reporting that I saw on it was like
This guy was just like all over the place not answering any it like question
Definitive
No anything
But the funniest part was that he was asked.
If you was using a voice
Altering
Thing on the phone
What does it matter if I should I
That would have been really wouldn't like
Lake Manawa
I wonder if it was like trying to get some extra work on the side
Conspiracy juboraj
I'm sure
Do you need an expert
Call
We got to start that
Goddamnit program
Study different thing
Timer 48 minutes into this episode and heard anything about
Supreme Court but here we go
Finally gets
Alex
Alright
And Trump knows other people
He is
For whom his son belching
Problematic
To try to block him
Trump is under investigation
By that extension he couldn't have the last guy either
Bingo
Nailed it
About what you were saying there over the clip I don't know how much of that is like I don't I don't know if I buy into
Too much to a lot of
That's dumb
Seems like
There could be some
Smoky or something like that but I'm not ready to jump on board and say that there were like
Backroom negotiations
And stuff like that understand that there is a connection in in terms of
Anthony Kennedy son worked at the bank where Trump owes a lot of money personally loaned him
Look up
Is true path around the Sun part
Right that isn't evidence
Necessarily
This being a screwjob
Jump too far into that I think that what you're doing is
Conspiracy theory as if that was the only thing if it was just like well his son
Was part of the bank that loaded all that money
Approval
His
However
This is something that people have kind of
Known about for a while
Like the two of them have been in contact pretty
There is a very suspicious
Circumstance retires
Exactly when he retired and election Network
This is this is the circumstantial evidence at this point outweighs my my steps
And even if it's even if
It's not true
Like it doesn't it doesn't f****** matter because someone
I have business deals with
That doesn't mean I can
Get my dad
You know what I mean like it is a completely separate person from me
The same thing
Kennedy and his dad right
Like I don't understand
There's a lot of stuff that smells bad
There's a lot of stuff
A lot of stuff button
The details of it I believe need to be more concrete
Then they are now in order for me to be to compel by I would have loved this
2 years ago this sort of thing would have been like oh hell yeah
Disparate details can be made
To seem like
Explanations of
Much larger puzzle
And I don't
I don't feel comfortable with that in
Until
What watching this episode of to be like
True but I don't want to spend
My pressure
Precious life debunking
Right-wing meme
Or something like that
Before even Kavanaugh was announced
The libs
The joblib
They printed out signs with all the possible names with
Well yeah because Mike Federal
Federalist Society gave us a list of names that we need to stop
I don't want to spend
Of my life diving into
There's so much to be like
We can
Weekend
You can talk about this a lot more
Competently
In the future
In the present all we can really say I
Responsibly
This looks bad
I'm trusting that reporters will follow the threads
That we can't
And I'm I'm totally on board with that I don't I'm not going to say it is true
I'm not here is why I'm having fun
Very self-conscious
About other
People
Did the show going off half-cocked believing
Here's why I'm having fun
Because
It doesn't matter either way
It doesn't f****** matter
Of course it regardless regardless if it's corrupt
It's corrupted
Everybody there's no there's no decision now
Coming out of this government that is not
Inherently
Teams with corruption
Regardless of whether or not it happened in this
Specific circumstances
Specific way
If you do start digging into it you're going to find out something else is
Incorrupt
Ironically
I really hope the people under
Stanley you're being
Slightly
Satirical
You know what you're right I'm not advocating violence
I really am not that's not the way to go I hate that I keep pushing you on it but it's just like
I mean like
I think if there's a lot of people who
Are like a Bill Maher
And then the last
Get accused of
Meyers BBQ
We could be
He was.
I did let me tell you something then
This is all about
Burned is like
Not maybe not a crime but it's on the
It's on the border of Lake
Maybe
He should be though
Like by any reasonable metric just like from a purely scientific standpoint
Of the people who are murdered that's not a possible consequence
All of the people who are murdered by the state
Right
Imagine
Are any of their crimes
Ever equal to
What is Scott Pruitt
Made so many decisions going to result in the deaths of hundreds of people
Maybe not maybe not he's going to
Exacerbate climate change to the point
Vermillion people died or whatever
Do have concrete
Numbers behind
Something like
This person alive
Ugly language could be accused of like right reactionary ISM or something like that
And maybe I'm being like
I know that hey this is
Play in the middle
Or whatever in correctly.
You know
Here's the best way I can describe
The way that I treat
My tendency towards advocating violence
If if
If that is what it can be called
In a court of law
But
Torture I think it is absolutely torture
For anybody to be held
Whitten solitary can
Yep Paul manafort was held in solitary confinement
23 hours out of every day
Still torture
Treehouse in solitary confinement for that long still torture
X logistical
Situations like I would never
Will be done is a putative thing
But
You know if you are a white supremacist
Can you get put into a prison where you're going to get killed
I think it's for your own safety might be the only option or cordoned off wings
White supremacist
Most prisons already get rid of prison
If you're going to attend I don't think it is right
For Paul manafort
To have to be
In that solitary
Multiple times culture is
However
I do think
It is an appropriate
Punishment based on the punishments that we've existed in the past
Sure like for his crimes fan I deserve
The punishment that we Dole out
For crimes that are far less damage
That's it that's all I'm saying
It's a it's a it's a it's like a mask
Like if you got if you got
One column of all the people who died because of your decision
And the punishment that you received in the other column
Most serial killers
Killed less people personally
Vans
And they are they are killed
Now my only argument against that I suppose
For how many months
You don't like I know that you're not out of
But I really don't like the idea of
Punishment
Justice system being involved in like
Biking
Hammurabi SS eye-for-an-eye like you deserves
Totally stupid
Is too much relishing the pain that you can cause someone who has caused other people paying I don't feel like that's a
A good thing for humans
Much more
I think we should
I think we should do that sounds like I was actually looking into
I was actually looking into this specifically because
I'm going through all the crimes that have been committed by
The people in bed
Inexplicably giving power to
And I'm trying to figure out
Could you actually prosecute them for the
And so much of it is actually legal
So then I was like well how if I were going to be elected
Or or something along those
How would I circumvent the fact that what they did was
Was not illegal here
But should be
And is other places we'll lure them to a foreign country
Looking up International Court of looking up all of this
How do we do the new Nuremberg trials like that kind
I'm stopping there really isn't any recourse
Well the Nuremberg trials
Post facto
Get punished
Against our laws
Should have like
Nazis
It should be written into every one of our laws
Vine with Kavanaugh
OK Google
Also he makes no
Point of being like
Now I know that I said I had real deep sources that said that
Nominate
Start that last week by saying I'm usually right
But the rest of it he never brings up
But like
I was I was wrong
You're probably pretend you never said that you ever seen Kevin on napoletana in the same room
Reasons why Alex
Shouldn't be
Should I guess
Here is a
Deferring to Presidential Power in
High-profile case
For instance after the Supreme Court ruled that enemy combatants
Detained in Guantanamo Bay have the right to
To challenge their detention
Camden Court
Cerbat of judges on
The circuit who subsequently ruled in ways that critics have said actively
Converted the high courts
Decision you can go after render it
Original
From a report on
MPR
Care about president
Should not be in favor I don't know absolutely
And it's not caring about pressing it at all this guy was super into like these people's Warehouse
Tortured in all this
Absolutely
And should be for Mr that
Anti-contraception
Environmental regulations
Croagunk
The South Carolina law that required
Which of course is a corner
Arizona voter to
Can we just call him
Death like everything you just described everything he's anti
And everything is Pro
Lead to people dying who don't
Who shouldn't
Who have no reason to die other than because of those positions
I think you might be dramatizing it and that neutrality a tiny bit but the other ones you
You're right on that
I agree with the rest of them kind of life and death
Slight right right
It does limit people's ability to organize
Congregate
I wish I could lead to
The death
I know you probably
And I'm passing
There's only one way to
Shutting the
I mean at this point
The thing that
Is anything that
Look at
Now with
Like a knowledge of History
Combines with like
Where we're going
People keep talking about how
He's going to
Swing the
The court conservative
Next 30 or 40
Right
If he is approved
Max
Before either the world ends
Or
There's a violent overthrow
Biggest
Indications that
I've been stopped myself before I get
Gloomy about this but
You know we have
Reordering of
National priority
Making friends with him
Pretending the Kim Jong moon is on the level
When he's clearly not
Please cook their reports coming out all over the place that they are still doing massive test
Hilariously not hilariously the Optics
Doing stuff like that
I'm partying up to Great extent with
Putin
Other authoritarian
And leaders around the world
Things like that
Things and we are not
Do you want to be on the road
15 years old
But like cuz there is beer there is
A world
Also see
As being popped
We're really bad decisions get made
Cooler heads
Prevail
And we are able to fix
Before things go too far
Going on has happened in America in the
The problem
With comparing those two is that
Mistakes
How much lower
Unpack lower in the past
You were just f****** with
People in America
Now you're f****** with the world
Technological advancement
You have weapons advancement
The ability to like
Before the Advent of the internet or the ubiquity of the internet and
The prevalence of social media
Much harder to
People like Alex are able to trick people
Just because we talked about it
Malicious influence
Butt video
The steaks that are so much higher are on one
Is it like
Outright destruction
Is right around the corner
A couple of bad decisions lead to like
Our weakest nuclear bomb now is twice's as like a thousand times as strong
That big boy and send Manuel like that whole thing but I think even more devastating is
Is that like
Now people are so in
Entrenched in their own opinion
And maybe we're guilty
Same time I'm willing
Clearly
Fairfax
I think one of the nice things about being a conservative
Like they just choose whatever I want to be mad out front
Anything like a videos
To one of them they're not even people
Dear Abby
No they are people but
Functionally they're not like
I do think the
This is
I'm coming out of his
Beautiful
About like
Value of people in
So you shouldn't
Like right people often
I'm ready to write off
Oh yeah a lot of people
It's not like it doesn't it doesn't matter anymore
Wrigley I'm ready
I know
15%
Population in America if it's just like
You guys just got a
Yourself you're hurting yourself
And hurting others more
Book the people who support Trump were like
Everything he's doing is great restarting this specifically going to
Them look like personally
Personal skin in the game
And they're not even really going to
It's bananas
Yeah because
Of that
Ubiquity of
The internet and social media less
Create things that look real one right
What's the technology where you know you have these videos now or you can make it look like someone saying
Like I could like
I mean I know this is also me being Duma gloomy like that could cause a war
You could very easily make a video of something like
Kim Jeong Hoon
Declaring war on America
I mean all the time card trick
Trump with that so easily f****** Stuttering John tricky with a prank call
Air Force 1
Lake Windward vision pre-internet
There was a f******
Cats that almost went wrong cause the end of the human race
Because some dude the only reason we're all still alive. Literally the only reason all of the human race
Jason still alive is because one dude was like
Don't think we need to press this button
And send all these new
Russian
Imagine
Dumbass president
Get the video
Plays and then
10 minutes later they issue a retraction
But it's too late he's already f****** dumb Chiron is is this real
Exactly
Still doesn't matter
To say
We need to start a war
He's going to do it
Hopefully not
Powers to the president episode
Alex talks about why he supports Trump
Is this
That's not good
To Amir couple months ago when Trump was shoving Isis up his dirty ass hoe
A few years ago when his gut said that he was a gangster
You had it from good already
Frontman for the
The Consortium
I don't even
I'd like
I don't know I just had to sort of brace myself a tiny bit
Are what you're about to board with this guy
Like that's the real face
Thousand
But at least there's some like
There's entry there
There's something that's like what are you what game are you playing exactly
A lot of options
Right right
There's that there's Dynamics there's a push and pull like
I know exactly what you're doing
This is
Boring you're adorable
Character in a bad movie
When the movie of 27
16 comes out eventually
He was a bad character in that show though
Really bad.
Yeah
Is very serious
Plug it a lot very weird
More people more people realize that
What about Alex Jones
Everywhere
Any publicity is good publicity
That version of him is
Even more interesting than now
Yeah
The only thing that interests me about this episode was like I learned a little bit more about how bad the Bundys
Alex tampio sucks
Bring up Andrew Napolitano anymore
That's a great way of putting experience listening to Alex Jones now
Anytime we listen to him in the Press
All of it
All that happens
We realize that the
The basement
Just got low
There's no
Bottom how much could a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could chuck chuck
Idaho
You know I mean it's just it's
Sort of a like
How many different ways can you suck Trump's dick
Like how many different ways are there
Eminem Eminem
Guess that would help
Maybe try a breath mint
Oh you could use one of those one of those strips one of those things that you put on there maybe put some LSD on there everybody
Contact high
Now I'm just
Weird thing about a job
Most of my problems come from me
I don't like your characterization
Because I don't think they're like
I know
I would frame it differently is just like how much
Lowercase
Can someone bring themselves
In service of
Something
Doesn't really
It's not
I want to say that it's not really what they're about what they're about as white supremacy
It did
Look how contorted does someone have to
To get in order to rationalize.
In a way that's not
You don't like
If he was interested
To me what
Here is like a bad
Like
You cuz it cuz here's what's going on
To the people Hughes
Talking to
They've already been sold
To the people that he's not talking
He's over selling
Every word he says just pushes them further
So why are you still trying to sell
Are you still trying to sell it in new and different
You're selling a vacuum
Or I have thrown a vacuum out the door why are you bothering with this
Go somewhere else
Well it's B
Because
We've already talked
Keep the Illusion for the 20% that he's still marketing to the hundred
Yeah
To keep doing that or else they would realize like
There's no
Where is a group of people who are providing a liar
Otherwise
The game kind of gets blown up
Like how would you both
Senior conservative everything Trump does is the best thing to Dule
Right while still being interested
Because he's not doing the ladder
I would say that the way Alex could do it
Is
Like ignore a lot of the news
He's not good at this anyway
And most of the time when he covers the news it's just
Reading headline and then maybe angrily ranting about something
I would say read the headline mostly the function of what you're doing anyway
What made you interested
Chimera stuff
Right like go back to The Well of like your old personality that people kind of enjoy
I'm in see what you can build off that
Yeah I can find other avenues that are like
That they're weird
And have just enough truth that you can yell about them
But are also
Complete
He's not weird any
No mainstream
Very mainstream now
But here's the problem was that
The problem with it is
That he was
Super successful
Inasmuch as
Sean Hannity is now him
Fox & Friends
Very closely mirrors him the lazy like before coffee
Version of Alex know I hated those sorts event
Anything on Fox News
Before
Very shity
Not full of garbage
But they were not
Couple years ago out-and-out white supremacist they were hiding
And you know I don't even think Tucker Carlson was that much of a white supremacist before
Full
Native some point
Probably
Hey we're going to edit out the part where you said the n-word 42 times in a row because
If it one that's Jackie Robinson's number
And two we can't behave
Have no notice you're wearing a bow tie in adults so it'll be fine
Don't be staring at that like
Expecting it to squirt on your desk
Fitbit
The thing is
Yeah
Who knows what lies in the hearts of men
As they say
You know like who knows if that was what those people like Bill O'Reilly or any of them was about there
Fox News
State television
Asian for Bush
Yeah I'll be like even as that was not nearly as crazy
Is Infowars
And now it kind of is
Alex
Because
Now that they're both on the same
Page
Even though they were on the same page as being against Obama
Weird he was screaming about like Frank Marshall Davis being
To reclaim the weird
Ireland has gotten too weird
And now he doesn't know how to weld
The quote Hunter S Thompson
When the going gets weird
The weird turn
Pro
Before or less
Yeah
Yeah he's actually even pulled back from the weird
Something that was
Really out there
Does this might actually be the best way to
To kill Alex Jones
Of his life career
Stuff like that
Productive
If I were Alec
Text Network Raven
Con man
I think that that is what I
That would be what prompt
Me to leave
The team is Malik
I can no longer be as
Crazy as I need to be
That's why you
You trying to juice it up somehow your girlfriend of four years suddenly gets a haircut and color is your hair
You're edging
Around 4
You think his beard is an indication that sound breakup
Deep deep sad
I really I really truly because after after I was alerted to that he had a beard
I was allowed to look at it
And it is the most disgusting thing
I think I've ever seen in my entire life can look at that in the mirror
Is a deeply depressed and unhappy
I would say is that like I hate
Latrobe on the TV shows of like when someone like
Gets a divorce
Something alcoholic
The girl beard Amazon
The beginning of the
Gyros
By Nathan Petrelli grow a beard
He was a drunk he thought he was responsible for Peter's death brother
You look like a sad clown
Accidentally
Absorb the guys power there was a nuclear bomb
Okay argument is annoying
And in order to save the city of New York from exploding
Does Peter couldn't control his powers grabbed him and threw him above the city
Staffing so you grow a beard
Drinking so much but
She couldn't show him drinking all the time
Anyway
Anyway my point is that
I hate it in hacking
Eviction
But I think in reality
Is bi Darkrai for
Alex needs
You got to shave that beard
Got to shave that s***
Oh yeah
It's
Definition
It is
First off
Not block Kavanaugh because that's never going to win
We're going to lose
And the world is over
Still hold out hope
Call senators and stuff like that like spilled
Give up even if
The prospects aren't good if you do nothing nothing will happen if everybody in America
Just call Susan Collins wants
And says whatever it is that Mitch McConnell says to you he is lying
Because he's always lied to you
And you are gullible
And maybe she won't vote for Kevin
Because she's going to be told
She's going to be told a million times
No don't worry about it having all respect
Precedent
And so he won't got Roe v Wade
To say any challenge comes to Roe v Wade
The
Will definitely be worth it and she's going to say yes and then it's going to be gutted and
She's going to be like
Well who knows
Anyway
Let's let's move this along
So
Collect Jordans
Alex acts like a
When you went down
Seattle
When I'm done with people on the street screaming
He's got a slightly different take on
Calling us names lying about us
Havaianas
Yelling screaming at us does something
Yes it does something it lets me know I'm right
About how
Immature and stupid
People are
I know you are but what am I
It means nothing
Doesn't it
Tell me when electrolyte ideas
Oh that's a good answer
Runaway
Pretty sure you just walked away when I offered the Goblin
As we call him
$10,000 and first
Because I wanted Freeport
He is an out-of-work
Wannabe professional wrestler announcer
Like tertiary
The Goblin
Where is rewriting history
Cuz I watch that video
Being a fugitive
Everybody
What else idea or is that like
Alright
I didn't I didn't think that was fake necessarily
Suspicions
At the time
But I wasn't ready to call it fake
It was fake because what I hear there is Alex being like we did this scene on the streets where this guy threw something at me and I
And it was hot coffee
He didn't react at all like
Flinching
What are you saying is like I had this Tech piece that we did
And then like Mike Rotondo I wanted to get him into
Studio because then I could make a real show out of it
I offered him $10,000 to do a thousand
I don't really want to do it I think I'm done with our
Do not think
I think that was good I realized even done that
Yeah he walked off with his wife
Alex is now trying to reframe it isn't saying words like I just wanted to
I think I would do it
I'm not going to lie to you
Show up on Infowars for 20 grand
I just sit there and stare
Like a serial killer
Stare
Because you know isn't that Errol Morris like sort of philosophy of documentary interviewing
Let people talk
Just what I would do I just
Oh yeah
Haha
Oh
What Alex Bill the space
Whatever
People want to talk about
Aren't you Google
There you go
Although I
Much like Pitbull
Mr. worldwide
Befitting that 14
Alex Azar a still talking about
Seattle
He's already called him a goblin
Right
He always does
It's just
What is it about
Minions of the system and make them so horrific to look at
Okay I got to stop by before we come back
Why is it always
Why is there always
Physical
Why is it always
Why I think
Really going to dive into it
I wouldn't even I actually I wouldn't even go with the
Just White
Because white supremacy is absolute
But even beyond that to like
The white supremacy eugenic
That only good ideas
Can come from beautiful looking
Genetically soup
Superior people
Like his death
So often
Part of it
It's not just it's not just the Jewish thing
Or the white thing it's always like
Although he listen to what Mitch McConnell says in that guy's a f****** troll so it's mostly in a
Completely out of my argument Trump is a f****** monster
Chandelier everybody's
Some stuff like that
Who is he talking about
Okay
Is he Jewish
No idea
Specific instance isn't as important
No I know like his tradition of people who have
Semitic qualities
Yeah f******
Hiatus medical cards in order to attack
Why is she always look like that
All of their
I'm not going to say Jewish characteristics but
But at the same time I love my wife's nose she's got a Regal nose
Jewish stereotype surrounded
Buckingham
Yes it does
Coronavirus
Exactly
We also have the gentleman
Thrown out of the electronic shop
Carlson
Get out of here
He's going to be
Liberal and appeared on Tucker Carlson you're alright get out
All of those things don't seem to fit
Together proper
This
Gentleman
Is a guy by the name
Name
Carefree
People come from
Video on YouTube
I believe it is
Posted in
You posted a video where you talkin about
Democratic Party
People who
Uses people of color in lgbtq
You people
But doesn't help them
I agree 100%
Movement
I do not pick up any Trash
Until fairly recently
A bunch of bots
Promoting
Analyses
Of these account
It really boost
#walk away
Trend
They are
There is one
That's how I was very clearly
Pointed out here in an article on
Bailey.
Thousand
At 45000 like
I am clearly a fake
Using
Spaghetti image
These are all
All
Like
Reverse Google image search
Search is a good idea Washington Post
I'm not here
I'm not here to say like or anything like that
But it's
Easy over and over and over again
It's less important
I am bored
Important that there are artificial forces
Yep that there are these box Farms
Who's that
The do that in order to buy organic
No absolutely not
Midterm election
Yes video got posted what
3 months ago
And now people are bringing it up
Order to
So Alex has the guy on because
Stuck in Love
This is this is a really unfortunate develop
I really don't know
Like it cuz here's the prop
The Democratic party is
Yes
Right and so you get that old b*******
You supported Bernie Sanders in that ruin Hillary and you voted for Hillary and I
You think she's s*** I don't I don't
How do we successfully
Destroy the Democratic party's leadership
Without at the same time undermining our ability to
Destroy the Republican party leader
The plant
Replace
Improve
Adjust
Well Dianne Feinstein needs to be gone
Burn their fields
There's a lot there's a lot of
Cuz what are they
Install
Just ineffective and not good
Folk
Rrr has
Positions of power in the Democratic Party
Dart not representative of what
Should be easy laugh
Party the main light party
Elizabeth Warren
Hey torpedo the entire party
Take that
Some people do believe that
I know I think there's a fine line to walk of
I agree the problem is I just don't know where that line
Because part of me wants to say torpedo the f****** party
We have Warren we have Cortez we have
So many good people
Right like we have so many great people in Democratic party it seems like the Democratic Party
Is always split between people who just want to get power
And people who give a
And the Republican party is always
Unified ideologically
Regardless of whether or not they're Kahneman
Nope
You're being unfair to them
There's some people who are just bad
There are some people
Who are real bad
That's a good point there aren't that there are
53 mom and pop bad
Your sister your mom and pop store bad versus your Walmart bad
With Mom and Pop dad
And that's the game everyone thinks
Is being played in
Like the rising tide is
Really bad
Nascent
Through its birth pains 89 years ago
Coming to
The world is whatever the people who are in power
Mccratic party side
Are ready to deal with that reality
Need to go
The same time I think
It's probably foolish
All hope
On
Like another party
And being able to create it from
The ground
I mean I'd love it
Another party was able to
To do that but I'm not sure that you are
I hope I hope you could
More effective
In order to
I think you'd be able to
The only thing the only thing that makes
To me in regards
To actually change
Sing the Democratic
Party leadership
Is to create a third
Party
That is
Purely about Progressive
Reviews
That only takes on Democrats
In situations where Democrats are overly overwhelmingly going
To win anyway
Like if Alexandria is Alexandria pull off a third-party victory
Against the Democratic Leadership knowing full well that no matter what
The progressive site is going to win that election
All of a sudden
Now we have a viable third-party
Candidates that hasn't
Split the vote and destroy the
Running as a third-party person
She would lose in a general election
It's possible
It's very actually know it's 100% if she was not running as a Democrat she wouldn't
The reason
Did run
Democrats come into the party
Try and push it left
Yeah as opposed to
Siphoning off votes
Because
Like
Now what
Create a perfect
You have the middle Democrats
Imaginary
Jeffy middle Republicans imaginary act as well as the people on the left
Making their own party
People on the right
Make your own Patriot party
Then you would have you have off from each candidate running
Right and you could
See what
Interesting
Experiment
With like Jill Stein
And Gary pencil existing in the 20s
16 election
But I think that you could have a much better
I think
Each of those parties
No
Third party
Only runs super Progressive
In areas where the Republicans are almost guaranteed
So then you start asking yourself
Is it
Then you start really dealing with the strategy that
Democrats have for red-state Democrats
Were there like maybe
Mostly Republican
But a little bit not Republic
Even Republicans and Democrats will vote for us
How's this policy back by there it would be interesting as an experiment
I mean
Okay
Cymbalta
Jordan
Chastising you a little bit maybe
About
How dare you
Pay for the crimes that I might have
But
I don't like
I just don't like any time that I feel like we're too close to Alec we're sounding like a I really don't like it end
I'll play this next clip
And use you if you agree with me
Word for word what I say
Physically attacking people in stores
A lot of it. Com
Bumper sticker
Videos of
6570 roll woman Beyond
Athol
Smyrna
Watch
Come up with grown man
He was saying that to himself how did I come up with that videos of
Documented children screaming in ice detention
Insiders so how do you come up with old men men beating up old women
F*** off
Want to kill people
Mineral that there is that and I think you're
I think you're better than
Yeah I do think you're better than to sending to the
The level of that like kind of rhetoric
That's all
Well
And this may be a very weak TR
My my
Difference I think there is that
I am not
Trying to
Like it
In terms of
The Vic
Like I disregard
Conservative
Like they are something to be
There nothing
Yeah I don't like none of your arguments make sense
Nothing you say is anything but
Destructive and you don't even know
You're a pet
You know you're the schlemiel
The people who have it
Coming though
That's the difference I feel like between me and Alex Jones
Faucet out to anybody
I don't think if you disagree with me that makes you
Evil
But I know there are evil people
Deserving
Look I mean like
Dick Cheney should be in jail
From
20 years ago until whenever he died
Like that is not on the table
I don't understand that
I don't understand why George W is not in jail
And so if I say
Okay
You functional
But but if I am saying like
Those two f****** need to be burned alive
The reality of what I'm saying is
They committed serious crimes and they are not being the responsible for countless people
Really burning alive
Like that the people who have it coming and the problem with the rhetoric and I understand I understand exactly where you're
Because the rhetoric makes
Sound like I am saying that Alex
They are I'm saying the same similar things that Alex is I don't want to I don't want that to be what you think I am
Using rhetoric
Has the same sound
Of like
These people to die
But what I really am trying to say is like
There is no accountability
To the people
Who are actually causing all of this s*** going
Alex
This is not talking about
Countability Alex
Talking about punished
I am not talking about punishment repression about punishing
I mean he does say lock her up
And she'll like that
He's talking about like
Protest
He's talking about just people
Politically
Disagree with them
I don't think I don't want
Physically
For Mitch McConnell
To be murdered
Right
At a certain point
Exactly how do you hold Mitch
McConnell accountable
So I'm fine with
I'm fine with that
No emotional rhetoric
Behind
You need to go to court
I understand that
An emotional appeal
It's not going to happen and there's no there's no part of me that wants to clip your emotional wings
Does it work
And disallow you or David you can I'm going to fly
It says like hey Jordan calmed down with your language or anything like that
I just think I think from time
2 time maybe and maybe I'm
Just doing this because this episode so boring
Like Alex that we were talking about
From time to time
Do you like just a dressing
Yeah there's a difference
When you scream burn the
This person
There's not a actual desire
To burn them
Emotional truth behind
Being set on fire
Like emotional
Like legitimate
Emotionally
I
Wood
Not ever be able to watch
Like if
If we burn Scott Pruitt alive
As a as a everyone would be like one of your big Villa
I could never ever watch it
It would destroy me emotionally the simple idea of
Thinking about like actually seeing it
And knowing that the
The consequence is it
Are they are real
Would wreck me
And the ideas
Would have some like
Part in bringing about
Direct me forever
However
Pruitt
Yeah he has personally killed
With the things that he said he with the stroke of a pen
People have died
Because of him
So how do you hold him
Accountable
You know what I'm saying that's what I really want I just want people
Murdered
At least
Call Mom
He's a murderer that part is
Is well-taken
He shouldn't he should not be a history
Quarantine from the recipe
Humanity because
He's not allowed
And I said
Long time ago
Standby this
And I have no
I've no place in my heart
That wishes to
People who are on
The last
Democrats
Be free
Give this sort of
The only way that I really think that
Pecan
Take the rock out of pallets
To assert next
First of all get money
Like we we mediately
To I don't know Public Finance
Titanfall campaign
The campaign season 2 like 3 months you get back to the point where there are limits on
Campaign
Contribution absolutely if any at all
Yeah for real
You take all that out of it
The purity of the
Horseback
Subject
Almost all politics
To International
Who cares if other countries do it too
But like
We have to we have to America is a city on The Shining Hill
Then f****** beat
You eat kind of
The only way that we talk about this all the time it's like
Like a George W bush committed war crimes
Trump is committing war crimes
The same time we're very
Acknowledging that Obama's
War crimes or has committed war crimes
The whole thing is that like
We have this
Complacency in the United States is like
In order to be president because
It's so difficult and challenging
I do so many complicated issues there's no way to do it without committing war crimes
Is part of the
Needs to go away
Needs to go away the only way that's ever going to
To happen is if
Some people are held at
Accountable hopefully all of them are held accountable
Because there needs to be a war in the future if you're the
The president
Kill
Thousands of civilians in a cup
Country where are you
You are
You preside over that you're not the one in
The plane or not calling the drill strike individually necessarily
But you preside over that
You are the altar
Responsibility
To happen
I would say
There is room in the conversation for rogue agent
On the lower level
As long as they're punished
You know like yeah
You find out who was the one
Responsible for
Then maybe it doesn't go all the way up to president
Their needs
To be sincere like
Just because we say send them to
To The Hague
Sound like they're going to end
The killing of maybe it's not
Ready it's not
Maybe we
Maybe we take a little breath
And say like
Listen these people committed war crimes we need to deal with it
We can't
Just kill them
4X cathartic
Is that would be
But what we do is we
You say
Alright your estate
He's gone yours we take away all Salgado gotten games
Yep we take away
A middle-class stature
Which would be a delightful thing for something like me to have Excel blood
What was the last president that doesn't belong in jail
It's been a long time
It might be all of them
Eat your stand
I know you are
I hope people understand what I'm saying
It's the only way that we're going to get better
Deal
With
The excuses that we have for why we're not bad right
And the little
Things that we play a little game that we play of like
Well Obama
Hospital in Redding
Well yeah
Was probably good intent there
That doesn't
It's not okay
All of it is not okay if your good intent is like instead of killing 1,000 people I want to kill
Is that
What good in the end like I guess
I get it right
And are on an idealistic level that's unacceptable
Victor
Conversation I'm trying to have
Is
Taking this rage
That you feel
About these politicians
Deserved
Cuz they do
Across-the-board
More Republicans
I think we've made that clear history on fortunately I think if you look at reality
Weird how conservatism leads
Towards
Good morning more to the right
Weird
But
My point is
Play I think we deal with this
Wake up out of can
Control local
Local
You know what cops way out of
Control
Write one of the best ways
Can be dealt with his with
Civilian review board
You have people who are not
Westerly politician
Provide some oversight
Accountable to a macro-level
And you look at what
I mean I'm willing to have another conversation about International courts not being perfect
I think there are
Which is not something to laugh addict
Gallows humor
No I agree
I think big picture if you look if you pulled
Typically pull the entire world
Yeah we should be crazy
Yeah
There's about 270
Percent
In terms of life
What
Buchanan
I would I would even argue that it's so much higher than
Conservative
I think Isaac
Going to be like
5% weird this way 5% weird that way the other weird
I'm sure 5% of us are there
You can't kill people
Fair enough
Do it like there are like a lot of friend
Change groups
Right
To do this there is
There should be a consequence for
Culturally about women driving cars and
I think we've gone very too
Too far on this but I
I still think
The only way home
Is through accountability
Require
Lot of people taking some
They don't want to take
On both
Exactly
And we can if you want
Lock her up
About Hillary
In all honesty
I bet you could find a reason
Like legitimately if you just had somebody
If you start looking to knit anybody who is f****** for it
Tripler
Not a natural thing
It doesn't happen in a vacuum
And it doesn't happen without committing some sort of atrocity
At the end of the day whether it's
Atrocity whether it's a
Calling website
Elon Musk
Screwing his employee rights employee
Level but I don't think
He's profoundly Wellfit
I think that's the trick
I don't I know that he's very well but I like
Blake Hyatt billionaire rich but also
From from the things I've looked into about him
Probably
Pretty on the level
But even so
Do more
I know
Acceptable loss
You know
I didn't what I want to say
Yeah
I survived off doing this podcast
And the generous donation
Good people
Provide
That's how I
Survive in
Is a tough tight wire
Let the word
Highwire
Highwire.com
It's a high-wire Act
Of me
Constantly just about to fall off this
Into the netting below
Yeah and I still
And I'm not saying this
Myself sound great
I still try to donate
Causes
I care about
Even though I'm at
The point where
I sometimes have to go to the
ReStore in a mic
You know like that sort of the
Sing I will try to give
A little bit of money here in there
Let's extrapolate that to
Do people like Hamdi ulukaya
All these billionaires
You could
F****** live on a million
And give 9
900 million dollars
To the advancement
Artifact is morally suspect
The concept of living on a million-dollar
Fargo
Crazy
It's such a
Human social thing where it's like well once I live on a million dollars I have
Have to justify
Spending all this money
Exact
Fuel to riches
Do you have an infinity pool
A bigger infinite
Corner of my building
Question that I I I
Wood
One love to know the answer to
Which is
I can't imagine living be like if I were if we were suddenly f******
TV personality
Who made millions of dollars
Which I'm not ready
Right absolutely not ready
You'll be ready
It's just like
From LA
Everyday we watch
Who am I I am the another character
I don't remember Escape From New York
I can't imagine living any way other only
Opulence the only luxury that I want is
To not have to be like
F*** am I going to make it
That's the only luxury that I really want
I think that's the case we're almost there
8 if you're a person who
Just keep
Accelerating the luxuries that they want
You're probably committing a crime I would love for like and I know I've
I brought this up a couple times and I don't
Like I've been selling my plasma
Yeah which I don't find
Yeah it's good to have some nights
Time to wrap
CC again
Your luxury is like
Like having
It's a bus trip over there bus trip by hour in the chair
You know but it
Exactly where is not a bad time
Is it I think
Everybody who wants
Bloviate
About about s***
Go do that a couple
Go spend some time down at the plaza
Go down there
Trying
To the people
Around here
Go talk to Aunt Jessie
Experience
The culture
I'm not saying it's a bad culture at all cuz I love it
I think that the
The people down there are awesome
But I would say it
It could open up
Customize people who
That
I don't know just
I think it a lot of
You don't realize
There are
So many people
Who
ReliOn
To make ends meet
Cuz no one going in
I'm sitting down and having their blood drawn
Then put back into them
For 20-30 $40
Accession
When's they're doing well
Know everyone down there is doing
It's
Well if you wanted if you want to even go into like are like if you want to talk about Bernie
You know like
Like at what point do we do we do it like a Mexican
President or president elect
I believe is his shortened
Nickname
His his promise of like
I am going to turn the presidential house
Into a f****** Muse
Museum
I'm going to live the way that I lived
Last week
I live the way that I lived a year ago I've been delivered Getty Museum
And then underneath it
Who knows what they think.
But that is like
Yeah
Trick the populist leaders pull I'm going to donate my salary
Becky's already a f******
Cortez versus Crowley
I've already forgotten his name cuz
One of her big boy
You don't f****** live here
You don't live with any of these people
We talked in a representative government
How can you represent people
Living in a million percent different way than you do
So maybe that's the third point of
Along with sending
The Hague
Yeah
And I think they were seeing the the blossom
Beginnings
In terms of
Like actual
Citizens
Big representative
That's always healthier than
Your politicians all of those at work
All of those themselves from high school all of those women
The people of
Color all of them for whom the Democratic party has voiced
So much non-support
If the past year
#walk away
To keep those people away from Power
Yes
Wonderful
I don't know
There's that there's a
So much a one step forward two
To step back
To set back
I mean sometimes
Survival means
Going through
Play Bad
Perhaps the survival of the democratic party will be
You getting their comeuppance
Recognizing
Like you're saying
Lb lgbtq
There
Whose voice is me
Need to be heard the most
Absolutely
People who
Eyemart
The most
At risk
With
Liberal platforms
Surviving
We have very little skin in the game and if
If we were
Craven
Manipulative weirdos
We should go to the Rain
We would f****** if we were if we were if we just only cared about
That would be the smart thing
To do
We are too smart
To con people the correct way
We would feel better about
We could f******
If we just
If we sat down
And wrote a conservative
We would f****** kallax Rodger
Rodger
We could f******
Rock your world you don't even know
If we sat down
You know the nice
Six pack
We could probably
Figure out a way
To mask
Liberal
Concern
Conservative talk
But all of these people seem to not be able to do
Which thankfully
Process bed
You see it over and over again
Yeah
Anyway anyway let's do it
We have one more question
I thought
Another clip about the
The Hammonds
And I was going to try and book end
The show
Fire
I didn't tell you every
Ono is there more to know another clip of Alex talking about how great
They are real arsonist
Hoover very close to
Committed manslaughter
News
Steven Dwight Hammond are also most likely
18 year old nephew
Police report
Several month
What's the discipline has gotten worse
7 worst
Dusty told me that two or three months ago keyence
Got into an argument
Doing his chores
Dusty stated that Steve
Became very upset and charged him
Dusty stated
To the closed fist knocking him to
Did the ground
Dusty stated
Steve Ventura
The gravel
Dusty stated that this action
Hurt
And made him fearful of C
The report says that when Dusty was
Caught with alcohol
David driven him at least
10 miles from the ranch
Handmade Dusty walk back
The report further states that
When Dusty was caught with
Tobacco store
Skoal smokeless tobacco then 10 Mi away from the ranch
I made him walk
On What occasion
2004 Dusty
Carpet mischel's into his chest
A little pin
Nothing that was going to give him
NASCAR racing like that but
Did that I don't know why I feel
I doubt he was young
Quote
He stated that
Steve told him that he was not going to let Dusty
Two-Face the family by Carpenter
Dusty stated this
Steven took him it began
Initials
Steve standard on each side of the chair
Just for at least 5 minutes
Steve used a very coarse sandpaper to
Standoff
The report goes on
Call Dusty told me that
The process. You should have said trigger warning
The process
This is not okay
I'm really not doing great
Because he knew that
Steve would continue to process
For a longer. Of time
Kroger
Paw Patrol
Steve told him that it's
He would fillet the initials off Dusty
Kids is like raising
Cows or dogs the reports
As recounted
The report
The Hammonds told me
Deep enough
And thought that we should
Interesting
Hey so your remember all that stuff I said about how I would feel bad if I watched
McConnell burn alive
That's gone
Nah that's a timeout
I'm out I can watch the worst things happen to that guy now
Watch the worst things happen
Funeral kid are people who
Trump just pardon
I could
The years later when he was 21
Quote when interviewed by federal agents
21-year old dusty
Kevin said that he feared that Wentz
You talk to police
But Stephen will come to the front door in
The paper said
Asked about their arson
Dusty
The quote Steven started handing out boxes
Strike anywhere matches
And said we're going to light up the whole country on fire
Dusty told the jury
He said that Steven pointed to a spot on the
Skyline Inn
Is there
Just you just said
Start walking that direction until you run out
Dusty
Quote Dwight
Keep my mouth shut that nobody
Need to know about the
These guys are serious
That's what these guys are
Strangler Behavior
These are psychopaths
Same story when he was told to like
Dropping
Matches until you ran out
He did that Dusty
He did that and then
He realize that he was becoming
Surrounded by fire
Yeah almost died
Escape
The fire that he and his uncle had started
Uncle and
And father
This is profound familial abuse
This is
To hear this sort of thing
All the arson
That's bad
You've called him billion dollars plus of damage
The United States with f******
What number is covering up your travel pillow
The people
You
F******
Unforgivable I don't know if you've ever read the road out of hell
It's a
It's a story about it
If you
Maybe read it absolutely
This is such that same story
It's at same story of this
F******
Abusive
Monstrous
Family
You really B evil will
F******
Corrupting this
Brutal
I hope this is f****** brutal no I'm I'm past it
All of my previous like a maybe
No
F****** burn these people alive I will watch this with f****** Joy Alex
I will watch it
Sheriff Arpaio or whatever that
Used to be little
Except for what's a phrase to Kim Kardashian
Oh yeah yeah
Chicken Grapevine
Burned alive
White and also been such a weird sister
Butler
Yeah there is a strategy
The other thing
The very very very very sharp Focus
Is the
The amount of play Alex
Gets off of
Beers
About these globalist
Child grabbing at abusing Network
And what have you
And when you really look at the reality of this sort of thing
The only attack
But more importantly
Does exist
On some
It's not as big
Is the abused
Traded by
Every time you talk about kids
The cages
We talked about this
The only stories
Ever going to find
Parents who keep their
With except
Can of our border collie
Well Savage
Has always brought up for the longest time
Like
Conservatives are so angry about trans people using the bathroom that they
Identify with
And who is the most likely to be assaulted or raped or sexually assaulted in those bathroom
Trans people
Who is the most likely
To sexually assault somebody
It is if you're f****** youth pastor
Like these are the people who you are protecting
Who are the ones that are good
People with
Access its
Positions
Truck tent
People's lives are generally
People who exploit
Child molesters are
What like 90% of the time somebody that
The family knows and trusts
Or like Uncle and quotes
I don't I don't want to give away
Cheese on that
But the reason
This stuff is so important
Tonight
I rebuke your
Trigger warning
Perhaps I should have brought it up I didn't realize how
Just talkin about
Cuz like
The reality of child abuse
In America
Is
A lot of it
Is Dawn by familial people
And bye-bye
People
Who are trusted
Like we said in the name of good parenting
Alex
Create
This Boogeyman
Bob Macabre network of satanists
Demons and what-have-you in order to
You get mad
A problem
What's the deal with
And like you said
I don't think
Is always the key
But it does seem
Pretty well
Little lot of times
Deportes
People who have
They're the people like
What we have here
People like
I mean
He always talks about there that day
Plane
We don't complain about Clinton being friends with Jeffrey Epstein
As we've gone over multiple multiple times
Has been on that guy
Champlain Trump is good friends with him
Camden interview talking about how he likes his women young
Crazy took like to me this is like
This is
Christina Moore
Yeah.
Cuz I don't believe that
Doesn't know
I don't believe that
You know what that's a good question haven't heard about this
And what he does it say
Snooze
Right
People will bend over backwards
Often
Make any kind of excuse for somebody
This is something that they meant
This is it what
The Dismount has arrived and this clip I would say actually goes back to conspiracy theory
Earlier in the shower
Peddling conspiracy theories
That's not fair to me
Trump
The Kennedy had backroom deal going on
Probably well Alex
Has Rodger Stone on
So they definitely did
Everything comes up
About
Back of the White House doesn't deny report from a secret deal with Timothy over
Respond to it
Regal
Anywhere on the internet
I want to be clear I don't think he's
Totally wrong I'm not a huge fan of the quadrant but at the same time
If your
If your targeted
By Rodger stone is being released
Tractable
Most fake news site
You're doing something
You're not my go-to for information
All right field Rodger
Is false
Is it cannot be taken seriously in any way
Speculation
I don't know that that happened
It would not be illegal
If the president Twitter
Is former Clerk
So
They are now having this conversation where they're like
Now if they
That that wouldn't be which makes me think
From
Collude with the Russians
Trump obstruct Justice it's not illegal people illegally
I told you earlier that I feel like there's no concrete footing for us to be on about this
The backroom deal and what have you
Make me more take a
Well if you did it it's totally cool that means I call
There's something even more illegal going on Public Defense
The trout
Okay so maybe
But we don't get we can't confirm
Maybe those meetings were illegal
But illegal doesn't even mean so maybe legal doesn't
He should be able to run everything forever forever by Rudy Giuliani
Hey I don't have any foreign clients anymore now that I'm in Trump's legal team torrent client
Are mysteriously sort of connected to Trump related
No big deal
This brings us to the end
This ship
Write with Rodger Stone
He knows but like two damaged
Control kind
Come to the place where now I just
Instinctively believe
And B is lying about are
Somehow
Somehow Rodger
Stone
Has taken
The
Lego
I called him load
F*** if it doesn't seem like he is
Everywhere always
But I also think he's wrong all the time like his priority was the one telling Alex is going to be
Supreme Court choice we can always just rely back on him for the fun of it
It's it's very
Unclear trying to figure out like where is
Where is the line of f****** around where's the lines like
This is what I care about your about like what are Stone motivation
It's interesting though to visit like
If the trend is very clear within his chaos of being like
I would offer a pre-emptive explanation
Right they do allow for us to have a conversation when the truth comes out that you can still sell
Your iodine
I'm going to tell you something
And I'm going to leave enough open space
For me to then tell you anything
And you might believe me
Regardless
Like it doesn't
His starting point is like an open question
It's always
He is such a psycho
Like he is such a palm reader where he's doing a cold read
And then he's reacting based on what year
Oh boy
No
He's just doing that cold
And then the the react based on how you react to him
And it is
He's so good at
He is he is a sleight-of-hand
Master
Decades
Rate we could
Lie to people
Maybe we wouldn't be good at it at first
But we could well if we put the work
April
You just skip to the end of what I was trying to say
Exactly
High stakes line
/ roommates
Goodbye to my friend
It wouldn't be as high stakes
Is he lying to
President of UK
Picture of stone-like was a part of the Stone manafort
Public relationship
Desperate you know what
They are no slouches in terms of f****** around and international policy
I'm going to be honest though
I kind of think I would do way better at lying to the president of Ukraine that I would like
I don't like that
What person how much more
Terrifying
F******
It would be the Delight of my life before I die
Before I die I want to lie to a present
But I think
This takes of it being so high
You're beautiful
Because
I don't know if I've ever lied to you
I really don't
I would have said I would have to really hard about it
My
But the best possibility for me to have lied to you would be like
You're like hey do you want to do something tonight and I'll be like
I got to go
That would be the most alike that's the way I live
Do you know what no I would not lie to it I'd like my family about having a
I wouldn't lie to you about that tell you the truth I'm not I'm not in for tonight
Right right right ordering a pizza and even gets badly
Give me maybe you and I are bad examples
Cuz like why the f*** would we live
Again
The depths of
You like
The f*** am I going to judge you for
That's a good point
Conversation
What are you going to lose while I at this point
Right you know that I live my life the way I live it
Neither it's great
There are people that you might want him
Press that you could lie to
So hard
I don't know man
But it's become something of an anti
He is f******
Walter White Breaking Bad dealer on Heroes
I want to see how far
Like I want to see
What is what is the comeuppance for his level of Life he's like the political Smokey and the Bandit
Is it going to make it
He is always one step
He is Aladdin
Need one step
I had
It's incredible
I don't think that's
No I don't think so
The booking in like a magiting what he's actually doing I think much more of a s*** head then
They were wrestling with
It's more fun than anything else
Because the rest of it really is
Just like
Alex pretending that you didn't save it fault I'm going to be the Supreme Court Justice Kavanaugh great
You know here
Was involved with bush
Italics
Indefinitely
In terms of like
US citizens were deemed enemy combatants don't have a right right
I meant Alex not taking into account the reality of who the
People that run
Pardon
The fact that they are child
Arrc
Enat
In some sort of a weird kind of way
No no
But the reality is
And here's why
The principles that would guide
To be against the
Real
Therefore show
The things matter
Are they like
Trump
Hardening the Hammond
Is it tip of the cap to the malicious
Yeah it's a tip of the cap to The Sovereign Center
Agreed in the world
If anybody
Gets it
Message received thank you so much Daddy
Yep there's that
Yes
That's a great way of putting it thank you so much Daddy
Heaven are coming in
Isn't Napolitano who's
Nut
He's a nut
Alex
Like really wrestled with it is like
Yeah it'll probably
Score points in terms of
Things that I care about
Not into immigrants he hates
Women's rights
Choose women
Access to healthcare
So like those are things that are real
The Chute that's realer
I don't like people
Some some f***
Sum fuk
King f***
Write the Liberals case for
Kavanaugh
Yeah exactly right like a light.
You even pretend that that is a headline that is acceptable
Go fuc
Are you shiting me
Liberals
A liberal case for running into a lake and then lighting yourself on fire and then
Hanging yourself
And then tying a rope to your f****** legs
With a rock attached to it and then falling into that f****** like
And then
Somehow underwater
Jerking off so hard you light yourself on fire again
The only way
Be something
Pages long
And it's inexpensive treaties
But how liberal doesn't leave caring about people right
And if it's nailed to a door
You know like that's the only way
I don't want it on internet but if it's like
You know what we're in a different time maybe
If that's the only way I give a s*** about that and even so I'm biggest quibble with Martin Luther
No safe
No that's the biggest issue I had with the old
The whole Protestant Reformation
No Staples
But you know like
For a while
Kind of
Comedy shows
Can I put up signs on post
Concealed carry concealed carry staple gun
People posting
Warning
About like
Reactionary Neo-Nazi signs
Put up anime
Play hide razor burn
Behind them
Luke Bryan
Verify
Like that I don't know why but
This on a visceral level
That is f***** me up
4 days
I don't really know if it's like
Endemic
But just the idea of it
So f****** like
That's so evil
Ears ears
The way I immediately react
That to me sounds
Exactly like the
Somebody's putting razor blades
In your Halloween candy it's possible
Right it sounds exactly like that and you have the same time
The people who are doing it
Steam like
Do that
It's money
It bothers me because I
The people who would do that
I'm not smart enough to think of that idea now they're going to throw it
That's a great way to be more evil than we already are
It's terrifying that's the way the modern
Holy s*** that's how we are the most terrifying thing that we are aware of is razor blades behind
Flyers are much more terrified about a lot of other things but like on a visceral level
What's up like that
Feel Again
Or like being surprised by
The momentum is all like
Yeah
Yeah no thanks
No
Just like the Liberals argument for why
Is okay for the Supreme Court
You just did a beep bop boop boop
Come on
No elephants
No but you are
On par with
Scatman
Alright
Good liberal
Recipes
Man's world
For somebody who's really interested in the
Alright
Alright no
I have not
Are you you are not going to play right now
Oh my God
Knowledge fight listeners Dan is
Plugging in his f****** phone
We're not even going to wind up doing a solid whose going to go f*** themselves
Where to be too busy listening to this entire goddamn song
Wild ROM
Burns Dan
Dan roam
Is burning
As we speak
Is going
Accepted as a
Supreme Court Justice
We're going to wind up dealing with this f***
At least another eight years before eventually
Somebody
Birds with f****** country to the ground
Could be them could be whomever but this country is going to be
Burned
To the f****** groud
If Kavanaugh is accepted as a
Supreme Court judge
Is my point right now
Is a goddamn Liberal Liberal
Peace
This song
Scatman's world
Okay
Alright but I believe should be okay
You got to finish that beer
Apple pepper
Oh my God
Wait
If you are a regular knowledge by Luther how bored is present
Sunday Alex Jones
He is so bored he's playing Scatman world or whatever the f*** it is calling out from scat line
Alright
If you listen to him
It'll earn
You got to learn to break free
You're learning your fantastic
Kattegat
And what have you
Leessang
Amazed you're still doing this bit listen to
Everybody
If you would me and sister
Scatman
Tell me about the color of Yellowstone
Welcome beautiful
This is how I know it's Friday
Not with a bang but with the scat
Lyric right there
If Part Of Your solution to pollution
I want to welcome you all right all right
If you wanted to look us up and hear more about
Scatman's world you could go to Morocco
Your website is knowledge.com good website
Go to
Rest in peace
And leave a review
Also look up Kevin
Riverview on
Pages weather
I had to choose
But
Alright
Actually I heard the end of it
Did you guys did you and Marty choose
We did
I believe it was Vince
Russo
Well I'm not
I'm not going to re-up on that
Terrible
Hammond
Hammond I don't know you got out
We got we got Kevin all we got
Many people who put the reality
Play Scatman
You know that Mike
I have to say
Whoever
Began
Sandals in the mix
But
You don't you don't know
54 what you do
I think
Whomever in
The Hammond
Who began that
A tradition of
That led to
Psychopath
Continuing
Endless destruction
Can of live
With no key
Is
I ultimately
Deserving of
The biggest go f*** your
Along with
The Hammond themselves
Again
I will
Watch
Burn alive
I agree with you that's incredibly vague
I will join you
Go fuc
Go f*** yourself Hammonds
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work