Holding
Alex
We are to be like to sit around and drink wine and watch the world burn
It sure is doing that
Listen to Infowars
In particular
Describe the events
Other unfold
My friend Jordan here
Consistently shots
Appalled
Overwhelmingly confused
Overwhelmingly
The world is on fire as we speak
We're recording this on Thursday afternoon
Attorney General Sessions
As they would say
He's in the soup
Up to his thorax
Who knows
At this point it's like it reminds me of that Patton Oswalt
George Bush and Dick Cheney
General Lee over there
Probably going to get out of this morning
Yeah
Don't feel like they are as slick as Bush
Is it like
What are the most fumbly bumbly dumbasses
In political History George W bush
Looks kind of slick
I think I think that was his genius at 9
I think that was the reason that he got away
And no matter how evil he
There is still that party those like
Just seems like a down-home country eats the marketing that like I
You want to go get a beer with him
I never felt that way I think that was just in here
Trillions and trillions of dollars
And here we are
Here we are also
It's come out
Met with Russian
All of the stuff in the dirty dossier is very true
Unfortunately at practice
When are recording this
Some of these Revelations came out after
Today's episode of The Alex Jones Show
Kushner news
Broke life
Right so I thought like f****** Alex Jones
Who's going to be on
Fire
Anyone about the case
He wasn't
He was subdued heartbroken
Boring
It was just like
He was calling
Bachelorette
The game is part of the job he's on the
Who's on the Senate subcommittee this job is to talk to the Russians meanwhile
Across-the-board
0 of them
He didn't feel the
Flames,
In today's episode but I think tomorrow
It's going to be a breakdown
You don't think it's possible that
He's finally seeing the writing on the wall of his own
I'm starting
Did you just pull your ear
Oh no
I just I don't know
Disinfecting all of us
We're all part of
Even though today's episode was kind of boring
There wasn't a lot of
Like worthwhile s***
Get a bunch of interviews with people who
But luckily
Some stuff from the wind
Wednesday March
First episode that were very necessary to talk about
Axel
Just some of the goings-on
Movie March 1st
Recession news breaking episode
His procession
Cuz he does bring up session
Of course
But I want to start the show off
Today Jordan
We talk too much s***
But Alex Jones
Listeners
I think it's important
That we let the man
Gibson
Improper
When he deserves
Right and I want to take a moment to celebrate some things that Alex Jones does incredibly well
Okay
First thing
Lie
These amazing why
His intro music
In-N-Out of commercial break
Strong
You are praising him for things he's not yet
Knew he was using that we probably
Moby's Extreme Ways comes in
Awesome Quarterflash Harden My Heart
Is a banger
You played a Triumph
Yeah you actually had
You texted me about that like a motherfuker is playing some solid music right now
Power Trio
Great you choosing good music
And I want to
Celebrate that
Cuz I'd forgotten about Quarterflash
Didn't you know he's in the groove salad musical cities
They're so I expect
At least some of that
Yeah but
This is a little bit about
Reviews on marijuana
No plan as more medicinal
Uses then
Mary Jane
I fully support this
That's amazing
Unqualified agreement with Alex Jones
We have
Found it
Connolly Middle Ground
Gym from here
Yeah so what we'll do that's why I want to talk about this
This is an episode that will be like no other
Because there's another one
I think they will both agree on
A hundred percent
I still think you're a big but I agree
Marijuana can be used for so many different things as there's no reason
He goes into talk dimensional shift so maybe we're all better off whenever Mary Jane is legal
I don't like your calling emergency
Who you Tom Petty get the f*** out of here
What about reefer
I didn't know that was one I feel like a little boy
Back in the day we found like this that long printout of slang terms of the years for marijuana and one of them was
Little Indian boy
Every now and again you'll see those breakdown
Call soda and some
50%
Soda 20%
And then like
Fizzy water
50/50
I like that a lot marijuana from now on
French for fizzy beverage
You tricked me so Alex actually if you talk to you in a little bit more I believe dinkova
Ultimate in
Plants that can heal people I have no idea
Nicolette
What's up you're never with mr. love
Global Noble
His feelings about marijuana and
Next clip
And one thing that's really actually
Super awesome about
This
Isn't that he talks about it in opposition
To the beliefs of the trumpet
What I don't know it's crazy
Legal marijuana
Support police
Funding
And Anna not demonizing PlayStation unity and holding up the good officers as an example
Realtree
Make an honorable profession so we get more good people
And don't make it be based on Revenue generation
What in God's name is happening one of you.
Text before this episode just like hey let's see what kind of cool should we can get him to say
Find the others
That's the whole reason that they that sessions wants to criminalize it
Because of Revenue
Because one of the things that is that
If they
Expect money
Involved with drugs
Yeah
Well
Seizure there a note
Challenge to that you
I can just take it
I put this
Clipart
And go to another clip
If you guys
Want to call Lynn
Disagree with me
About my gushing over Trump please call in and make sure real point
I don't like the asset forfeiture seizures a lot of us unconstitutional
F*** is happening
Corrupt
And there are some bad places in East Texas from there
No I'm not bashing
Mrs. Basham
Can you text
He's a nose
Casinos in old lady
You got a man who's like
Sweet old lady
Yet another thing we agree with him a
Forfeit forfeiture is
I think that to some degree you should be able to take ill-gotten
Games from
People you know like
Marauder
Antique dealers who get their shift taken away
It should be all sorts of like only apply
Higher Global recession
Write all of the rules that
Reception
Nice
Topicals fuc
No like those guys
Destroyed everything
But because they're still billionaires
Now you know
Making all that s*** is getting repealed because they're rich enough to buy Republican
Yep
The more f***** up is the Wii
Concrete examples
But Alex is saying
Philosophical agreement
So
24 the plus column
Yeah
And what is it 6470
Before in the negative forgot little check marks on the other
Man
Alright on the weed brother
Again he is in Austin
In like I bet
I bet he walks
On the streets and just smells marijuana
All day everyday
If you're if you're that
Do kind of believe
That if he just
Accepted a lot more black people
Into his life and
Is community
He would think the same way about them as he does about marijuana where's inside
We should just leave those people alone
What are we doing
Tanya Burr
No
But if he didn't erroneously the globalist were behind everything
He might be a great person
Comes from his belief
Benny thinks that it's
Social manipulation
And trying to control us
Through getting rid of genders
I'm trying to spark race Wars
And stuff like that if he didn't believe that there was a shadow
New Order
Really what do you think
What's behind it
Believe that
Federal Way
I kind of angry dudes
Who'd also believes that weed should be legal and doesn't think the cop should fuk with you
Then
See that
That's the ultimate issue here
He's only anti-immigrant
Inasmuch as he speaks about on his show right because he thinks that the globalists are flooding our country
With emigrants to destroy up
Does he is that really why he's anti-immigrant is it the racism is it the racism
Comes from the global or is it the globalism comes from the race that's a great great
Yeah it's the chicken legs aren't allowed to procreate
Tuskegee I don't know that one got away from me
Anyway this is all going to be in Alex Jones lovefest just not
I wanted to know it is important
We are fair
We're not here to just
S*** on everything
He says
He has some good points but I also want to say
They will when we get to this
I want to remember
The pro decriminalization of marijuana
And the anti civil forfeiture
Right
And I want us to think about how little agreeing philosophically really matters
How is it that
Doesn't
Take the very same
For those thing
That he makes
And then realized
Is that he is making the eggs
Exact opposite of those
For so many others
You don't know how do you not have
Any kind of logical
I don't know I mean
Admittedly this is not a trait that is unique to him
Who suffer from
This is kind of a human
Situation
Well like being in the news
Now where it's like
Shyamalan movie The Village
Starring Jon Hamm the most handsome man that
Aliens I've ever created
No the town that
Was overwhelmingly Proto
70% of the Town voted for them
And then all the sudden
They know a guy who getting
Kicked out there like
Oh wait I didn't think you were going to kick out a good illegal immigrant
No
I feel no sympathy for them I feel Sympathy for the guy was getting deported
Although although no it's kind of like dude
Those guys kind of hated you
You see that right
You know what it is it's the inverse
Of the Guard guns
Yeah it's like they're going to keep
Literally what they're saying violent criminals and illegals
That's not what's going to happen
Cuz that's how you keep
You can't
Figured that out at the other side
Meanwhile
The right is
Obama
He's not right
Please stop that's not
Lorde
I mean
I think it's
Genuinely turned into everybody now lives in their own reality
And
Cloosiv
The GOP
Although the GOP is
Entirely
Living inside its own reality
Yeah
There's only three possible
You're either
In denial
You are stupid
And I think all three of those I think they've mailed it
Is the
He's the only pure Trump I think he's the only global
We war games that last night
Yeah we there's just no downside in all of this
Tear itself apart with his
Fake
A hundred-thousand-dollar a year salary sitting on
Possible hundred billion.
Plug-in
Tower like Scrooge McDuck he knows that the only downside possible
Is another proxy war
And the only downside to that
He might lose some troops but most of the casualties will be
Of whatever country
And the Beanstalk
Write like in Syria in
It's nonsense
That's not a real.
But you know with with other with other autocratic dictators you know like your
You're saddam's
Of the world
I assume there's more
They
That you know that guy
After Iraq fell
Hiding in underground bunker
And then
Right
You do not see Putin get murdered
Even if the entire country unites against
He's in a helicopter
Can Mars tomorrow living like a billionaire
What is a base on the
No way you get
Rambling talking about weed
Cuz here's where it takes a strange makes an admission about
Jeff sessions
And we don't want to run around
Going after half the young people smoke pot
Quit smoking pot Senator sessions
Listen to Michelle I'm sleep with that
I know
Well that's scary
Don't answer me
And you do that
He was very proud of that in another reminder
It was the day before
These
It's amazing now that we're on a What A Difference A Day Makes every single day
He keeps ending up one that's why I wish
Then the next day you would have been in hardcore defense mode as opposed to just dismissive
This is nothing that's boring
Right
Position of that isn't really
It is not really that much different
His habit
Cuz he doesn't think all this is real
I didn't think all the Russian stuff in
The perjury stuff is in the same way that I made the argument
Kind of does because he has said in the past that
Who was involved in the election
We agree on.
And
You don't want to start a fight with
What's the statistic
That's Google tell me American smoke marijuana
This is a disaster for Trump
Then I would say it's not hypocritical but liquor kills a lot
He said marijuana causes people to be
And causes violent no it doesn't
Marijuana
The road,
Heating up this is beside of Alex B
Warriors
Dumb people in
Yeah again because
I hate that our first 25 minutes
Love Love Fest
Well I mean over the
The course of this last
I don't know 23 months
Listening to him everyday
Never heard him break rank
With the Trump Administration
The only time he's ever criticized Trump was about torture
And we played that clip on this episode has reasonings because it
You shouldn't torture people cuz it causes bad PR
You got to kill him that was his ark
Like if you arrest people for marijuana
Is marijuana
Then killer monkey syllogism but yeah I've never heard him
Like even
Will you be like
This is a bad idea don't do this
Write the only other thing I guess
Maybe like kind of agree with him
If a different reason
He was like don't let
Flynn resign
Yes I agree with him
But but only if we're being strategic about Trump's goals
Just getting head
When would have been a
Great distraction
For that
Flynn there
The more he's like the
The beach house
Yeah and everybody else is all of their Russian connections the entire f***
In administration
Yeah you need like role-playing games
You need to tell you need someone who's just got a lot of hit points
The wizard in the background
I don't think sessions
Can betta tank
Yeah he's a half elf half half wig
He's got a phone call
And then the Dominos.
Just keep going to hold strong with Flynn
But once he wants
Then everybody it because and we said this back then
Now there's blood in the water is everywhere
Different size
Impressive
To me to see that
Disagreement with
He's about team
Yes
If it's me it's early meaning
I hope
.
I would like it if you was more like this
Regularly
I would like literally anybody
It was more like
This regularly
They just voted against
Trump from releasing attack
Tax return
Or anybody
Some Senator came out of the secret room where they've got the new healthcare bill
And he was quoted as saying there
Rand Paul went on a nice little chick today
Brought a printer with
Also it was a giant didn't have like a travel bag with a
Knightsville printer is old school
With the with the poles that you have to punch off
Carrie the paperweight
There's a show called House of Cards
Cuz this house of cards
Fall seems like it
At least people
What's the show up until his wife gave a dying due to handjob and then I kind of
Like I'm out of here
Wait what
I watch the first season
And then the first episode of the second season whenever you push that reporter off of the
Spoiler alert
Where are we are we doing that let's not turn this into
TV review show agree with him without then just kind of rambling off.
What the f*** is happening
The premise of our shipment
Premise of the show is to document what he's up to
Unfortunately it's usually terrible
Terrible
Hey
You support marijuana legalization
You also support
Keeping trans people stuck into their f******
Horrible
Here is our next clip
This gets away from the good bad
Dichotomy
Rite Aid this is just Alex through talkin about how he's not a fear monger
And then also gets a little bit into the Trump
Speech before the house
There are there
Other
Groups world
He popularize a lot of those I can say our audiences
Get that info out I always believe that
The world
Exposed
I probably always existed
I've gone
A lot of stuff that he Direct
People to
And it doesn't say the things you do
Equine
Of course
In much the same way that he just misrepresent
New stories that read based on headlines and bakes building up his case
That
Evil globalist
You don't here's the weirdest part I am starting the more I listen to him
The more I'm starting to notice the
Parallels between his globalist
Ranting
Billionaires
Like it does seem like all billionaires basically
All of them are directing every country
Like even though I am
Now I support Alex Jones out of marijuana which basically means I agree with everything he's ever said now
The more the more I think about this whole Trump situation
The more I think you know who the real enemy is
Billionaires
The entire government
And this is always been true but now they finally won
These people don't
They don't have any association
Oh no
They don't care if the country goes well or Batman care about poor people
What's a really care about is getting as much money out of
Guess what
You are
Just to be listenable
World governments good we should all just accept it and so what if it's an elected
How far we've come
Trump taking control of it
I don't think
Anything even
Similar to ordering people
Loan
Money is a small bit
Certainly not
Federal Reserve is private really weird murky territory
But also I don't know if
Authority to take over
Frankly I have read so much about
The Federal Reserve
Still have
No f****** clue what do other than sometimes somebody will go on TV and be like
Point
They do 5% control the money supply
In order to
Make sure that our
Dollar doesn't
Become valuable
That's a large part of what they do
Okay
A mother
Yeah it's not it's not a government
It is its own
What is a thing
Intimately intertwined with
Otherwise it with
Otherwise you just cut ring
Private doesn't take everything
Account but it is
If you just take that simple fact
Really more of the details about the government being able to impose things on it
Nefarious
Nearest Microcenter
Currency is
Regulator
She's just
The fearless leader van like
I have no clue what it is that
The Federal Reserve
We aren't Economist policy was the Federal Reserve
Truxedo power of the Bigfoot
That's why they are
Particularly
Power us and it be dismantled
It's dinner
So when
Yeah.
I wish
Soul winning
Trump actual number friends
Strfkr
Sure thing would hang out with him but also that
I lost my phone
What I'm not the first
Now
Come on we're going to win win win
No
I remember
You're totally right
Been in the video he's about to hit the desk really hard and fake laugh
Oh my God come on man
Clunky he was he was about to pray and then he started laughing like what is happening to emphasize his wife by hit
Does he hit the desk all the f****** time
You can here in just about every clip
Sunk
I hear that my
Dreams
But turn towards truly next level
1st BC
Trump
Started talk about again in science and technology
Right around the corner and look in his eyes they are got them
From the top dimensional beings
Trump
Before I'd the water in the vaccines with additives
What the hell have people
Go to more Focus
Here's this is after the State of the Union
It wasn't the State of the Union Address
Even though
Prices like
Well he sure did
Look presidential guy
Like
What a group of pussies
It's an a for effort
You know it's like
Damning someone with faint Praise of like grading it was just
Plus minus
It's literally what it was I who went to like an alternative school
About
Feel me
Feel about
School
Cures and all that
We're going to let loose all of the
B all these life-saving technology
That's not what Trump is doing
Maryland
Still not a thing
No talking about Aldi's
Chores and stuff like that what he's talking about is making it easier for drugs to get on the market
About repealing regulations of the FDA
Drug don't have to be tested
Who is going to Tesla
Then people would be cured of cancer
The most expensive part of creating a drug
Because you could do serious damage to people
Yeah and I can't wait for the FDA
Literally
I don't think that you should have to serve drugs work
What
Yeah I was like I don't think the environment
Imma get it
Alex being like
Marijuana should not be Criminal
Right down the middle
Yeah
Him saying that Trump is about to release these mysterious secret cancer cures
Some s*** is him reading into what Trump is saying
Is essentially I'm going
To make
8004 drug companies f*** you over
Where is his interpretation of Alex
Oh my God all the secret technology we're about to go
And this is where he becomes an idiot
Although although now I
Do you think
Tell Trump
Doral Academy
I don't know no cabinet
Nobody in the government
The cabinet by the week
Yeah he's running
I saw earlier today that they
Confirmed
Wait
I think the worst part is that Rick Perry is probably the most blameless person
I don't know if he knows where he is at any given point in time he is becoming the
The cabinet member
He strikes me as a less funny version of
From the critic
It is also she has those Hillbilly Bears
Where do bears who sing for Duke
Is everything you read about
And heard about it
More
And they just make up news reports weather
With his son-in-law
Decided
Of Defense intelligence
He's complaining things there
That's very different view makeup
The well done steak and
Jamaican look gauche
Who cares
Who cares whatever bulshit
You're revealing a lot about
Good writing articles
People like giffer will eventually get big enough for the wapo
To be pissed off about your food choice
Are we could only help
But the Japanese thing
The prime minister.
Situation
Vector pictures
They're pictures of that
Everybody's watching it
Good reporting on that know the intelligence as the good reporting show.
The intelligence was like
Maybe don't do this
So are you playing golf or some s***
That's what they said at the same time that the Yemen raid was going on
All of this
No one
You're making up is it true
But goddamnit he can repeat it real strong
Goddamn
He did
Maybe not randomly randomly
Of him over a well done steak
Indigent with that steak knife
Poor and more and more catch up on
Just going like
Let's just send one guy
Yeah
Just just Ryan
Poor Widow is used as a
Prop we're going to get to that in a second
I mean nothing
Nothing but respect for our fallen
Yeah I don't have any
Pain and some people got killed
Welfare rolls
The glory
Soldier
Do you think he's going to say that Trump is trying to
Steal the glory agreed with him multiple times today so
Noemi's Noemi
Whammy
A sailor
Trump's opportunistic
Chicken
Standing ovation
No one said ratings
Argument of writing saying it was tacky for him
Bring soda
Crowd response
It was manipulative tacky
Military folk that I've seen responding to a degree with
Since he died
Incredibly inappropriate
I do I do want to I do know I
I don't know how much I agree and disagree with
That's what they signed up
Because there is a certain amount of that word is
Military
You are a Navy SEAL
You knew when you want on this
This mission that there was a possibility of the
Entry level position
Those dudes go through
Crazy
Training
The others thought that I have
Which is that one of the main reasons that
Because they are
Airport
The way out
They aren't all these programs
Insurance
College
Nobody's going in there
Especially if you join during peace times and then there's a rapport
And then you're in if you get stopped lost Futurama episode where is like
Unless
Declared
And then
Lower back tattoos
TV review
Never going to stop but yeah I agree with you that it's a murky area the idea of just missing Soldier
That's because they signed for it
First of all you should never minimize
Their deaths
Because of that
But secondary
I think there is difference
Supreme
A private entrance
And someone on the seals
3rd there's a difference in
There's
Their goals are what they're capable
Absolutely because if it's
I mean it is one of those things where you know one who knows
You do know that
The seals are really really good at this s***
And there's a
There's a possibility
Maybe not a great one
That he completely secede
No one signs up
What's a good way to go we're not going to get some Valor
If your family is like people who died by the cops
To say some crazy people choose death by cops
Yeah
That's one way to do it a little less Valor and that situation plum
Some more thought
Her feel good and it was so
Charisma
Admittedly
Got a whole bunch of hard drives and computers and the rest of it that's why they didn't just drop a bunch of
They didn't get any
Good information
Multiple
Multiple sources
Yep
Very clearly said
No we got nothing
Yet
So there is a decent chance that maybe something will come out but it was a success
Decent is very Optimus
There's a possibility I would not
Decent
I'm sure there's an outside possibility, login
Whatever
Preston
Making the argument that they got great information out of it
A Michael Moore is suggesting otherwise
Absolutely just lying
So
I don't care that you like weed
This was the
For much of the Middle East
And their headquarters
Wasn't
Or they could have just
C-130
Howitzer
And blown the place in the molten slag
They want
That's the point of going on the mission
Also they couldn't have done that because I would have been in
Credible war cry
Yeah
No and it's even like
Hachi
Vicki killed like what 30 civilian I like I like how you very nearly said
Even for America that's a war
Even for us
Indiscriminate like going in killed tons of civilian
Them bombing would have killed hundreds
Civilians
China Wok
I mean
Yeah Obama killed a lot of civilian
You you can't argue that point
And he's not off the hook
We are concerned
We are liberal-minded people who have always been opposed to that
Then we've spoken Houghton
Maybe yeah
So like it been himym saying like you can't go with that
Scorched-earth
Iteknic
At no point
Does anybody bring up
Cuz it's
Yeah scorched-earth is bad
We know that cuz we didn't
We don't learn the lesson
Let's break it down
You got to get to a show so we've got a shorter episode today
Yes I apologize
I am going to drop it
Quit after our theme song
Which is the better I love you
I have to do some major editing
Recorded episode a couple weeks
Dear friend. Hilarious comedian Marty DeRosa
We recorded episode after the Superbowl
Breakdown of the Super Bowl
Into the end of this episode after after we're done so look forward to that
Before we get out of here we got one more clip
This
Is where everything goes
But we started on such a good one
The
The graph for this is the opposite of the graph for climate
This clip is why no matter what you think about his philosophical beliefs about
Super Why
Asset forfeiture
Marijuana legalization
I just can't get this guy cuz he's a f****** dick
He's a f****** dick in an idiot
Here we go
We got to start over cuz you yelled
So much worse
If that was too much
Scared
Over guilt
At 16 years of age with a half-drunk six-pack beer
Two girls in the car my buddy coming back from the beach driving back to Dallas
And because we are both have blonde hair
Hitler
In that white racism
Very much so just say that I haven't seen any white racism and then
Say Heil Hitler comes up with
Zachary water
Now
Watch as he continues the story
Alright
Doesn't get the point and then
Lipsett anti-black
Alright
Balances on
Because you can
That's why you don't do something to somebody cuz what color they are
What somebody does and what they stand for
Racist white stuff I've seen I've got
From
What
A white male
Comment fait stuff about it go
Weird
Takes about a subject to think about all the angle
The white nationalist angles you can
Was
2 minutes long
It's not edited in any way and it's fully exposes
I hate you racist man I hate it when we take him out of
We have contact
I'm policy walk
White racism doesn't exist a Nazi pulled me over and let me go cuz I was white
Sherwood want to be black getting pulled over by this guy
What did walking Justice
I wouldn't want to be A different race because of this racist
Who's White
Also 300-401
Noches
Hypothetically created the exact
Right
Image in his head
To be black be pulled over by this guy
Ford Amphitheater in that situation was not empathy it was an imaginary situation image of a black person
Pulled over by this guy would be wild
Nazi has
Never pulled over a black guy
Yeah he's like
It's
If you want to think
Then he's halfway there
But he's not
He's Living on a Prayer
He's not halfway there this is ever going to make progress
No she has
Enough
Maybe maybe on his Deathbed
He'll be like
No
Not enough
On his deathbed is going to be like
Trump has a life-saving cures going to come in a pack
Trump has already been hung for treason when he's on his deathbed he's like
There was a false flag hanging
So like
I mean this is I think
The essence of what I always want
The show.
To be about
And I'm glad that it can be very clear in this up
Despite some
Some decent
Things that he says
Which are
Incredibly rare
He is one of the worst people
Ever
Terrible
Is always
Is always the weird thing
About
Families in my own and I'm sure plenty of our listeners have the same
Dissonance
He describes
This is how I raised my children
Raise them to be tolerant I raise them to love people
Yeah
You're doing great
He's like but also I teach them of that white racism doesn't exist
You're doing wrong what white racism doesn't exist but racism against exact 100 times more
More than anything else
All of the all of the Christian
Is now just going like
Hey we should love everybody Jesus said love thy neighbor as thyself
All of this stuff and then the like but yeah let's kick immigrants out as quickly as possible and ruin their lives
You're so close
Not close it appears close so far away
It appears close to not close at all it's so hard to sit at thank
Thanksgiving
And listen to My Brother's Day
And not be like
You're a bad person
Not really.
I know my mom wouldn't like all this
Made my mom mad
Suck it you just made Jesus Christ
That's not a first for us
I wish
That we had more time
I also wish
But Alex would stop playing
What's good music on
Michelle
The bums me out as soon as we stop
Twitter
You can email us at knowledge
Seeing our listeners grow
Ridiculously fast
And it's amazing
The only way we can keep it up is if you share the show and you helped us out cuz we're in marketing
If you like the show tell your friends about it
We have our friend of you.
I made us a shirt
It says I'm a policy walk across that is amazing
To gauge interest if any of you would like to buy a shirt
Please email us at knowledge fight at gmail.com
How to gauge interest in
Into seeing whether or not anybody would
Chicago
And so if
If you guys would be
Just didn't want to would want to come
I don't know why anybody would want to listen to b no clue what's going on
Interested let us know email us at knowledge fight at gmail.com
With all that
Show information
Whenever on Stitcher
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Today's weather
He's not dead but he's just not with us in studio
So filling in as replacement Jordan ladies and gentlemen
The very hilarious.
Marta Rosa
This is B of A
Child conspiracy
Sadly we're both too busy for these days
Claim success people
One of the two
Or
I I well I'll say this
Honda on these we haven't we haven't we haven't crossed
Microphone
In a while
You've been so successful lately. The Illuminati
I really start to doubt him I'm also
You mentioned that
Have not been
Ninja Warrior
That's good probably
I used to wake up and go to
Infowars
Drudge
Zerohedge
Those things seriously right
I know a whole
Which
C forums
It still might be
They are they had a big guy there's a
We got to get to Alex Jones before we leave is important to bring this up
There was a guy
Posting anonymously on 4chan
Anonymous Reddit squared-circle
Oh yeah
19 something
If I can stay in here
Who's going to win every match
F****** right every
Oh wow
SpongeBob this guy might not be as accurate
Role-playing as a FBI Insider and then a bunch of
Predictions they all came true
Recording this on Monday
And he is saying that Hillary Clinton
Penance 30-plus big-time
How cold named politicians are about to get rolled up
Okay
That investigation which is a little ambitious
Please let me down
Twice
First off
I thought we
Hillary
Sure
We go we both kind of got a little bit duped by that her being sick
Oh s***
And then
I wish I wish we would have talked more about that when you were having those feelings I could have helped you out a little bit
And I do her eye hurt
I got an A List
A-listers
Celebrity ringleader
Eyebrows
How to write his name
Cuz I'm not going to
Stillwater run slander laws
And and I think
Mostly excited to know what you think
Is an a-lister
But some people. He was head of the
Cuz there's always that
Corey Feldman
Celebrity
Story is old
Last time a real big celebrity
If you know what I mean
Yeah
Wink clear I do think that's that there is
Abuse that goes on absolutely
Dennis
Doing some stuff he was directing
For Disney's not molester
You know that kind of goes pedophile
Sure
Power exists everywhere and
Damaged quote
Absolute power
Kurupt kurupt
People in Dubai
Enjoy your Super Bowl gif
Teaching
Teaching underprivileged children
Adobe funny
Baby funny
And
I say entrepreneur
Your sense of humor
Eyeglass
Toboggan
Just do lunch football jokes
Like the greatest Super Bowl of all
What time was the first one that ever went to overtime
It was and it was the largest
Pretty nuts that this year we had all of these major sports championships be like really Buckwild
Defeated
The Cavs
Came back from 3-1 to win
The Cubs
Broke 108 in Maine
Heat off of
Golden State
Because the Golden State blue 3-1 lead
It seems fun
Well
During the Super Bowl Lady Gaga
Illuminati ceremony
You're coming out to visit
Your coming-out ceremony much sure there was
Little to say about that
Literally and figuratively
I just start off the show
Theme
Overarching theme of the show is
Insecurities
Polish people
Fruit
All the same
Waking up in the poll numbers show him going straight up
41 before the election was
Hours for Trump
Is real numbers are above 70 right now
Because there are internal polls
That that that that you can cut the hair
Methodology
Call.
Houston and
Scallop and so many others this is very
The real news
He's not
First thing that's funny is there anymore
It's gone down yeah I pulled up these Bowl
Okay Rasmussen
He cites
Actually pretty good
54% approval rating 46 disapproval
The only one that has big of a swing
Is a Politico online poll
41% disapprove
Those are the only 13 Hazmat favor abilities of a
Approve - disapprove
He also cited the gout
-9
Metaphorical
43% approve 52% disapprove
Look it's not good
Basically if you average out what is like 10 poles that were taken in the last
Week and a half or so 44.9% approve 47.4 disapprove
On average
-2.6 net approval
Now
To break it down a little bit further
It turns out
But he does
Better in polls where you can be anonymous
Internet polls and that sort of thing he does very well comparatively on those
The ones where you're actually talking to somebody on the phone
Not so good
Moscato
Election to
Yeah
People just don't want to admit
Is that it
Admit I didn't there's some people I mean if your
Some basic ass white person in
Indiana Ohio or
Nearest Pilot
So far so good
Not really affected me much
You know
Be the same people who probably think like
Feminist
Way things are
Quite a few people who want
But if you go
The trumpet his people you would
Course they are
Everybody's
Very important
OSHA
How do you
So yeah I think a lot of it is
And then also
Trump
That was it that was ill-advised
Hey bro bro bro bro bro bro
Notre Dame
Alright
Delusional is f***
Cookie is listen
East Allen Reagan photo
You know the General Public
But what's really going to hurt me is
Being on the street
You care so much
What's really going to hurt him is when people can't afford to buy his b*******
Have you ever
Graphs
Got some beautiful Reagan
Trump won
He was selling them for 9
$18
These are too cheap tomorrow
They are in the hallway
Cuz the lights aren't
America is on the rise
Also this is an important point that I want to bring up
I've noticed he brings up Americana a lot
And I think that in the next like 6 months or so we're going to see that become a really dark buzzword where there's America
Yeah we're going to see like the Americana movement
Sounds good I'll share this like America Tropicana I like both of those things
No this is
This is white nationalism with another guy
Now it's
It's pretty scary
Kind of feel
I might be wrong
Possible
He's been saying it for a while now and I kind of think it's like
Just not going to happen
So I don't know I don't know how you feel about sports
Talking about sports
It's you know what it is
The people who are interested in a certain thing
I love that except
30 for 30
Oh yeah
The nature of sport
Okay
When does Super Bowl
I can care less about the Atlanta
Aw
Seriously I'm having a
Falcons
Bulshit
I know this is all been built up and designed so that men put their normal male Energies
In a watching a bunch of other
Overpaid spoiled rotten men
Involve themselves in what is Proto
Virtual reality
The original
A business
Competition
But it's not real
At this point I don't totally disagree with his metaphor
Foot sports are a way for us to get out Primal aggressions in a healthy
But I don't like that's not his
That's not what he saying
Right
If that's what he was saying I would agree with
Leasing there's some evil
Motive
He was Alex would rather you actually go to war
The NFL has decided is a boner pill
Sure because he was talk hey for men over 40
It's so expensive how much is it I think it's like 60 bucks for a bottle
Maybe I'll buy you a bottle
You were so close to actually Buy credit card
Alright what would you want
He has more to say about that
Weird cat
Metaphor
By the way my daughter seen a mouse
In the kitchen I never seen it
Crazy 4 hours don't chase laser pointers
Dog man
Portuguese
Healthy overall it's force-fed
Messages messages
All the anti Trump messages
All the feminist anti-family garbage
All the green police Audi commercial
I've been force-feeding us the devil worshiper
Lady Gaga tall the weird rituals they conducted its the big pageant of the Superbowl
Wallzone
This is the most
Bring in all the world nothing is more important
Meanwhile
I don't think he knows what his point was
They're also his show is the laser pointer
Of
Politics
Is a lot of Black Cadillacs a and he also
Seems to have no sense of irony
That
Him and
People like him if
Created
Sort of inside joke of the Illuminati
It's a punchline in jokes now
Go to clothing stores like Illuminati
T-shirt Lubbock the Eye of Horus
Make no mistake about it
People like Lady Gaga
Know that
And there
Putting this in their stuff
Number one
It looks cool
Denver to it makes them seem like
Video on Steam
Illuminati
Princess
Gives Alex
Yeah I thought that I
I saw someone post
I'm not that confident
I just thought
People putting all of these Illuminati symbols and stuff
In things
Is kind of marketing to a
Another crowd people interested in a movie unless
It'll take a certain subset
They do free promotion for you if you just put a bunch of weirdos
Movie app
Possibly negative promotion but
No princess bad press right
Yeah
And
You know if your mom and dad are
You know
Hey
Heard our neighbor down the street surreal like in Payson
Mom and dad
Cox of a joke
It's so funny
They don't know that I'd cuts
Alex is done basically with like
Used to talk about Bilderberg in Grove all the time
Davos
Yeah is this new one
Yeah
Close bank account to show out of
Borat tell you what
I went
I saw that
I'm not Shyamalan movie Split
Yeah no
418 from
I don't think so
Menorah
Suzuki versa
Does cats eat avocado from Japan
New Japan World
Florida. Ocala Florida
6 Stars
Meltzer
So you just mad about everything you're right
Videos more thoughts about the actual Super Bowl
The get into
How much
She's really weird
Actually
I feel like I
I'm skipping a clip here
Because
Yeah he's yelling about
Commercials
Really
Because they give you a p**** green agenda
Mcfucking Budweiser
The commercial f******
Talk about immigrants
This country
F****** mean to him
This
Americana
Accepting immigrants
Paperwork
I'll talk to the Scorsese
Movie about
Gangs of New York
Propaganda
Fake news
New so he right here's where his thought goes after that complained about the Super Bowl it goes straight into this
The last clip ended with meanwhile in this one will start with me loud
You know it's abridging of thought
We discovered three years ago via ice sources
And it was later confirmed
Call places
McAllen Texas
And
Only 70% are actually children and adults
Serious diseases
Videos
A fingerboard
Million
The most important step in the world
Hear what your purpose is
Vegetables
And they say no
We don't
Nations
Obama done for before for the same
The same time
You're not better
And I said oh my gosh
Would you plenty of wedding as is I think it's been pretty well-documented
New York Times covered
The story about how their corrupt border agents
You take bribes
To let people in his nothing to do with Obama being like
Either they're being ordered by the government to let people in
It's about people having a side business
Stand is I have
I have some
David tell
Aldi snake
Is it possible that a person's ID agency
Is just one of your wacky collars
Carolina
It's the super fun
To call him
And why your way in
Lie your way into him think
I don't think I'm from Chicago
I don't think he works in Rahm Emanuel.
Help
I don't think that you need
That much
Crap right
Yeah I think you could win this
Blackout I'll be up
UB Alex
Hey
I don't have much time.
I work
I've already waited too long to cut you off
Oh yeah Robin manual
Son of Sam
4 p.m.
And he's a bad
He's trying to
Uchicago essay
America
We know all about it
Send your documents
At one of those spy cameras like in the old movie
Well you were getting to
Any substance
They would go to
The break music woodstar play I am fascinated by the hang on for a second I got to tell some Reagan with you
It's
Flip that he believes
United States should control the world
The NFL
And all this stuff is just
Your wife
It's a joke
And then George
Walker the author of the world government program to get rid of our sovereignty
Who got the deal
I control
Imagine planet
What
Daddy Ozzy
Are you sure he wasn't
Other events
What's his name
I thought
That
Vince Russo
He didn't
Does Alex say that
Vince Russo
Herbert Walker
Yeah I'm sure he is on the
Like a
He's a little cagey when it when it comes
Kind of like
Talkingshit about that here in a little bit
What's going on
It gets really weird just Super Bowls part of Americana
It is a big part of American Prosperity there's a lot of money in Atlanta
Houston made a lot of money
Strippers
It was raining
Abused
Weirdo f****** thoughts about that
Super Bowl
And someone who's involved in it
Maybe you shouldn't
And then Lady Gaga and the Pope
That's a new show on HBO
Videos of Super Bowl
Yeah
He should have a stupor
Toilet bowl
Yeah they would have been a little bit slicker
But I think you would like
Crapper
Gets into a real fecal riff here
Also we still
Super crappers
When the
You tell me all about it
You got to order something
And your blood pathogen
A blood-borne pathogen
What is super male Vitality of a joke in all of a sudden
I don't like this podcast is done Alex's right
Dish rags
Barrel chest you're just like hey
Crazy
And she call her friends
Want to share you with the world I got her some super female Vitality is like
A flume
Ladies ladies don't
We'll try it but you ladies
Actually he said on the show many times
Good in a pinch
If you're out of super male vitality
Will assure you know why
Here's more
Watch it on television
George Herbert Walker Bush and the Pope
Lady Gaga and Madonna and a bunch of spoiled rotten Whitehead football players and
Volcom
Get inside the Porta-Potty and go to town on you
Ether Sports is healthy
Don't have family
Just go to the big corporate Sports
Rituals and all the Satanism and ride
All the drunkenness
Clearly big giant evil event
Take a second to pause here
I've noticed that he starts rubbing his ears
As a nervous tic
And when he said all the drunkenness he rubs his ears which is just wasted public
You've been caught a couple times at the inauguration
F****** drunk off your ass
Like I think you might
Oops
Oops I open myself up to attack
Also
Tom Brady
Eat but he's not one of these spoiled
No no
He's not right
Quarterback
Ryder
So he's fine
Which means what
Depuy talk
Is not.
One more person wants to use the porta potty on people
Is a big toilet
Super Bowl
And squat in your mouth
He said a few months ago that he believed in nationalism
Our support Donald Trump
That you quote are someone that takes sexual pleasure and eating feces
Not true at all
That's not true at all
Support
R4.
PCC
Keeping
Keep doing it
Say that weirdo
Talking about
The Pope says person
He's not really my Pope
Not my phone
Protesting when he got put in right you wanted that.
Seabeck
Pedophile
Apologist
Said essentially was the people who
Delight
Spreading and
Taking in
Of obviously
Free fake
News
All these stories
It's the equivalent
Sexual pleasure
Maybe he did say that
Please play a different way
Go to let you go with a different way
The thing of things anyway
This statement is just all about
Insecurities it's real nice
This is really what Alex
What is all about on this episode
Is that Infowars and himself in particular
Are not getting the recognition they deserve
They need to be everyone's favorite thing
They're not
Is really pissing out
I was watching
Press conference
Very funny
Cherise is mine
And
Obama
What's up
They're Skyping in
Questions now
Because they certainly weren't for like weirdo podcast
Directly show
Apparently that's the modus operandi
First of all but I congratulate you on a wonderful victory
President Trump has always been always will be a friend of the show
Any justice f******
Weirdo
You know and his questions are like
Does Donald Trump and if maybe a hard-hitting question does Donald Trump know he's doing a great job cuz he is
Will he ever
Doubt that he's doing a great job but if he does he can come to my show everyday
First date first time
Yeah
The real
What
Fox
We had to get degrees
Hey bro bro bro
Sure there was a whole thing about the White House said that they did not offer Alex
Infowars
Alex
It's for the taking
He started opening up a washer
Camden Bureau
Jerome corsi
Who is a guy who as I mentioned wrote an entire book about how Obama
And also was a guy behind the Swift boat attack
That were proven
Tubi
Erroneous
And the term swiftboating
Has become getting rats
It's like dirty political trick
Hey man
Empire
And the guy
He was probably alone in it one of the main guys behind it is now Alex Jones
The bureau
Chief who is trying to get credentials for to be in the pressroom
Yeah it's
F****** insane
Real procreate
Brain Force
DNA Force
She is very careful not to answer that question
Okay does he not
Poison Journal
You know how whenever drop his ass
Like the most recent one was
You've got a bad man out
They wield one out of the Superbowl
The bad duties
Globalist
L dentist
Alex has a lot of that
That kind of thing and like we really need to worry about the Communist Chinese that's what he's more up on
Whatever Russia comes up it's like
Saudi Arabia the Communist Chinese
Matt Damon
He just went on Rogan's podcast and he kind of
Sort of Cox out
List
Okay I can watch it
But never really had him desire to watch it
When you mentioned I had come on we'll talk about it
It was way more of a train wreck that expect
Brogan's
Little cohort
Anyway he's
Alex unintentionally disparaging things about Joe Rogan
Alex yeah
But then I'd ever won a Superbowl
They're not
They're not cry babies
They're not act like acting out War
Is football a fake volcano
Yeah I don't think that'll be as argument but it would probably be more logically sound
Okay
Anyway
This is
Incredibly in
Secure and very sad
Podcast get out the pups we already dominate to a great extent
The internet
Political news
Infowars all put together
Media outlets in the world
Not sure but also
I want to save this
This is going to go on for a little while it's a little bit long and I apologize
Put in the middle of
Alex accidentally said one of the funnies
Just wait you'll know it when I was going to say that me when it's ready
I trust my comedic chops
For me it's not a big we are
Hi daughter.
200 million people
Watch or listen to
The podcast out some people obviously don't see the whole thing but
Infowars
Basically do the same thing
The biggest
I went on Joe show
Did you catch that was fun that was
Look I don't care we do that or more I don't care about numbers
Yeah also that so wrong
That's awesome selfie
There's no way
That many people
It's hard to tell it because it's a gather they're not a hug
What he calls the derivatives are really trust attractive
I don't know what it adds up to
After like
45 days or so
The episode on YouTube was about like 2 million
But if you would say that
Like 100 200.
Joe Rogan
Pulling in now
You would not be able to leave your house.
Watching Joe Rogan
Okay
That's probably true
Public
Would be
All Joe Rogan all the time
I just realized if you like to yell about her CNN
Like their best shows have Abby worship of 1 million
So Rogan's getting
200 * 7
They're only get 1 million
Ever
And he said he's been on iTunes for 7 8:30 years since they started he said it never happened
Up to the very top of the charts
And of course you know there's hundreds of YouTube versions of it was 1.9 million three hundred thousand thousand thousand
Blackout
I just remember time to research 45 minutes
Why he's going he's going on all the different
Things and counting the numbers and stuff while he's spending like 5 minutes of his own show talking about how many views
What the f*** I got a notepad
Just right number
Old timey adding machine
Pink
First of all I mean like
Not accounting for overlap gas abilities
Anyway
Still haven't got the image of Alex
45 minutes
Would generally he broadcast for like 4 hours a day yeah other research
Well who needs to do research you just
I can go half cocked and everything
Number one
Rockstars top movie stars everybody on
Joseph movie star TV star
East Alton
What's up people come to see him alone
But still
Chicago theater
Probably not 20000
A lot
Please
Shows in a row
The Cap City Comedy Club
I'm coming over shows biggest thing ever happened to it
ITunes is blocked us having our own
Podcast video
You just kick ass off because they will dominate
Everything else we do because we know we're talkin about
Jesus Christ
You judge a tree by its fruit
Juiciest fruit I've ever seen
Such unfortunate phrase
Call Chuck Daddy
He's got a little bit more up head
Tell me he likes what I do I could care less
I was even put on
All sorts of big stations XM
He's like a far-off radio station
About me okay it's about the mission
I'm telling you
Warren all the Superbowl rings in the radio world
Whatever it is
Number one
Dominate
Maui map
Joseph Watson all he does is sort of race-baiting
Complain about social justice Warriors
But you just makes me super manipulative videos
About like a
He attack
He builds up tweets
As a straw man for himself to attack
No nobody on the left really agrees with that
He probably isn't
Angry
He looks like he's about to cry all the time
Looks like
In desperate need of some like red eyes
He is the world's biggest p**** and he's always at the vet
Boulder social justice Warriors make me
Is British guy I hate
I hate him
It's
You know it's me
Not like this
Today this whole thing is the prologue
Joke around
I didn't buy him a
Resurrect
Time machine
Sing together
His eyes are straight now
Hallelujah
Other stuff goes on on this episode that's not really important
One of the things
He has Rodger Stone on
Rodger
Ready to schedule stomach
Narrative
I think everyone laugh
And now he's just not using that all
They tried to spend that as that wasn't actually Putin it is MI6
Which is
Unnecessary layers for
Anyway
He was on it what they were talking about is about how there's leak
Coming out of the
Trump's house
And if there's a civil war within the administration
Yes
Americana Grill Trump Folk
Evan you have kellyanne Conway and rims
Priebus
We're trying to sink the ship
Work there never trumper's
Is hanging on
Because they know that they can
Keep some power
And it's fascinating
Yeah
Okay
We tried to make a Democrat
The enemies of their consolidate against us
What do you do
There's division in the ranks
Yeah I ran
With with
They tweeted did anyone else
It's just like
He sounds like a weird
Star Wars
We're going to get to the
But
Dragon Ball Z made it through the parsec
Nobody
There's cat look
These people
Around me
There's no way driving to get
Even if Papa
With words fun is your ear like I was talking about this on the last episode that I have a little bit of hope that everything
I'm going to workout
And one of the reasons is because of this trend that I'm seeing
Which is once you start blaming your own
Deck collapse
Gangnam Style
Do you think I'll make it out for you
No
No I really don't think so
They're already
Mexico
Impeachment
He's doing it to himself
He's making the case for himself
Look I'm no super liberal I'm not a big limit
But like
Course he has to be in
This is
We're going to end up in the weirdest f******
Situation in the world cuz he General Flynn
At the same time they're getting a dick sucked by Russia in 69 they're both everyone's dick-sucking with 60
Usher comes out
If you want us to fight Isis with you a rain comes with the package deal
Ran Rush is going to be mad about that
Think about that possible angle
Oh no I have a crazy wife
So none of this is going to work out it's all embarrassing
Sup
Got a guy killed
Kill tons of civilians
Including a child
Who I was the daughter of that out
Atari guy
He was a US citizen
Who's over there
Also you know what
She was a citizen
You're not living at
Abroad
They killed in the sub
Does raid in Yemen perforce that's Obama's fault
Anyway
But yet know it
Once we have this narrative being
Insolvent
Listen
The real problem
Is it within our own org
Organization there are
We're witnessing essentially like
Come out about
Get were darker
The weekday
Trump loves the
Cuz it keeps people guessing but also cheap
Getting together
Hey
Have a little bit of a clip about
Yemen
And delete
Crazy fanfiction
You're on the air
American snakes
I saw that earlier in the week and then I
And the list
Because it was so effective and you know
Obama doesn't want us to get rolled up because
Hillary and Saudi Arabia
Yes
And we know Obama wouldn't bring like these list
Special Operations
Want to go after
That's what happened
Instead
Obama wants because it's his real command bases
And then that now moles in those very groups have now leaks
Fortune show up
In the world
Inform
That's one Theory
Yeah it's
Not substantiated or backed up
Wasn't in the war room
New York Times
They talked about this
These
Yeah but when
Secret service agent
Telling him about Hillary
It was a patriot
Course I get the word out
Yeah course
Put a tiny bit on that
Seriously
Petty against
Trump by leaking the location
And that will get good man killed
Waiting for that bread
You know
In some bizarre world.
Maybe possible but also another possibility is
Just doing a really bad job with preparation
And going in half-cocked not knowing what the
Situation is on the ground
Never go in halftime to be by my male Vitality quarters are better
Everything I've seen seems to indicate
That is what happened
They did not
Thoroughly
Figure out what was going on on the ground
Why they walked into the situations they were unprepared for
And
I don't think the Lakers fault
Tappan Department
Yeah but it's so much more satisfying
How to say you like someone else
It's a great narrative there's no
Curious to see if he ever does call
Call trompo.
But it's a great narrative
Torture torture
Which was interesting but his reasons for being
Against torture we're not really morally
Flat major chord
That my problem
The main room
Aromas Pizza
Patriot
Apple crate
Is reasons we're like that if you torture them people can
Use that against
PR campaign
The garlic
That's not the real
This is a little bit of a shorter show in terms of I liked because it was
Yeah
I think
I don't think this is your fault
I think this is Alex's fault
Okay this show is not boring
Not I'm not saying
I think it's the Lord's Day
And it was the Superbowl
The Super Bowl
Hey you not going to eat
Here we go
It's the weather
Coverage Super Bowl 51
Here you go ladies and gentlemen
Turn it up
Good luck
If you was going on he started this by saying I'm boycotting the Super Bowl and then started playing the Super Bowl
Live live streaming at Super Ron's guns illegal also
NFL
But also it's the opposite of boycott
Hey guys I'm going live to prove it
Put on get from some grapefruit
Boycotts this a little
Thanks, stupid crap thank you sir for your world government
Everybody hates the 41st president of the United States
Super Bowl
It's the possums versus the dirtbags
MSNBC warband by David Brock
Before Trump been in office
The president-elect Obama passes a law signs it
Fake news
Drudge Report
Economy are you guys even now
Congress right now
On what websites
Facebook
Woodforest
Everybody should be a piece of toilet paper
Still 430 bucks is a big old thick juicy color photos
Making of a president 2016
All shows got Trump's here is here
And they're trying to censor it because it went to number one on Amazon political and it usually goes number one after that
They want to ignore the fact
Play Alex Joe Rogan podcast
They just blocked it
Show again
Everything we do everything
No they give you the false number one
So
That's Petty as hell to me how like
He's doing the show on Sunday
And he can't stop
Just talkin about how great he is and how people don't give him enough attention
Basically breaking multiple deadly sins
Who's there
With Trump
Yeah
Sing upgrade
Does new man it's false humility and it's disgusting
But
In the middle he talked about how they're trying to ban websites that thing that Obama pushed through this legislation
I would everyone if you're curious about this go ahead and read it
It is a bill
What is
Call
Oh I'm just a bill
I'd love to hear that
Important propaganda and disinformation act
It is
Poppycock bulshit I'll address to website you go online and find
Also one of his bigger narratives is that it was pushed through by Obama during Christmas so no one would notice it
In a bipartisan group
Into Congress
In March
Well that's
Dad Christmas
That's communism
They just celebrating Chinese New Year over there
Chicago dance
E-Check your
You check your records i m Chinese Lunar New Year
I apologize
Is March
Alright fair enough
Calendar
I have
For $30
You let me send you my poop
Idea to that like
Anytime there's censorship stuff we got to leave
Also play this really quick
It's probably one of the funniest things I've ever heard
I'm a policy wonk
Alex
Okay that makes sense
I want that just to be like
I'm going to have that always ready on my phone
Just in case I get in conversation I don't want to be in
What does that mean I'm a policy wonk
It's an expression that people use
In political circles
Play I'm about policy
Yeah and people who like dick into the
Like the little parts of bills
Get into the tax code is a detailed understanding
She doesn't understand
S*** about codes in the Rogan episode
Keep
Claimed
Chemtrails were justified by this
Subsection 1520 paragraph B
But you said
Consent is required of any human subjects
She is no
I'm a policy wonk
He is not a policy wonk
What a deck
Hurt my voice
I apologize
Dan
Yeah this is
Felix my holy Quest
Sit around and talk about Alex Jones
All that
It's worked as me
I was a
Alex Joseph
Yeah it's
If there's a siren song it's
Seductive
Vehicle wrap this up so you can go watch some wrestling
You can pretend it's Warfare, Riesling
Describe we would appreciate it Jordan studio tomorrow get another episode for you
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
I love you guys all 2